<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>印度妇女的地位如何?</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>印度妇女的地位如何?</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 18:05:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>印度妇女的地位如何?[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1855633-1-1.html</link>
      <description>印度妇女的地位如何?&#13;
What is the status of women in India?印度妇女的地位如何? 以下是Quora读者的评论：Shalini PalI am an educated independent Indian woman and I want to talk about the position of women in Indian society. It is disheartening to see how discrimination against women is so well blended into religion and to realize it we just have to start questioning the "normal" things. Why a widow is not allowed to sit in some pujas (holy functions)? Why remarriage of widows is looked down upon but remarriage of widowers is seen as a necessity for life. Why a father is head of the family? Why a mother who carries a child in her womb, feeds her/him, bathes him/her doesn't gets the same place and respect as father? Why in hindu marriage we have ritual of kanyadaan? Why in some parts of India only the mother have to touch feets of their daughters and son in laws to pay them respect but fathers don’t need to? Why a women after marriage is expected to accept her in laws as her own family and the man is not? Maybe we should also start questioning ourselves. How can I respect my husband and trust him if he married me after getting a hefty dowry from my family? How can I live a respectful life knowing that I have taken dowry (price tag for a man's services as husband) from my wife? How can we teach our daughters that no matter how educated or how well off they are they will always be inferior to men? How can we teach our sons that life is easy for them because they have already won the gender toss?我是一个受过教育的独立印度女性，我想谈谈女性在印度社会中的地位。令人沮丧的是，对女性的歧视是如此深刻地融入宗教，我们必须开始质疑“正常”的事情。为什么寡妇不能参加一些礼拜？为什么寡妇再婚会被人轻视，而寡妇再婚就被人视为是生活所迫。为什么父亲就一定是一家之主？为什么一个母亲怀孕生子，喂养她/他，给他/她洗澡，却得不到跟孩子父亲同样的尊重？为什么在印度教婚姻中我们有洗脚仪式？为什么在印度的某些地区，只有母亲必须触摸儿媳的脚来表示尊重，父亲却不需要？为什么女人在婚后要在法律上把公婆当成自己的家人，而男人却不用？也许我们也应该开始问问自己。如果我的丈夫从我家里拿了一大笔嫁妆，娶了我，我要怎么尊重他，信任他呢？我若从我的妻子那里拿了一笔嫁妆，该怎么过有尊严的生活呢？我们怎么能教育我们的女儿们，不管她们受教育程度如何，不管她们家境有多富裕，她们就是不如男人？我们怎么能教育我们的儿子们，因为他们赢了性别竞赛，所以生活对他们来说就不费力气？I am not a strict follower of anything or anyone. And all I want to say is nothing is perfect. Not man. Not society. Not religion. If you follow anyone or practice any religion, take the good, realize what is not and correct it. We don't have to go all out and become a social worker. All we have to do is ensure we don't become an accomplice in promoting hatred, racism, or any form of social evil. Some things which our society or religion teaches us may no longer be valid. We cannot turn a blind eye and just keep practising them. Even in a very short span of a year, we change our clothing to suit the weather. Then how can we just assume that all the teachings of our ancient religion are still valid.我不是任何事情或任何人的虔诚信徒。我想说的是，没有什么是完美的。人无法完美。社会无法完美。宗教也无法完美。如果你追随任何人或信仰任何宗教，那就接受好的地方，辨别糟粕并改正。我们不需要全力以赴成为社会工作者。我们所要做的就是确保我们不会成为煽动仇恨、种族主义或任何形式的社会罪恶的帮凶。我们的社会或宗教教给我们的一些东西可能不再有效。我们不能视而不见，继续奉行。即使是在很短的时间内，我们也会根据天气增减衣服。那么，我们怎么能认为我们古代宗教的所有教义至今依然有效呢？
&#13;
Neha Verma, Engineer at Rolls Royce Aero Engines (2016-present)1.obsessed with white skin as white is only beautiful here. Brown girls are asked to take care of their skin tone as otherwise parents will have difficulty in finding perfect guy.2.Girls are taught at home to hide periods, buy pads in newspaper so that no one sees it. Urinating in public is fine, alcohol is fine, smoking is fine, teasing ladies in broad daylight is fine but buying pads openly is not.3.Girls consent in sex hardly matters, as it’s the right of a man to enjoy his bodily pleasures but the girls body is a temple designed only for giving birth to babies.4.A girl fulfilling bodily pleasures like a man is a slut. But not the uncle who touches inappropriately at her home.5.If something wrong happens, girls character is questioned.6.It’s a compulsion for a girl to learn household chores as after all they are meant for that.7.Girls have proved their equal potential in every field, but still if a guests visits home only mothers or the females go in the kitchen to make tea or coffee.8.Fathers name is compulsory everywhere. no one asks for a mother’s name, (only husband or father).9.A girl when young is gifted with kitchen set to play with,but a boy is gifted with racing cars.10.Boys don’t cry, tears are meant for girls译文来源：三泰虎 http://www.santaihu.com/48293.html译者：Joyceliu1.痴迷白皮肤，因为在这里，白皮肤就代表着美。棕色皮肤的女孩被要求注意自己的肤色，否则父母很难帮她找到白马王子。2.在家里，女孩们被教导不能公开谈论月经，买卫生巾要用报纸包起来，这样才不会被人看到。在公共场合小便没问题，喝酒没问题，抽烟没问题，在光天化日之下戏弄女士没问题，但公开购买卫生巾就是不行。3.女孩在性方面是否同意并不重要，因为这是男人享受身体乐趣的权利，而女孩的身体是一座专为生孩子而设计的神庙。4.像男人一样满足肉体快感的女孩就是个荡妇。但那个在她家吃她豆腐的叔叔没有错。5.如果发生了什么不好的事，女孩的品性就会遭受质疑。6.对一个女孩来说，学习家务是必需的，毕竟女孩天生就该做家务。7.女孩们在各个领域都表现出了同样的潜能，但即便如此，如果家里来客人了，她们只能去厨房泡茶或煮咖啡。8.父亲的姓在任何地方都是强制性的。没有人会问起母亲的姓(只有丈夫或父亲)。9.女孩小时候就得到厨房玩具，而男孩则能得到赛车。10.男孩不哭，眼泪是女孩的专利。
&#13;
Hari Nair, Vasudaiva Kutumbakam: The world is one FamilyLet me tell you a story. I hope I answer this question by the end of that story.She is born into a world of happiness. They pamper her with gifts and with love. She is constantly told that she is the apple of their eye, the princess of their paradise. Gradually she grows up. She is asked to go to school. She is asked to study. She does her part and does it well. She plays with her brothers and friends. Then she is slowly asked to stay away from them. When she asks why, they tell her "Because its not right." When she asks why? They say, "Because the society says so." Out of love, out of respect she obeys. She watches them play from her room, through her window. But she is not unhappy. She creates a world inside those four walls. A room filled with imagination. A room were everyone has a happy ending. An ever ever land of solitude and peace.我来给你讲个故事。希望故事的末尾能看出我对这个问题的回答。她出生在一个幸福的世界。他们用礼物和爱宠溺着她。她经常听周围的人说，她是他们的掌上明珠，是他们天堂里的公主。渐渐地，她长大了。她得上学。她得学习。她做好了自己的工作。她和她的兄弟和朋友们一起玩。然后周围的人要求她跟他们保持距离。她问为什么，他们告诉她:“因为这不对。”她问为什么不对？他们说，“因为大家都这么觉得。”出于爱，出于尊重，她服从了。她在房间里，透过窗户看着他们玩耍嬉闹。但她并不不快乐。她在这四面墙里创造了一个世界。一个充满想象力的房间。一个每个人都有幸福结局的房间。一个永远孤独与和平的国度。She grows up to realize the differences between the sexes, she grows up to understand the realities of life. She is told, she is the giver of life. But what she doesn't understand however is, despite all this why is she still inside those four walls. Why is her place in the kitchen? Despite having the same education as her brother and having scored better than him, why is he studying further not her? Why is it more important to learn to cook than what she wants to learn? When she walks out of her house, why does she feel like a sheep for slaughter? Why doesn't she feel safe in her own country? A country, which promises her the right to freedom and the right of expression. Why does she feel violated a 100 times a day without anyone even touching her?长大后，她意识到性别之间的差异，了解到生活的现实。她被告知，她是生命的赐予者。但她不明白的是，尽管如此，为什么她还被困那四面墙里。为什么被困在厨房里？尽管和她哥哥受到一样的教育，成绩也比哥哥好，但为什么他能继续深造，而她不行？为什么学做饭比她自己想学的东西更重要？当她走出家门时，为什么她觉得自己像只待宰的羊？为什么她在自己的国家没有安全感？这可是一个承诺给她自由和表达权利的国家！She falls in love. A man she knows will keep her happy. A man she knows will do good by her. He reminds her of her family. An innocent romance of words and eye contact. But they find out about it. They tell her its wrong. They don't ask her about him. They don't want to know why she loves him. But they tell her she is wrong. Why she asks? They don't have an answer. Why? She asks again. They tell her, "The society says so". They say they will kill her if she doesn't leave him. Out of love, out of respect she obeys. She forgets the man of her dreams. Out of love, she forgets. She is asked to stay away from strangers, especially men. She is doubted despite her innocence. She is asked to go back to her room. The four walls she is so accustomed to now. Only now, it had lost some of its magic. She starts doubting the capacity of life, to offer happy endings. She wonders, if this is how the world treats its princess's.她坠入爱河。她认识的男人让她快乐，对她充满善意。他令她想起她的家人。言语和目光中充满了天真和浪漫。但是他们发现了。他们告诉她这是错的。他们不问他的情况。他们不想知道她为什么爱他。但是他们说，她错了。她问为什么？他们没有答案。为什么？她又问。他们告诉她，“大家都这么说”。他们说如果她不离开他，他们就杀了她。出于爱，出于尊重，她服从了。她忘记了她的梦中情人。出于爱，她忘记了。他们要求她远离陌生人，尤其是男人。尽管她很清白，她还是受到了怀疑。他们要求她回自己的房间。她现在已经习惯了四堵墙。她开始怀疑生命的能力，怀疑它能否带来幸福。她想知道，这是不是世界对待公主的方式。Then one day, she is asked to serve coffee to some random man. After he leaves, they tell her, he is her groom. They tell her she is a lucky girl. She knows, that's not true. She knows that, its not right. Before she can figure out what is going on, she is inside another room. Only this one is unfamiliar and strange. The very people who had warned her, to stay away from strangers, had locked her inside a room with one. She is scared. But she doesn't give up on her parents, she trusts them and finds love in her new life. She understands that the game of life is filled with sacrifices. She is happy when she realizes that she is pregnant. Her family is happy and so is her husband. She gives birth to a boy. She raises him like a prince. Happiness finds her again and this time she is blessed with a daughter. Her children grow up together. She pampers her son. He tells her she is his Queen. She loved her daughter. She becomes best friends with her. She inducts her into the kitchen. When her daughter tells her that she wants to study further, she tells her, that's not her place. She asks why, she tells her "The society says so". Her son climbs the corporate ladder. But her daughter elopes with her boyfriend. She felt disgraced. She felt rejected. The society told her, "You are a bad Mother". She started hating her daughter.然后有一天，她被要求给一个陌生男人倒咖啡。当他离开后，他们告诉她，他就是她的新郎。他们告诉她，她是一个幸运的女孩。她知道，那不是真的。她知道那不是真的。在她弄清楚发生了什么之前，她已经在另一个房间里了。正是那些警告她远离陌生人的人，把她锁在了一个房间里。她很害怕。但是她没有对她的父母感到绝望，她还是相信他们，在她的新生活中寻找爱。她明白生活的游戏充满了妥协。当她发现自己怀孕时，她很高兴。她的家人很开心，她的丈夫也很开心。她生了一个男孩。她像王子一样抚养他。幸运再次降临到她头上，这次她有了一个女儿。她的孩子们一起长大。她溺爱她的儿子。他告诉她，她是他的王后。她爱她的女儿。她和她成为了最好的朋友。她带着她进入厨房。当她的女儿告诉她，她想继续学习时，她告诉她，那不是她该去的地方。女儿问为什么，她告诉她“大家都是这么说的”。她的儿子在公司里步步高升。可她的女儿和男朋友私奔了。她感到蒙羞。她感到排挤。社会告诉她，“你是个坏妈妈”。她开始憎恨她的女儿。Years have passed now, she is alone. All who she knew, have left her behind. She was staying with her son, who had barely any time. His wife, the girl she chose for him, had no time for her. She was left alone to fight her battles. She wonders, if this is the way the world treated a Queen? One day she ran into her daughter. She looked older and beautiful. She had her grand daughter with her. The moment she saw her mother, she just hugged her and started crying. She told her she was sorry. She told her she could not leave him. She told her of the days she spent crying over her family. Her mother felt sad too. She was near the end of her life and her grudge on her daughter had faded away. They made their peace and said their good byes. 许多年过去了，她独身一人。她所认识的人都把她抛在身后。她和儿子一起住，儿子几乎没有时间。他的妻子，她为他选择的女孩，没有时间陪她。她独自一人在战斗。她想知道，这是不是世界对待女王的方式？一天，她碰见了她的女儿，虽然看起来老了点，但很漂亮，身边带着她的外孙女。女儿一看见母亲就抱住她哭了起来，说她很抱歉，说她不能离开他。她讲述了她为家人哭泣的那段日子。她的母亲也感到难过。她已至暮年，对女儿的怨恨也渐渐消失了。她们言归于好，告别了。Her daughter came to see her today. She was shocked at the way her mother was being treated. She felt insulted that her own mother who had taught her the lessons of life was barely living on her son's mercy. She shouted at her sister in law and dragged her mother out of the house. She was now in her daughters house. She felt at ease with her. She felt like she had gained her best friend back. She learned that her daughter was working now. She had finished her studies upon the insistence of her husband. She asked her, "Who takes care of the kitchen". She told her, they earn enough to hire a house keeper. Her daughter seemed very happy with her life. That somehow made her happy. She wondered how some one she hated so much, could bring her so much joy. She met him that evening. Her son-in-law. She was nervous. She was scared if she would be asked to leave. But he surprised her by greeting her with love and seeking her blessings. She realized that he was every bit the man, she wanted her son to be.她女儿今天来看她。她对母亲遭受的境遇感到震惊。她感到受了侮辱，因为她自己的母亲教给她生活的道理，却只能勉强依靠儿子的怜悯生活。她对她的嫂子大喊大叫，把她母亲拖出了房子。她现在住在她女儿的家里。她和女儿一起住，感到很自在。她觉得她又找回了最好的朋友。她得知女儿现在在工作。在丈夫的坚持下，她完成了学业。她问她:“谁做饭?”她告诉她，他们挣的钱足够雇一个管家。女儿似乎对自己的生活很满意，这让她很高兴。她不明白，她那么恨的一个人，怎么会给她带来这么多的欢乐。那天晚上她遇见了他，她的女婿。她很紧张。如果他要求她离开，她会感到害怕。他却用爱问候她，求她赐福，让她诧异不已。她意识到他完全就是那个她心目中自己儿子该成为的模样。Days passed by and once again she started feeling like a queen. She started feeling like, she was the part of a family. Her daughter felt the same way. She was excited to have her best friend back. They would talk till the end of the night. She fell in love with her grand daughter. She was an angel. But then on that fateful day she fell sick. She knew she was not going to make it. She asked for her grand daughter. On seeing her she started crying. Her daughter told her that everything was going to be ok. She asked her not to be sad. She silenced her saying, she was not sad. She was happy for her grand daughter. She was happy that she would be brought up by her daughter. She was happy that she would not have to live through the circumstance of her mother. She was happy that she was her grand daughter and not her daughter. She placed a hand on her grand daughter's head. But the hand fell limp as life left her body. But there was a smile on her face. Because in that ultimate moment when life was leaving her, she realized, she was finally going to REST IN PEACE.日子一天天过去，她又开始觉得自己像个女王了。她开始觉得，她成为了家庭的一分子。她女儿也有同感。她很高兴她最好的朋友回来了。她们会聊到深夜。她爱上了她的外孙女。她就是个天使。但就在那命中注定的一天，她病倒了。她知道她时日不多了。她要看看她的外孙女。她一看见她就哭了起来。她女儿告诉她一切都会好起来的，叫她不要难过。她不说话了，她并不伤心。她为外孙女感到高兴。她很高兴外孙女将由女儿抚养成人。她很高兴她不用经历女儿所经历的一切。她很高兴她是她的外孙女而不是女儿。她把手放在外孙女的头上。当生命离开她的身体时，她的手软弱无力。但是她的脸上露出了笑容。因为在生命即将离开她的那一刻，她意识到，她终于可以安息了。
&#13;
Rebecca Cunningham, Medical StudentI don’t think I’ve cried this much in a long time. This girl is so brave,so honest and so,so alone(to understand just how alone,read the vile comments below the video). She has been perpetually suffocated at home, treated badly by her brothers and her casteist and sexist father’s goons(and her own brother) are after her life.She still hopes for a place in her father’s heart and his love, after all that she has tolerated at his hands. Her disgusting brother has been writing vile comments about her(the present weeping is only for show/out of shame at having been outed.)我想我很久都没这么哭过了。这个女孩是如此的勇敢，如此的诚实，如此的孤独。她在家里一直过得很压抑，受到哥哥们的虐待，她父亲的男尊女卑和性别歧视的打手(还有她自己的弟弟)也在追杀她。她仍然希望能在父亲心中占有一席之地，得到他的爱，尽管她在父亲的手下忍受了那么多。她那令人作呕的哥哥一直在写关于她的卑鄙评论(现在哭泣只是为了作秀/因为被曝光而感到羞耻)。
&#13;
Gurnoor Pannu, Brutally honest, Writer, Motivation speaker, FeministAs a woman in India, I feel really empowered. I feel many men are now stepping forward for women rights. I love to offer my seat to a tired man in a metro because I believe in gender equality. Life is pretty awesome. Men are actually scared of getting caught up in harassment or rape cases. It's awesome being a woman.Sadly, it's not the same for all the women in the country. But I have hope. Soon, even the women in rural India will feel empowered and things will change for the better. The only thing I fear is that feminism is sometimes mistaken for giving priority to women. Equality should not, must not be compromised作为印度女性，我感到很有力量。我觉得现在很多男人都在为妇女争取权利。我喜欢在地铁里给一个疲惫的男人让座，因为我相信性别平等。生活真是太棒了。男性其实很害怕被卷入性骚扰或强奸案件。做女人真是太棒了。遗憾的是，这并不适用于所有的女性。但我仍心怀希望。很快，就连印度农村妇女也会感到被赋予了力量，情况也会变得更好。我唯一担心的是，女权主义有时会被误认为优先考虑女性。平等不应该，也不应该妥协。
&#13;
Shubham Sharma, works at Sagar Institute of Research and Technology : SIRT BhopalAs a mother she is god....as a wife she is life....as a daughter she is laughter....india,bharat,hindustan is a place where womens are treated divine in scriptures.i would mention despite all the atrocities that happens .we the indians repect ,value , and moreover accept their role whatsoever it is. Hope one fine day all women of this world would think about being indian.I could have written about rapes ,molestations ,and dowry to earn sympathy but for me a women is all that maintains decorum in home, discipline in life and the urge to become better by each passing day.....# proud to be indian作为一个母亲，她是神……作为妻子，她就是生活……作为一个女儿，她是欢笑……印度，巴拉特，印度斯坦是一个奉女人为神的地方。我想说的是，尽管发生过种种暴行，我们印度人尊重、重视并接受她们的角色。希望有一天，世界上所有的女人都会希望自己是印度人。我本可以写强奸、性骚扰和嫁妆来博取同情，但对我而言，一个在家庭中保持着端庄，在生活中保持着自律，在每一天都渴望变得更好的女人……我为自己身为印度人而自豪。
&#13;
Ali Akram, lives in IndiaThere are many aspects of it lets have a look.1.First of all, the basic aspects of the democracy is available for the Indian women, i.e- the universal adult franchise. means they participate and organize themselves for the electoral posts of any running democratic organization.2.Women in India have the perfect blend of strength and tenderness. They have the beautiful quality to manage home and the outer world simultaneously.3.Though at some levels like dowry, crimes like rape, sexual harassment at office or public places, and molestation, eve-teasing, even after over sixty years of independence women are still exploited, which is the shameful side of our country. Yet one can’t deny that the situation has improved since the earlier times4.Women, who now represent 48.2% of the population, are getting access to education, and then employment. From 5.4 million girls enrolled at the primary level in 1950-51 to 61.1 million girls in 2004-05. At the upper primary level, the enrollment increased from 0.5 million girls to 22.7 million girls.我们来看看几个方面：1.首先，印度妇女享有皿煮的基本方面。成人公民权，是指可以参加和组织竞选任何进行中的皿煮组织的选举职务。2.印度女性拥有力量和温柔的完美结合。她们拥有同时管理家庭内外的优秀才能。3.虽然在某些程度上，比如嫁妆，强奸，办公室或公共场所的性骚扰，甚至在独立60多年后的今天，妇女仍然被剥削，这些都是我们国家可耻的一面。然而，我们不能否认，这种情况已经有所改善了。4.妇女现在占人口的48.2%，她们接受教育，参加工作。从1950-51年的540万名小学入学女童到2004-05年的6110万名女童。小学高年级女生入学率由50万人提高到2270万人。
&#13;
Reenaa Toomarr, former Travel Content WriterStatus of an Indian woman:The women of the present generation have generally received higher education than the women of their preceding generation. There have been far reaching consequences in the economic status of their families.Roles of an Indian woman:The modern women are inclined towards the social issues, and trying hard to improve the social status of women at large.印度妇女的地位:当代妇女普遍比上一代妇女接受了更多的高等教育。她们家庭的经济状况受到了深远的影响。印度女人的角色:现代女性倾向于关注社会问题，努力提高女性的社会地位。http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-24/dd9c47d67c1d4722435cc137dbaec88f.jpg</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>狒狗: </b><br>
<span>印度妇女的地位如何?</span><br>
<span>What is the status of women in India?印度妇女的地位如何? 以下是Quora读者的评论：Shalini PalI am an educated independent Indian woman and I want to talk about the position of women in Indian society. It is disheartening to see how discrimination against women is so well blended into religion and to realize it we just have to start questioning the "normal" things. Why a widow is not allowed to sit in some pujas (holy functions)? Why remarriage of widows is looked down upon but remarriage of widowers is seen as a necessity for life. Why a father is head of the family? Why a mother who carries a child in her womb, feeds her/him, bathes him/her doesn't gets the same place and respect as father? Why in hindu marriage we have ritual of kanyadaan? Why in some parts of India only the mother have to touch feets of their daughters and son in laws to pay them respect but fathers don’t need to? Why a women after marriage is expected to accept her in laws as her own family and the man is not? Maybe we should also start questioning ourselves. How can I respect my husband and trust him if he married me after getting a hefty dowry from my family? How can I live a respectful life knowing that I have taken dowry (price tag for a man's services as husband) from my wife? How can we teach our daughters that no matter how educated or how well off they are they will always be inferior to men? How can we teach our sons that life is easy for them because they have already won the gender toss?我是一个受过教育的独立印度女性，我想谈谈女性在印度社会中的地位。令人沮丧的是，对女性的歧视是如此深刻地融入宗教，我们必须开始质疑“正常”的事情。为什么寡妇不能参加一些礼拜？为什么寡妇再婚会被人轻视，而寡妇再婚就被人视为是生活所迫。为什么父亲就一定是一家之主？为什么一个母亲怀孕生子，喂养她/他，给他/她洗澡，却得不到跟孩子父亲同样的尊重？为什么在印度教婚姻中我们有洗脚仪式？为什么在印度的某些地区，只有母亲必须触摸儿媳的脚来表示尊重，父亲却不需要？为什么女人在婚后要在法律上把公婆当成自己的家人，而男人却不用？也许我们也应该开始问问自己。如果我的丈夫从我家里拿了一大笔嫁妆，娶了我，我要怎么尊重他，信任他呢？我若从我的妻子那里拿了一笔嫁妆，该怎么过有尊严的生活呢？我们怎么能教育我们的女儿们，不管她们受教育程度如何，不管她们家境有多富裕，她们就是不如男人？我们怎么能教育我们的儿子们，因为他们赢了性别竞赛，所以生活对他们来说就不费力气？I am not a strict follower of anything or anyone. And all I want to say is nothing is perfect. Not man. Not society. Not religion. If you follow anyone or practice any religion, take the good, realize what is not and correct it. We don't have to go all out and become a social worker. All we have to do is ensure we don't become an accomplice in promoting hatred, racism, or any form of social evil. Some things which our society or religion teaches us may no longer be valid. We cannot turn a blind eye and just keep practising them. Even in a very short span of a year, we change our clothing to suit the weather. Then how can we just assume that all the teachings of our ancient religion are still valid.我不是任何事情或任何人的虔诚信徒。我想说的是，没有什么是完美的。人无法完美。社会无法完美。宗教也无法完美。如果你追随任何人或信仰任何宗教，那就接受好的地方，辨别糟粕并改正。我们不需要全力以赴成为社会工作者。我们所要做的就是确保我们不会成为煽动仇恨、种族主义或任何形式的社会罪恶的帮凶。我们的社会或宗教教给我们的一些东西可能不再有效。我们不能视而不见，继续奉行。即使是在很短的时间内，我们也会根据天气增减衣服。那么，我们怎么能认为我们古代宗教的所有教义至今依然有效呢？</span><br>
<span>Neha Verma, Engineer at Rolls Royce Aero Engines (2016-present)1.obsessed with white skin as white is only beautiful here. Brown girls are asked to take care of their skin tone as otherwise parents will have difficulty in finding perfect guy.2.Girls are taught at home to hide periods, buy pads in newspaper so that no one sees it. Urinating in public is fine, alcohol is fine, smoking is fine, teasing ladies in broad daylight is fine but buying pads openly is not.3.Girls consent in sex hardly matters, as it’s the right of a man to enjoy his bodily pleasures but the girls body is a temple designed only for giving birth to babies.4.A girl fulfilling bodily pleasures like a man is a slut. But not the uncle who touches inappropriately at her home.5.If something wrong happens, girls character is questioned.6.It’s a compulsion for a girl to learn household chores as after all they are meant for that.7.Girls have proved their equal potential in every field, but still if a guests visits home only mothers or the females go in the kitchen to make tea or coffee.8.Fathers name is compulsory everywhere. no one asks for a mother’s name, (only husband or father).9.A girl when young is gifted with kitchen set to play with,but a boy is gifted with racing cars.10.Boys don’t cry, tears are meant for girls译文来源：三泰虎 http://www.santaihu.com/48293.html译者：Joyceliu1.痴迷白皮肤，因为在这里，白皮肤就代表着美。棕色皮肤的女孩被要求注意自己的肤色，否则父母很难帮她找到白马王子。2.在家里，女孩们被教导不能公开谈论月经，买卫生巾要用报纸包起来，这样才不会被人看到。在公共场合小便没问题，喝酒没问题，抽烟没问题，在光天化日之下戏弄女士没问题，但公开购买卫生巾就是不行。3.女孩在性方面是否同意并不重要，因为这是男人享受身体乐趣的权利，而女孩的身体是一座专为生孩子而设计的神庙。4.像男人一样满足肉体快感的女孩就是个荡妇。但那个在她家吃她豆腐的叔叔没有错。5.如果发生了什么不好的事，女孩的品性就会遭受质疑。6.对一个女孩来说，学习家务是必需的，毕竟女孩天生就该做家务。7.女孩们在各个领域都表现出了同样的潜能，但即便如此，如果家里来客人了，她们只能去厨房泡茶或煮咖啡。8.父亲的姓在任何地方都是强制性的。没有人会问起母亲的姓(只有丈夫或父亲)。9.女孩小时候就得到厨房玩具，而男孩则能得到赛车。10.男孩不哭，眼泪是女孩的专利。</span><br>
<span>Hari Nair, Vasudaiva Kutumbakam: The world is one FamilyLet me tell you a story. I hope I answer this question by the end of that story.She is born into a world of happiness. They pamper her with gifts and with love. She is constantly told that she is the apple of their eye, the princess of their paradise. Gradually she grows up. She is asked to go to school. She is asked to study. She does her part and does it well. She plays with her brothers and friends. Then she is slowly asked to stay away from them. When she asks why, they tell her "Because its not right." When she asks why? They say, "Because the society says so." Out of love, out of respect she obeys. She watches them play from her room, through her window. But she is not unhappy. She creates a world inside those four walls. A room filled with imagination. A room were everyone has a happy ending. An ever ever land of solitude and peace.我来给你讲个故事。希望故事的末尾能看出我对这个问题的回答。她出生在一个幸福的世界。他们用礼物和爱宠溺着她。她经常听周围的人说，她是他们的掌上明珠，是他们天堂里的公主。渐渐地，她长大了。她得上学。她得学习。她做好了自己的工作。她和她的兄弟和朋友们一起玩。然后周围的人要求她跟他们保持距离。她问为什么，他们告诉她:“因为这不对。”她问为什么不对？他们说，“因为大家都这么觉得。”出于爱，出于尊重，她服从了。她在房间里，透过窗户看着他们玩耍嬉闹。但她并不不快乐。她在这四面墙里创造了一个世界。一个充满想象力的房间。一个每个人都有幸福结局的房间。一个永远孤独与和平的国度。She grows up to realize the differences between the sexes, she grows up to understand the realities of life. She is told, she is the giver of life. But what she doesn't understand however is, despite all this why is she still inside those four walls. Why is her place in the kitchen? Despite having the same education as her brother and having scored better than him, why is he studying further not her? Why is it more important to learn to cook than what she wants to learn? When she walks out of her house, why does she feel like a sheep for slaughter? Why doesn't she feel safe in her own country? A country, which promises her the right to freedom and the right of expression. Why does she feel violated a 100 times a day without anyone even touching her?长大后，她意识到性别之间的差异，了解到生活的现实。她被告知，她是生命的赐予者。但她不明白的是，尽管如此，为什么她还被困那四面墙里。为什么被困在厨房里？尽管和她哥哥受到一样的教育，成绩也比哥哥好，但为什么他能继续深造，而她不行？为什么学做饭比她自己想学的东西更重要？当她走出家门时，为什么她觉得自己像只待宰的羊？为什么她在自己的国家没有安全感？这可是一个承诺给她自由和表达权利的国家！She falls in love. A man she knows will keep her happy. A man she knows will do good by her. He reminds her of her family. An innocent romance of words and eye contact. But they find out about it. They tell her its wrong. They don't ask her about him. They don't want to know why she loves him. But they tell her she is wrong. Why she asks? They don't have an answer. Why? She asks again. They tell her, "The society says so". They say they will kill her if she doesn't leave him. Out of love, out of respect she obeys. She forgets the man of her dreams. Out of love, she forgets. She is asked to stay away from strangers, especially men. She is doubted despite her innocence. She is asked to go back to her room. The four walls she is so accustomed to now. Only now, it had lost some of its magic. She starts doubting the capacity of life, to offer happy endings. She wonders, if this is how the world treats its princess's.她坠入爱河。她认识的男人让她快乐，对她充满善意。他令她想起她的家人。言语和目光中充满了天真和浪漫。但是他们发现了。他们告诉她这是错的。他们不问他的情况。他们不想知道她为什么爱他。但是他们说，她错了。她问为什么？他们没有答案。为什么？她又问。他们告诉她，“大家都这么说”。他们说如果她不离开他，他们就杀了她。出于爱，出于尊重，她服从了。她忘记了她的梦中情人。出于爱，她忘记了。他们要求她远离陌生人，尤其是男人。尽管她很清白，她还是受到了怀疑。他们要求她回自己的房间。她现在已经习惯了四堵墙。她开始怀疑生命的能力，怀疑它能否带来幸福。她想知道，这是不是世界对待公主的方式。Then one day, she is asked to serve coffee to some random man. After he leaves, they tell her, he is her groom. They tell her she is a lucky girl. She knows, that's not true. She knows that, its not right. Before she can figure out what is going on, she is inside another room. Only this one is unfamiliar and strange. The very people who had warned her, to stay away from strangers, had locked her inside a room with one. She is scared. But she doesn't give up on her parents, she trusts them and finds love in her new life. She understands that the game of life is filled with sacrifices. She is happy when she realizes that she is pregnant. Her family is happy and so is her husband. She gives birth to a boy. She raises him like a prince. Happiness finds her again and this time she is blessed with a daughter. Her children grow up together. She pampers her son. He tells her she is his Queen. She loved her daughter. She becomes best friends with her. She inducts her into the kitchen. When her daughter tells her that she wants to study further, she tells her, that's not her place. She asks why, she tells her "The society says so". Her son climbs the corporate ladder. But her daughter elopes with her boyfriend. She felt disgraced. She felt rejected. The society told her, "You are a bad Mother". She started hating her daughter.然后有一天，她被要求给一个陌生男人倒咖啡。当他离开后，他们告诉她，他就是她的新郎。他们告诉她，她是一个幸运的女孩。她知道，那不是真的。她知道那不是真的。在她弄清楚发生了什么之前，她已经在另一个房间里了。正是那些警告她远离陌生人的人，把她锁在了一个房间里。她很害怕。但是她没有对她的父母感到绝望，她还是相信他们，在她的新生活中寻找爱。她明白生活的游戏充满了妥协。当她发现自己怀孕时，她很高兴。她的家人很开心，她的丈夫也很开心。她生了一个男孩。她像王子一样抚养他。幸运再次降临到她头上，这次她有了一个女儿。她的孩子们一起长大。她溺爱她的儿子。他告诉她，她是他的王后。她爱她的女儿。她和她成为了最好的朋友。她带着她进入厨房。当她的女儿告诉她，她想继续学习时，她告诉她，那不是她该去的地方。女儿问为什么，她告诉她“大家都是这么说的”。她的儿子在公司里步步高升。可她的女儿和男朋友私奔了。她感到蒙羞。她感到排挤。社会告诉她，“你是个坏妈妈”。她开始憎恨她的女儿。Years have passed now, she is alone. All who she knew, have left her behind. She was staying with her son, who had barely any time. His wife, the girl she chose for him, had no time for her. She was left alone to fight her battles. She wonders, if this is the way the world treated a Queen? One day she ran into her daughter. She looked older and beautiful. She had her grand daughter with her. The moment she saw her mother, she just hugged her and started crying. She told her she was sorry. She told her she could not leave him. She told her of the days she spent crying over her family. Her mother felt sad too. She was near the end of her life and her grudge on her daughter had faded away. They made their peace and said their good byes. 许多年过去了，她独身一人。她所认识的人都把她抛在身后。她和儿子一起住，儿子几乎没有时间。他的妻子，她为他选择的女孩，没有时间陪她。她独自一人在战斗。她想知道，这是不是世界对待女王的方式？一天，她碰见了她的女儿，虽然看起来老了点，但很漂亮，身边带着她的外孙女。女儿一看见母亲就抱住她哭了起来，说她很抱歉，说她不能离开他。她讲述了她为家人哭泣的那段日子。她的母亲也感到难过。她已至暮年，对女儿的怨恨也渐渐消失了。她们言归于好，告别了。Her daughter came to see her today. She was shocked at the way her mother was being treated. She felt insulted that her own mother who had taught her the lessons of life was barely living on her son's mercy. She shouted at her sister in law and dragged her mother out of the house. She was now in her daughters house. She felt at ease with her. She felt like she had gained her best friend back. She learned that her daughter was working now. She had finished her studies upon the insistence of her husband. She asked her, "Who takes care of the kitchen". She told her, they earn enough to hire a house keeper. Her daughter seemed very happy with her life. That somehow made her happy. She wondered how some one she hated so much, could bring her so much joy. She met him that evening. Her son-in-law. She was nervous. She was scared if she would be asked to leave. But he surprised her by greeting her with love and seeking her blessings. She realized that he was every bit the man, she wanted her son to be.她女儿今天来看她。她对母亲遭受的境遇感到震惊。她感到受了侮辱，因为她自己的母亲教给她生活的道理，却只能勉强依靠儿子的怜悯生活。她对她的嫂子大喊大叫，把她母亲拖出了房子。她现在住在她女儿的家里。她和女儿一起住，感到很自在。她觉得她又找回了最好的朋友。她得知女儿现在在工作。在丈夫的坚持下，她完成了学业。她问她:“谁做饭?”她告诉她，他们挣的钱足够雇一个管家。女儿似乎对自己的生活很满意，这让她很高兴。她不明白，她那么恨的一个人，怎么会给她带来这么多的欢乐。那天晚上她遇见了他，她的女婿。她很紧张。如果他要求她离开，她会感到害怕。他却用爱问候她，求她赐福，让她诧异不已。她意识到他完全就是那个她心目中自己儿子该成为的模样。Days passed by and once again she started feeling like a queen. She started feeling like, she was the part of a family. Her daughter felt the same way. She was excited to have her best friend back. They would talk till the end of the night. She fell in love with her grand daughter. She was an angel. But then on that fateful day she fell sick. She knew she was not going to make it. She asked for her grand daughter. On seeing her she started crying. Her daughter told her that everything was going to be ok. She asked her not to be sad. She silenced her saying, she was not sad. She was happy for her grand daughter. She was happy that she would be brought up by her daughter. She was happy that she would not have to live through the circumstance of her mother. She was happy that she was her grand daughter and not her daughter. She placed a hand on her grand daughter's head. But the hand fell limp as life left her body. But there was a smile on her face. Because in that ultimate moment when life was leaving her, she realized, she was finally going to REST IN PEACE.日子一天天过去，她又开始觉得自己像个女王了。她开始觉得，她成为了家庭的一分子。她女儿也有同感。她很高兴她最好的朋友回来了。她们会聊到深夜。她爱上了她的外孙女。她就是个天使。但就在那命中注定的一天，她病倒了。她知道她时日不多了。她要看看她的外孙女。她一看见她就哭了起来。她女儿告诉她一切都会好起来的，叫她不要难过。她不说话了，她并不伤心。她为外孙女感到高兴。她很高兴外孙女将由女儿抚养成人。她很高兴她不用经历女儿所经历的一切。她很高兴她是她的外孙女而不是女儿。她把手放在外孙女的头上。当生命离开她的身体时，她的手软弱无力。但是她的脸上露出了笑容。因为在生命即将离开她的那一刻，她意识到，她终于可以安息了。</span><br>
<span>Rebecca Cunningham, Medical StudentI don’t think I’ve cried this much in a long time. This girl is so brave,so honest and so,so alone(to understand just how alone,read the vile comments below the video). She has been perpetually suffocated at home, treated badly by her brothers and her casteist and sexist father’s goons(and her own brother) are after her life.She still hopes for a place in her father’s heart and his love, after all that she has tolerated at his hands. Her disgusting brother has been writing vile comments about her(the present weeping is only for show/out of shame at having been outed.)我想我很久都没这么哭过了。这个女孩是如此的勇敢，如此的诚实，如此的孤独。她在家里一直过得很压抑，受到哥哥们的虐待，她父亲的男尊女卑和性别歧视的打手(还有她自己的弟弟)也在追杀她。她仍然希望能在父亲心中占有一席之地，得到他的爱，尽管她在父亲的手下忍受了那么多。她那令人作呕的哥哥一直在写关于她的卑鄙评论(现在哭泣只是为了作秀/因为被曝光而感到羞耻)。</span><br>
<span>Gurnoor Pannu, Brutally honest, Writer, Motivation speaker, FeministAs a woman in India, I feel really empowered. I feel many men are now stepping forward for women rights. I love to offer my seat to a tired man in a metro because I believe in gender equality. Life is pretty awesome. Men are actually scared of getting caught up in harassment or rape cases. It's awesome being a woman.Sadly, it's not the same for all the women in the country. But I have hope. Soon, even the women in rural India will feel empowered and things will change for the better. The only thing I fear is that feminism is sometimes mistaken for giving priority to women. Equality should not, must not be compromised作为印度女性，我感到很有力量。我觉得现在很多男人都在为妇女争取权利。我喜欢在地铁里给一个疲惫的男人让座，因为我相信性别平等。生活真是太棒了。男性其实很害怕被卷入性骚扰或强奸案件。做女人真是太棒了。遗憾的是，这并不适用于所有的女性。但我仍心怀希望。很快，就连印度农村妇女也会感到被赋予了力量，情况也会变得更好。我唯一担心的是，女权主义有时会被误认为优先考虑女性。平等不应该，也不应该妥协。</span><br>
<span>Shubham Sharma, works at Sagar Institute of Research and Technology : SIRT BhopalAs a mother she is god....as a wife she is life....as a daughter she is laughter....india,bharat,hindustan is a place where womens are treated divine in scriptures.i would mention despite all the atrocities that happens .we the indians repect ,value , and moreover accept their role whatsoever it is. Hope one fine day all women of this world would think about being indian.I could have written about rapes ,molestations ,and dowry to earn sympathy but for me a women is all that maintains decorum in home, discipline in life and the urge to become better by each passing day.....# proud to be indian作为一个母亲，她是神……作为妻子，她就是生活……作为一个女儿，她是欢笑……印度，巴拉特，印度斯坦是一个奉女人为神的地方。我想说的是，尽管发生过种种暴行，我们印度人尊重、重视并接受她们的角色。希望有一天，世界上所有的女人都会希望自己是印度人。我本可以写强奸、性骚扰和嫁妆来博取同情，但对我而言，一个在家庭中保持着端庄，在生活中保持着自律，在每一天都渴望变得更好的女人……我为自己身为印度人而自豪。</span><br>
<span>Ali Akram, lives in IndiaThere are many aspects of it lets have a look.1.First of all, the basic aspects of the democracy is available for the Indian women, i.e- the universal adult franchise. means they participate and organize themselves for the electoral posts of any running democratic organization.2.Women in India have the perfect blend of strength and tenderness. They have the beautiful quality to manage home and the outer world simultaneously.3.Though at some levels like dowry, crimes like rape, sexual harassment at office or public places, and molestation, eve-teasing, even after over sixty years of independence women are still exploited, which is the shameful side of our country. Yet one can’t deny that the situation has improved since the earlier times4.Women, who now represent 48.2% of the population, are getting access to education, and then employment. From 5.4 million girls enrolled at the primary level in 1950-51 to 61.1 million girls in 2004-05. At the upper primary level, the enrollment increased from 0.5 million girls to 22.7 million girls.我们来看看几个方面：1.首先，印度妇女享有皿煮的基本方面。成人公民权，是指可以参加和组织竞选任何进行中的皿煮组织的选举职务。2.印度女性拥有力量和温柔的完美结合。她们拥有同时管理家庭内外的优秀才能。3.虽然在某些程度上，比如嫁妆，强奸，办公室或公共场所的性骚扰，甚至在独立60多年后的今天，妇女仍然被剥削，这些都是我们国家可耻的一面。然而，我们不能否认，这种情况已经有所改善了。4.妇女现在占人口的48.2%，她们接受教育，参加工作。从1950-51年的540万名小学入学女童到2004-05年的6110万名女童。小学高年级女生入学率由50万人提高到2270万人。</span><br>
<span>Reenaa Toomarr, former Travel Content WriterStatus of an Indian woman:The women of the present generation have generally received higher education than the women of their preceding generation. There have been far reaching consequences in the economic status of their families.Roles of an Indian woman:The modern women are inclined towards the social issues, and trying hard to improve the social status of women at large.印度妇女的地位:当代妇女普遍比上一代妇女接受了更多的高等教育。她们家庭的经济状况受到了深远的影响。印度女人的角色:现代女性倾向于关注社会问题，努力提高女性的社会地位。http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-24/dd9c47d67c1d4722435cc137dbaec88f.jpg</span><br>
</p><p><b>wuxan94: </b><br>
<span>本朝都3700万三哥那边的形势……</span><br>
</p><p><b>spoony: </b><br>
<span>为什么在印度的某些地区，只有母亲必须触摸儿媳的脚来表示尊重，父亲却不需要？   。。。邮局港剧。。。</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1855633[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
