<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>美国《时代》杂志公布2010年代十佳游戏名单</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>美国《时代》杂志公布2010年代十佳游戏名单</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 11:08:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>美国《时代》杂志公布2010年代十佳游戏名单[50-100]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1905473-1-1.html</link>
      <description>美国《时代》杂志公布2010年代十佳游戏名单&#13;
排名不分先后
&#13;
1 .《GTA5》
&#13;
2. 《塞尔达传说: 旷野之息》
&#13;
3. 《堡垒之夜》
&#13;
4. 《黑暗之魂》
&#13;
5. 《英雄联盟》
&#13;
6. 《宝可梦GO》
&#13;
7. 《我的世界》
&#13;
8. 《上古卷轴5: 天际》
&#13;
9. 《传送门2》
&#13;
10.《极乐迪斯科》 </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>qianoooo: </b><br>
<span>000000 发表于 2019-12-25 10:59</span><br>
<span>算是游戏圈平权事件最大的一桩了，超200女性员工罢工，集体诉讼</span><br>
<span>拳头态度也很积极，道歉，1000万赔偿，增 ...</span><br>
<span>拳头表态太慢了 我去年八月份看到kotaku文章，拳头今年大规模女性员工罢工才开始慢慢表态</span><br>
<span>拳头老总对这种东西非常模棱两可的 只不过今年要扩张业务了 得罪女性的话很难招到新员工</span><br>
</p><p><b>000000: </b><br>
<span>qianoooo 发表于 2019-12-25 23:46</span><br>
<span>拳头表态太慢了 我去年八月份看到kotaku文章，拳头今年大规模女性员工罢工才开始慢慢表态</span><br>
<span>拳头老总对这种 ...</span><br>
<span>也是，从reddit面试爆料开始算，其实也挺假装失明的</span><br>
</p><p><b>FUZE: </b><br>
<span>拳头pc这件事很出名吧</span><br>
<span>算是一个典范例子来解释欧美电子游戏为何如此pc</span><br>
</p><p><b>orangeth: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 orangeth 于 2019-12-26 01:26 编辑 </span><br>
<span>Zest 发表于 2019-12-25 17:02</span><br>
<span>极乐迪斯科是啥玩意</span><br>
<span>在不玩弄meta这种文本杂技的情况下目前最合格的视觉小说之一</span><br>
<span>在折腾了一大圈之后，终于有人发现小说与互动性的结合并不是把几个不同的故事塞进一个开头了</span><br>
</p><p><b>历史厨: </b><br>
<span>隔行如隔山,专职游戏媒体搞这个都经常闹出争议,主流综合性媒体真没必要来凑这个热闹.</span><br>
</p><p><b>四氢化钠: </b><br>
<span>选的还蛮好的啊，除了迪斯科都算有巨大影响力的作品。</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>fox: </b><br>
<span>时代周刊，就是那个把瑞典环保萝莉评为2019年度人物的白左杂志了，在我心中地位已经塌得连小岛都不如了，不去环保在这儿搞啥游戏排名呢浪费纸</span><br>
</p><p><b>紫毛母猩猩: </b><br>
<span>堡垒之夜</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>pf67: </b><br>
<span>看评价，这10大其实代表了10个不同类型的游戏的代表作，不是真的去选top10</span><br>
<span>独立游戏代表选迪斯科作为一个收尾也没啥问题吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>moeblack: </b><br>
<span>orangeth 发表于 2019-12-26 01:19</span><br>
<span>在不玩弄meta这种文本杂技的情况下目前最合格的视觉小说之一</span><br>
<span>在折腾了一大圈之后，终于有人发现小说与互 ...</span><br>
<span>希望下一个十年有人能做出革命性的galgame作品</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MIX 3, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>Chia: </b><br>
<span>任何一作都做到了数个层面的难以取代，肯定不丢人了</span><br>
</p><p><b>费老师: </b><br>
<span>堡垒之夜的确现象级，但是吃鸡上一个还是要上正宗吃鸡</span><br>
</p><p><b>ace8848: </b><br>
<span>没有一个sony第一方，巨硬也就mc勉强搭个边，可以的。</span><br>
</p><p><b>绿冰: </b><br>
<span>小修 发表于 2019-12-25 20:40</span><br>
<span>我觉得这个排行榜挺靠谱的。</span><br>
<span>出了黑魂其他都没问题。感觉血源，黑魂3，只狼三选一 ...</span><br>
<span>虽然写的是黑魂1，但实际上是包含整个魂系列+血源，以及对业界带来的长远影响</span><br>
<span>旷野之息还说了带Switch的护航作用</span><br>
<span>总得来说，除了最后两个都相当有说服力</span><br>
</p><p><b>修罗王: </b><br>
<span>moeblack 发表于 2019-12-26 03:09</span><br>
<span>希望下一个十年有人能做出革命性的galgame作品</span><br>
<span>极乐迪斯科这个框架就挺适合装个gal的</span><br>
</p><p><b>破罐子: </b><br>
<span>monolithsoft 发表于 2019-12-25 17:05</span><br>
<span>要说影响力 吃鸡和部落冲突得有吧</span><br>
<span>吃鸡在婆罗门眼里太LOW，玩的人再多也不能让上台面。</span><br>
</p><p><b>wwdzcjsmxx: </b><br>
<span>感觉还行啊，字面上十佳的话感觉还有争议，但是论这十年对游戏行业的影响，差不多了，不然还有哪个？</span><br>
<span>然后感觉迪斯科这个，影响还没出来吧？有其他可以替代么？</span><br>
<span>老滚5知道不错，但是对其影响了解不多，巫师3不能比？</span><br>
</p><p><b>哈曼的YY: </b><br>
<span>极乐迪斯科的专楼好歹时不时出现在第一页呢</span><br>
</p><p><b>pgain2004: </b><br>
<span>wwdzcjsmxx 发表于 2019-12-26 09:03</span><br>
<span>感觉还行啊，字面上十佳的话感觉还有争议，但是论这十年对游戏行业的影响，差不多了，不然还有哪个？</span><br>
<span>然后 ...</span><br>
<span>猎魔人3其实应该也够格，但老滚5更早，是原创，而且老滚5本身的控制台开放性和玩家创作阵容（质量兼优，以至于成了少女卷轴）很有代表性。</span><br>
</p><p><b>OTAKU100: </b><br>
<span>第一个我玩过</span><br>
</p><p><b>杨雪崩: </b><br>
<span>以媒体人视角评德拉诺</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HUAWEI VOG-AL10, Android 10上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>血翼龙: </b><br>
<span>把黑魂1比作地下丝绒的首砖喷了…销量惨淡，玩过的人十个有九个去做游戏了</span><br>
</p><p><b>ChrisSnake: </b><br>
<span>这只是一种宣传策略 在一堆大哥里面放一个明显有问题的 既能显示客观性 又能引起大家论战 刷一波热度</span><br>
<span>不然他放一堆大家都没意见的 你看一眼就过了 谁还去讨论</span><br>
</p><p><b>operatbig: </b><br>
<span>这种榜单应该按营收排。</span><br>
</p><p><b>yellow0507: </b><br>
<span>尼哥打拳滚粗好不好   这真是唯一一个看到就犯恶心的游戏偏偏这游戏群体喜欢到处刷存在感</span><br>
</p><p><b>萨拉丁: </b><br>
<span>wwdzcjsmxx 发表于 2019-12-26 09:03</span><br>
<span>感觉还行啊，字面上十佳的话感觉还有争议，但是论这十年对游戏行业的影响，差不多了，不然还有哪个？</span><br>
<span>然后 ...</span><br>
<span>虽然我不喜欢老滚5，但还是要说，不能。</span><br>
</p><p><b>观自在: </b><br>
<span>平野绫入选“传说中的声优”既视感</span><br>
</p><p><b>mjzs07: </b><br>
<span>堡垒之夜中国不火啊，吃鸡倒是全世界都火</span><br>
</p><p><b>citrus: </b><br>
<span>按营收fgo怕不是吊打榜上一半游戏，而且下个十年可能还是cod、fifa、刺客信条霸榜。目前这个榜感觉迪斯科换成巫师3就差不多。以爆款新类型游戏而言，吃鸡和pokemon go差不多，个人感觉吃鸡在游戏玩家中影响力更大，pgo在大众文化中影响力更大。选堡垒不选吃鸡可能也是因为后者在大众文化中影响力不如前者</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1905473[50-100]</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>美国《时代》杂志公布2010年代十佳游戏名单[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1905473-1-1.html</link>
      <description>美国《时代》杂志公布2010年代十佳游戏名单&#13;
排名不分先后
&#13;
1 .《GTA5》
&#13;
2. 《塞尔达传说: 旷野之息》
&#13;
3. 《堡垒之夜》
&#13;
4. 《黑暗之魂》
&#13;
5. 《英雄联盟》
&#13;
6. 《宝可梦GO》
&#13;
7. 《我的世界》
&#13;
8. 《上古卷轴5: 天际》
&#13;
9. 《传送门2》
&#13;
10.《极乐迪斯科》 </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>bairn: </b><br>
<span>美国《时代》杂志公布2010年代十佳游戏名单</span><br>
<span>排名不分先后</span><br>
<span>1 .《GTA5》</span><br>
<span>2. 《塞尔达传说: 旷野之息》</span><br>
<span>3. 《堡垒之夜》</span><br>
<span>4. 《黑暗之魂》</span><br>
<span>5. 《英雄联盟》</span><br>
<span>6. 《宝可梦GO》</span><br>
<span>7. 《我的世界》</span><br>
<span>8. 《上古卷轴5: 天际》</span><br>
<span>9. 《传送门2》</span><br>
<span>10.《极乐迪斯科》 </span><br>
</p><p><b>何然: </b><br>
<span>要素过多</span><br>
</p><p><b>Zest: </b><br>
<span>极乐迪斯科是啥玩意</span><br>
</p><p><b>超紳士: </b><br>
<span>然后封面如果是无人深空就好了</span><br>
</p><p><b>茛菪: </b><br>
<span>十佳这种怎么评都是扯淡的，至少这些都算是在时代上刻下印记的作品了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>monolithsoft: </b><br>
<span>要说影响力 吃鸡和部落冲突得有吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>naclken.: </b><br>
<span>极乐迪斯科真有这么神？在2019得奖不说还10年影响力？</span><br>
</p><p><b>bairn: </b><br>
<span>Zest 发表于 2019-12-25 17:02</span><br>
<span>极乐迪斯科是啥玩意</span><br>
<span>不知道 但看吹这么狠明年出了中文应该要玩一下了TGA也拿了不少奖</span><br>
</p><p><b>Yukibet: </b><br>
<span>明明是给不玩游戏的人看的杂志却选了个婆罗门游戏充场</span><br>
</p><p><b>黑修士: </b><br>
<span>和自己10年来最喜欢的游戏，好歹重叠了一个</span><br>
</p><p><b>武内P: </b><br>
<span>Zest 发表于 2019-12-25 17:02</span><br>
<span>极乐迪斯科是啥玩意</span><br>
<span>就是今年tga连拿4奖的那个</span><br>
</p><p><b>无限弹手炮: </b><br>
<span>LOL和MC？小编数死早</span><br>
</p><p><b>FUZE: </b><br>
<span>堡垒之夜鸡巴笑爆</span><br>
</p><p><b>十字骷髅高达: </b><br>
<span>极乐迪斯科是什么鬼啊直接进10年最佳，虽然明年出中文必玩</span><br>
</p><p><b>ammk: </b><br>
<span>顶级巨魔，不知道报纸有没有评论区</span><br>
</p><p><b>000000: </b><br>
<span>发现小众、婆罗门、持续运营类、商业成功、老树新花、顶级IP都涵盖了……</span><br>
<span>其实感觉还行哎</span><br>
</p><p><b>000000: </b><br>
<span>he video game industry was already a billion dollar behemoth when it rolled into the 2010s. Over the past decade, the cultural cache of video games has grown and its profits are now greater than movies, television or music. The 2010s are when the hobby stopped being something semi-niche, and solidly took its place in the mainstream.</span><br>
<span>The tension between art and commerce isn’t the same in video games as it is in movies. There are fewer auteurs and more venture capitalists. During the past decade, some artists broke free of the business side and produced works of astounding beauty on par with any prestige television show. The business of video games also exploded, pulling in such obscene amounts of cash that legislators started to ask questions and consider regulations, particularly with regard to games including “microtransactions” which some have compared with gambling. This decade, parents didn’t worry about violence in video games so much as they worried about time and money spent on neverending live services like Fortnite and Star Wars: Battlefront II.</span><br>
<span>RELATED STORIES</span><br>
<span>TECH</span><br>
<span>Here Are the 10 Best PlayStation 4 Games to Play Right Now</span><br>
<span>ENTERTAINMENT</span><br>
<span>How Respawn Made the Best ‘Star Wars’ Game in a Decade</span><br>
<span>Here are the games that defined the decade and don’t forget to read TIME’s list of the best songs, TV shows, miniseries, movies, movie performances, nonfiction books, fiction books, gadgets and albums of the decade.</span><br>
<span>Grand Theft Auto V (2013)</span><br>
<span>SharePlay Video</span><br>
<span>Rockstar’s Grand Theft Auto V is the most financially successful entertainment product of all time. At $6 billion in revenue and growing, the open world crime simulator has raked in more cash than Gone With the Wind or the Star Wars film franchise. The series reached its zenith with the fifth installment, mixing open world madness with an ambitious story. The cultural impact of Grand Theft Auto is hard to quantify. It’s been the center of multiple lawsuits, a focus for parents worried about violent video games and the subject of made-for-TV dramatizations. It’s so well known and so ubiquitous, that Ryan Reynolds is starring in a high-budget action blockbuster inspired by, but not directly based on, its online multiplayer mode.</span><br>
<span>The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild (2017)</span><br>
<span>SharePlay Video</span><br>
<span>Get The Brief. Sign up to receive the top stories you need to know right now.</span><br>
<span>Enter your email address</span><br>
<span> I can confirm I have read and accept the Terms Of Use.</span><br>
<span>SIGN UP NOW</span><br>
<span>You may unsubscribe from email communication at any time. See our Privacy Policy for further details.</span><br>
<span>With The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild, Nintendo proved it could make a modern open world game. More than that, it proved it could create an open world game that was more interesting than what the competition was doing. Untethered from linear progression, players were free to explore Hyrule at their own pace and create their own adventures. It was also the Nintendo Switch’s killer app, a game that moved systems and delighted fans, when it launched with the new console.</span><br>
<span>Fortnite (2017)</span><br>
<span>SharePlay Video</span><br>
<span>PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds may have popularized the 1 vs. 100, battle royale shooter genre, but Fortnite flat out turned it into an inescapable cultural phenomenon. Fortnite started as a modular base building game. When developer Epic Games patched in the battle royale multiplayer mode (after the success of PUBG) and gave it away for free, players—especially young players—picked up Fortnite by the millions. Epic Games made so much money so fast that it launched its own distribution platform. The game is popular it’s launched the careers of superstar streamers like Ninja and scared parents about the addictive nature of video games.</span><br>
<span>Dark Souls (2011)</span><br>
<span>Dark Souls_ Official HD Trailer</span><br>
<span>Dark Souls_ Official HD Trailer</span><br>
<span>SharePlay Video</span><br>
<span>Dark Souls, from developer From Software, loomed over the decade like a gargoyle. The original Dark Souls has proven to be like the Velvet Underground’s first album; not everyone played it, but it inspired everyone who did. The very tough but fair difficulty, background approach to storytelling and satisfyingly tight control scheme has been repeatedly replicated and iterated upon, but never quite perfected, by other developers. From Software’s biggest success with its formula came with 2015’s Bloodborne—which ditched Dark Souls’ medieval aesthetic and focused on a Lovecraftian gothic nightmare where the best defense is a good offense. The most recent game to pay homage to Dark Souls is Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order. The blocking-focused lightsaber combat, replenishing enemies by gaining health and losing progress with death are straight out of From Software’s playbook.</span><br>
<span>SPOTLIGHT STORY</span><br>
<span>The 50 Best Podcasts to Listen to Right Now</span><br>
<span>From "Dolly Parton's America" to "Code Switch," here's what you should listen to right now.</span><br>
<span>League of Legends (2009)</span><br>
<span>SharePlay Video</span><br>
<span>Developer Riot Games released League of Legends at the end of 2009, but the game that helped define the multiplayer online battle arena game genre wouldn’t become a global phenomenon for a few more years. Now, it’s the gold standard for esports. League of Legends tournaments pack stadiums across the world and draw more viewers than the Super Bowl. In the past 10 years, Riot Games typified another theme of gaming’s 2010s: sexism. Gaming spent decades perceived as a boy’s club, and that toxic culture permeated the top levels of gaming’s biggest companies, with Riot Games executives being credibly accused of abuse by former employees.</span><br>
<span>Pokémon Go (2016)</span><br>
<span>Pokémon GO Trailer</span><br>
<span>Pokémon Company unveiled its latest Pocket Monster experience called Pokemon Go.</span><br>
<span>SharePlay Video</span><br>
<span>ENTERTAINMENT</span><br>
<span>‘Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order’ Is Out of This World</span><br>
<span>For a few months there in 2016, it felt like the whole planet was playing Niantic’s mobile augmented reality game Pokémon Go. If you weren’t playing it, then you knew about it because everyday brought a fresh stream of news stories about the joys, adventures and mishaps of the people who walked around in real life, seeking virtual pocket monsters in hopes of catching them all. Players found a dead body while hunting rare Pokémon, tragically died when their hunts ran afoul of crime and generally gripped the nation for months. Years later, players still find new thrills and chills hunting Pokémon in the real world.</span><br>
<span>Minecraft (2009)</span><br>
<span>SharePlay Video</span><br>
<span>Minecraft is another game released in 2009 that grew into a cultural institution in the 2010s. If you’ve got kids, or know people who do, you know what Minecraft is. Ten years after its release, Minecraft is still the most watched game on YouTube, beating Fortnite by more than 40 billion views. In 2014, Minecraft creator Notch tweeted that he’d like to sell off the game and Microsoft stepped in to take it off his hands for $2.5 billion. Today, it’s the second best-selling game of all time behind the Nintendo Wii’s pack in game Wii Sports. With constant updates and a new mobile augmented reality version launching soon, Minecraft is poised to take its domination into the next decade.</span><br>
<span>TECH</span><br>
<span>'Pokémon Sword' and 'Shield' Are Worth Playing</span><br>
<span>The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim (2011)</span><br>
<span>Skyrim Special Edition – Gameplay Trailer #2</span><br>
<span>Skyrim Special Edition gameplay trailer</span><br>
<span>SharePlay Video</span><br>
<span>Bethesda unleashed The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim on the world in 2011 and it’s remained at the top of the sales charts ever since. The flagship role-playing game has transitioned from one console generation to another, been ported to virtual reality and tweaked for release on the Nintendo Switch. Skyrim’s enduring charm is its open ended play style set in a gigantic and detailed open world. And it’s been helped along by a dedicated community of modders who have even further molded the game into a fantasy playground.</span><br>
<span>Other developers would chase this ideal through the decade, but few would achieve it.</span><br>
<span>Portal 2 (2011)</span><br>
<span>SharePlay Video</span><br>
<span>Developer Valve screamed into the new decade with the incredible Portal 2: a first person puzzle game that built off of the successful first game in every way, with a satisfying story and an increasingly clever mechanic in its teleporting portal gun.</span><br>
<span>Portal 2’s release was bittersweet. It marked the beginning of a decade where Valve stopped doing what made it so famous: making incredible video games. The 2000s saw the release of Half-Life 2, Left 4 Dead and Counter-Strike, all enormously successful games. In the 2010s, Valve mostly iterated on Dota 2, released the Vive virtual reality headset with HTC and dodged questions about Half-Life 3.</span><br>
<span>Valve has continued to make billions from its Steam distribution platform but failed to produce a game as genre bending and enjoyable as Portal 2. It ended the decade by finally announcing a follow up to Half-Life, something fans had waited more than 15 years for. But Half-Life: Alyx is a virtual reality title and it’s unclear if Valve can bring its game-making magic to the new platform, or, for that matter, a new decade.</span><br>
<span>Thankfully, we’ll always have GLaDOS, Chell and Wheatley.</span><br>
<span>Disco Elysium (2019)</span><br>
<span>SharePlay Video</span><br>
<span>Released just months before the start of the 2020s, Disco Elysium is the perfect punctuation mark on a decade of excellent games. It’s a video game that’s steeped in the past but looking towards the future. It’s the kind of video game that only comes at the turn of the decade, that special time when something ends and something new is born.</span><br>
<span>In this very dense role-playing game, players wake up with a killer hangover in a grungy hotel room and quickly realize they’re a police officer in the hotel to solve a crime. But that’s all they remember. The details of the crime—and their personal life—are gone and it’s up to the player to fill in the blanks.</span><br>
<span>Disco Elysium is a game that looks and plays like a game from 1999, a 2D isometric throwback with fully rendered backgrounds and point and click navigation. The storytelling and mechanics, however, feel like they come from the future. Players put points into stats like “Esprit De Corps” which allows them to understand what cops are thinking, or “Shivers” which allows the city’s streets to speak to you. Leveling up involves pondering strange ideas that alter your skills and change the way your detective sees the world. It’s a game that breathes new life into the old RPG format.</span><br>
<span>Disco Elysium is proof of what video game fans have known for years: that the medium has special strengths and can tell unique stories you won’t see on TV or read in a book. It’s a game that highlights how all video games are art.</span><br>
</p><p><b>有优越感的人: </b><br>
<span>000000 发表于 2019-12-25 18:14</span><br>
<span>发现小众、婆罗门、持续运营类、商业成功、老树新花、顶级IP都涵盖了……</span><br>
<span>其实感觉还行哎 ...</span><br>
<span>该有的都有了</span><br>
</p><p><b>pgain2004: </b><br>
<span>看了一下具体评价，这评得挺好的</span><br>
</p><p><b>YoungYiba: </b><br>
<span>感觉更应该说是最有代表性的吧 </span><br>
<span>—— 来自 OnePlus HD1900, Android 10上的 S1Next-鹅版 v1.3.3.2-play</span><br>
</p><p><b>ieahgiergn: </b><br>
<span>还可以吧，时代就一综合性周刊，排名分先后，但上榜的都很有代表性</span><br>
</p><p><b>memphiseme: </b><br>
<span>极乐迪斯科我第一次听到这个游戏的名字。。。看来是我火星了</span><br>
</p><p><b>turtlejk: </b><br>
<span>极乐迪斯科这就评上了啊..敲碗等中文..</span><br>
</p><p><b>hshiki: </b><br>
<span>有魂1，这榜我服</span><br>
</p><p><b>綺麗: </b><br>
<span>野狼迪斯科</span><br>
</p><p><b>资本剑客: </b><br>
<span>极乐迪斯科可以换一个</span><br>
</p><p><b>Bojenkins: </b><br>
<span>有迪斯科</span><br>
<span>这个排名真的是f**king based</span><br>
</p><p><b>pgain2004: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 pgain2004 于 2019-12-25 19:51 编辑 </span><br>
<span>主楼和楼上的转帖都太随意，我来</span><br>
<span>https://time.com/5752663/best-video-games-2010s-decade/</span><br>
<span>The 10 Best Video Games of the 2010s</span><br>
<span>The video game industry was already a billion dollar behemoth when it rolled into the 2010s. Over the past decade, the cultural cache of video games has grown and its profits are now greater than movies, television or music. The 2010s are when the hobby stopped being something semi-niche, and solidly took its place in the mainstream.</span><br>
<span>The tension between art and commerce isn’t the same in video games as it is in movies. There are fewer auteurs and more venture capitalists. During the past decade, some artists broke free of the business side and produced works of astounding beauty on par with any prestige television show. The business of video games also exploded, pulling in such obscene amounts of cash that legislators started to ask questions and consider regulations, particularly with regard to games including “microtransactions” which some have compared with gambling. This decade, parents didn’t worry about violence in video games so much as they worried about time and money spent on neverending live services like Fortnite and Star Wars: Battlefront II.</span><br>
<span>游戏业在这十年发展得更加庞大，总收入甚至超过了影视和音乐，跃身主流。而且在艺术方面有脱离商业桎梏诞生的好作品，在商业方面也因为资金的大量进入而爆发，甚至让父母更担心氪金而不是什么暴·力·色·情。</span><br>
<span>Grand Theft Auto V (2013)</span><br>
<span>Rockstar’s Grand Theft Auto V is the most financially successful entertainment product of all time. At $6 billion in revenue and growing, the open world crime simulator has raked in more cash than Gone With the Wind or the Star Wars film franchise. The series reached its zenith with the fifth installment, mixing open world madness with an ambitious story. The cultural impact of Grand Theft Auto is hard to quantify. It’s been the center of multiple lawsuits, a focus for parents worried about violent video games and the subject of made-for-TV dramatizations. It’s so well known and so ubiquitous, that Ryan Reynolds is starring in a high-budget action blockbuster inspired by, but not directly based on, its online multiplayer mode.</span><br>
<span>史上最成功娱乐产品，60亿收益，干掉了《飘》和《星战》全系列。文化影响难以估量，多起诉讼、暴力电游、影视化……其知名度高到死侍演员瑞安·雷诺兹出演了一部受启发于其多人模式的动作大片。The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild (2017)</span><br>
<span>With The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild, Nintendo proved it could make a modern open world game. More than that, it proved it could create an open world game that was more interesting than what the competition was doing. Untethered from linear progression, players were free to explore Hyrule at their own pace and create their own adventures. It was also the Nintendo Switch’s killer app, a game that moved systems and delighted fans, when it launched with the new console.</span><br>
<span>为NS护航的这款杀手级游戏证明任天堂能搞开放世界，顺手就吊打了之前所有同类作品。</span><br>
<span>Fortnite (2017)</span><br>
<span>PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds may have popularized the 1 vs. 100, battle royale shooter genre, but Fortnite flat out turned it into an inescapable cultural phenomenon. Fortnite started as a modular base building game. When developer Epic Games patched in the battle royale multiplayer mode (after the success of PUBG) and gave it away for free, players—especially young players—picked up Fortnite by the millions. Epic Games made so much money so fast that it launched its own distribution platform. The game is popular it’s launched the careers of superstar streamers like Ninja and scared parents about the addictive nature of video games.</span><br>
<span>PUBG推广了大逃杀模式，而堡垒之夜则将之变成文化现象。它跟风跟得如此成功，一下子吸纳了千万玩家；它吸金吸得如此暴力，让Epic都敢自己搞游戏平台了；它带起了一堆超级主播，它所展现的电游黏性吓摊了一堆家长。</span><br>
<span>Dark Souls (2011)</span><br>
<span>Dark Souls, from developer From Software, loomed over the decade like a gargoyle. The original Dark Souls has proven to be like the Velvet Underground’s first album; not everyone played it, but it inspired everyone who did. The very tough but fair difficulty, background approach to storytelling and satisfyingly tight control scheme has been repeatedly replicated and iterated upon, but never quite perfected, by other developers. From Software’s biggest success with its formula came with 2015’s Bloodborne—which ditched Dark Souls’ medieval aesthetic and focused on a Lovecraftian gothic nightmare where the best defense is a good offense. The most recent game to pay homage to Dark Souls is Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order. The blocking-focused lightsaber combat, replenishing enemies by gaining health and losing progress with death are straight out of From Software’s playbook.</span><br>
<span>该作就像地下丝绒的首专，其难度设置、叙事模式和操控设计在这十年间一直被模仿，从未被超越。从同一公式延伸而成的血源再次阐述了最好的防御便是进攻。League of Legends (2009)</span><br>
<span>Developer Riot Games released League of Legends at the end of 2009, but the game that helped define the multiplayer online battle arena game genre wouldn’t become a global phenomenon for a few more years. Now, it’s the gold standard for esports. League of Legends tournaments pack stadiums across the world and draw more viewers than the Super Bowl. In the past 10 years, Riot Games typified another theme of gaming’s 2010s: sexism. Gaming spent decades perceived as a boy’s club, and that toxic culture permeated the top levels of gaming’s biggest companies, with Riot Games executives being credibly accused of abuse by former employees.</span><br>
<span>电竞的楷模，其赛事观众超过了超级碗。同时Riot也成为电游领域的性别歧视现象的代表。</span><br>
<span>Pokémon Go (2016)</span><br>
<span>For a few months there in 2016, it felt like the whole planet was playing Niantic’s mobile augmented reality game Pokémon Go. If you weren’t playing it, then you knew about it because everyday brought a fresh stream of news stories about the joys, adventures and mishaps of the people who walked around in real life, seeking virtual pocket monsters in hopes of catching them all. Players found a dead body while hunting rare Pokémon, tragically died when their hunts ran afoul of crime and generally gripped the nation for months. Years later, players still find new thrills and chills hunting Pokémon in the real world.</span><br>
<span>16年那几个月让人觉得全地球都在玩这AR作品，就算没玩也会被玩家到处乱窜抓怪的相关新闻轰炸，甚至有人因此丧命。几年过去，玩家活跃度仍然很高。</span><br>
<span>Minecraft (2009)</span><br>
<span>Minecraft is another game released in 2009 that grew into a cultural institution in the 2010s. If you’ve got kids, or know people who do, you know what Minecraft is. Ten years after its release, Minecraft is still the most watched game on YouTube, beating Fortnite by more than 40 billion views. In 2014, Minecraft creator Notch tweeted that he’d like to sell off the game and Microsoft stepped in to take it off his hands for $2.5 billion. Today, it’s the second best-selling game of all time behind the Nintendo Wii’s pack in game Wii Sports. With constant updates and a new mobile augmented reality version launching soon, Minecraft is poised to take its domination into the next decade.</span><br>
<span>另一款成为文化的作品，只要认识孩子就认识它。十年过去，MC仍守着YT最高播放量游戏的宝座(过四百亿)。随着内容更新和AR移动版发售，可预见它还能烧偏下十年。</span><br>
<span>The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim (2011)</span><br>
<span>Bethesda unleashed The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim on the world in 2011 and it’s remained at the top of the sales charts ever since. The flagship role-playing game has transitioned from one console generation to another, been ported to virtual reality and tweaked for release on the Nintendo Switch. Skyrim’s enduring charm is its open ended play style set in a gigantic and detailed open world. And it’s been helped along by a dedicated community of modders who have even further molded the game into a fantasy playground.</span><br>
<span>Other developers would chase this ideal through the decade, but few would achieve it.</span><br>
<span>自从被发布就一直在销量榜上没走过，从单平台一直延伸至全平台，它自身开放巨大又精致，强力的社区UGC更让它成为瑰丽的游乐场。</span><br>
<span>Portal 2 (2011)</span><br>
<span>Developer Valve screamed into the new decade with the incredible Portal 2: a first person puzzle game that built off of the successful first game in every way, with a satisfying story and an increasingly clever mechanic in its teleporting portal gun.</span><br>
<span>Portal 2’s release was bittersweet. It marked the beginning of a decade where Valve stopped doing what made it so famous: making incredible video games. The 2000s saw the release of Half-Life 2, Left 4 Dead and Counter-Strike, all enormously successful games. In the 2010s, Valve mostly iterated on Dota 2, released the Vive virtual reality headset with HTC and dodged questions about Half-Life 3.</span><br>
<span>Valve has continued to make billions from its Steam distribution platform but failed to produce a game as genre bending and enjoyable as Portal 2. It ended the decade by finally announcing a follow up to Half-Life, something fans had waited more than 15 years for. But Half-Life: Alyx is a virtual reality title and it’s unclear if Valve can bring its game-making magic to the new platform, or, for that matter, a new decade.</span><br>
<span>Thankfully, we’ll always have GLaDOS, Chell and Wheatley.</span><br>
<span>成功的首作，超成功的续作，也成了G胖摸鱼10年不数3的开端。</span><br>
<span>Disco Elysium (2019)</span><br>
<span>Released just months before the start of the 2020s, Disco Elysium is the perfect punctuation mark on a decade of excellent games. It’s a video game that’s steeped in the past but looking towards the future. It’s the kind of video game that only comes at the turn of the decade, that special time when something ends and something new is born.</span><br>
<span>In this very dense role-playing game, players wake up with a killer hangover in a grungy hotel room and quickly realize they’re a police officer in the hotel to solve a crime. But that’s all they remember. The details of the crime—and their personal life—are gone and it’s up to the player to fill in the blanks.</span><br>
<span>Disco Elysium is a game that looks and plays like a game from 1999, a 2D isometric throwback with fully rendered backgrounds and point and click navigation. The storytelling and mechanics, however, feel like they come from the future. Players put points into stats like “Esprit De Corps” which allows them to understand what cops are thinking, or “Shivers” which allows the city’s streets to speak to you. Leveling up involves pondering strange ideas that alter your skills and change the way your detective sees the world. It’s a game that breathes new life into the old RPG format.</span><br>
<span>Disco Elysium is proof of what video game fans have known for years: that the medium has special strengths and can tell unique stories you won’t see on TV or read in a book. It’s a game that highlights how all video games are art.</span><br>
<span>作为本十年的完美句号，沉浸于历史而展望未来，这是一款标志着结束与开始的作品。它的形式仿佛来自1999，它的叙事与机制却仿佛源自未来，它为RPG老公式带来新生。</span><br>
<span>该作证明了玩家熟知多年的一件事：电子游戏，这种媒体能让你体验到无法从荧幕与书页中获得的独特故事。正是这样的作品说明了，电子游戏为什么是艺术。</span><br>
<span>然后顺手简译了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>ebuw: </b><br>
<span>迪斯科没玩过。英雄联盟和堡垒之夜换成守望先锋和绝地求生，这个榜单就完美了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>注册一个: </b><br>
<span>意外的还行</span><br>
</p><p><b>病態極端: </b><br>
<span>ebuw 发表于 2019-12-25 19:11</span><br>
<span>迪斯科没玩过。英雄联盟和堡垒之夜换成守望先锋和绝地求生，这个榜单就完美了。 ...</span><br>
<span>TIMES的巨魔力還未夠班口牙</span><br>
</p><p><b>pgain2004: </b><br>
<span>ebuw 发表于 2019-12-25 19:11</span><br>
<span>迪斯科没玩过。英雄联盟和堡垒之夜换成守望先锋和绝地求生，这个榜单就完美了。 ...</span><br>
<span>堡垒那里有先提PUBG的作品和角色。</span><br>
</p><p><b>melting: </b><br>
<span>感觉像是最有影响力的10个游戏，看评论还挺靠谱</span><br>
</p><p><b>acejoe: </b><br>
<span>极乐迪斯科屌，但是凭什么？</span><br>
</p><p><b>小修: </b><br>
<span>我觉得这个排行榜挺靠谱的。</span><br>
<span>出了黑魂其他都没问题。感觉血源，黑魂3，只狼三选一</span><br>
</p><p><b>btts: </b><br>
<span>加上评语以后感觉还行，虽然迪斯科怎么看都太婆了</span><br>
</p><p><b>samaleg: </b><br>
<span>ebuw 发表于 2019-12-25 19:11</span><br>
<span>迪斯科没玩过。英雄联盟和堡垒之夜换成守望先锋和绝地求生，这个榜单就完美了。 ...</span><br>
<span>别，守望不配拿来换lol</span><br>
</p><p><b>ebuw: </b><br>
<span>samaleg 发表于 2019-12-25 21:39</span><br>
<span>别，守望不配拿来换lol</span><br>
<span>守望也是抄袭作。但好玩。</span><br>
<span>像lol和fortnite这样无聊的抄袭作不配上榜。</span><br>
<span>换成the last of us也行。</span><br>
</p><p><b>pgain2004: </b><br>
<span>ebuw 发表于 2019-12-25 21:55</span><br>
<span>守望也是抄袭作。但好玩。</span><br>
<span>像lol和fortnite这样无聊的抄袭作不配上榜。</span><br>
<span>换成the last of us也行。 ...</span><br>
<span>你要知道这是Times，好玩与否并非第一考量因素。</span><br>
<span>顺便好不好玩这种超级主观的东西……</span><br>
</p><p><b>hyde999: </b><br>
<span>无聊的抄袭作玩家数量倍杀好玩的抄袭作，是21世纪10年代玩家的错。</span><br>
</p><p><b>charseer: </b><br>
<span>没守望先锋好意思叫十佳？？</span><br>
</p><p><b>000000: </b><br>
<span>守望先锋的理由呢？</span><br>
</p><p><b>000000: </b><br>
<span>Developer Riot Games released League of Legends at the end of 2009, but the game that helped define the multiplayer online battle arena game genre wouldn’t become a global phenomenon for a few more years. Now, it’s the gold standard for esports. League of Legends tournaments pack stadiums across the world and draw more viewers than the Super Bowl. In the past 10 years, Riot Games typified another theme of gaming’s 2010s: sexism. Gaming spent decades perceived as a boy’s club, and that toxic culture permeated the top levels of gaming’s biggest companies, with Riot Games executives being credibly accused of abuse by former employees.</span><br>
</p><p><b>bairn: </b><br>
<span>000000 发表于 2019-12-25 22:50</span><br>
<span>Developer Riot Games released League of Legends at the end of 2009, but the game that helped define...</span><br>
<span>这都能提一句性别歧视我是没想到的</span><br>
</p><p><b>dumplingpro: </b><br>
<span>极乐迪斯科 虽然屌，但屌不到这种程度吧？ 评选的人都是CRPG婆罗门么？</span><br>
</p><p><b>000000: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 000000 于 2019-12-25 23:01 编辑 </span><br>
<span>bairn 发表于 2019-12-25 22:55</span><br>
<span>这都能提一句性别歧视我是没想到的</span><br>
<span>算是游戏圈平权事件最大的一桩了，超200女性员工罢工，集体诉讼</span><br>
<span>拳头态度也很积极，道歉，1000万赔偿，增加内部女性高管，算是解决地很迅速</span><br>
</p><p><b>终结之心: </b><br>
<span>拳头被搞怕了   </span><br>
<span>今年三个主题曲，男女比例2:6</span><br>
<span>男的还是两黑人说唱，亚洲也要兼顾</span><br>
<span>愣是一个白皮男性都没</span><br>
</p><p><b>urvark: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 urvark 于 2019-12-25 23:13 编辑 </span><br>
<span>这所谓的十佳，到底是哪方面佳？盈利？销量？口碑？影响力？好玩？</span><br>
<span>哪怕你说是影响力，所谓的话题作品，前面9个我也都认了，这极乐迪斯科如何跟其它的相提并论？（虽然确实做得不错）</span><br>
<span>说到底，游戏评选，我觉得也该跟摇滚名人堂一样，起码得是首个版本发售后五年或者十年的游戏，才能纳入评选范畴。能经历时间考验的作品，才是真的好游戏</span><br>
</p><p><b>000000: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 000000 于 2019-12-25 23:29 编辑 </span><br>
<span>终结之心 发表于 2019-12-25 23:10</span><br>
<span>拳头被搞怕了   </span><br>
<span>今年三个主题曲，男女比例2:6</span><br>
<span>男的还是两黑人说唱，亚洲也要兼顾</span><br>
<span>今年主题曲主要还是为了迎合美国主流音乐市场，黑人音乐太火了，我平时关注的几个和LOL没关联的黑人react up，比如常年专注进行白人摇滚再学习的Crown Family（https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCDdw6n7EOZp4HAZqc1wO6nw）都做了LOL主题曲，效果确实不错。</span><br>
<span>白皮现在连Ed Sheeran都跑去做嘻哈了，市场说话。拳头现在最大的问题其实是公布各种RPG新项目都是女性主管和用了很多女性员工，本来自己就经验不足，这次效率上可能更难了，搞不好看起来完全不靠谱的FPS都比几个RPG快，毕竟游戏兄弟会文化的又不是只有拳头自己一家，女性从业者仅占10%的业界这么积极的强行上，有点孤掌难鸣。</span><br>
</p><p><b>j5g27: </b><br>
<span>没啥问题，对我来说槽点比ign一类的媒体评的少太多。</span><br>
<span>不过迪斯科上榜到底是里面的各个派系政治思想的文本因素，还是包含各种交叉选项和roll败新场景的玩法因素那就不清楚了。反正已经开到第三个档玩新结局了，每天下班回来玩一会，快乐。</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1905473[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
