<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>彭博新闻-波音737max空难原因: 软件系统外包印度,含致命错误</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>彭博新闻-波音737max空难原因: 软件系统外包印度,含致命错误</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 19:22:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>彭博新闻-波音737max空难原因: 软件系统外包印度,含致命错误[50-100]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1843385-1-1.html</link>
      <description>彭博新闻-波音737max空难原因: 软件系统外包印度,含致命错误&#13;
 本帖最后由 李恭暔 于 2019-7-1 01:20 编辑 

先上摘要：（原文见后，最后面还有一篇早期的相关中文报道） 
&#13;
波音为了压缩成本，大规模解聘自家经验丰富的资深软件工程师，
&#13;
并将软件开发外包给印度HCL公司。
&#13;
解聘外包都是波音高层的印度裔大力促成, 
&#13;
他贱名Vishwa Uddanwadiker，历史罪人！
&#13;
近12年，他主导波音解聘超1200软件工程师，时任波音IT部门主管，
&#13;
尤其是在2010年一次解雇1000名软件工程师，业界震动。
&#13;
再后来这个印度死贱种官至波音副总裁，全力大规模外包印度。
&#13;
HCL向波音谎称：印叉工程师富有航空航天经验。
&#13;
事实上，HCL让刚出校门的毕业生开发飞行姿态控制软件，完全没有经验，
&#13;
并且没进行软件测试！！
&#13;
这故事\事故 给我们什么启示呢？那就是，
&#13;
波音787软件系统也是同一家公司HCL做的，
&#13;
且787和737max两个软件系统存在完全相同的组件。
&#13;
737max已经禁飞了，但787还在自由翱翔
&#13;
所以，订机票时，S1胖友们要正确选择机型
&#13;
最后补充，我认为原文观点有误，原作者天真地以为，
&#13;
9美元一小时薪水太低，只能聘用不合格的印叉软狗。
&#13;
可是他不知道，就算给到900美元一小时，甚至9000美元一小时，
&#13;
能够聘到的阿三还是素质极端低下。
&#13;
印叉全民贱叉，无药可救，所有人都他妈的一个烂德行。
&#13;
唯一解法就是核平印度本土，另外将在美全体死印叉抓来枪决。
&#13;
Boeing’s 737 Max Software Outsourced to $9-an-Hour Engineers
&#13;
By Peter Robison
&#13;
June 28, 2019, 9:46 PM GMT+1
&#13;
 Planemaker and suppliers used lower-paid temporary workers
&#13;
 Engineers feared the practice meant code wasn’t done right
&#13;
It remains the mystery at the heart of Boeing Co.’s 737 Max crisis: how a company renowned for meticulous design made seemingly basic software mistakes leading to a pair of deadly crashes. Longtime Boeing engineers say the effort was complicated by a push to outsource work to lower-paid contractors.
&#13;
The Max software -- plagued by issues that could keep the planes grounded months longer after U.S. regulators this week revealed a new flaw -- was developed at a time Boeing was laying off experienced engineers and pressing suppliers to cut costs.
&#13;
Increasingly, the iconic American planemaker and its subcontractors have relied on temporary workers making as little as $9 an hour to develop and test software, often from countries lacking a deep background in aerospace -- notably India.
&#13;
First Flight Of The Boeing Co. Max 737 Jet
&#13;
Boeing 737 Max prepares for take off during testing in 2016.Photographer: Mike Kane/Bloomberg
&#13;
Related: Pilots Flagged Software Problems on Boeing Jets Besides Max
&#13;
In offices across from Seattle’s Boeing Field, recent college graduates employed by the Indian software developer HCL Technologies Ltd. occupied several rows of desks, said Mark Rabin, a former Boeing software engineer who worked in a flight-test group that supported the Max.
&#13;
The coders from HCL were typically designing to specifications set by Boeing. Still, “it was controversial because it was far less efficient than Boeing engineers just writing the code,” Rabin said. Frequently, he recalled, “it took many rounds going back and forth because the code was not done correctly.”
&#13;
Boeing’s cultivation of Indian companies appeared to pay other dividends. In recent years, it has won several orders for Indian military and commercial aircraft, such as a $22 billion one in January 2017 to supply SpiceJet Ltd. That order included 100 737-Max 8 jets and represented Boeing’s largest order ever from an Indian airline, a coup in a country dominated by Airbus.
&#13;
Based on resumes posted on social media, HCL engineers helped develop and test the Max’s flight-display software, while employees from another Indian company, Cyient Ltd., handled software for flight-test equipment.
&#13;
Costly Delay
&#13;
In one post, an HCL employee summarized his duties with a reference to the now-infamous model, which started flight tests in January 2016: “Provided quick workaround to resolve production issue which resulted in not delaying flight test of 737-Max (delay in each flight test will cost very big amount for Boeing).”
&#13;
Boeing said the company did not rely on engineers from HCL and Cyient for the Maneuvering Characteristics Augmentation System, which has been linked to the Lion Air crash last October and the Ethiopian Airlines disaster in March. The Chicago-based planemaker also said it didn’t rely on either firm for another software issue disclosed after the crashes: a cockpit warning light that wasn’t working for most buyers.
&#13;
“Boeing has many decades of experience working with supplier/partners around the world,” a company spokesman said. “Our primary focus is on always ensuring that our products and services are safe, of the highest quality and comply with all applicable regulations.”
&#13;
In a statement, HCL said it “has a strong and long-standing business relationship with The Boeing Company, and we take pride in the work we do for all our customers. However, HCL does not comment on specific work we do for our customers. HCL is not associated with any ongoing issues with 737 Max.”
&#13;
Recent simulator tests by the Federal Aviation Administration suggest the software issues on Boeing’s best-selling model run deeper. The company’s shares fell this week after the regulator found a further problem with a computer chip that experienced a lag in emergency response when it was overwhelmed with data.
&#13;
Engineers who worked on the Max, which Boeing began developing eight years ago to match a rival Airbus SE plane, have complained of pressure from managers to limit changes that might introduce extra time or cost.
&#13;
“Boeing was doing all kinds of things, everything you can imagine, to reduce cost, including moving work from Puget Sound, because we’d become very expensive here,” said Rick Ludtke, a former Boeing flight controls engineer laid off in 2017. “All that’s very understandable if you think of it from a business perspective. Slowly over time it appears that’s eroded the ability for Puget Sound designers to design.”
&#13;
Rabin, the former software engineer, recalled one manager saying at an all-hands meeting that Boeing didn’t need senior engineers because its products were mature. “I was shocked that in a room full of a couple hundred mostly senior engineers we were being told that we weren’t needed,” said Rabin, who was laid off in 2015.
&#13;
Boeing 737 Max Timeline
&#13;
Boeing could take three more months to fix the latest software glitch on the 737 Max, its best-selling model.
&#13;
(Source: TicToc)
&#13;
The typical jetliner has millions of parts -- and millions of lines of code -- and Boeing has long turned over large portions of the work to suppliers who follow its detailed design blueprints.
&#13;
Starting with the 787 Dreamliner, launched in 2004, it sought to increase profits by instead providing high-level specifications and then asking suppliers to design more parts themselves. The thinking was “they’re the experts, you see, and they will take care of all of this stuff for us,” said Frank McCormick, a former Boeing flight-controls software engineer who later worked as a consultant to regulators and manufacturers. “This was just nonsense.”
&#13;
Sales are another reason to send the work overseas. In exchange for an $11 billion order in 2005 from Air India, Boeing promised to invest $1.7 billion in Indian companies. That was a boon for HCL and other software developers from India, such as Cyient, whose engineers were widely used in computer-services industries but not yet prominent in aerospace.
&#13;
Rockwell Collins, which makes cockpit electronics, had been among the first aerospace companies to source significant work in India in 2000, when HCL began testing software there for the Cedar Rapids, Iowa-based company. By 2010, HCL employed more than 400 people at design, development and verification centers for Rockwell Collins in Chennai and Bangalore.
&#13;
That same year, Boeing opened what it called a “center of excellence” with HCL in Chennai, saying the companies would partner “to create software critical for flight test.” In 2011, Boeing named Cyient, then known as Infotech, to a list of its “suppliers of the year” for design, stress analysis and software engineering on the 787 and the 747-8 at another center in Hyderabad.
&#13;
The Boeing rival also relies in part on offshore engineers. In addition to supporting sales, the planemakers say global design teams add efficiency as they work around the clock. But outsourcing has long been a sore point for some Boeing engineers, who, in addition to fearing job losses say it has led to communications issues and mistakes.
&#13;
Moscow Mistakes
&#13;
Boeing has also expanded a design center in Moscow. At a meeting with a chief 787 engineer in 2008, one staffer complained about sending drawings back to a team in Russia 18 times before they understood that the smoke detectors needed to be connected to the electrical system, said Cynthia Cole, a former Boeing engineer who headed the engineers’ union from 2006 to 2010.
&#13;
“Engineering started becoming a commodity,” said Vance Hilderman, who co-founded a company called TekSci that supplied aerospace contract engineers and began losing work to overseas competitors in the early 2000s.
&#13;
U.S.-based avionics companies in particular moved aggressively, shifting more than 30% of their software engineering offshore versus 10% for European-based firms in recent years, said Hilderman, an avionics safety consultant with three decades of experience whose recent clients include most of the major Boeing suppliers.
&#13;
With a strong dollar, a big part of the attraction was price. Engineers in India made around $5 an hour; it’s now $9 or $10, compared with $35 to $40 for those in the U.S. on an H1B visa, he said. But he’d tell clients the cheaper hourly wage equated to more like $80 because of the need for supervision, and he said his firm won back some business to fix mistakes.
&#13;
HCL, once known as Hindustan Computers, was founded in 1976 by billionaire Shiv Nadar and now has more than $8.6 billion in annual sales. With 18,000 employees in the U.S. and 15,000 in Europe, HCL is a global company and has deep expertise in computing, said Sukamal Banerjee, a vice president. It has won business from Boeing on that basis, not on price, he said: “We came from a strong R&amp;D background.”
&#13;
Still, for the 787, HCL gave Boeing a remarkable price – free, according to Sam Swaro, an associate vice president who pitched HCL’s services at a San Diego conference sponsored by Avionics International magazine in June. He said the company took no up-front payments on the 787 and only started collecting payments based on sales years later, an “innovative business model” he offered to extend to others in the industry.
&#13;
The 787 entered service three years late and billions of dollars over budget in 2011, in part because of confusion introduced by the outsourcing strategy. Under Dennis Muilenburg, a longtime Boeing engineer who became chief executive in 2015, the company has said that it planned to bring more work back in-house for its newest planes.
&#13;
Engineer Backwater
&#13;
The Max became Boeing’s top seller soon after it was offered in 2011. But for ambitious engineers, it was something of a “backwater,” said Peter Lemme, who designed the 767’s automated flight controls and is now a consultant. The Max was an update of a 50-year-old design, and the changes needed to be limited enough that Boeing could produce the new planes like cookie cutters, with few changes for either the assembly line or airlines. “As an engineer that’s not the greatest job,” he said.
&#13;
Rockwell Collins, now a unit of United Technologies Corp., won the Max contract for cockpit displays, and it has relied in part on HCL engineers in India, Iowa and the Seattle area. A United Technologies spokeswoman didn’t respond to a request for comment.
&#13;
Boeing 737 Max
&#13;
Boeing 737 Max airplanes at the company’s manufacturing facility in Renton, Washington.Photographer: David Ryder/Bloomberg
&#13;
Contract engineers from Cyient helped test flight test equipment. Charles LoveJoy, a former flight-test instrumentation design engineer at the company, said engineers in the U.S. would review drawings done overnight in India every morning at 7:30 a.m. “We did have our challenges with the India team,” he said. “They met the requirements, per se, but you could do it better.”
&#13;
Multiple investigations – including a Justice Department criminal probe – are trying to unravel how and when critical decisions were made about the Max’s software. During the crashes of Lion Air and Ethiopian Airlines planes that killed 346 people, investigators suspect, the MCAS system pushed the planes into uncontrollable dives because of bad data from a single sensor.
&#13;
That design violated basic principles of redundancy for generations of Boeing engineers, and the company apparently never tested to see how the software would respond, Lemme said. “It was a stunning fail,” he said. “A lot of people should have thought of this problem – not one person – and asked about it.”
&#13;
Boeing also has disclosed that it learned soon after Max deliveries began in 2017 that a warning light that might have alerted crews to the issue with the sensor wasn’t installed correctly in the flight-display software. A Boeing statement in May, explaining why the company didn’t inform regulators at the time, said engineers had determined it wasn’t a safety issue.
&#13;
“Senior company leadership,” the statement added, “was not involved in the review.”
&#13;
后面附上一个旧闻
&#13;
波音737 MAX半年两次坠毁，787飞控软件竟由这家印度公司编写 2019-03-11 18:29
&#13;
最近四个多月内，波音737 MAX 8客机连续发生两起严重的坠机惨剧，造成345人遇难，这在人类航空史上都非常罕见。关于事故原因，目前尚无官方确认的说法，但是外界猜测是由于飞机上的传感器给出了错误的攻角数据，自动控制飞机低头俯冲。这本是一个可以修正的错误，然而不知道什么原因，波音公司竟然设定机器比飞行员拥有等级更高的操控优先权，最终导致惨剧两次发生。http://5b0988e595225.cdn.sohucs.com/images/20190311/4a2a27a30e6c445fbcefcaa1b31f97a6.jpeg埃航的波音737 MAX8客机实际上，这并不是波音飞机现在才出现类似的问题。早在2013年10月10日，日本航空公司国际航线三架波音787梦想客机就先后因故障而中途折返，其中一架事后明确查出是电气事故。不仅如此，在2012年一年时间内，波音787客机出现了四次电气系统故障。而据福克斯2012年12月初的一篇文章报道，波音787客机电气系统的软件，恰恰是由印度HCL公司外包的。http://5b0988e595225.cdn.sohucs.com/images/20190311/62c61e9d21c0445b94ada6cc56effb51.jpeg波音787梦想变成了梦碎HCL公司，原名印度斯坦电脑公司，它是印度一家全球性IT服务公司，总部设在诺伊达。该公司提供多种服务，包括软件咨询，企业转型，远程基础设施管理，工程和研发服务以及业务流程外包。HCL已经在31个国家设有办公室，向各行各业提供服务，在2015年2月15日，其市值为224.8亿美元，成为印度上市公司前20强。http://5b0988e595225.cdn.sohucs.com/images/20190311/f5c3d019e5394208b1c0287b39d74af3.jpeg印度HCL公司是波音787客机的软件外包商福克斯的文章中提到，记者通过内线获知，HCL通过哈密尔顿转包，与波音合作开发787梦想客机，2009年2月还获得了波音金质杰出奖。另外，波音787梦想客机的ES工程样板软件也是由印度HCL公司编写的，美国联邦航空管理局已经下令禁止使用该软件。http://5b0988e595225.cdn.sohucs.com/images/20190311/bf627751724d431fbd040b008ca8705a.jpeg福克斯的文章原文不仅如此，波音787梦想客机，从具体组件生产到最关键的整机飞机控制软件，印度公司都得到了很重要的合同。而且据波音高级管理人员Dinesh Keskar在2018年表示，“波音787大型飞机很有可能在印度制造，但需要很长时间，因为对资金、技术和基础设施的要求很高。”http://5b0988e595225.cdn.sohucs.com/images/20190311/d1f7cb7e81dd46709b34317597197ca5.jpeg印度近年来在航空领域野心很大虽然没有证据表明此次发生事故的波音737 MAX 8客机的飞控软件也与HCL或者其他印度公司有关，但是发生在787梦想客机身上的事，也许能够提供给我们追本溯源的一个新思路。</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>莉蒂亚丝: </b><br>
<span>三哥大量移民美帝，从内部搞烂美帝，该颁发全体在美三哥一吨重的大勋章</span><br>
</p><p><b>法皇干政: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 法皇干政 于 2019-7-1 08:52 编辑 </span><br>
<span>按小动物观察者网的张仲璘的说法，现在FAA为了避免自己政治性死亡已经从力挺波音转为弃车保帅了，这次新捅出来一个新的737MAX漏洞就是由“不愿意具名的有关人士”说出来的，用脚指头想都知道消息源是谁。</span><br>
</p><p><b>杨松: </b><br>
<span>那么谁会是当代拉玛努金呢</span><br>
</p><p><b>refo2613: </b><br>
<span>把锅往软件上推，所以修补一下就可以用了么？</span><br>
<span>原来说的，静不平衡是主因呢？</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 vivo NEX A, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>上将郝萌: </b><br>
<span>出现了，国际范儿的甩锅临时工</span><br>
</p><p><b>mengsu: </b><br>
<span>法皇干政 发表于 2019-7-1 08:50</span><br>
<span>按小动物观察者网的张仲璘的说法，现在FAA为了避免自己政治性死亡已经从力挺波音转为弃车保帅了，这次新捅 ...</span><br>
<span>波音和FAA谁是车谁是帅还不好说的呀</span><br>
</p><p><b>爱与和平的道化者: </b><br>
<span>想起那一年，我们船在印度，公司给安排了罗经工程师，给陀螺罗经做保养。</span><br>
<span>我好好的陀螺罗经，三哥拆了之后我从他的表情上，感觉是装不起来了。把我耗到凌晨4点多还下不了班。然后这逼一脸不自然的表情，跟我说好了。我用天狼星一测，误差超过20°</span><br>
<span>我草泥马啊！我好好的陀螺罗经啊！20°啊！</span><br>
</p><p><b>干将莫邪: </b><br>
<span>虽然外包印度是有时不靠谱，但是主因是硬件缺陷吧，锅也分大小的</span><br>
</p><p><b>自業自得: </b><br>
<span>typeunknown 发表于 2019-6-30 20:57</span><br>
<span>这1200人都去哪了</span><br>
<span>是时候出一批由被解雇而心怀愤恨的it做反派的好莱坞大片了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>不入流美术: </b><br>
<span>看样子只能坐能安全送你上天也能安全送你落地的春秋航空了，毕竟清一色A320</span><br>
</p><p><b>Rufus.X: </b><br>
<span>外包出问题，说明交付时的验收没做好，责任还是在波音本身</span><br>
<span>软件这东西和持续采购的原材料不一样，总不会是刚验收的时候是好的，后来供应的都是次品吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>aji47: </b><br>
<span>嘿嘿，阿三那边bug修不出来。居然还好意思电话会议过来问我们上海site，脸皮要多厚有多厚。和他们项目完全无关的team。</span><br>
<span>帮了一次，还要第二次。我们没义务帮你，自己google不会？</span><br>
</p><p><b>nice女武神: </b><br>
<span>波音这锅甩的就算是火星小绿人编的程序波音你不进行检查和校验？拜托这可是上百人的交通工具</span><br>
</p><p><b>nice女武神: </b><br>
<span>法皇干政 发表于 2019-7-1 08:50</span><br>
<span>按小动物观察者网的张仲璘的说法，现在FAA为了避免自己政治性死亡已经从力挺波音转为弃车保帅了，这次新捅 ...</span><br>
<span>faa自己就是波音的卒子</span><br>
</p><p><b>lysh_233: </b><br>
<span>tonyshijie 发表于 2019-6-30 21:17</span><br>
<span>我觉得还是管理责任居多</span><br>
<span>管理也是阿三怎么办？</span><br>
</p><p><b>lifesking: </b><br>
<span>这是临时工，不对，是印度人的锅。我们白白才不会做这种事呢！</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能手机投票的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>十六夜pad长: </b><br>
<span>lifesking 发表于 2019-7-1 17:39</span><br>
<span>这是临时工，不对，是印度人的锅。我们白白才不会做这种事呢！</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能手机投票的 Stage1官方 ...</span><br>
<span>但决定裁工程师的人也是三哥，验收的最终负责人不出意外应该是it部的头头，也还是他……</span><br>
<span>这锅只能往任命三哥的总裁头上扣了……</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 OPPO PCCM00, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>箭猪: </b><br>
<span>如果没有测试，都能让这些飞机飞成这样</span><br>
<span>阿三的软件编程能力确实太牛逼了…人家说印度软件冠绝全球，实在不是贬义，真是褒义——不服的可以随便找个程序问问，真不开玩笑</span><br>
</p><p><b>碎片整理: </b><br>
<span>nicebody 发表于 2019-6-30 20:40</span><br>
<span>楼主是被三哥强奸了妹妹？这么深仇大恨的</span><br>
<span>虽然楼主过于激动，但所有被win10喂过屎的应该都有过类似的情绪吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>bluescope: </b><br>
<span>powwow 发表于 2019-6-30 20:37</span><br>
<span>锅全甩外包头上，波音其他人都是吃干饭的吗？聘用不合格的外包并且没有检查测试，正规标准的开发流程不走， ...</span><br>
<span>就是甩鍋。飛控不上模擬器嗎？説到底是波音利欲熏心。而且從去年本該發佈的升級一拖再拖看，他們連亡羊補牢的積極性都沒有，就是想靠店大欺客。</span><br>
</p><p><b>caliburn: </b><br>
<span>当时科普过很多次了，机型有问题。波音这锅甩得难看</span><br>
</p><p><b>nicebody: </b><br>
<span>碎片整理 发表于 2019-7-1 18:14</span><br>
<span>虽然楼主过于激动，但所有被win10喂过屎的应该都有过类似的情绪吧</span><br>
<span>有点脑子都知道，甩锅给外包和临时工背锅是一个水准的。</span><br>
<span>楼主还当发现新大陆一样使劲黑。</span><br>
<span>只能理解是有不共戴天之仇了</span><br>
</p><p><b>3Psm: </b><br>
<span>春哥亲自 发表于 2019-6-30 20:43</span><br>
<span>已知HAL击落军机</span><br>
<span>HCL击落客机</span><br>
<span>你要不要去看看印度的科研？</span><br>
<span>军民都已经有了，就剩下科研了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>セト: </b><br>
<span>多傻逼会信没进行测试这种话。</span><br>
<span>真要这样那你阿三才是神仙</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>松川奈々: </b><br>
<span>锅还是波音自己的。另外微软的阿三ceo我还是非常佩服的。</span><br>
</p><p><b>荡寇将军张嶷: </b><br>
<span>安全系统都当独立DLC卖了，特意甩给一个族裔真特么搞笑。。。</span><br>
</p><p><b>Endle: </b><br>
<span>nice女武神 发表于 2019-7-1 15:32</span><br>
<span>波音这锅甩的就算是火星小绿人编的程序波音你不进行检查和校验？拜托这可是上百人的交通工具 ...</span><br>
<span>说的对，外包给谁不重要，关键是质量控制和最终的验收是怎么做的</span><br>
<span>这口大锅波音肯定是甩不掉</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1843385[50-100]</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>彭博新闻-波音737max空难原因: 软件系统外包印度,含致命错误[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1843385-1-1.html</link>
      <description>彭博新闻-波音737max空难原因: 软件系统外包印度,含致命错误&#13;
 本帖最后由 李恭暔 于 2019-7-1 01:20 编辑 

先上摘要：（原文见后，最后面还有一篇早期的相关中文报道） 
&#13;
波音为了压缩成本，大规模解聘自家经验丰富的资深软件工程师，
&#13;
并将软件开发外包给印度HCL公司。
&#13;
解聘外包都是波音高层的印度裔大力促成, 
&#13;
他贱名Vishwa Uddanwadiker，历史罪人！
&#13;
近12年，他主导波音解聘超1200软件工程师，时任波音IT部门主管，
&#13;
尤其是在2010年一次解雇1000名软件工程师，业界震动。
&#13;
再后来这个印度死贱种官至波音副总裁，全力大规模外包印度。
&#13;
HCL向波音谎称：印叉工程师富有航空航天经验。
&#13;
事实上，HCL让刚出校门的毕业生开发飞行姿态控制软件，完全没有经验，
&#13;
并且没进行软件测试！！
&#13;
这故事\事故 给我们什么启示呢？那就是，
&#13;
波音787软件系统也是同一家公司HCL做的，
&#13;
且787和737max两个软件系统存在完全相同的组件。
&#13;
737max已经禁飞了，但787还在自由翱翔
&#13;
所以，订机票时，S1胖友们要正确选择机型
&#13;
最后补充，我认为原文观点有误，原作者天真地以为，
&#13;
9美元一小时薪水太低，只能聘用不合格的印叉软狗。
&#13;
可是他不知道，就算给到900美元一小时，甚至9000美元一小时，
&#13;
能够聘到的阿三还是素质极端低下。
&#13;
印叉全民贱叉，无药可救，所有人都他妈的一个烂德行。
&#13;
唯一解法就是核平印度本土，另外将在美全体死印叉抓来枪决。
&#13;
Boeing’s 737 Max Software Outsourced to $9-an-Hour Engineers
&#13;
By Peter Robison
&#13;
June 28, 2019, 9:46 PM GMT+1
&#13;
 Planemaker and suppliers used lower-paid temporary workers
&#13;
 Engineers feared the practice meant code wasn’t done right
&#13;
It remains the mystery at the heart of Boeing Co.’s 737 Max crisis: how a company renowned for meticulous design made seemingly basic software mistakes leading to a pair of deadly crashes. Longtime Boeing engineers say the effort was complicated by a push to outsource work to lower-paid contractors.
&#13;
The Max software -- plagued by issues that could keep the planes grounded months longer after U.S. regulators this week revealed a new flaw -- was developed at a time Boeing was laying off experienced engineers and pressing suppliers to cut costs.
&#13;
Increasingly, the iconic American planemaker and its subcontractors have relied on temporary workers making as little as $9 an hour to develop and test software, often from countries lacking a deep background in aerospace -- notably India.
&#13;
First Flight Of The Boeing Co. Max 737 Jet
&#13;
Boeing 737 Max prepares for take off during testing in 2016.Photographer: Mike Kane/Bloomberg
&#13;
Related: Pilots Flagged Software Problems on Boeing Jets Besides Max
&#13;
In offices across from Seattle’s Boeing Field, recent college graduates employed by the Indian software developer HCL Technologies Ltd. occupied several rows of desks, said Mark Rabin, a former Boeing software engineer who worked in a flight-test group that supported the Max.
&#13;
The coders from HCL were typically designing to specifications set by Boeing. Still, “it was controversial because it was far less efficient than Boeing engineers just writing the code,” Rabin said. Frequently, he recalled, “it took many rounds going back and forth because the code was not done correctly.”
&#13;
Boeing’s cultivation of Indian companies appeared to pay other dividends. In recent years, it has won several orders for Indian military and commercial aircraft, such as a $22 billion one in January 2017 to supply SpiceJet Ltd. That order included 100 737-Max 8 jets and represented Boeing’s largest order ever from an Indian airline, a coup in a country dominated by Airbus.
&#13;
Based on resumes posted on social media, HCL engineers helped develop and test the Max’s flight-display software, while employees from another Indian company, Cyient Ltd., handled software for flight-test equipment.
&#13;
Costly Delay
&#13;
In one post, an HCL employee summarized his duties with a reference to the now-infamous model, which started flight tests in January 2016: “Provided quick workaround to resolve production issue which resulted in not delaying flight test of 737-Max (delay in each flight test will cost very big amount for Boeing).”
&#13;
Boeing said the company did not rely on engineers from HCL and Cyient for the Maneuvering Characteristics Augmentation System, which has been linked to the Lion Air crash last October and the Ethiopian Airlines disaster in March. The Chicago-based planemaker also said it didn’t rely on either firm for another software issue disclosed after the crashes: a cockpit warning light that wasn’t working for most buyers.
&#13;
“Boeing has many decades of experience working with supplier/partners around the world,” a company spokesman said. “Our primary focus is on always ensuring that our products and services are safe, of the highest quality and comply with all applicable regulations.”
&#13;
In a statement, HCL said it “has a strong and long-standing business relationship with The Boeing Company, and we take pride in the work we do for all our customers. However, HCL does not comment on specific work we do for our customers. HCL is not associated with any ongoing issues with 737 Max.”
&#13;
Recent simulator tests by the Federal Aviation Administration suggest the software issues on Boeing’s best-selling model run deeper. The company’s shares fell this week after the regulator found a further problem with a computer chip that experienced a lag in emergency response when it was overwhelmed with data.
&#13;
Engineers who worked on the Max, which Boeing began developing eight years ago to match a rival Airbus SE plane, have complained of pressure from managers to limit changes that might introduce extra time or cost.
&#13;
“Boeing was doing all kinds of things, everything you can imagine, to reduce cost, including moving work from Puget Sound, because we’d become very expensive here,” said Rick Ludtke, a former Boeing flight controls engineer laid off in 2017. “All that’s very understandable if you think of it from a business perspective. Slowly over time it appears that’s eroded the ability for Puget Sound designers to design.”
&#13;
Rabin, the former software engineer, recalled one manager saying at an all-hands meeting that Boeing didn’t need senior engineers because its products were mature. “I was shocked that in a room full of a couple hundred mostly senior engineers we were being told that we weren’t needed,” said Rabin, who was laid off in 2015.
&#13;
Boeing 737 Max Timeline
&#13;
Boeing could take three more months to fix the latest software glitch on the 737 Max, its best-selling model.
&#13;
(Source: TicToc)
&#13;
The typical jetliner has millions of parts -- and millions of lines of code -- and Boeing has long turned over large portions of the work to suppliers who follow its detailed design blueprints.
&#13;
Starting with the 787 Dreamliner, launched in 2004, it sought to increase profits by instead providing high-level specifications and then asking suppliers to design more parts themselves. The thinking was “they’re the experts, you see, and they will take care of all of this stuff for us,” said Frank McCormick, a former Boeing flight-controls software engineer who later worked as a consultant to regulators and manufacturers. “This was just nonsense.”
&#13;
Sales are another reason to send the work overseas. In exchange for an $11 billion order in 2005 from Air India, Boeing promised to invest $1.7 billion in Indian companies. That was a boon for HCL and other software developers from India, such as Cyient, whose engineers were widely used in computer-services industries but not yet prominent in aerospace.
&#13;
Rockwell Collins, which makes cockpit electronics, had been among the first aerospace companies to source significant work in India in 2000, when HCL began testing software there for the Cedar Rapids, Iowa-based company. By 2010, HCL employed more than 400 people at design, development and verification centers for Rockwell Collins in Chennai and Bangalore.
&#13;
That same year, Boeing opened what it called a “center of excellence” with HCL in Chennai, saying the companies would partner “to create software critical for flight test.” In 2011, Boeing named Cyient, then known as Infotech, to a list of its “suppliers of the year” for design, stress analysis and software engineering on the 787 and the 747-8 at another center in Hyderabad.
&#13;
The Boeing rival also relies in part on offshore engineers. In addition to supporting sales, the planemakers say global design teams add efficiency as they work around the clock. But outsourcing has long been a sore point for some Boeing engineers, who, in addition to fearing job losses say it has led to communications issues and mistakes.
&#13;
Moscow Mistakes
&#13;
Boeing has also expanded a design center in Moscow. At a meeting with a chief 787 engineer in 2008, one staffer complained about sending drawings back to a team in Russia 18 times before they understood that the smoke detectors needed to be connected to the electrical system, said Cynthia Cole, a former Boeing engineer who headed the engineers’ union from 2006 to 2010.
&#13;
“Engineering started becoming a commodity,” said Vance Hilderman, who co-founded a company called TekSci that supplied aerospace contract engineers and began losing work to overseas competitors in the early 2000s.
&#13;
U.S.-based avionics companies in particular moved aggressively, shifting more than 30% of their software engineering offshore versus 10% for European-based firms in recent years, said Hilderman, an avionics safety consultant with three decades of experience whose recent clients include most of the major Boeing suppliers.
&#13;
With a strong dollar, a big part of the attraction was price. Engineers in India made around $5 an hour; it’s now $9 or $10, compared with $35 to $40 for those in the U.S. on an H1B visa, he said. But he’d tell clients the cheaper hourly wage equated to more like $80 because of the need for supervision, and he said his firm won back some business to fix mistakes.
&#13;
HCL, once known as Hindustan Computers, was founded in 1976 by billionaire Shiv Nadar and now has more than $8.6 billion in annual sales. With 18,000 employees in the U.S. and 15,000 in Europe, HCL is a global company and has deep expertise in computing, said Sukamal Banerjee, a vice president. It has won business from Boeing on that basis, not on price, he said: “We came from a strong R&amp;D background.”
&#13;
Still, for the 787, HCL gave Boeing a remarkable price – free, according to Sam Swaro, an associate vice president who pitched HCL’s services at a San Diego conference sponsored by Avionics International magazine in June. He said the company took no up-front payments on the 787 and only started collecting payments based on sales years later, an “innovative business model” he offered to extend to others in the industry.
&#13;
The 787 entered service three years late and billions of dollars over budget in 2011, in part because of confusion introduced by the outsourcing strategy. Under Dennis Muilenburg, a longtime Boeing engineer who became chief executive in 2015, the company has said that it planned to bring more work back in-house for its newest planes.
&#13;
Engineer Backwater
&#13;
The Max became Boeing’s top seller soon after it was offered in 2011. But for ambitious engineers, it was something of a “backwater,” said Peter Lemme, who designed the 767’s automated flight controls and is now a consultant. The Max was an update of a 50-year-old design, and the changes needed to be limited enough that Boeing could produce the new planes like cookie cutters, with few changes for either the assembly line or airlines. “As an engineer that’s not the greatest job,” he said.
&#13;
Rockwell Collins, now a unit of United Technologies Corp., won the Max contract for cockpit displays, and it has relied in part on HCL engineers in India, Iowa and the Seattle area. A United Technologies spokeswoman didn’t respond to a request for comment.
&#13;
Boeing 737 Max
&#13;
Boeing 737 Max airplanes at the company’s manufacturing facility in Renton, Washington.Photographer: David Ryder/Bloomberg
&#13;
Contract engineers from Cyient helped test flight test equipment. Charles LoveJoy, a former flight-test instrumentation design engineer at the company, said engineers in the U.S. would review drawings done overnight in India every morning at 7:30 a.m. “We did have our challenges with the India team,” he said. “They met the requirements, per se, but you could do it better.”
&#13;
Multiple investigations – including a Justice Department criminal probe – are trying to unravel how and when critical decisions were made about the Max’s software. During the crashes of Lion Air and Ethiopian Airlines planes that killed 346 people, investigators suspect, the MCAS system pushed the planes into uncontrollable dives because of bad data from a single sensor.
&#13;
That design violated basic principles of redundancy for generations of Boeing engineers, and the company apparently never tested to see how the software would respond, Lemme said. “It was a stunning fail,” he said. “A lot of people should have thought of this problem – not one person – and asked about it.”
&#13;
Boeing also has disclosed that it learned soon after Max deliveries began in 2017 that a warning light that might have alerted crews to the issue with the sensor wasn’t installed correctly in the flight-display software. A Boeing statement in May, explaining why the company didn’t inform regulators at the time, said engineers had determined it wasn’t a safety issue.
&#13;
“Senior company leadership,” the statement added, “was not involved in the review.”
&#13;
后面附上一个旧闻
&#13;
波音737 MAX半年两次坠毁，787飞控软件竟由这家印度公司编写 2019-03-11 18:29
&#13;
最近四个多月内，波音737 MAX 8客机连续发生两起严重的坠机惨剧，造成345人遇难，这在人类航空史上都非常罕见。关于事故原因，目前尚无官方确认的说法，但是外界猜测是由于飞机上的传感器给出了错误的攻角数据，自动控制飞机低头俯冲。这本是一个可以修正的错误，然而不知道什么原因，波音公司竟然设定机器比飞行员拥有等级更高的操控优先权，最终导致惨剧两次发生。http://5b0988e595225.cdn.sohucs.com/images/20190311/4a2a27a30e6c445fbcefcaa1b31f97a6.jpeg埃航的波音737 MAX8客机实际上，这并不是波音飞机现在才出现类似的问题。早在2013年10月10日，日本航空公司国际航线三架波音787梦想客机就先后因故障而中途折返，其中一架事后明确查出是电气事故。不仅如此，在2012年一年时间内，波音787客机出现了四次电气系统故障。而据福克斯2012年12月初的一篇文章报道，波音787客机电气系统的软件，恰恰是由印度HCL公司外包的。http://5b0988e595225.cdn.sohucs.com/images/20190311/62c61e9d21c0445b94ada6cc56effb51.jpeg波音787梦想变成了梦碎HCL公司，原名印度斯坦电脑公司，它是印度一家全球性IT服务公司，总部设在诺伊达。该公司提供多种服务，包括软件咨询，企业转型，远程基础设施管理，工程和研发服务以及业务流程外包。HCL已经在31个国家设有办公室，向各行各业提供服务，在2015年2月15日，其市值为224.8亿美元，成为印度上市公司前20强。http://5b0988e595225.cdn.sohucs.com/images/20190311/f5c3d019e5394208b1c0287b39d74af3.jpeg印度HCL公司是波音787客机的软件外包商福克斯的文章中提到，记者通过内线获知，HCL通过哈密尔顿转包，与波音合作开发787梦想客机，2009年2月还获得了波音金质杰出奖。另外，波音787梦想客机的ES工程样板软件也是由印度HCL公司编写的，美国联邦航空管理局已经下令禁止使用该软件。http://5b0988e595225.cdn.sohucs.com/images/20190311/bf627751724d431fbd040b008ca8705a.jpeg福克斯的文章原文不仅如此，波音787梦想客机，从具体组件生产到最关键的整机飞机控制软件，印度公司都得到了很重要的合同。而且据波音高级管理人员Dinesh Keskar在2018年表示，“波音787大型飞机很有可能在印度制造，但需要很长时间，因为对资金、技术和基础设施的要求很高。”http://5b0988e595225.cdn.sohucs.com/images/20190311/d1f7cb7e81dd46709b34317597197ca5.jpeg印度近年来在航空领域野心很大虽然没有证据表明此次发生事故的波音737 MAX 8客机的飞控软件也与HCL或者其他印度公司有关，但是发生在787梦想客机身上的事，也许能够提供给我们追本溯源的一个新思路。</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>李恭暔: </b><br>
<span>彭博新闻-波音737max空难原因: 软件系统外包印度,含致命错误</span><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 李恭暔 于 2019-7-1 01:20 编辑 </span><br>
<span>先上摘要：（原文见后，最后面还有一篇早期的相关中文报道） </span><br>
<span>波音为了压缩成本，大规模解聘自家经验丰富的资深软件工程师，</span><br>
<span>并将软件开发外包给印度HCL公司。</span><br>
<span>解聘外包都是波音高层的印度裔大力促成, </span><br>
<span>他贱名Vishwa Uddanwadiker，历史罪人！</span><br>
<span>近12年，他主导波音解聘超1200软件工程师，时任波音IT部门主管，</span><br>
<span>尤其是在2010年一次解雇1000名软件工程师，业界震动。</span><br>
<span>再后来这个印度死贱种官至波音副总裁，全力大规模外包印度。</span><br>
<span>HCL向波音谎称：印叉工程师富有航空航天经验。</span><br>
<span>事实上，HCL让刚出校门的毕业生开发飞行姿态控制软件，完全没有经验，</span><br>
<span>并且没进行软件测试！！</span><br>
<span>这故事\事故 给我们什么启示呢？那就是，</span><br>
<span>波音787软件系统也是同一家公司HCL做的，</span><br>
<span>且787和737max两个软件系统存在完全相同的组件。</span><br>
<span>737max已经禁飞了，但787还在自由翱翔</span><br>
<span>所以，订机票时，S1胖友们要正确选择机型</span><br>
<span>最后补充，我认为原文观点有误，原作者天真地以为，</span><br>
<span>9美元一小时薪水太低，只能聘用不合格的印叉软狗。</span><br>
<span>可是他不知道，就算给到900美元一小时，甚至9000美元一小时，</span><br>
<span>能够聘到的阿三还是素质极端低下。</span><br>
<span>印叉全民贱叉，无药可救，所有人都他妈的一个烂德行。</span><br>
<span>唯一解法就是核平印度本土，另外将在美全体死印叉抓来枪决。</span><br>
<span>Boeing’s 737 Max Software Outsourced to $9-an-Hour Engineers</span><br>
<span>By Peter Robison</span><br>
<span>June 28, 2019, 9:46 PM GMT+1</span><br>
<span> Planemaker and suppliers used lower-paid temporary workers</span><br>
<span> Engineers feared the practice meant code wasn’t done right</span><br>
<span>It remains the mystery at the heart of Boeing Co.’s 737 Max crisis: how a company renowned for meticulous design made seemingly basic software mistakes leading to a pair of deadly crashes. Longtime Boeing engineers say the effort was complicated by a push to outsource work to lower-paid contractors.</span><br>
<span>The Max software -- plagued by issues that could keep the planes grounded months longer after U.S. regulators this week revealed a new flaw -- was developed at a time Boeing was laying off experienced engineers and pressing suppliers to cut costs.</span><br>
<span>Increasingly, the iconic American planemaker and its subcontractors have relied on temporary workers making as little as $9 an hour to develop and test software, often from countries lacking a deep background in aerospace -- notably India.</span><br>
<span>First Flight Of The Boeing Co. Max 737 Jet</span><br>
<span>Boeing 737 Max prepares for take off during testing in 2016.Photographer: Mike Kane/Bloomberg</span><br>
<span>Related: Pilots Flagged Software Problems on Boeing Jets Besides Max</span><br>
<span>In offices across from Seattle’s Boeing Field, recent college graduates employed by the Indian software developer HCL Technologies Ltd. occupied several rows of desks, said Mark Rabin, a former Boeing software engineer who worked in a flight-test group that supported the Max.</span><br>
<span>The coders from HCL were typically designing to specifications set by Boeing. Still, “it was controversial because it was far less efficient than Boeing engineers just writing the code,” Rabin said. Frequently, he recalled, “it took many rounds going back and forth because the code was not done correctly.”</span><br>
<span>Boeing’s cultivation of Indian companies appeared to pay other dividends. In recent years, it has won several orders for Indian military and commercial aircraft, such as a $22 billion one in January 2017 to supply SpiceJet Ltd. That order included 100 737-Max 8 jets and represented Boeing’s largest order ever from an Indian airline, a coup in a country dominated by Airbus.</span><br>
<span>Based on resumes posted on social media, HCL engineers helped develop and test the Max’s flight-display software, while employees from another Indian company, Cyient Ltd., handled software for flight-test equipment.</span><br>
<span>Costly Delay</span><br>
<span>In one post, an HCL employee summarized his duties with a reference to the now-infamous model, which started flight tests in January 2016: “Provided quick workaround to resolve production issue which resulted in not delaying flight test of 737-Max (delay in each flight test will cost very big amount for Boeing).”</span><br>
<span>Boeing said the company did not rely on engineers from HCL and Cyient for the Maneuvering Characteristics Augmentation System, which has been linked to the Lion Air crash last October and the Ethiopian Airlines disaster in March. The Chicago-based planemaker also said it didn’t rely on either firm for another software issue disclosed after the crashes: a cockpit warning light that wasn’t working for most buyers.</span><br>
<span>“Boeing has many decades of experience working with supplier/partners around the world,” a company spokesman said. “Our primary focus is on always ensuring that our products and services are safe, of the highest quality and comply with all applicable regulations.”</span><br>
<span>In a statement, HCL said it “has a strong and long-standing business relationship with The Boeing Company, and we take pride in the work we do for all our customers. However, HCL does not comment on specific work we do for our customers. HCL is not associated with any ongoing issues with 737 Max.”</span><br>
<span>Recent simulator tests by the Federal Aviation Administration suggest the software issues on Boeing’s best-selling model run deeper. The company’s shares fell this week after the regulator found a further problem with a computer chip that experienced a lag in emergency response when it was overwhelmed with data.</span><br>
<span>Engineers who worked on the Max, which Boeing began developing eight years ago to match a rival Airbus SE plane, have complained of pressure from managers to limit changes that might introduce extra time or cost.</span><br>
<span>“Boeing was doing all kinds of things, everything you can imagine, to reduce cost, including moving work from Puget Sound, because we’d become very expensive here,” said Rick Ludtke, a former Boeing flight controls engineer laid off in 2017. “All that’s very understandable if you think of it from a business perspective. Slowly over time it appears that’s eroded the ability for Puget Sound designers to design.”</span><br>
<span>Rabin, the former software engineer, recalled one manager saying at an all-hands meeting that Boeing didn’t need senior engineers because its products were mature. “I was shocked that in a room full of a couple hundred mostly senior engineers we were being told that we weren’t needed,” said Rabin, who was laid off in 2015.</span><br>
<span>Boeing 737 Max Timeline</span><br>
<span>Boeing could take three more months to fix the latest software glitch on the 737 Max, its best-selling model.</span><br>
<span>(Source: TicToc)</span><br>
<span>The typical jetliner has millions of parts -- and millions of lines of code -- and Boeing has long turned over large portions of the work to suppliers who follow its detailed design blueprints.</span><br>
<span>Starting with the 787 Dreamliner, launched in 2004, it sought to increase profits by instead providing high-level specifications and then asking suppliers to design more parts themselves. The thinking was “they’re the experts, you see, and they will take care of all of this stuff for us,” said Frank McCormick, a former Boeing flight-controls software engineer who later worked as a consultant to regulators and manufacturers. “This was just nonsense.”</span><br>
<span>Sales are another reason to send the work overseas. In exchange for an $11 billion order in 2005 from Air India, Boeing promised to invest $1.7 billion in Indian companies. That was a boon for HCL and other software developers from India, such as Cyient, whose engineers were widely used in computer-services industries but not yet prominent in aerospace.</span><br>
<span>Rockwell Collins, which makes cockpit electronics, had been among the first aerospace companies to source significant work in India in 2000, when HCL began testing software there for the Cedar Rapids, Iowa-based company. By 2010, HCL employed more than 400 people at design, development and verification centers for Rockwell Collins in Chennai and Bangalore.</span><br>
<span>That same year, Boeing opened what it called a “center of excellence” with HCL in Chennai, saying the companies would partner “to create software critical for flight test.” In 2011, Boeing named Cyient, then known as Infotech, to a list of its “suppliers of the year” for design, stress analysis and software engineering on the 787 and the 747-8 at another center in Hyderabad.</span><br>
<span>The Boeing rival also relies in part on offshore engineers. In addition to supporting sales, the planemakers say global design teams add efficiency as they work around the clock. But outsourcing has long been a sore point for some Boeing engineers, who, in addition to fearing job losses say it has led to communications issues and mistakes.</span><br>
<span>Moscow Mistakes</span><br>
<span>Boeing has also expanded a design center in Moscow. At a meeting with a chief 787 engineer in 2008, one staffer complained about sending drawings back to a team in Russia 18 times before they understood that the smoke detectors needed to be connected to the electrical system, said Cynthia Cole, a former Boeing engineer who headed the engineers’ union from 2006 to 2010.</span><br>
<span>“Engineering started becoming a commodity,” said Vance Hilderman, who co-founded a company called TekSci that supplied aerospace contract engineers and began losing work to overseas competitors in the early 2000s.</span><br>
<span>U.S.-based avionics companies in particular moved aggressively, shifting more than 30% of their software engineering offshore versus 10% for European-based firms in recent years, said Hilderman, an avionics safety consultant with three decades of experience whose recent clients include most of the major Boeing suppliers.</span><br>
<span>With a strong dollar, a big part of the attraction was price. Engineers in India made around $5 an hour; it’s now $9 or $10, compared with $35 to $40 for those in the U.S. on an H1B visa, he said. But he’d tell clients the cheaper hourly wage equated to more like $80 because of the need for supervision, and he said his firm won back some business to fix mistakes.</span><br>
<span>HCL, once known as Hindustan Computers, was founded in 1976 by billionaire Shiv Nadar and now has more than $8.6 billion in annual sales. With 18,000 employees in the U.S. and 15,000 in Europe, HCL is a global company and has deep expertise in computing, said Sukamal Banerjee, a vice president. It has won business from Boeing on that basis, not on price, he said: “We came from a strong R&D background.”</span><br>
<span>Still, for the 787, HCL gave Boeing a remarkable price – free, according to Sam Swaro, an associate vice president who pitched HCL’s services at a San Diego conference sponsored by Avionics International magazine in June. He said the company took no up-front payments on the 787 and only started collecting payments based on sales years later, an “innovative business model” he offered to extend to others in the industry.</span><br>
<span>The 787 entered service three years late and billions of dollars over budget in 2011, in part because of confusion introduced by the outsourcing strategy. Under Dennis Muilenburg, a longtime Boeing engineer who became chief executive in 2015, the company has said that it planned to bring more work back in-house for its newest planes.</span><br>
<span>Engineer Backwater</span><br>
<span>The Max became Boeing’s top seller soon after it was offered in 2011. But for ambitious engineers, it was something of a “backwater,” said Peter Lemme, who designed the 767’s automated flight controls and is now a consultant. The Max was an update of a 50-year-old design, and the changes needed to be limited enough that Boeing could produce the new planes like cookie cutters, with few changes for either the assembly line or airlines. “As an engineer that’s not the greatest job,” he said.</span><br>
<span>Rockwell Collins, now a unit of United Technologies Corp., won the Max contract for cockpit displays, and it has relied in part on HCL engineers in India, Iowa and the Seattle area. A United Technologies spokeswoman didn’t respond to a request for comment.</span><br>
<span>Boeing 737 Max</span><br>
<span>Boeing 737 Max airplanes at the company’s manufacturing facility in Renton, Washington.Photographer: David Ryder/Bloomberg</span><br>
<span>Contract engineers from Cyient helped test flight test equipment. Charles LoveJoy, a former flight-test instrumentation design engineer at the company, said engineers in the U.S. would review drawings done overnight in India every morning at 7:30 a.m. “We did have our challenges with the India team,” he said. “They met the requirements, per se, but you could do it better.”</span><br>
<span>Multiple investigations – including a Justice Department criminal probe – are trying to unravel how and when critical decisions were made about the Max’s software. During the crashes of Lion Air and Ethiopian Airlines planes that killed 346 people, investigators suspect, the MCAS system pushed the planes into uncontrollable dives because of bad data from a single sensor.</span><br>
<span>That design violated basic principles of redundancy for generations of Boeing engineers, and the company apparently never tested to see how the software would respond, Lemme said. “It was a stunning fail,” he said. “A lot of people should have thought of this problem – not one person – and asked about it.”</span><br>
<span>Boeing also has disclosed that it learned soon after Max deliveries began in 2017 that a warning light that might have alerted crews to the issue with the sensor wasn’t installed correctly in the flight-display software. A Boeing statement in May, explaining why the company didn’t inform regulators at the time, said engineers had determined it wasn’t a safety issue.</span><br>
<span>“Senior company leadership,” the statement added, “was not involved in the review.”</span><br>
<span>后面附上一个旧闻</span><br>
<span>波音737 MAX半年两次坠毁，787飞控软件竟由这家印度公司编写 2019-03-11 18:29</span><br>
<span>最近四个多月内，波音737 MAX 8客机连续发生两起严重的坠机惨剧，造成345人遇难，这在人类航空史上都非常罕见。关于事故原因，目前尚无官方确认的说法，但是外界猜测是由于飞机上的传感器给出了错误的攻角数据，自动控制飞机低头俯冲。这本是一个可以修正的错误，然而不知道什么原因，波音公司竟然设定机器比飞行员拥有等级更高的操控优先权，最终导致惨剧两次发生。http://5b0988e595225.cdn.sohucs.com/images/20190311/4a2a27a30e6c445fbcefcaa1b31f97a6.jpeg埃航的波音737 MAX8客机实际上，这并不是波音飞机现在才出现类似的问题。早在2013年10月10日，日本航空公司国际航线三架波音787梦想客机就先后因故障而中途折返，其中一架事后明确查出是电气事故。不仅如此，在2012年一年时间内，波音787客机出现了四次电气系统故障。而据福克斯2012年12月初的一篇文章报道，波音787客机电气系统的软件，恰恰是由印度HCL公司外包的。http://5b0988e595225.cdn.sohucs.com/images/20190311/62c61e9d21c0445b94ada6cc56effb51.jpeg波音787梦想变成了梦碎HCL公司，原名印度斯坦电脑公司，它是印度一家全球性IT服务公司，总部设在诺伊达。该公司提供多种服务，包括软件咨询，企业转型，远程基础设施管理，工程和研发服务以及业务流程外包。HCL已经在31个国家设有办公室，向各行各业提供服务，在2015年2月15日，其市值为224.8亿美元，成为印度上市公司前20强。http://5b0988e595225.cdn.sohucs.com/images/20190311/f5c3d019e5394208b1c0287b39d74af3.jpeg印度HCL公司是波音787客机的软件外包商福克斯的文章中提到，记者通过内线获知，HCL通过哈密尔顿转包，与波音合作开发787梦想客机，2009年2月还获得了波音金质杰出奖。另外，波音787梦想客机的ES工程样板软件也是由印度HCL公司编写的，美国联邦航空管理局已经下令禁止使用该软件。http://5b0988e595225.cdn.sohucs.com/images/20190311/bf627751724d431fbd040b008ca8705a.jpeg福克斯的文章原文不仅如此，波音787梦想客机，从具体组件生产到最关键的整机飞机控制软件，印度公司都得到了很重要的合同。而且据波音高级管理人员Dinesh Keskar在2018年表示，“波音787大型飞机很有可能在印度制造，但需要很长时间，因为对资金、技术和基础设施的要求很高。”http://5b0988e595225.cdn.sohucs.com/images/20190311/d1f7cb7e81dd46709b34317597197ca5.jpeg印度近年来在航空领域野心很大虽然没有证据表明此次发生事故的波音737 MAX 8客机的飞控软件也与HCL或者其他印度公司有关，但是发生在787梦想客机身上的事，也许能够提供给我们追本溯源的一个新思路。</span><br>
</p><p><b>你妈的为什么: </b><br>
<span>从内部攻破我们的敌人</span><br>
<span>阿三伟大</span><br>
</p><p><b>powwow: </b><br>
<span>锅全甩外包头上，波音其他人都是吃干饭的吗？聘用不合格的外包并且没有检查测试，正规标准的开发流程不走，锅还是不负责任的波音的。</span><br>
</p><p><b>曲终人未散: </b><br>
<span>这下终于放心了</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>nicebody: </b><br>
<span>楼主是被三哥强奸了妹妹？这么深仇大恨的</span><br>
</p><p><b>春哥亲自: </b><br>
<span>已知HAL击落军机</span><br>
<span>HCL击落客机</span><br>
<span>HBL是干什么的</span><br>
</p><p><b>薄皮破船: </b><br>
<span>于是，摔锅阿三，波音继续毫无错误？</span><br>
</p><p><b>WDLEZ: </b><br>
<span>飞控软件外包这么大的事，居然没人过问，这责任三哥只能占一半</span><br>
</p><p><b>tyfsam: </b><br>
<span>这种软件居然还外包给三哥，也是牛逼</span><br>
</p><p><b>woodcoin: </b><br>
<span>没好的测试流程我是信的</span><br>
<span>没有软件测试那能飞起来就是十分魔幻了</span><br>
</p><p><b>钢铁侠: </b><br>
<span>所以说摔飞机是阿三自带的属性？</span><br>
</p><p><b>typeunknown: </b><br>
<span>这1200人都去哪了</span><br>
</p><p><b>sionlnm: </b><br>
<span>记得快十年前，对硅谷阿三程序员吹的飞起，这下直接飞机打脸</span><br>
</p><p><b>風駿: </b><br>
<span>阿三似乎成了不靠谱的代名词……</span><br>
</p><p><b>skullgreymon: </b><br>
<span>春哥亲自 发表于 2019-6-30 21:43</span><br>
<span>已知HAL击落军机</span><br>
<span>HCL击落客机</span><br>
<span>击落游戏机（指ns</span><br>
</p><p><b>神道设教: </b><br>
<span>没用的，外野码农多，屁股坐在那一边你也是知道的。</span><br>
</p><p><b>曾经的小书: </b><br>
<span>印度发展那么快，分分钟是第二中国</span><br>
</p><p><b>钢琴男: </b><br>
<span>这不是波音掉下来后大家都津津乐道的话题么…… （当然还是有几个杠精跳出来帮阿三洗）只是现在被官方实锤了……</span><br>
</p><p><b>tonyshijie: </b><br>
<span>我觉得还是管理责任居多</span><br>
</p><p><b>Tackstone: </b><br>
<span>一开始都只是玩梗，结果这锅还真甩到印度人头上了</span><br>
</p><p><b>消亡值语义: </b><br>
<span>美国资本家嫌硅谷工程师工资太高？</span><br>
</p><p><b>帕蕾莉亚: </b><br>
<span>被阿三趴到头上的美国公司有好下场吗？</span><br>
</p><p><b>布里希嘉曼: </b><br>
<span>想看印度网友评论</span><br>
<span>----发送自 STAGE1 App for Android.</span><br>
</p><p><b>flypig_zhy: </b><br>
<span>所以美国白人就不背锅？</span><br>
</p><p><b>gambleman: </b><br>
<span>那么裁的1200资深工程师来商飞吼不吼啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>qazesz: </b><br>
<span>阿三，人类的绝望</span><br>
</p><p><b>LoliType: </b><br>
<span>这口锅还真到阿三头上了。不过这和印度国内的外包没啥关系，主要问题在于聘请不了解航空行业的人来写航空软件，这活你只要找外包，不管哪国的外包，不管给多少钱都一样会出问题，所以谁决定请外包，那就是谁的锅，主楼后面的话是在是太狭隘了。</span><br>
<span>哦，是个阿三决定开掉原有IT请外包的啊。干死阿三</span><br>
</p><p><b>naclken.: </b><br>
<span>好，不管是真锅还是甩锅，总之是好，撕得用力一点。</span><br>
</p><p><b>月神的长弓: </b><br>
<span>3L +10086，软件外包的多了，就你波音出这么大娄子，还想甩锅呐？</span><br>
</p><p><b>李恭暔: </b><br>
<span>tyfsam 发表于 2019-6-30 20:53</span><br>
<span>这种软件居然还外包给三哥，也是牛逼</span><br>
<span>因为力主将软件业务外包的贱叉就是印度叉主管啊！</span><br>
<span>深挖下去，那家伙没有收受外包公司HCL的利益，谁会信呢！</span><br>
</p><p><b>qzlhzlj: </b><br>
<span>今天招来一个阿三，明天一飞机的阿三就来帮你实现美国梦了，有什么不满意的？</span><br>
<span>----发送自 ZUK ZUK Z2151,Android 8.0.0</span><br>
</p><p><b>MaXia0: </b><br>
<span>然后重新卖就说软件bug修复了？</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 6, Android 8.0.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>yanhan0410: </b><br>
<span>我记得这事出来的第一时间就有人说可能是印度程序员的问题。</span><br>
</p><p><b>Alexmacau8: </b><br>
<span>安啦 不了了之的事情</span><br>
</p><p><b>hanyuwei70: </b><br>
<span>我看什么时候印度裔的名声彻底在IT臭掉</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>wuxan94: </b><br>
<span>hanyuwei70 发表于 2019-7-1 01:07</span><br>
<span>我看什么时候印度裔的名声彻底在IT臭掉</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 Android客户端 ...</span><br>
<span>闭嘴！我们在讨论瘟⑩</span><br>
</p><p><b>wuxan94: </b><br>
<span>薄皮破船 发表于 2019-6-30 20:48</span><br>
<span>于是，摔锅阿三，波音继续毫无错误？</span><br>
<span>裁掉1200根红苗正的白皮工程师……</span><br>
<span>这B29也整成一式陆攻了吧～</span><br>
</p><p><b>Okumur: </b><br>
<span>hanyuwei70 发表于 2019-7-1 01:07</span><br>
<span>我看什么时候印度裔的名声彻底在IT臭掉</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 Android客户端 ...</span><br>
<span> 印度时报下面评论说 Indians are coding for everything. Except for boeing everything's fine. </span><br>
<span>我们coding了宇宙万物都没事，怎么就你波音有事</span><br>
</p><p><b>シャスタ: </b><br>
<span>帕蕾莉亚 发表于 2019-6-30 21:59</span><br>
<span>被阿三趴到头上的美国公司有好下场吗？</span><br>
<span>谷歌微软啊,两家股价现在都很高</span><br>
<span>微软更是沉默了快15年股价不动.然后一路攀升超过泡沫前历史最高并且一路向上了.</span><br>
</p><p><b>Surlert: </b><br>
<span>彭博fake news</span><br>
<span>跟黑间谍主板一样的动机</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Meizu PRO 6 Plus, Android 7.0.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>希望之花: </b><br>
<span>月神的长弓 发表于 2019-6-30 22:51</span><br>
<span>3L +10086，软件外包的多了，就你波音出这么大娄子，还想甩锅呐？</span><br>
<span>因为普通软件甚至win10更新出问题了都可以打个哈哈上patch当无事发生</span><br>
<span>飞机出问题就是命啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>sykeash: </b><br>
<span>不愧是三哥全面感染</span><br>
</p><p><b>lipo: </b><br>
<span>港真，现在美国航空工程的很多子分支里最牛叉的就是印度裔大牛，按你的说法干光他们，米国的航空工业至少倒退十几年。</span><br>
</p><p><b>akirt: </b><br>
<span>你要省钱 就得承担起相应的风险</span><br>
<span>我觉得类似的案例应该不止发生在波音身上</span><br>
</p><p><b>mu1: </b><br>
<span>lipo 发表于 2019-7-1 02:06</span><br>
<span>港真，现在美国航空工程的很多子分支里最牛叉的就是印度裔大牛，按你的说法干光他们，米国的航空工业至少倒 ...</span><br>
<span>没事，反正这MAX是50年前的设计微改</span><br>
</p><p><b>fallout: </b><br>
<span>看完帖回头看了下楼主不是废狗老师</span><br>
</p><p><b>nohope: </b><br>
<span>阿三容易成帮是真的，一个阿三就能带来一队阿三</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 8, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>xenox: </b><br>
<span>powwow 发表于 2019-6-30 20:37</span><br>
<span>锅全甩外包头上，波音其他人都是吃干饭的吗？聘用不合格的外包并且没有检查测试，正规标准的开发流程不走， ...</span><br>
<span>外包就是用来背锅的，锅都不背，我还要你外包何用？</span><br>
</p><p><b>zhy_2018: </b><br>
<span>这个阿三真爱国，想尽办法给老家创造就业机会</span><br>
</p><p><b>ccow: </b><br>
<span>太扯了，业务逻辑不可能是阿三公司定的。</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1843385[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
