<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Donald Trump的黑历史, 英语长文, 曲折精彩, 建议组织翻译</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>Donald Trump的黑历史, 英语长文, 曲折精彩, 建议组织翻译</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 20:32:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump的黑历史, 英语长文, 曲折精彩, 建议组织翻译[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1832041-1-1.html</link>
      <description>Donald Trump的黑历史, 英语长文, 曲折精彩, 建议组织翻译&#13;
 本帖最后由 朱卉菲 于 2019-5-20 19:31 编辑 

在知呼上看了中文黑材料, 但是语焉不详,特地去翻NYT找出原文来观赏一下
&#13;
二楼五楼是当年报道
&#13;
Donald Trump Soured on a Deal, and Hong Kong Partners Became Litigants
&#13;
Supporters of Donald J. Trump waiting for him at a campaign rally in April in Bridgeport, Conn. He has often portrayed himself as uniquely capable of wringing concessions out of China.CreditDamon Winter/The New York Times
&#13;
https://static01.nyt.com/images/2016/05/30/us/31trumpchina-web1/31trumpchina-web1-articleLarge.jpg?quality=75&amp;auto=webp&amp;disable=upscale
&#13;
Imagehttps://static01.nyt.com/images/2016/05/30/us/31trumpchina-web1/31trumpchina-web1-articleLarge.jpg?quality=75&amp;auto=webp&amp;disable=upscale
&#13;
Supporters of Donald J. Trump waiting for him at a campaign rally in April in Bridgeport, Conn. He has often portrayed himself as uniquely capable of wringing concessions out of China.CreditCreditDamon Winter/The New York Times
&#13;
By Farah Stockman and Keith Bradsher
&#13;
May 30, 2016
&#13;
Donald J. Trump, who has made reversing America’s trade imbalance a pillar of his campaign, often portrays himself as uniquely capable of wringing concessions out of China through hard-nosed business tactics he has honed over the years.
&#13;
In fact, he says, he has a personal track record to back up his boasts.
&#13;
“I beat China all the time,” Mr. Trump declared in a speech the day he announced his candidacy. “I own a big chunk of the Bank of America building at 1290 Avenue of the Americas that I got from China in a war. Very valuable.”
&#13;
Mr. Trump does have an investment in the building, an office tower near Rockefeller Center. But court documents and interviews with people involved in the deal tell a very different story of how he ended up with it.
&#13;
It began when a group of Hong Kong billionaires, including one who has been called the Donald Trump of China, helped rescue Mr. Trump from the verge of bankruptcy by investing in one of his properties in Manhattan.
&#13;
For years, the carefully cultivated relationship between Mr. Trump and his Hong Kong partners proved lucrative for both sides, and stands out as perhaps the closest that Mr. Trump has come to international diplomacy.
&#13;
To strike the deal, Mr. Trump had to attend elaborate dinner parties featuring foreign foods he did not want to eat. He delayed the closing because of Chinese spiritual beliefs and hunted around New York for a “feng shui” master to help with the building décor, instead of indulging his tastes for marble and gold, according to former associates of Mr. Trump who were involved in the deal.
&#13;
But when his Hong Kong partners sold the property without his support, Mr. Trump waged a bitter, long-shot legal battle against them. And far from winning his share of the Bank of America building, according to court documents, he had to settle for it after losing in court. In the end, Mr. Trump’s alliance and eventual rivalry with some of Hong Kong’s richest men proved to be a tale of Mr. Trump at the extremes. It showcased his unflagging confidence in his ability to turn a bad financial situation around. But it also underscored his willingness to destroy a fruitful relationship with aggressive litigation.
&#13;
Their partnership began in 1994, after the collapse of the real estate market left Mr. Trump deeply in debt. He could not afford to make the bank payments on a 77-acre swath of land near Lincoln Center known as Riverside South, let alone to develop the property.
&#13;
1290 Avenue of the Americas in Manhattan. Mr. Trump has an investment in the building, an office tower near Rockefeller Center.CreditSam Hodgson for The New York Times
&#13;
https://static01.nyt.com/images/2016/05/30/us/31trumpchina-web2/31trumpchina-web2-articleLarge.jpg?quality=75&amp;auto=webp&amp;disable=upscale
&#13;
Imagehttps://static01.nyt.com/images/2016/05/30/us/31trumpchina-web2/31trumpchina-web2-articleLarge.jpg?quality=75&amp;auto=webp&amp;disable=upscale
&#13;
1290 Avenue of the Americas in Manhattan. Mr. Trump has an investment in the building, an office tower near Rockefeller Center.CreditSam Hodgson for The New York Times
&#13;
In need of cash, he agreed to meet with intermediaries from a consortium of Hong Kong billionaires who were willing to buy the land, assume Mr. Trump’s debts and pay him 30 percent of the profits, as well as fees for helping to manage the development of the site, which they agreed to finance. It was by far the best offer he received. The group included Henry Cheng Kar-shun, one of the world’s richest developers, and Vincent Lo, who is Mr. Trump’s Chinese counterpart in more ways than one.
&#13;
Like Mr. Trump, Mr. Lo comes from a wealthy family. He is well known for creating a hip restaurant area in Shanghai called Xintiandi, or “new heaven on earth,” an upscale brand he has replicated across China. His life has been chronicled by tabloids and society pages, especially his divorce from his first wife and his marriage to a beauty pageant winner, Miss Hong Kong of 1977.Despite their similarities, Mr. Trump hesitated when he received an invitation to travel to Hong Kong to negotiate the deal. He does not like to travel, and he feared that negotiating on the Hong Kong developers’ turf would put him at a disadvantage and make him appear weak, said Abe Wallach, Mr. Trump’s executive vice president of acquisitions and finance at the time.But face-to-face meetings are crucial in Chinese business culture, where personal bonds and political connections, collectively known as guanxi, are relied upon to avoid and resolve business disputes, sometimes more than the legal system. Eventually, Mr. Trump’s aides convinced him that he had to make the trip.
&#13;
In Hong Kong, the golf games, dinner parties and intensive talks featured the awkwardness and cultural miscues that can crop up in any high-stakes international negotiation. Mr. Lo and Mr. Cheng invited Mr. Trump to play golf, but Mr. Trump was appalled when they told him they usually bet more than $1,000 on each hole. They ended up betting $100 per hole, and Mr. Trump wound up losing more than he won, Mr. Lo recalled in an interview this month.
&#13;
“He’s a good golfer, but we had the local knowledge — he probably was jet-lagged,” Mr. Lo said.
&#13;
Mr. Lo and Mr. Cheng invited Mr. Trump to dinner at the home of Mr. Cheng’s father, an uncommon honor in Chinese culture. But the evening was a trying experience for Mr. Trump.“He didn’t like the food, and couldn’t use chopsticks,” recalled Mr. Wallach, who was there. “The first course was a whole fish, with the head still on. You could see the face of the fish and the teeth, which really looked grotesque. The servant put the fish in front of Donald. Donald said, ‘The honor belongs to Abe.’ I took my chopsticks and began to pick at it.”
&#13;
Mr. Cheng and Mr. Lo also half-jokingly proposed an informal drinking contest, which Mr. Trump, a teetotaler, declined.The Hong Kong partners were wary of Mr. Trump’s well-earned reputation for litigiousness. But for more than a decade, Mr. Trump avoided conflict with them. Indeed, he often deferred to them. Chase Manhattan Bank, which held Mr. Trump’s mortgage, initially scheduled the closing of the deal during China’s Ghost Month, during which some believe the spirits of the dead roam the earth.
&#13;
Henry Cheng Kar-shun, one of the world’s richest developers, at a news conference in 2011 in Hong Kong.CreditImaginechina, via Associated Press
&#13;
https://static01.nyt.com/images/2016/05/30/us/31trumpchina-web4/31trumpchina-web4-articleLarge.jpg?quality=75&amp;auto=webp&amp;disable=upscale
&#13;
Imagehttps://static01.nyt.com/images/2016/05/30/us/31trumpchina-web4/31trumpchina-web4-articleLarge.jpg?quality=75&amp;auto=webp&amp;disable=upscale
&#13;
Henry Cheng Kar-shun, one of the world’s richest developers, at a news conference in 2011 in Hong Kong.CreditImaginechina, via Associated Press
&#13;
“The Chinese told me that we would have to wait until after the fifteenth of September to close the deal,” Mr. Wallach wrote in a chapter of an unpublished book he is writing about his years with Mr. Trump. “Trump went apoplectic.” But he said that Mr. Trump went along.
&#13;
(Mr. Lo said that any delay had been caused by a need to complete paperwork, and that he and his business partners were not superstitious.)
&#13;
The project proved extremely profitable, as the New York real estate market rebounded. In 2005, the Hong Kong partners sold the development for $1.76 billion. Although it was believed to be the largest residential real estate transaction in the city’s history, Mr. Trump was furious, and contends to this day that his partners did not consult him first.
&#13;
“I said: ‘Why didn’t you come talk to me? Whatever price you got, I could have gotten more money,’” Mr. Trump recalled in an interview this month.
&#13;
Mr. Lo said that Mr. Trump had been informed of the decision, and that in any case it would have been very hard to shop such a large property around without Mr. Trump’s becoming aware of it.Instead of accepting his share of the proceeds, Mr. Trump sued his partners for “staggering breach” of fiduciary duty in a lawsuit that demanded $1 billion in damages. Mr. Lo, who felt that Mr. Trump should have been appreciative of the deal he had received, called the lawsuit “a shock.”
&#13;
And when the Hong Kong partners sought to invest the proceeds from the sale in Bank of America buildings in San Francisco and New York, Mr. Trump sought an injunction to scuttle the deal.
&#13;
The judge ruled against him. Instead of receiving the cash he wanted, Mr. Trump had to accept a 30 percent share in the profits from the two Bank of America buildings, tied up in a partnership that is slated to last until 2044. But today, Mr. Trump counts that legal defeat as a victory.
&#13;
“Through more luck than talent, I ended up much better because the buildings have increased in value,” he said. “In the end, it was fine.”
&#13;
https://static01.nyt.com/images/2016/05/30/us/31trumpchina-web3/31trumpchina-web3-articleLarge.jpg?quality=75&amp;auto=webp&amp;disable=upscale
&#13;
Vincent Lo, a businessman whose life has been chronicled by tabloids and society pages, in 2011 in Shanghai.CreditPhilippe Lopez/Agence France-Presse — Getty Images
&#13;
Nonetheless, Mr. Trump’s litigation over Riverside South dragged on for at least four years. He forced his partners to produce more than 166,000 pages of documents in court and accused them of various transgressions, including fraud and tax evasion.
&#13;
During the litigation, Mr. Lo was forced to keep his trips to the United States secret, out of concern that Mr. Trump’s lawyers would serve him with court papers that would force him to remain in the United States.
&#13;
Outside court, Mr. Trump’s battle seemed to take the shape of a personal rivalry with Mr. Lo, who had just bankrolled a Chinese reality television show called “Wise Man Takes All.” It loosely resembled Mr. Trump’s show “The Apprentice,” although Mr. Lo appeared just once on the show and handed out start-up capital to the winners instead of jobs.
&#13;
Mr. Trump announced that he was going to take a version of “The Apprentice” to China to compete with Mr. Lo’s show, although Mr. Trump’s show there does not appear to have gotten off the ground. In an interview, Mr. Trump asked a reporter how Mr. Lo’s show had turned out, then answered his question: “Let’s put it this way. It wasn’t ‘The Apprentice,’ which was a big success.”
&#13;
Mr. Lo said his show had met his real goal of promoting entrepreneurship in China.
&#13;
After the lawsuit, the Hong Kong partners moved swiftly to cut all ties to Mr. Trump. Mr. Lo sold his shares in the partnership to the Cheng family, which sold to Vornado Realty Trust, now the owner of a 70 percent interest in the Bank of America buildings.
&#13;
But in the interview, Mr. Trump sounded almost wistful about his former partners, marveling at the money they had made together and at the fact that they no longer spoke. He acknowledged that his former partners might have gotten the best deal possible on Riverside South, after all.
&#13;
“It’s too bad that this happened,” Mr. Trump told a reporter.
&#13;
“If you speak to Vincent and Henry, tell them I think they are fantastic people,” he said. “You let them know that Donald Trump has great respect for them, O.K.?”
&#13;
Eight thousand miles away, in his penthouse office in Hong Kong, Mr. Lo laughed when told of Mr. Trump’s comment. He made clear that he had not forgotten being sued for $1 billion.
&#13;
“Well, that’s him,” Mr. Lo said. “To file a lawsuit is nothing. It’s just like having lunch.”</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>朱卉菲: </b><br>
<span>Donald Trump的黑历史, 英语长文, 曲折精彩, 建议组织翻译</span><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 朱卉菲 于 2019-5-20 19:31 编辑 </span><br>
<span>在知呼上看了中文黑材料, 但是语焉不详,特地去翻NYT找出原文来观赏一下</span><br>
<span>二楼五楼是当年报道</span><br>
<span>Donald Trump Soured on a Deal, and Hong Kong Partners Became Litigants</span><br>
<span>Supporters of Donald J. Trump waiting for him at a campaign rally in April in Bridgeport, Conn. He has often portrayed himself as uniquely capable of wringing concessions out of China.CreditDamon Winter/The New York Times</span><br>
<span>https://static01.nyt.com/images/2016/05/30/us/31trumpchina-web1/31trumpchina-web1-articleLarge.jpg?quality=75&auto=webp&disable=upscale</span><br>
<span>Imagehttps://static01.nyt.com/images/2016/05/30/us/31trumpchina-web1/31trumpchina-web1-articleLarge.jpg?quality=75&auto=webp&disable=upscale</span><br>
<span>Supporters of Donald J. Trump waiting for him at a campaign rally in April in Bridgeport, Conn. He has often portrayed himself as uniquely capable of wringing concessions out of China.CreditCreditDamon Winter/The New York Times</span><br>
<span>By Farah Stockman and Keith Bradsher</span><br>
<span>May 30, 2016</span><br>
<span>Donald J. Trump, who has made reversing America’s trade imbalance a pillar of his campaign, often portrays himself as uniquely capable of wringing concessions out of China through hard-nosed business tactics he has honed over the years.</span><br>
<span>In fact, he says, he has a personal track record to back up his boasts.</span><br>
<span>“I beat China all the time,” Mr. Trump declared in a speech the day he announced his candidacy. “I own a big chunk of the Bank of America building at 1290 Avenue of the Americas that I got from China in a war. Very valuable.”</span><br>
<span>Mr. Trump does have an investment in the building, an office tower near Rockefeller Center. But court documents and interviews with people involved in the deal tell a very different story of how he ended up with it.</span><br>
<span>It began when a group of Hong Kong billionaires, including one who has been called the Donald Trump of China, helped rescue Mr. Trump from the verge of bankruptcy by investing in one of his properties in Manhattan.</span><br>
<span>For years, the carefully cultivated relationship between Mr. Trump and his Hong Kong partners proved lucrative for both sides, and stands out as perhaps the closest that Mr. Trump has come to international diplomacy.</span><br>
<span>To strike the deal, Mr. Trump had to attend elaborate dinner parties featuring foreign foods he did not want to eat. He delayed the closing because of Chinese spiritual beliefs and hunted around New York for a “feng shui” master to help with the building décor, instead of indulging his tastes for marble and gold, according to former associates of Mr. Trump who were involved in the deal.</span><br>
<span>But when his Hong Kong partners sold the property without his support, Mr. Trump waged a bitter, long-shot legal battle against them. And far from winning his share of the Bank of America building, according to court documents, he had to settle for it after losing in court. In the end, Mr. Trump’s alliance and eventual rivalry with some of Hong Kong’s richest men proved to be a tale of Mr. Trump at the extremes. It showcased his unflagging confidence in his ability to turn a bad financial situation around. But it also underscored his willingness to destroy a fruitful relationship with aggressive litigation.</span><br>
<span>Their partnership began in 1994, after the collapse of the real estate market left Mr. Trump deeply in debt. He could not afford to make the bank payments on a 77-acre swath of land near Lincoln Center known as Riverside South, let alone to develop the property.</span><br>
<span>1290 Avenue of the Americas in Manhattan. Mr. Trump has an investment in the building, an office tower near Rockefeller Center.CreditSam Hodgson for The New York Times</span><br>
<span>https://static01.nyt.com/images/2016/05/30/us/31trumpchina-web2/31trumpchina-web2-articleLarge.jpg?quality=75&auto=webp&disable=upscale</span><br>
<span>Imagehttps://static01.nyt.com/images/2016/05/30/us/31trumpchina-web2/31trumpchina-web2-articleLarge.jpg?quality=75&auto=webp&disable=upscale</span><br>
<span>1290 Avenue of the Americas in Manhattan. Mr. Trump has an investment in the building, an office tower near Rockefeller Center.CreditSam Hodgson for The New York Times</span><br>
<span>In need of cash, he agreed to meet with intermediaries from a consortium of Hong Kong billionaires who were willing to buy the land, assume Mr. Trump’s debts and pay him 30 percent of the profits, as well as fees for helping to manage the development of the site, which they agreed to finance. It was by far the best offer he received. The group included Henry Cheng Kar-shun, one of the world’s richest developers, and Vincent Lo, who is Mr. Trump’s Chinese counterpart in more ways than one.</span><br>
<span>Like Mr. Trump, Mr. Lo comes from a wealthy family. He is well known for creating a hip restaurant area in Shanghai called Xintiandi, or “new heaven on earth,” an upscale brand he has replicated across China. His life has been chronicled by tabloids and society pages, especially his divorce from his first wife and his marriage to a beauty pageant winner, Miss Hong Kong of 1977.Despite their similarities, Mr. Trump hesitated when he received an invitation to travel to Hong Kong to negotiate the deal. He does not like to travel, and he feared that negotiating on the Hong Kong developers’ turf would put him at a disadvantage and make him appear weak, said Abe Wallach, Mr. Trump’s executive vice president of acquisitions and finance at the time.But face-to-face meetings are crucial in Chinese business culture, where personal bonds and political connections, collectively known as guanxi, are relied upon to avoid and resolve business disputes, sometimes more than the legal system. Eventually, Mr. Trump’s aides convinced him that he had to make the trip.</span><br>
<span>In Hong Kong, the golf games, dinner parties and intensive talks featured the awkwardness and cultural miscues that can crop up in any high-stakes international negotiation. Mr. Lo and Mr. Cheng invited Mr. Trump to play golf, but Mr. Trump was appalled when they told him they usually bet more than $1,000 on each hole. They ended up betting $100 per hole, and Mr. Trump wound up losing more than he won, Mr. Lo recalled in an interview this month.</span><br>
<span>“He’s a good golfer, but we had the local knowledge — he probably was jet-lagged,” Mr. Lo said.</span><br>
<span>Mr. Lo and Mr. Cheng invited Mr. Trump to dinner at the home of Mr. Cheng’s father, an uncommon honor in Chinese culture. But the evening was a trying experience for Mr. Trump.“He didn’t like the food, and couldn’t use chopsticks,” recalled Mr. Wallach, who was there. “The first course was a whole fish, with the head still on. You could see the face of the fish and the teeth, which really looked grotesque. The servant put the fish in front of Donald. Donald said, ‘The honor belongs to Abe.’ I took my chopsticks and began to pick at it.”</span><br>
<span>Mr. Cheng and Mr. Lo also half-jokingly proposed an informal drinking contest, which Mr. Trump, a teetotaler, declined.The Hong Kong partners were wary of Mr. Trump’s well-earned reputation for litigiousness. But for more than a decade, Mr. Trump avoided conflict with them. Indeed, he often deferred to them. Chase Manhattan Bank, which held Mr. Trump’s mortgage, initially scheduled the closing of the deal during China’s Ghost Month, during which some believe the spirits of the dead roam the earth.</span><br>
<span>Henry Cheng Kar-shun, one of the world’s richest developers, at a news conference in 2011 in Hong Kong.CreditImaginechina, via Associated Press</span><br>
<span>https://static01.nyt.com/images/2016/05/30/us/31trumpchina-web4/31trumpchina-web4-articleLarge.jpg?quality=75&auto=webp&disable=upscale</span><br>
<span>Imagehttps://static01.nyt.com/images/2016/05/30/us/31trumpchina-web4/31trumpchina-web4-articleLarge.jpg?quality=75&auto=webp&disable=upscale</span><br>
<span>Henry Cheng Kar-shun, one of the world’s richest developers, at a news conference in 2011 in Hong Kong.CreditImaginechina, via Associated Press</span><br>
<span>“The Chinese told me that we would have to wait until after the fifteenth of September to close the deal,” Mr. Wallach wrote in a chapter of an unpublished book he is writing about his years with Mr. Trump. “Trump went apoplectic.” But he said that Mr. Trump went along.</span><br>
<span>(Mr. Lo said that any delay had been caused by a need to complete paperwork, and that he and his business partners were not superstitious.)</span><br>
<span>The project proved extremely profitable, as the New York real estate market rebounded. In 2005, the Hong Kong partners sold the development for $1.76 billion. Although it was believed to be the largest residential real estate transaction in the city’s history, Mr. Trump was furious, and contends to this day that his partners did not consult him first.</span><br>
<span>“I said: ‘Why didn’t you come talk to me? Whatever price you got, I could have gotten more money,’” Mr. Trump recalled in an interview this month.</span><br>
<span>Mr. Lo said that Mr. Trump had been informed of the decision, and that in any case it would have been very hard to shop such a large property around without Mr. Trump’s becoming aware of it.Instead of accepting his share of the proceeds, Mr. Trump sued his partners for “staggering breach” of fiduciary duty in a lawsuit that demanded $1 billion in damages. Mr. Lo, who felt that Mr. Trump should have been appreciative of the deal he had received, called the lawsuit “a shock.”</span><br>
<span>And when the Hong Kong partners sought to invest the proceeds from the sale in Bank of America buildings in San Francisco and New York, Mr. Trump sought an injunction to scuttle the deal.</span><br>
<span>The judge ruled against him. Instead of receiving the cash he wanted, Mr. Trump had to accept a 30 percent share in the profits from the two Bank of America buildings, tied up in a partnership that is slated to last until 2044. But today, Mr. Trump counts that legal defeat as a victory.</span><br>
<span>“Through more luck than talent, I ended up much better because the buildings have increased in value,” he said. “In the end, it was fine.”</span><br>
<span>https://static01.nyt.com/images/2016/05/30/us/31trumpchina-web3/31trumpchina-web3-articleLarge.jpg?quality=75&auto=webp&disable=upscale</span><br>
<span>Vincent Lo, a businessman whose life has been chronicled by tabloids and society pages, in 2011 in Shanghai.CreditPhilippe Lopez/Agence France-Presse — Getty Images</span><br>
<span>Nonetheless, Mr. Trump’s litigation over Riverside South dragged on for at least four years. He forced his partners to produce more than 166,000 pages of documents in court and accused them of various transgressions, including fraud and tax evasion.</span><br>
<span>During the litigation, Mr. Lo was forced to keep his trips to the United States secret, out of concern that Mr. Trump’s lawyers would serve him with court papers that would force him to remain in the United States.</span><br>
<span>Outside court, Mr. Trump’s battle seemed to take the shape of a personal rivalry with Mr. Lo, who had just bankrolled a Chinese reality television show called “Wise Man Takes All.” It loosely resembled Mr. Trump’s show “The Apprentice,” although Mr. Lo appeared just once on the show and handed out start-up capital to the winners instead of jobs.</span><br>
<span>Mr. Trump announced that he was going to take a version of “The Apprentice” to China to compete with Mr. Lo’s show, although Mr. Trump’s show there does not appear to have gotten off the ground. In an interview, Mr. Trump asked a reporter how Mr. Lo’s show had turned out, then answered his question: “Let’s put it this way. It wasn’t ‘The Apprentice,’ which was a big success.”</span><br>
<span>Mr. Lo said his show had met his real goal of promoting entrepreneurship in China.</span><br>
<span>After the lawsuit, the Hong Kong partners moved swiftly to cut all ties to Mr. Trump. Mr. Lo sold his shares in the partnership to the Cheng family, which sold to Vornado Realty Trust, now the owner of a 70 percent interest in the Bank of America buildings.</span><br>
<span>But in the interview, Mr. Trump sounded almost wistful about his former partners, marveling at the money they had made together and at the fact that they no longer spoke. He acknowledged that his former partners might have gotten the best deal possible on Riverside South, after all.</span><br>
<span>“It’s too bad that this happened,” Mr. Trump told a reporter.</span><br>
<span>“If you speak to Vincent and Henry, tell them I think they are fantastic people,” he said. “You let them know that Donald Trump has great respect for them, O.K.?”</span><br>
<span>Eight thousand miles away, in his penthouse office in Hong Kong, Mr. Lo laughed when told of Mr. Trump’s comment. He made clear that he had not forgotten being sued for $1 billion.</span><br>
<span>“Well, that’s him,” Mr. Lo said. “To file a lawsuit is nothing. It’s just like having lunch.”</span><br>
</p><p><b>朱卉菲: </b><br>
<span>同一件事, 当年报道</span><br>
<span>How the Chengs Finessed Trump                                                      By EDWARD A. GARGANJULY 15, 1994                                                            </span><br>
<span>                                          https://s1.nyt.com/timesmachine/pages/1/1994/07/15/001619_360W.png                                                                              View page in TimesMachine                  </span><br>
<span>                   July 15, 1994, Page 00001Buy Reprints The New York Times Archives      </span><br>
<span>    It may be one of the last big real estate deals in New York City, but to Henry Cheng, Riverside South, the multibillion-dollar joint venture that could transform Manhattan's largest buildable waterfront land into a community of 16 largely upscale apartment towers along with shops and parks, is just another development.</span><br>
<span>"In Hong Kong, China, we've done bigger projects than this, much bigger," said Mr. Cheng, a man parsimonious with words. He and his father, Cheng Yu-tong, have built one of Hong Kong's biggest global property and project development conglomerates, with substantial holdings stretching across Asia and into the United States.</span><br>
<span>For the Chengs, Donald J. Trump was not a rival but merely a target of opportunity. Mr. Trump first sketched out the plan for developing the 75-acre site along the Hudson River, blocks from Lincoln Center, but his recent financial problems allowed the Hong Kong group to buy his $250 million debt on the land for a bargain price of some $90 million and take over Riverside South.</span><br>
<span>Construction could start within a year, and Mr. Trump will share in the profits. But people familiar with the Chengs' operations agree that they, not Mr. Trump, will call the shots.</span><br>
<span>For the Chengs, one of Hong Kong's richest families, with a net worth reportedly about $3.3 billion, the Manhattan project is a minuscule part of their investments, but it is attractive.</span><br>
<span>"We think it is a very good investment opportunity," the 47-year-old Mr. Cheng said in an interview in his unostentatious office here. "We think the United States economy has started to pick up.""New York is a very slow growth market," he added. "But we believe it has already bottomed out, so we are happy about the existing market. New York is still one of the major cities in the world."</span><br>
<span>With land here virtually exhausted, and with extensive interests across Asia, including China, the Chengs have been on the lookout for opportunities in the United States for some time, according to Paul Y. L. Tong, the general manager of the New World Development Company, the centerpiece of the Cheng empire.</span><br>
<span>"Previously we have been buying bricks and mortar," Mr. Tong said, referring to the group's vast chain of hotels and residential apartments in the United States, including the upscale Renaissance hotels. "We feel that perhaps this is the right time to do development. We had to look for a partner because we don't know the local situation."</span><br>
<span>Because New World does not invest directly in real estate outside Asia, Henry Cheng assembled a consortium of investors to complete the Riverside South deal. "The shareholders are a group of our good friends that got together," Mr.Cheng said. "We bought the debt at a discount." The group also bought the company that owns title to the site."A project of that size is really pin money for these guys," said David Faulkner, a partner at Brooke Hillier Parker, an international property concern with offices here.</span><br>
<span>How Henry Cheng's father, Cheng Yu-tong, ascended to the pinnacle of economic power is a familiar tale among the colony's wealthiest families. From his first job, as an apprentice in the Chow Tai Fook jewelry store at the age of 14, he rose quickly to build the largest jewelry chain in Hong Kong. Then he assembleda diversified empire of land, hotels, telecommunications, power projects and roads that branched in stages into China and the rest of Asia.</span><br>
<span>Today, New World, a publicly traded company which the elder Mr. Cheng controls with 35 percent of the stock, has a market capitalization of about $5.8 billion, making it one of Hong Kong's blue chip companies. CTF, as the Chow Tai Fook chain is known, functions as his wholly owned company, and holds his 35 percent share in New World.Now 69, Mr. Cheng has built a reputation for hard work and disciplined deal-making. He and his son share adjoining offices in an undistinguished office tower in the central business district, offices that are notable for the lack of opulence so central to Mr. Trump's public image.</span><br>
<span>Ever the businessman, Mr. Cheng moved swiftly to build his company's holdings in China in the wake of the June 1989 Tiananmen Square massacre, at a time when many investors held back, hurting China's world trade.</span><br>
<span>He went to school with Li Ziliu, now the mayor of Guangzhou, where New World has major projects. But Mr. Cheng insists that he has never exploited valuable friendships. "Everything must follow the right way," he told The South China Morning Post last year in one of his rare interviews. "I don't like doing things through the back door." Owner of Ramada HotelsNew World is perhaps the biggest hotel operator in Hong Kong, with two of the colony's best, the Regent and the Grand Hyatt. The company also owns Ramada International Hotels and Resorts in the United States, a concern that includes 45 Renaissance hotels, with one in New York City, and the Stouffer hotel chain. New World also owns hotels in China, Macao, Australia and the Bahamas, and over the next few years is planning new hotels in Taipei, Bangkok, Phuket, Kuala Lumpur, Kota Kinabalu, Manila and Ho Chi Minh City.According to Mr. Faulkner, New World's diversification represents much of its strength. New World has major stakes in container terminals and tunnels, owns one of Hong Kong's four fixed-line telephone licenses and is developing road projects in the New Territories, the stretch of the colony that runs to the border with China. The company also has interests in infrastructure projects in China, including power, water plants and the ring road in Guangzhou.Central to the Chengs' investment strategy has been the building up of New World's land banks. While his start in the property business focused on Hong Kong, where he controls about 12 million square feet, he has in recent years acquired far more property in China, where New World owns around 20 million square feet of space, analysts here say."China of course is the flavor of the month, but they're not putting all their eggs in the China basket, particularly because the economy there is having a bumpy landing," Mr. Faulkner said. "The very large groups have outgrown Hong Kong."</span><br>
<span>Still, Henry Cheng said that New World intended to put about one-quarter of its assets in China. "We believe in China in the long term," he said. Among the group's recent projects is a $580 million coal-fired power plant in neighboring Guangdong Province. High-Tech Buildings</span><br>
<span>Joining Mr. Cheng in the Riverside South project is Vincent Lo, the chairman of the Shui On Group, one of the territory's largest construction concerns. Mr.Lo's group is best known for its modern buildings, particularly Citibank Plaza.With its advanced equipment for teleconferences, sophisticated power management and elevators that never leave patrons waiting more than 15 seconds, Citibank Plaza is considered the most high-tech building in Hong Kong.Franklin Lam, a property analyst at Salomon Brothers, said it was also outstanding for what is known in Chinese as Feng-shui -- a traditional practice of determining a building's auspicious setting, orientation and furnishing. Feng-shui is important even to very Westernized Hong Kong builders.Mr. Trump first came to the attention of the Chengs through their American investment arm, Polylinks International Ltd., Mr. Tong said. "Then three months ago, we knew that the bank was prepared to sell his paper," he said, referring to the $250 million held by Chase Manhattan Bank. "Through a couple of agents, we started looking seriously."Neither Mr. Tong nor Henry Cheng would discuss details of the Chengs' arrangement with Mr. Trump, or describe the elder Mr. Cheng's involvment. But, as to the latter, analysts here have no doubts."Cheng Yu-tung is a much richer man than Donald Trump ever was," said Clive Wheedon, a director at Asia Equity Ltd. "I don't believe any of these guys would ever allow a Westerner to drive one of these deals. Most of them regard the Western entrepreneurs as being pretty sleepy. They're not wrong about that."</span><br>
</p><p><b>rhocas: </b><br>
<span>有啥用</span><br>
<span>觉得川普傻逼的不会改变观点</span><br>
<span>川粉也不会改变观点</span><br>
<span>浪费时间啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>雨井绫: </b><br>
<span>什么，川伟人的黑历史还用得着特意找？</span><br>
</p><p><b>朱卉菲: </b><br>
<span>还是同一件事, 当年报道</span><br>
<span>Hong Kong Investors Finance a Trump Project</span><br>
<span>By DAVID W. DUNLAPJULY 1, 1994</span><br>
<span>A group of Hong Kong investors stepped in yesterday with the money that Donald J. Trump needs to begin building the first towers of Riverside South, a project that could profoundly alter the Upper West Side of Manhattan by creating homes for thousands of wealthy residents on what is now an abandoned riverfrontrail yard.Construction could start within a year, Mr. Trump said yesterday after he signed a financing deal and joint-venture agreement with a consortium that includes the New World Development Company Ltd., headed by Y. T. Cheng and his son, Henry, and the Shui On Group Ltd., headed by Vincent Lo.Now, we're at the really productive level," Mr. Trump said, 10 years afterhe took control of the 75-acre site along the Hudson River, from 59th to 72d Street.The new "multi-billion-dollar joint venture" -- the partners would be no more specific about the amounts of money involved -- represents a high-profile plunge into the New York market by Hong Kong investors."We've traveled to various cities," said Daniel K. S. Yiu, president of Polylinks International Ltd. of Hong Kong, which advises private and public companies, including New World. "With all the potential, the people, the demographics, we really think that New York can't be substituted."      Continue reading the main story    </span><br>
<span>            Their arrival is not only crucial for Mr. Trump, who has been struggling to emerge from millions of dollars of debt, but is also a "solid vote of confidence in New York City," Mayor Rudolph W. Giuliani said."Development of Riverside South will mean the creation of thousands of construction jobs at a time when that industry is at nearly 50 percent unemployment," Mr. Giuliani said in a statement released by his press office. "It will create thousands of permanent jobs and will brings hundreds of millions of dollars in sales and other tax revenues to the city."Mr. Trump and his new partners said no final decision had been made on whichparcels would be developed first, or how many. For now, they said, they are contemplating a mix of rental buildings and one condominium tower for the opening phase.Under plans approved by city officials in 1992, there may ultimately be 5,700 apartments in 16 towers. At least 12 percent of the housing must be set aside for moderate- and low-income residents. There would be 1.8 million square feet of commercial space at the southern end of the site. A waterfront park would bebuilt in phases, along with construction of the towers."We have no intention whatsoever of changing the original plans," Mr. Yiu said.Money Talks, but QuietlyThe developers would not disclose anything about the amounts of money involved in yesterday's deal, citing a confidentiality agreement with the ChaseManhattan Bank, which holds the mortgage on the property. Mr. Trump would say only, "Essentially the mortgage has been purchased by this group, so we don't have any debt."Mr. Yiu said the Polylinks group was formed a little over a year ago to lookfor investment opportunities in the United States, particularly in New York, San Francisco and Honolulu. New World bought the Renaissance hotel chain in 1989 and the Stouffer hotel chain last year."We put more of a focus on New York," Mr. Yiu said. He said Polylinks has already purchased large blocks of condominium apartments in Park Avenue Court, at Lexington Avenue and 86th Street, and the Horizon, at First Avenue and 37th Street.Because of the size of Riverside South, Polylinks sought other investors as well, including Shui On, a diversified company involved in hotels, constructionand development; the Edward Wong Group, and the Far Eastern Consortium Ltd., whose holdings include the Warwick Hotel, at Avenue of the Americas and 54th Street.</span><br>
<span>Frankie Y. L. Wong, a group managing director of Shui On, attended yesterday's signing, along with Mr. Yiu. Afterward, he said: "New York is coming out of the recession. So is the United States. We see a big potential for property development."When asked what attracted Shui On to Riverside South, Mr. Wong simply pointed across the room to Mr. Trump. "You see him there," he said.But Mr. Wong also said the sheer size of Riverside South made it unusual. "You don't find such large-scale projects easily in New York or in the United States," he said.Until the arrival of the Hong Kong investors, it was not exactly clear how Mr. Trump would realize his $3 billion vision for the old Penn Yards site, given the debt he was carrying.But yesterday, he said he was "just about finished" retiring that debt, crediting in part the income from his Atlantic City casinos and hotels, which he said "have broken every record" in the last two years.For Riverside South, Mr. Trump and his partners may take advantage of the "80-20" mixed-income housing program. Tax-exempt bonds are available to financeprojects in which 20 percent of the units are set aside for lower-income tenants, with the other 80 percent available at market rates.Mr. Trump's original plan for the site was something far grander: Trump City, which was to have had 7,600 apartments, a regional shopping mall and the tallest building in the world.This highly unpopular proposal was withdrawn in 1991, after Mr. Trump entered into an unusual alliance with several civic, neighborhood and environmental groups, including the Municipal Art Society and the Parks Council: the very people he had been battling over Trump City. Under the name Riverside South Planning Corporation, this alliance devised the new plan.Although Riverside South was opposed by the local community board and the local Councilwoman, Ronnie M. Eldridge, it was approved by Borough President Ruth W. Messinger and the City Planning Commission. It passed the City Council in December 1992.The executive director of the Parks Council, Linda Davidoff, said about yesterday's deal: "The financial wizardry involved is beyond my ken. But the net result -- that an investor is prepared to build -- is thrilling and a great step forward in building a new and marvelous waterfront on the West Side of Manhattan."There are still many critics of the project. Among their concerns is that Riverside South would add to the already overtaxed North River Sewage TreatmentPlant in Harlem. A group led by the Coalition for a Livable West Side has filedsuit in Federal court seeking to prevent further hookups to the North River sewage treatment plant and another one on Wards Island.Mr. Yiu said yesterday that the investors had reached "a certain comfort level that this issue can be resolved over time as the project moves along."Mr. Wong added that "city officials have already done a lot to reduce the flow, so there is a lot of capacity."</span><br>
</p><p><b>kamarus: </b><br>
<span>啥，美国还有政客没黑历史的？</span><br>
</p><p><b>cxn: </b><br>
<span>各国领导人的黑历史都不少，关键是谁信</span><br>
</p><p><b>QShen: </b><br>
<span>这，本来都是英文了，阅读起来已经有一定障碍了，排版也没有修一修，读起来更费劲了……</span><br>
</p><p><b>Archlich: </b><br>
<span>QShen 发表于 2019-5-16 23:02</span><br>
<span>这，本来都是英文了，阅读起来已经有一定障碍了，排版也没有修一修，读起来更费劲了…… ...</span><br>
<span>你只要读懂三个字就行了：New York Times</span><br>
<span>其实这种把川表现为无能狂怒的小丑的描述我也觉得没什么意思。人家最后还是坐上了能让他对所有人指手画脚的位置嘛。</span><br>
</p><p><b>ykyin09: </b><br>
<span>看多了神皇的推，现在这些正经的长文已经没耐心看了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>山竹罐头: </b><br>
<span>这文章不就是典型的历史虚无主义嘛</span><br>
</p><p><b>朱卉菲: </b><br>
<span>山竹罐头 发表于 2019-5-17 00:02</span><br>
<span>这文章不就是典型的历史虚无主义嘛</span><br>
<span>不尽然, 翻翻旧账而已</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1832041[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
