<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>《好莱坞报道者》:《TLOU2》在叙事艺术上开始超越电影</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>《好莱坞报道者》:《TLOU2》在叙事艺术上开始超越电影</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 11:49:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>《好莱坞报道者》:《TLOU2》在叙事艺术上开始超越电影[50-100]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1941758-1-1.html</link>
      <description>《好莱坞报道者》:《TLOU2》在叙事艺术上开始超越电影&#13;
'The Last of Us Part II': Game Review12:01 AM PDT 6/12/2020 by Brittany Vincent
&#13;
[*] FACEBOOK
&#13;
[*] TWITTER
&#13;
[*] EMAIL ME
&#13;
https://archive.md/vE0v7/aa99025465f6c238ea86e8a3eb34dea2e83491b4.jpgCourtesy of Sony
&#13;
'The Last of Us Part II'
&#13;
THE BOTTOM LINEA beautifully — and even gruesomely — crafted pinnacle of what video games can be.  TWITTER
&#13;
Naughty Dog and Sony deliver the next installment of the thrilling post-apocalyptic action-adventure franchise.How far would you go to seek revenge on those who wronged you? Would you let a maddening drive for retribution fester until it plagued your every waking thought? Could you let it go, and allow the cooling salve of sanity return you to your senses?
&#13;
The Last of Us Part II, the next installment in Naughty Dog’s thrilling post-apocalyptic action-adventure franchise, attempts to answer these questions in an alarmingly bleak yet refreshingly realistic manner. The journey picks up five years after the conclusion of the first game, which originally debuted on PlayStation 3 in 2013. 
&#13;
The ballad of the haggard, paternal Joel and plucky, teenage Ellie continues as the pair attempt to make a new life for themselves. Most of the world’s population was wiped out years earlier by the spread of a mutated strain of the Cordyceps fungus. It ripped through the world like wildfire, turning most of humanity into zombie-like creatures known as the Infected. 
&#13;
Joel and Ellie now find themselves in Jackson City, Wyoming, at a settlement owned by Joel’s estranged brother, Tommy. Life is as peaceful as it can be in Jackson, until a traumatic event threatens to shatter everything Joel and Ellie hold dear. Pushed to her limits, Ellie vows to make those responsible pay. With the aid of those close to her, she makes the snap decision to seek an eye for an eye in this tale of revenge.
&#13;
Ellie, now 19, is an unrepentant assailant, brimming with white-hot rage and perpetually on the brink of boiling over. Even so, this hostility can barely mask the agony she's clearly feeling inside. Her maelstrom of emotion makes for an **-laden trip from place to place as she seeks out anyone she believes is responsible for the injustice she’s suffered, systematically eliminating anyone in the way and moving ever forward on her quest to rain hellfire down on some very unlucky individuals.
&#13;
But despite her propensity to shoot first and ask questions later, Ellie isn't remorseless. It's clear from her actions that many of those who fall to the barrel of her gun will undoubtedly be burned into her memory for the rest of her days. Still, she presses on. She has to — if not her, then who?
&#13;
Ellie won’t be able to achieve her goal without a lot of resistance, though. Warring factions such as the WLF (Washington Liberation Front) and the Scars (Seraphites) are waiting around every corner, and they don't take kindly to strangers. They'll also kill without a second thought, but there's a certain humanity to them that you don't find in most other games. 
&#13;
When they get in the way, the only path forward is through them via lengthy, brutal combat scenes. The stop-and-pop gunplay of games like Uncharted is present here, but it’s more polished than ever. It feels effortless in a way that transforms those endless segments from prior Naughty Dog games, and even the first The Last of Us, into something much more exciting. There’s also the stealth option — Ellie can simply use her listening ability to concentrate and seek out enemies that make noise around her. 
&#13;
Each and every human Ellie dispatches feels like one more meaningful life lost. It's easy to steel yourself and become a mostly numb killing machine for the sake of the game, but the terrifyingly human screams that permeate the sound of gunfire won't let you. As corpses pile up on the battlefield, so do the pools of blood that blossom beneath those Ellie has downed. 
&#13;
You remember each one of them, each of their cries for help, and each of their companions' tortured screams as they realize allies — friends and even family — have been murdered. It's tough to watch the beloved dogs that patrol alongside Ellie’s enemies rush toward her because they, too, must be put down. 
&#13;
The Last of Us Part II manages to touch a nerve, accomplishing something shocking: getting you to care about the seemingly endless hordes of "bad guys" out to get you. They all had names. They had families. They had lives. Is what Ellie’s after really worth the violence she leaves in her wake? These are questions you have to ask yourself as you progress.
&#13;
Normal humans aren't the only targets Ellie comes face to face with. The Infected were human once, too, but now they're mere shells of their former selves. They come in a variety of forms, such as “Clickers” and the mostly blind, lumbering behemoths with super strength. If you don't take care of them quickly, you’re in for disaster — and sometimes, instant death. Luckily, there are a wide variety of weapons with which Ellie can destroy the monsters, including a pistol, bow and shotgun. 
&#13;
There’s more to the journey than combat. Exploration is encouraged and rewarded. In addition to optional locations to investigate for cool pop culture references — and even opportunities for Ellie to play guitar, just like she learned from Joel — there's a lengthy list of collectibles to discover as well, from trading cards and notes to codes that open safes containing goodies to add to Ellie's stores. You can never have too much ammo, after all.
&#13;
That’s right — supplies are limited, of course, as this is the post-apocalypse. Thankfully, Ellie is handy with materials found throughout the land. She can craft items such as med kits, Molotov cocktails and even improvised suppressors for weapons she picks up while on her mission. This can be done anywhere on the field, even while Ellie is prone, hiding in the tall grass. Ellie can also stop at workbenches scattered throughout the abandoned storefronts and homes of the post-Clicker world, where she can apply weapon upgrades. 
&#13;
There’s a lot of death in store for players as well, and it comes swiftly and without warning. Several Clicker assaults result in instant kills, meaning you’ll have to be quicker on the draw than ever before. At any moment, one of the monsters could saunter up behind Ellie and tear her throat out, only a brief flash of her fate shown before a quick fade to black. 
&#13;
But you can press on, and press on you will. Because the story beats in The Last of Us Part II are cohesive in a way that echo some of the best TV shows of the past decade. There isn't a single thread untouched by the end, and the entire experience is riddled with lore-building notes, photographs, and other pieces of information that serve to further enrich the world. 
&#13;
As the narrative unfolds, it feels like binge-watching an expertly written drama punctuated by interactive shootouts. The heartbreak is just as real and the losses just as painful. If you’ve followed Joel and Ellie since the beginning, the highs and lows will be even more personal. That’s the mark of excellent media, though. It transcends the boundaries of fiction and becomes a story in which you could see yourself. And at the end of it all, even when faced with characters and situations you may not agree with, you can’t help but come out of the experience with a sense of compassion, even toward those responsible for setting Ellie on her path of destruction.
&#13;
There's no sugar-coating it: The Last of Us Part II is as raw as games come, with one foot firmly entrenched within the realm of agonizingly realistic video game conventions and Hollywood blockbusters. At times, the lines blur in such a way that, to anyone casually observing, it seems almost more like a film than anything you’d play on a console. Therein lies its magic. 
&#13;
Beautifully and even gruesomely crafted, The Last of Us Part II represents the pinnacle of what video games can be. It’s an unflinching, impeccable example of how the medium can be used to propel the art form forward by employing the same visceral storytelling techniques and disturbing imagery you’d see from Oscar-nominated films. Critics have been asking when video games would “grow up” for years. The real question is this: when will films catch up with video games like The Last of Us Part II?</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>S.I.R: </b><br>
<span>lemon鱿鱼 发表于 2020-6-15 14:22</span><br>
<span>叙事不再是艺术，现在只是技术</span><br>
<span>当然我也很期待看到tlou2能把叙事重新拔高到艺术这个层次</span><br>
<span>我也认为叙事是技术，但是游戏业普遍还在蹒跚学步状态。至于是不是艺术，只有技术达标了才有可能。</span><br>
</p><p><b>吃货红毛: </b><br>
<span>前不是还有大表哥2吗 人家那演出什么的也拉满了啊 意思是玩过大表哥2之后 还是觉得tlou2高出一大截吗……</span><br>
</p><p><b>S.I.R: </b><br>
<span>其实我认为，对于大部分媒体人和游戏主播来说。一款挑战行业底限或是巅峰的产品，是一定会得到得分加权的。原因很简单，这些人每天的工作就在不断地玩游戏和了解游戏，总体来说肯定一年到头没几个游戏是能真正让人感觉“这个不一样”的，早就审美疲劳了。无论tlou2的体验到底如何，只要是他们没有体验过的，产业没人敢做的，就会得到相当的加权，大表哥2为什么很多人说什么都好就是不好玩，但是在媒体那里就是一众100分。其实就是因为他们知道大表哥2这样的产品，是一种冲击巅峰的挑战，要再多也没有了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>lemon鱿鱼: </b><br>
<span>S.I.R 发表于 2020-6-15 14:55</span><br>
<span>其实我认为，对于大部分媒体人和游戏主播来说。一款挑战行业底限或是巅峰的产品，是一定会得到得分加权的。 ...</span><br>
<span>死亡搁浅咋算</span><br>
</p><p><b>黑夜守望者: </b><br>
<span>clover293 发表于 2020-6-15 13:58</span><br>
<span>只有日本ign敢，fami打了39分估计也是害怕</span><br>
<span>fami评分也出来了吗，edge也是9分。不行，有内味了</span><br>
</p><p><b>S.I.R: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 S.I.R 于 2020-6-15 15:05 编辑 </span><br>
<span>lemon鱿鱼 发表于 2020-6-15 14:57</span><br>
<span>死亡搁浅咋算</span><br>
<span>死亡搁浅真的挑战了什么东西吗。其实只是包装精美的独立游戏概念。有一套奇特的机制，但不会让你感觉wow，这个其中包含了技术或设计或题材敢为天下先的意味。你可以感觉好玩，但就像很多独立创新游戏你也可以觉得好玩一样。</span><br>
</p><p><b>hshiki: </b><br>
<span>RDR2不也就是包装更精美的RDR1吗，有啥wow的，R星创造一个西部世界的壮举早在RDR1里做到了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>yxzdr: </b><br>
<span>虽然预购了，但还是很悲观，从战神我就知道我跟这帮游戏媒体的剧情口味完全不在一条线上，希望别给我啥不爽的体验。</span><br>
</p><p><b>Redis: </b><br>
<span>jockeyjoestar 发表于 2020-6-15 10:07</span><br>
<span>游戏超越电影不是理所应当的吗，现在电影的体裁就很僵硬，而游戏没有时长限制，很多游戏玩家可以控制剧情的 ...</span><br>
<span>电影已经很僵化了</span><br>
<span>就算是好莱坞，这几年最好的故事也不在电影里面</span><br>
</p><p><b>Redis: </b><br>
<span>RookieTnT 发表于 2020-6-15 12:24</span><br>
<span>《疯狂的麦克斯》系列等影片的导演乔治·米勒是业界传奇人物之一，也是被小岛秀夫视为精神导师的人。日前他 ...</span><br>
<span>岛哥哥连英语都不会，写得出啥好剧本</span><br>
<span>而且岛哥哥基本没在米国生活过吧，他对于米国的很多认知来源于其他文艺作品，凑合起来怎么说呢，大概就是我国人看功夫熊猫，日本人玩儿阴阳师的感觉。就是有些地方不自然。</span><br>
</p><p><b>aceback: </b><br>
<span>芷雅居 发表于 2020-6-15 09:13</span><br>
<span>万般赞美也抵不过婆罗门一句“剧情一般，游戏性拉跨，我get不到点”</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能手机投票的 Stage ...</span><br>
<span>“剧情很容易猜到，不理解为什么这么多人吹”</span><br>
</p><p><b>撸一记: </b><br>
<span>电影＝好莱坞？这是什么自我中心的逻辑</span><br>
</p><p><b>海拉尔的风: </b><br>
<span>S.I.R 发表于 2020-06-15 12:32:49</span><br>
<span>tlou2可以单设置资源多少。我看到有日本人说把其它拉到最难然后资源最大应该最好玩。 ...原来如此，我按照一代想当然了</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>SaGaReuniverSE: </b><br>
<span>lemon鱿鱼 发表于 2020-6-15 14:57</span><br>
<span>死亡搁浅咋算</span><br>
<span>恭喜你发现了一枚gk</span><br>
</p><p><b>看别人玩游戏: </b><br>
<span>有种“王婆卖瓜，自卖自夸”的感觉…</span><br>
</p><p><b>小命4: </b><br>
<span>Redis 发表于 2020-6-15 15:15</span><br>
<span> 岛哥哥连英语都不会，写得出啥好剧本 而且岛哥哥基本没在米国生活过吧，他对于米国的很多认知来源于其他 ...</span><br>
<span>不会英语不至于吧，不然他怎么和他那些朋友交流，手语吗</span><br>
</p><p><b>Zuranium: </b><br>
<span>游戏超越电影是不可能的，但是商业游戏超越商业电影是已经在路上了</span><br>
</p><p><b>wbtsy: </b><br>
<span>小命4 发表于 2020-6-15 21:44</span><br>
<span>不会英语不至于吧，不然他怎么和他那些朋友交流，手语吗</span><br>
<span>只要有人脉和资源，交流不一定需要语言有多好。</span><br>
<span>反正他英语应该一般版。</span><br>
<span>他的各种采访都是说日语，然后有人翻译。2016年TGA上获奖感言，只能磕磕巴巴憋几句 Love you。</span><br>
</p><p><b>归家那单车小径: </b><br>
<span>我这两年最喜欢的娱乐项目就是看媒体钦点游戏翻车了</span><br>
</p><p><b>十字骷髅高达: </b><br>
<span>继续吹，我在听</span><br>
</p><p><b>yym: </b><br>
<span>真逗，一部作品超越一个媒介，作品只能超越作品，tlou2是超了哪部电影啊，房间还是教父？</span><br>
</p><p><b>飞姆托: </b><br>
<span>aceback 发表于 2020-06-15 15:23:58</span><br>
<span>“剧情很容易猜到，不理解为什么这么多人吹”“吹的是叙事手法又不是吹剧情，你们怎么这么多事”</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>acejoe: </b><br>
<span>S.I.R 发表于 2020-6-15 12:28</span><br>
<span>游戏业因为上限高所以对编剧的要求比电影工业本质要更高。</span><br>
<span>但现实是游戏业的编剧水平普遍远不如电影工业， ...</span><br>
<span>编剧要求反而低，因为游戏上限高在体验，体验超出电影的关键是互动。</span><br>
<span>所以不需要编剧去处理“如何合理展示信息”这个相当重要的问题，让角色互动就行了，怎么互动交给导演。</span><br>
<span>角色和台词也是，潜台词和角色行为等等这些细节，互动替代了大部分。</span><br>
</p><p><b>我不是曾小贤: </b><br>
<span>S.I.R 发表于 2020-06-15 12:32:49</span><br>
<span>tlou2可以单设置资源多少。我看到有日本人说把其它拉到最难然后资源最大应该最好玩。 ...感觉这才比较像个样子嘛</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>eulereld: </b><br>
<span>我開始期待解鎖後的泥潭了哈哈哈哈哈</span><br>
</p><p><b>dsaaa: </b><br>
<span>估计还是动作声音比较拟真吧。之前不是有个新闻说瞎子都能通关嘛</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能手机投票的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>李白白: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 李白白 于 2020-6-16 17:17 编辑 </span><br>
<span>芷雅居 发表于 2020-6-15 09:13</span><br>
<span>万般赞美也抵不过婆罗门一句“剧情一般，游戏性拉跨，我get不到点”</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能手机投票的 Stage ...</span><br>
<span>呵呵，希望你玩到亲手操作一个胳膊比你大腿都粗的跨跨用高尔夫球棒敲碎乔尔头时候，你能GET剧情的升华</span><br>
<span>涉及剧透，反白了，但估计你们真玩到这段时候就会在想“老子当初为什么没看剧透，看了我还花钱买这JB玩意”，</span><br>
<span>反正我的铁盒预购是退了，我现在就想看这**游戏销量暴死</span><br>
</p><p><b>dumplingpro: </b><br>
<span>S.I.R 发表于 2020-6-15 14:55</span><br>
<span>其实我认为，对于大部分媒体人和游戏主播来说。一款挑战行业底限或是巅峰的产品，是一定会得到得分加权的。 ...</span><br>
<span>突然想到，那半条命VR这种VR叙事算啥……</span><br>
<span>都脱离屏幕了，算是挑战现有技术下，沉浸感的极限了</span><br>
</p><p><b>superlink: </b><br>
<span>吹叙事不如吹十三机兵，我到想看看出美版了，mc给几分</span><br>
</p><p><b>dumplingpro: </b><br>
<span>acejoe 发表于 2020-6-16 00:02</span><br>
<span>编剧要求反而低，因为游戏上限高在体验，体验超出电影的关键是互动。</span><br>
<span>所以不需要编剧去处理“如何合理展 ...</span><br>
<span>其实我在想，半条命VR算啥……</span><br>
<span>VR互动方式是电影和传统游戏都没有的……</span><br>
</p><p><b>lzpandakun: </b><br>
<span>塞钱不少啊</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>比较坐骑: </b><br>
<span>怎么感觉黑豹的路线那么像呢</span><br>
</p><p><b>S.I.R: </b><br>
<span>dumplingpro 发表于 2020-6-16 17:23</span><br>
<span>突然想到，那半条命VR这种VR叙事算啥……</span><br>
<span>都脱离屏幕了，算是挑战现有技术下，沉浸感的极限了 ...</span><br>
<span>半条命VR我没玩过，没法具体谈，但分也不低啊。</span><br>
</p><p><b>谢同学: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 谢同学 于 2020-6-16 20:20 编辑 </span><br>
<span>编辑了</span><br>
</p><p><b>kelveen: </b><br>
<span>谢同学 发表于 2020-6-16 18:26</span><br>
<span>为什么你会知道剧情？</span><br>
<span>引用会去反白</span><br>
<span>他说的那段，很早就有泄露的实机视频。</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 samsung SM-G9750, Android 10上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.2.2.1</span><br>
</p><p><b>聚散浮云: </b><br>
<span>游戏为什么要和电影比？游戏有自己的叙事风格手法，也应该有自己的评价标准。</span><br>
<span>即使是游戏中播片的部分也不应该直接拿来和电影比，和同类游戏中的播片比还差不多。</span><br>
</p><p><b>旺角卡门: </b><br>
<span>所以好莱坞提名电影的名字可以说一下吗？这样很难做横向比较欸</span><br>
</p><p><b>junqqq999: </b><br>
<span>要是看过大宝贝的表演，ps时代的表演就超电影了~~~~</span><br>
</p><p><b>penggelie111: </b><br>
<span>小命4 发表于 2020-6-15 21:44</span><br>
<span>不会英语不至于吧，不然他怎么和他那些朋友交流，手语吗</span><br>
<span>岛哥哥连获奖感言这种可以背诵的东西都需要翻译，英语水平还是算了吧。朋友嘛，正所谓富在深山有远亲</span><br>
</p><p><b>000000: </b><br>
<span>dumplingpro 发表于 2020-6-16 17:25</span><br>
<span>其实我在想，半条命VR算啥……</span><br>
<span>VR互动方式是电影和传统游戏都没有的…… ...</span><br>
<span>半条命VR实际玩起来比3A游戏更有电影镜头，阀门的运镜做得非常传统</span><br>
<span>100%超越电影，没人吹纯粹是伪玩家太多，连VR设备都不愿意掏钱买</span><br>
<span>扼腕惋惜一下</span><br>
</p><p><b>dumplingpro: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 dumplingpro 于 2020-6-17 12:46 编辑 </span><br>
<span>000000 发表于 2020-6-17 12:32</span><br>
<span>半条命VR实际玩起来比3A游戏更有电影镜头，阀门的运镜做得非常传统</span><br>
<span>100%超越电影，没人吹纯粹是伪玩家太 ...</span><br>
<span>应该说VR是玩家自己控制镜头，所以没法运镜，而是通过引导吸引玩家注意力，或者用常识引导玩家注意力，属于新玩法了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>芷雅居: </b><br>
<span>penggelie111 发表于 2020-6-17 11:02</span><br>
<span>岛哥哥连获奖感言这种可以背诵的东西都需要翻译，英语水平还是算了吧。朋友嘛，正所谓富在深山有远亲 ...</span><br>
<span>TGA拿奖的日本人不是都说日语</span><br>
</p><p><b>SICP: </b><br>
<span>芷雅居 发表于 2020-6-17 17:34</span><br>
<span>TGA拿奖的日本人不是都说日语</span><br>
<span>“剧情一般，游戏性拉跨，我get不到点”</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1941758[50-100]</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>《好莱坞报道者》:《TLOU2》在叙事艺术上开始超越电影[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1941758-1-1.html</link>
      <description>《好莱坞报道者》:《TLOU2》在叙事艺术上开始超越电影&#13;
'The Last of Us Part II': Game Review12:01 AM PDT 6/12/2020 by Brittany Vincent
&#13;
[*] FACEBOOK
&#13;
[*] TWITTER
&#13;
[*] EMAIL ME
&#13;
https://archive.md/vE0v7/aa99025465f6c238ea86e8a3eb34dea2e83491b4.jpgCourtesy of Sony
&#13;
'The Last of Us Part II'
&#13;
THE BOTTOM LINEA beautifully — and even gruesomely — crafted pinnacle of what video games can be.  TWITTER
&#13;
Naughty Dog and Sony deliver the next installment of the thrilling post-apocalyptic action-adventure franchise.How far would you go to seek revenge on those who wronged you? Would you let a maddening drive for retribution fester until it plagued your every waking thought? Could you let it go, and allow the cooling salve of sanity return you to your senses?
&#13;
The Last of Us Part II, the next installment in Naughty Dog’s thrilling post-apocalyptic action-adventure franchise, attempts to answer these questions in an alarmingly bleak yet refreshingly realistic manner. The journey picks up five years after the conclusion of the first game, which originally debuted on PlayStation 3 in 2013. 
&#13;
The ballad of the haggard, paternal Joel and plucky, teenage Ellie continues as the pair attempt to make a new life for themselves. Most of the world’s population was wiped out years earlier by the spread of a mutated strain of the Cordyceps fungus. It ripped through the world like wildfire, turning most of humanity into zombie-like creatures known as the Infected. 
&#13;
Joel and Ellie now find themselves in Jackson City, Wyoming, at a settlement owned by Joel’s estranged brother, Tommy. Life is as peaceful as it can be in Jackson, until a traumatic event threatens to shatter everything Joel and Ellie hold dear. Pushed to her limits, Ellie vows to make those responsible pay. With the aid of those close to her, she makes the snap decision to seek an eye for an eye in this tale of revenge.
&#13;
Ellie, now 19, is an unrepentant assailant, brimming with white-hot rage and perpetually on the brink of boiling over. Even so, this hostility can barely mask the agony she's clearly feeling inside. Her maelstrom of emotion makes for an **-laden trip from place to place as she seeks out anyone she believes is responsible for the injustice she’s suffered, systematically eliminating anyone in the way and moving ever forward on her quest to rain hellfire down on some very unlucky individuals.
&#13;
But despite her propensity to shoot first and ask questions later, Ellie isn't remorseless. It's clear from her actions that many of those who fall to the barrel of her gun will undoubtedly be burned into her memory for the rest of her days. Still, she presses on. She has to — if not her, then who?
&#13;
Ellie won’t be able to achieve her goal without a lot of resistance, though. Warring factions such as the WLF (Washington Liberation Front) and the Scars (Seraphites) are waiting around every corner, and they don't take kindly to strangers. They'll also kill without a second thought, but there's a certain humanity to them that you don't find in most other games. 
&#13;
When they get in the way, the only path forward is through them via lengthy, brutal combat scenes. The stop-and-pop gunplay of games like Uncharted is present here, but it’s more polished than ever. It feels effortless in a way that transforms those endless segments from prior Naughty Dog games, and even the first The Last of Us, into something much more exciting. There’s also the stealth option — Ellie can simply use her listening ability to concentrate and seek out enemies that make noise around her. 
&#13;
Each and every human Ellie dispatches feels like one more meaningful life lost. It's easy to steel yourself and become a mostly numb killing machine for the sake of the game, but the terrifyingly human screams that permeate the sound of gunfire won't let you. As corpses pile up on the battlefield, so do the pools of blood that blossom beneath those Ellie has downed. 
&#13;
You remember each one of them, each of their cries for help, and each of their companions' tortured screams as they realize allies — friends and even family — have been murdered. It's tough to watch the beloved dogs that patrol alongside Ellie’s enemies rush toward her because they, too, must be put down. 
&#13;
The Last of Us Part II manages to touch a nerve, accomplishing something shocking: getting you to care about the seemingly endless hordes of "bad guys" out to get you. They all had names. They had families. They had lives. Is what Ellie’s after really worth the violence she leaves in her wake? These are questions you have to ask yourself as you progress.
&#13;
Normal humans aren't the only targets Ellie comes face to face with. The Infected were human once, too, but now they're mere shells of their former selves. They come in a variety of forms, such as “Clickers” and the mostly blind, lumbering behemoths with super strength. If you don't take care of them quickly, you’re in for disaster — and sometimes, instant death. Luckily, there are a wide variety of weapons with which Ellie can destroy the monsters, including a pistol, bow and shotgun. 
&#13;
There’s more to the journey than combat. Exploration is encouraged and rewarded. In addition to optional locations to investigate for cool pop culture references — and even opportunities for Ellie to play guitar, just like she learned from Joel — there's a lengthy list of collectibles to discover as well, from trading cards and notes to codes that open safes containing goodies to add to Ellie's stores. You can never have too much ammo, after all.
&#13;
That’s right — supplies are limited, of course, as this is the post-apocalypse. Thankfully, Ellie is handy with materials found throughout the land. She can craft items such as med kits, Molotov cocktails and even improvised suppressors for weapons she picks up while on her mission. This can be done anywhere on the field, even while Ellie is prone, hiding in the tall grass. Ellie can also stop at workbenches scattered throughout the abandoned storefronts and homes of the post-Clicker world, where she can apply weapon upgrades. 
&#13;
There’s a lot of death in store for players as well, and it comes swiftly and without warning. Several Clicker assaults result in instant kills, meaning you’ll have to be quicker on the draw than ever before. At any moment, one of the monsters could saunter up behind Ellie and tear her throat out, only a brief flash of her fate shown before a quick fade to black. 
&#13;
But you can press on, and press on you will. Because the story beats in The Last of Us Part II are cohesive in a way that echo some of the best TV shows of the past decade. There isn't a single thread untouched by the end, and the entire experience is riddled with lore-building notes, photographs, and other pieces of information that serve to further enrich the world. 
&#13;
As the narrative unfolds, it feels like binge-watching an expertly written drama punctuated by interactive shootouts. The heartbreak is just as real and the losses just as painful. If you’ve followed Joel and Ellie since the beginning, the highs and lows will be even more personal. That’s the mark of excellent media, though. It transcends the boundaries of fiction and becomes a story in which you could see yourself. And at the end of it all, even when faced with characters and situations you may not agree with, you can’t help but come out of the experience with a sense of compassion, even toward those responsible for setting Ellie on her path of destruction.
&#13;
There's no sugar-coating it: The Last of Us Part II is as raw as games come, with one foot firmly entrenched within the realm of agonizingly realistic video game conventions and Hollywood blockbusters. At times, the lines blur in such a way that, to anyone casually observing, it seems almost more like a film than anything you’d play on a console. Therein lies its magic. 
&#13;
Beautifully and even gruesomely crafted, The Last of Us Part II represents the pinnacle of what video games can be. It’s an unflinching, impeccable example of how the medium can be used to propel the art form forward by employing the same visceral storytelling techniques and disturbing imagery you’d see from Oscar-nominated films. Critics have been asking when video games would “grow up” for years. The real question is this: when will films catch up with video games like The Last of Us Part II?</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>chenzj8309: </b><br>
<span>《好莱坞报道者》:《TLOU2》在叙事艺术上开始超越电影</span><br>
<span>'The Last of Us Part II': Game Review12:01 AM PDT 6/12/2020 by Brittany Vincent</span><br>
<span>[*] FACEBOOK</span><br>
<span>[*] TWITTER</span><br>
<span>[*] EMAIL ME</span><br>
<span>https://archive.md/vE0v7/aa99025465f6c238ea86e8a3eb34dea2e83491b4.jpgCourtesy of Sony</span><br>
<span>'The Last of Us Part II'</span><br>
<span>THE BOTTOM LINEA beautifully — and even gruesomely — crafted pinnacle of what video games can be.  TWITTER</span><br>
<span>Naughty Dog and Sony deliver the next installment of the thrilling post-apocalyptic action-adventure franchise.How far would you go to seek revenge on those who wronged you? Would you let a maddening drive for retribution fester until it plagued your every waking thought? Could you let it go, and allow the cooling salve of sanity return you to your senses?</span><br>
<span>The Last of Us Part II, the next installment in Naughty Dog’s thrilling post-apocalyptic action-adventure franchise, attempts to answer these questions in an alarmingly bleak yet refreshingly realistic manner. The journey picks up five years after the conclusion of the first game, which originally debuted on PlayStation 3 in 2013. </span><br>
<span>The ballad of the haggard, paternal Joel and plucky, teenage Ellie continues as the pair attempt to make a new life for themselves. Most of the world’s population was wiped out years earlier by the spread of a mutated strain of the Cordyceps fungus. It ripped through the world like wildfire, turning most of humanity into zombie-like creatures known as the Infected. </span><br>
<span>Joel and Ellie now find themselves in Jackson City, Wyoming, at a settlement owned by Joel’s estranged brother, Tommy. Life is as peaceful as it can be in Jackson, until a traumatic event threatens to shatter everything Joel and Ellie hold dear. Pushed to her limits, Ellie vows to make those responsible pay. With the aid of those close to her, she makes the snap decision to seek an eye for an eye in this tale of revenge.</span><br>
<span>Ellie, now 19, is an unrepentant assailant, brimming with white-hot rage and perpetually on the brink of boiling over. Even so, this hostility can barely mask the agony she's clearly feeling inside. Her maelstrom of emotion makes for an **-laden trip from place to place as she seeks out anyone she believes is responsible for the injustice she’s suffered, systematically eliminating anyone in the way and moving ever forward on her quest to rain hellfire down on some very unlucky individuals.</span><br>
<span>But despite her propensity to shoot first and ask questions later, Ellie isn't remorseless. It's clear from her actions that many of those who fall to the barrel of her gun will undoubtedly be burned into her memory for the rest of her days. Still, she presses on. She has to — if not her, then who?</span><br>
<span>Ellie won’t be able to achieve her goal without a lot of resistance, though. Warring factions such as the WLF (Washington Liberation Front) and the Scars (Seraphites) are waiting around every corner, and they don't take kindly to strangers. They'll also kill without a second thought, but there's a certain humanity to them that you don't find in most other games. </span><br>
<span>When they get in the way, the only path forward is through them via lengthy, brutal combat scenes. The stop-and-pop gunplay of games like Uncharted is present here, but it’s more polished than ever. It feels effortless in a way that transforms those endless segments from prior Naughty Dog games, and even the first The Last of Us, into something much more exciting. There’s also the stealth option — Ellie can simply use her listening ability to concentrate and seek out enemies that make noise around her. </span><br>
<span>Each and every human Ellie dispatches feels like one more meaningful life lost. It's easy to steel yourself and become a mostly numb killing machine for the sake of the game, but the terrifyingly human screams that permeate the sound of gunfire won't let you. As corpses pile up on the battlefield, so do the pools of blood that blossom beneath those Ellie has downed. </span><br>
<span>You remember each one of them, each of their cries for help, and each of their companions' tortured screams as they realize allies — friends and even family — have been murdered. It's tough to watch the beloved dogs that patrol alongside Ellie’s enemies rush toward her because they, too, must be put down. </span><br>
<span>The Last of Us Part II manages to touch a nerve, accomplishing something shocking: getting you to care about the seemingly endless hordes of "bad guys" out to get you. They all had names. They had families. They had lives. Is what Ellie’s after really worth the violence she leaves in her wake? These are questions you have to ask yourself as you progress.</span><br>
<span>Normal humans aren't the only targets Ellie comes face to face with. The Infected were human once, too, but now they're mere shells of their former selves. They come in a variety of forms, such as “Clickers” and the mostly blind, lumbering behemoths with super strength. If you don't take care of them quickly, you’re in for disaster — and sometimes, instant death. Luckily, there are a wide variety of weapons with which Ellie can destroy the monsters, including a pistol, bow and shotgun. </span><br>
<span>There’s more to the journey than combat. Exploration is encouraged and rewarded. In addition to optional locations to investigate for cool pop culture references — and even opportunities for Ellie to play guitar, just like she learned from Joel — there's a lengthy list of collectibles to discover as well, from trading cards and notes to codes that open safes containing goodies to add to Ellie's stores. You can never have too much ammo, after all.</span><br>
<span>That’s right — supplies are limited, of course, as this is the post-apocalypse. Thankfully, Ellie is handy with materials found throughout the land. She can craft items such as med kits, Molotov cocktails and even improvised suppressors for weapons she picks up while on her mission. This can be done anywhere on the field, even while Ellie is prone, hiding in the tall grass. Ellie can also stop at workbenches scattered throughout the abandoned storefronts and homes of the post-Clicker world, where she can apply weapon upgrades. </span><br>
<span>There’s a lot of death in store for players as well, and it comes swiftly and without warning. Several Clicker assaults result in instant kills, meaning you’ll have to be quicker on the draw than ever before. At any moment, one of the monsters could saunter up behind Ellie and tear her throat out, only a brief flash of her fate shown before a quick fade to black. </span><br>
<span>But you can press on, and press on you will. Because the story beats in The Last of Us Part II are cohesive in a way that echo some of the best TV shows of the past decade. There isn't a single thread untouched by the end, and the entire experience is riddled with lore-building notes, photographs, and other pieces of information that serve to further enrich the world. </span><br>
<span>As the narrative unfolds, it feels like binge-watching an expertly written drama punctuated by interactive shootouts. The heartbreak is just as real and the losses just as painful. If you’ve followed Joel and Ellie since the beginning, the highs and lows will be even more personal. That’s the mark of excellent media, though. It transcends the boundaries of fiction and becomes a story in which you could see yourself. And at the end of it all, even when faced with characters and situations you may not agree with, you can’t help but come out of the experience with a sense of compassion, even toward those responsible for setting Ellie on her path of destruction.</span><br>
<span>There's no sugar-coating it: The Last of Us Part II is as raw as games come, with one foot firmly entrenched within the realm of agonizingly realistic video game conventions and Hollywood blockbusters. At times, the lines blur in such a way that, to anyone casually observing, it seems almost more like a film than anything you’d play on a console. Therein lies its magic. </span><br>
<span>Beautifully and even gruesomely crafted, The Last of Us Part II represents the pinnacle of what video games can be. It’s an unflinching, impeccable example of how the medium can be used to propel the art form forward by employing the same visceral storytelling techniques and disturbing imagery you’d see from Oscar-nominated films. Critics have been asking when video games would “grow up” for years. The real question is this: when will films catch up with video games like The Last of Us Part II?</span><br>
</p><p><b>柰子辟谷: </b><br>
<span>吹过了吹过了影不起影不起</span><br>
<span>我就买了当生化危机玩儿，爱咋黑深残咋黑深残去</span><br>
<span>—— 來自 Xiaomi Redmi Note 9S, Android 10上的 S1Next-鵝版 v2.2.2.1</span><br>
</p><p><b>miu255: </b><br>
<span>叙事艺术和电影有什么关系？好莱坞难道也停工？这么闲还打游戏。</span><br>
</p><p><b>chenzj83: </b><br>
<span>miu255 发表于 2020-6-15 08:01</span><br>
<span>叙事艺术和电影有什么关系？好莱坞难道也停工？这么闲还打游戏。</span><br>
<span>他们设了个游戏版块</span><br>
</p><p><b>kelveen: </b><br>
<span>接着吹，接着吹。</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 samsung SM-G9750, Android 10上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.2.2.1</span><br>
</p><p><b>ace8848: </b><br>
<span>这标题就是个病句，tlou2已经是个完成了的作品，所以超越了就超越了，没超越就没超越，哪来什么开始超越，薛定谔的超越么？</span><br>
</p><p><b>ShiKi847: </b><br>
<span>The real question is this: when will films catch up with video games like The Last of Us Part II</span><br>
</p><p><b>pgain2004: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 pgain2004 于 2020-6-15 10:02 编辑 </span><br>
<span>Because the story beats in The Last of Us Part II are cohesive in a way that echo some of the best TV shows of the past decade. There isn't a single thread untouched by the end, and the entire experience is riddled with lore-building notes, photographs, and other pieces of information that serve to further enrich the world.</span><br>
<span>因为The Last of Us Part II的叙事节奏令人想起过去十年某些最佳的剧集。一条线索都不会被落下，流程中充斥着刻画背景的笔记、照片和其它进一步丰富世界观的信息。</span><br>
<span>That’s the mark of excellent media, though. It transcends the boundaries of fiction and becomes a story in which you could see yourself. And at the end of it all, even when faced with characters and situations you may not agree with, you can’t help but come out of the experience with a sense of compassion, even toward those responsible for setting Ellie on her path of destruction.</span><br>
<span>There's no sugar-coating it: The Last of Us Part II is as raw as games come, with one foot firmly entrenched within the realm of agonizingly realistic video game conventions and Hollywood blockbusters. At times, the lines blur in such a way that, to anyone casually observing, it seems almost more like a film than anything you’d play on a console. Therein lies its magic.</span><br>
<span>而这便是优秀媒体的标志。它突破了小说的边界，成了能让你内省的故事。当这一切结束，即使是无法认同的人物和情景，即使是令艾丽暴走的源头，也会让你不禁感到同情。</span><br>
<span>没有糖衣炮弹：The Last of Us Part II的游戏体验返璞归真，踏入了电子游戏伤痕写实和好莱坞大片的境界。两者界限有时十分模糊，甚至会让路人旁观者觉得它更像电影而不是在主机上玩的游戏。此即其魔力所在。</span><br>
<span>Beautifully and even gruesomely crafted, The Last of Us Part II represents the pinnacle of what video games can be. It’s an unflinching, impeccable example of how the medium can be used to propel the art form forward by employing the same visceral storytelling techniques and disturbing imagery you’d see from Oscar-nominated films. Critics have been asking when video games would “grow up” for years. The real question is this: when will films catch up with video games like The Last of Us Part II?</span><br>
<span>The Last of Us Part II被漂亮甚至骇人地打造成电子游戏巅峰的代表。这是毫不留情、无懈可击的例子，通过采用奥斯卡提名电影相同的叙事内核和令人不安的图像，展示了如何利用媒介来推动艺术形式发展。多年来，评论家一直在问电子游戏何时才能 "长大"。而真正的问题是：电影何时才能赶上The Last of Us Part II这样的电子游戏？</span><br>
<span>主要是这几段，确实是盛赞。</span><br>
</p><p><b>抖S君: </b><br>
<span>奇迹，世不二出，超越电影，这是越来越牛啤酒了</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>芷雅居: </b><br>
<span>万般赞美也抵不过婆罗门一句“剧情一般，游戏性拉跨，我get不到点”</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能手机投票的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>clover293: </b><br>
<span>什么超越，泥潭都说一般美剧啦</span><br>
</p><p><b>朝日Asahi: </b><br>
<span>“请问美国末日2这个游戏到底神在哪里？”是不是又能钓几百楼</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 samsung SM-N9600, Android 10上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.2.2.1</span><br>
</p><p><b>槲寄生: </b><br>
<span>吹叙事又不是吹剧情。为啥不敢吹剧情，不用想，肯定剧情拉跨。</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>pgain2004: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 pgain2004 于 2020-6-15 12:04 编辑 </span><br>
<span>顺便一提，这评论人是女的，而且本来就是游戏领域的人。</span><br>
<span>Brittany Vincent has been covering video games, anime and tech for over a decade for publications like Otaku USA, G4, Maxim, Engadget, Playboy and more. Fueled by horror, rainbow-sugar-pixel-rushes, and video games, she's a freelancer who survives on surrealism and ultraviolence. When she's not writing, watching anime or gaming, she's searching for the perfect successor to visual novel Saya no Uta. 沙耶之歌忠实拥趸</span><br>
<span>Brittany Vincent is an accomplished video game and entertainment writer whose work has been featured in various publications and online venues over the years. She’s been writing professionally for 13+ years and enjoys combining her lifelong love of gaming and extensive video game knowledge with her passion for the written word.</span><br>
<span>Her work can be seen throughout dozens of print and digital outlets such as Popular Science, Maxim, Official Xbox Magazine, PlayStation: The Official Magazine, Hyper Magazine, Otaku USA, PSM3, BuzzFeed, Eurogamer, Engadget, Maximum PC, AskMen, Shacknews, Modojo, Tom’s Guide, Laptop Magazine, GameSpot, G4, Kotaku, Joystiq, IGN, Destructoid and GamesRadar. Recently, she also contributed to Guinness World Records 2018 Gamer's Edition.</span><br>
<span>Over the past few years, she’s also worked with PR representatives to build relationships and obtain review products for her work, having managed her own gaming website and small teams to attend video game conventions such as PAX East in 2010 and E3 in 2011. In addition, she was previously the community manager at Japanator and associate editor at Destructoid. More recently, she served as Interim Games Editor at Cinema Blend, Co-Editor-in-Chief at G4@Syfygames, Editor-in-Chief at Modojo, News Editor at Twinfinite, News Editor at The Indie Game Website, and Senior Editor at Shacknews. </span><br>
<span>Though gaming attention deficit disorder has Brittany firmly in its clutches with tempting new releases here and there, DLC every other month, and money burning a hole in her pocket, she’s gone back to enjoy several of these favorites time and time again — titles that are dear to her heart. These consist of but are not limited to Parasite Eve, Final Fantasy IX, Halo, Chrono Cross, No One Lives Forever, Rise of the Triad, Space Channel 5, System Shock 2, Dead Space, Day of the Tentacle, and Um Jammer Lammy. 最喜欢的作品包括但不限于寄生前夜、FF9、光环、时空之轮、无人永生、龙霸三合会、Space Channel 5(音游)、System Shock 2、死亡空间、触手也疯狂和拉米乐队等。</span><br>
<span>Brittany is always willing to take on new projects and can offer coverage on various subjects, including video games, technology, entertainment, music and more. Please contact her if you feel she may be a good fit for your publication!某沙雕普片看到说是女的就以为在黑，这只能反映你自己内心隐藏的偏见。</span><br>
</p><p><b>jokertx: </b><br>
<span>泥潭某些人已经为巨魔而巨魔到一定境界了……</span><br>
</p><p><b>tuatha: </b><br>
<span>前两天刚蹭热度看完乱世佳人</span><br>
<span>不知道2020年划时代叙事能打几个1940年老古董</span><br>
</p><p><b>jockeyjoestar: </b><br>
<span>游戏超越电影不是理所应当的吗，现在电影的体裁就很僵硬，而游戏没有时长限制，很多游戏玩家可以控制剧情的走向，比电影灵活得多。</span><br>
<span>更让人在意的是这句：</span><br>
<span>“成了能让你内省的故事。当这一切结束，即使是无法认同的人物和情景，即使是令艾丽暴走的源头，也会让你不禁感到同情。</span><br>
<span>没有糖衣炮弹：The Last of Us Part II以最原始的游戏形式，一脚踏进了令人痛苦的写实电子游戏和好莱坞大片的领域。”</span><br>
<span>不止好莱坞报道者，顽皮狗这次到底写了什么傻逼白左圣母剧情？让所有评测者都觉得很痛苦？</span><br>
</p><p><b>Bojenkins: </b><br>
<span>一个码字的也能算业内？她要是在playboy上发照片可能还更有价值</span><br>
</p><p><b>mintpie: </b><br>
<span>很多传统媒体涉足游戏评测，实际上只是看重这块读者群，所以也还是从游戏圈子里聘请写手。你要是觉得HR的评测就能反映好莱坞对游戏的看法，那你就大错特错了。非圈子内的评论家对游戏的评测是很有看点的，但是大牛的影评人根本不屑于做这些事，我印象里滚石杂志评测GTA4算是个挺有趣的例子。</span><br>
</p><p><b>199april: </b><br>
<span>这十年的商业电影市场 已经被老鼠的流水线工业电影带坏了，我甚至觉得在叙事方面反而比之前退步了</span><br>
</p><p><b>hshiki: </b><br>
<span>那什么时候能超过小说？</span><br>
</p><p><b>bwsusaga: </b><br>
<span>所以这游戏倒底有没有一个专楼，怎么全是看起来像黑楼的楼，</span><br>
<span>1代就觉的战斗不爽，</span><br>
<span>我就想问下，2代战斗这一块是不是量大管饱，资源够不够，强化改装系统深度怎么样，如果还行的话我就当一个优秀的TPS玩应该也不亏。</span><br>
</p><p><b>ztkong: </b><br>
<span>所以之前剧透的那个到底是真的还是假的。。。玩还是会玩的。。。</span><br>
</p><p><b>Rivercat: </b><br>
<span>这些年的商业片从叙事上大多数都很偷懒，美剧倒是有不少佳作，但很多因为商业运作模式，故意设置各种cliffhanger，拖到烂尾潦草收场的不在少数。</span><br>
<span>但电影的叙事艺术也不是那些流水线爆米花产品能够代表的。</span><br>
</p><p><b>acejoe: </b><br>
<span>游戏叙事的上限是高，但tlou2真超越了吗</span><br>
</p><p><b>ShiKi847: </b><br>
<span>bwsusaga 发表于 2020-6-15 10:21</span><br>
<span>所以这游戏倒底有没有一个专楼，怎么全是看起来像黑楼的楼，</span><br>
<span>1代就觉的战斗不爽，</span><br>
<span>真正的粉丝都在剧透楼，你别指望你覃好好讨论索尼的游戏了，这些人有没有PS4都是个问题</span><br>
</p><p><b>kelveen: </b><br>
<span>bwsusaga 发表于 2020-6-15 10:21</span><br>
<span>所以这游戏倒底有没有一个专楼，怎么全是看起来像黑楼的楼，</span><br>
<span>1代就觉的战斗不爽，</span><br>
<span>游戏都没出，怎么跟你讨论系统如何。</span><br>
<span>一代我觉得还可以，但照样大把人恨不得批倒批臭</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 samsung SM-G9750, Android 10上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.2.2.1</span><br>
</p><p><b>Kazepollar: </b><br>
<span>我觉得这游戏一代的游戏系统已经很完美了，二代新加的那些我甚至担心会不会有些多余</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>chivalry: </b><br>
<span>美末2真的逼疯了泥潭不少人，看着挺可怜的</span><br>
</p><p><b>ace8848: </b><br>
<span>不过这跨界踩一捧一倒是和多边形一个思路，这么看国内游戏媒体的写手倒也不输美国很多。</span><br>
</p><p><b>RookieTnT: </b><br>
<span>《疯狂的麦克斯》系列等影片的导演乔治·米勒是业界传奇人物之一，也是被小岛秀夫视为精神导师的人。日前他在观看了《死亡搁浅》的最新演示之后盛赞小岛秀夫的勇气和创造力，同时称在这部作品上看到了一些电影大师才具有的技法，游戏里所有的一切都是为了带给玩家崭新的游戏体验而存在的。</span><br>
<span>《好莱坞报道者》:《TLOU2》在叙事艺术上开始超越电影</span><br>
<span>Neil > 小岛秀夫 ?</span><br>
</p><p><b>Kazepollar: </b><br>
<span>RookieTnT 发表于 2020-06-15 12:24:35</span><br>
<span>《疯狂的麦克斯》系列等影片的导演乔治·米勒是业界传奇人物之一，也是被小岛秀夫视为精神导师的人。日前他 ...从编剧水平上来讲也没啥问题，tlou一代剧情虽然一般但挺合理的。MGS后面几代的剧情我感觉跟闹着玩儿一样</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能手机投票的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>S.I.R: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 S.I.R 于 2020-6-15 12:29 编辑 </span><br>
<span>游戏业因为上限高所以对编剧的要求比电影工业本质要更高。</span><br>
<span>但现实是游戏业的编剧水平普遍远不如电影工业，像UBI那种游戏压根就谈不上有叙事可言。最大的问题还真的不是单纯的故事，就是讲故事的水平不到位。</span><br>
</p><p><b>海拉尔的风: </b><br>
<span>bwsusaga 发表于 2020-06-15 10:21:24</span><br>
<span>所以这游戏倒底有没有一个专楼，怎么全是看起来像黑楼的楼，</span><br>
<span>1代就觉的战斗不爽，</span><br>
<span>我就想问下，2代战斗这 ...我觉得tlou2应该匹配不了你的需求。资源稀缺是这个游戏的核心要素之一</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>ace8848: </b><br>
<span>好莱坞工厂制来说，叙事基本上就是导演的工作，编剧很少干预的余地的。</span><br>
</p><p><b>clover293: </b><br>
<span>pgain2004 发表于 2020-6-15 09:53</span><br>
<span>顺便一提，这评论人是女的，而且本来就是游戏领域的人。</span><br>
<span>某沙雕普片看到说是女的就以为在黑，这只能反映你 ...</span><br>
<span>这人喜欢FF9和时空之轮，应该算老 屁 眼 了</span><br>
</p><p><b>S.I.R: </b><br>
<span>海拉尔的风 发表于 2020-6-15 12:29</span><br>
<span>我觉得tlou2应该匹配不了你的需求。资源稀缺是这个游戏的核心要素之一</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 ...</span><br>
<span>tlou2可以单设置资源多少。我看到有日本人说把其它拉到最难然后资源最大应该最好玩。</span><br>
</p><p><b>mjzs07: </b><br>
<span>超越哪部电影？富春山居图是电影黑暗骑士也是电影</span><br>
</p><p><b>仲雪春山: </b><br>
<span>之前实体店定了还没发货，泥潭这个劲儿……让我想起前不到一个月发现豆瓣有游戏测评，随手搜了搜也有一百多人打分</span><br>
</p><p><b>燃烬之眼: </b><br>
<span>LGBT 牛逼</span><br>
</p><p><b>iceprince10: </b><br>
<span>泥潭现在对tlou2只要来一句政治正确就可以了，反正所有媒体都被政治正确绑架了，只有日本媒体敢勇于揭露事实</span><br>
</p><p><b>mintpie: </b><br>
<span>clover293 发表于 2020-6-15 12:31</span><br>
<span>这人喜欢FF9和时空之轮，应该算老 屁 眼 了</span><br>
<span>PS时代开始接触电子游戏，在美国远远算不上老玩家。老玩家必须得是FC入坑，换句话说，完整经历了现代主机游戏发展过程的。</span><br>
</p><p><b>sgvvvv: </b><br>
<span>这吹法真的没问题吗</span><br>
<span>非要和电影比</span><br>
</p><p><b>ace8848: </b><br>
<span>sgvvvv 发表于 2020-6-15 13:37</span><br>
<span>这吹法真的没问题吗</span><br>
<span>非要和电影比</span><br>
<span>其实比倒也没什么，但至少在两个领域都要有一定的知识水平，结果这篇也好，多边形那篇也好，一边说着超越电影，一边不时以“像”电影为荣，“像”的又都是“好莱坞”，“奥斯卡提名”这种未必是电影叙事天花板的东西，这就很露拙了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>clover293: </b><br>
<span>iceprince10 发表于 2020-6-15 13:27</span><br>
<span>泥潭现在对tlou2只要来一句政治正确就可以了，反正所有媒体都被政治正确绑架了，只有日本媒体敢勇于揭露事 ...</span><br>
<span>只有日本ign敢，fami打了39分估计也是害怕</span><br>
</p><p><b>misaki_d: </b><br>
<span> Ps 独占就是原罪</span><br>
</p><p><b>miu255: </b><br>
<span>sgvvvv 发表于 2020-6-15 13:37</span><br>
<span>这吹法真的没问题吗</span><br>
<span>非要和电影比</span><br>
<span>当然没问题，电影核心不是叙事艺术，游戏核心也不是叙事艺术，孰高孰低都无所谓。</span><br>
</p><p><b>ChrisSnake: </b><br>
<span>所以叙事艺术是个什么艺术 第十艺术?</span><br>
</p><p><b>makar0601: </b><br>
<span>S.I.R 发表于 2020-6-15 12:32</span><br>
<span>tlou2可以单设置资源多少。我看到有日本人说把其它拉到最难然后资源最大应该最好玩。 ...</span><br>
<span>感觉这样确实不错啊。符合打带跑理念</span><br>
</p><p><b>lemon鱿鱼: </b><br>
<span>叙事不再是艺术，现在只是技术</span><br>
<span>当然我也很期待看到tlou2能把叙事重新拔高到艺术这个层次</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能手机投票的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1941758[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
