<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>该不会就此结束 就此分手 爱却分明还没到尽头 会不会难...</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>该不会就此结束 就此分手 爱却分明还没到尽头 会不会难...</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 18:11:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>该不会就此结束 就此分手 爱却分明还没到尽头 会不会难...[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1854745-1-1.html</link>
      <description>该不会就此结束 就此分手 爱却分明还没到尽头 会不会难...&#13;
Personal experience in China: Foreigner privilege dissipating fast in China.
&#13;
在中国的个人体会：外国人在中国的特权迅速消散（正文及评论）
&#13;
Given 10-15 more years max, it probably won't exist in any substantial form anymore. Overseas Chinese privilege has completely disappeared already.
&#13;
最多还有10到15年，外国人在中国可能不会再有任何实质形式的特权。海外华人的特权现在已经完全没有了。
&#13;
I'll begin by saying that White privilege still exists in China: when you see a white guy, there is a 50% chance that he's with a Chinese girl. But when you see a white woman, you almost never see a Chinese guy next to her. Ukrainian models still get paid more than Chinese models on average. OK. With that out of the way, let me tell you what I have observed on the ground:
&#13;
我首先要说的是，在中国现在仍然存在着白人特权：如果你看到一个白人男子，那有50%的可能他会和一个中国女孩在一起。但你要是看到一个白人女性，那你几乎不会在她旁边看到一个中国男人。乌克兰模特得到的平均报酬仍然要比中国模特的高。好吧，我们先不谈这些，我来告诉你们我实地观察到的东西：
&#13;
1. Back in the 80s-90s, if you were an overseas Chinese or from HK or TW, you literally got worshipped like a rock star. For example, back in the 80s, a Chinese American man who owned a restaurant in Boston became an advisor on economic development to the mayor of my hometown. He had no credentials and owned no other businesses other than his Chinese restaurant in Boston, and my hometown is a mega-city you've definitely heard of. Today: returnees with degrees from the Ivy league have a hard time competing with locals.
&#13;
在上世纪八十到九十年代，如果你是一个来自香港或台湾的海外华人，毫不夸张的说你会受到像摇滚明星一样的崇拜。例如，在八十年代时，一个在波士顿开餐馆的美籍华人成了我家乡城市市长的经济发展顾问。这个人没有文凭，除了在波士顿的中餐馆也没有其他生意，而我的家乡是个你们肯定听说过的大城市。如今，拥有常春藤名校学位的海归也很难和本地人竞争。
&#13;
2. In the 90s, pop culture in China was monopolized by HK entertainers, who were literally treated like gods. If HK changed its name to "Heaven" or "This is the life you want but can't have, poor mainlanders", people in China would have supported it because that's exactly what HK symbolized to every single mainlander in the 90s. Today: People see HK as a place in rapid decline, a place with no future, and when was the last blockbuster movie from HK? I don't remember.
&#13;
九十年代时，中国的流行文化被香港艺人所垄断，不夸张的说他们被当作神来对待。如果香港把名字改成“天堂”或者“这是你们想拥有却没有的生活，可怜的大陆人”，中国的老百姓也会支持，因为在九十年代香港对于每个大陆人来说确实就是这样的象征。如今，人们把香港视为一个迅速衰落的地方，一个没有未来的地方，最近一部轰动的香港大片是什么时候？我是记不清了。
&#13;
3. In the 80s - 90s, if you were a guy from HK or Taiwan, you could literally marry any woman you wanted, even girls from well-connected families. Today: in Shanghai where I live, being from HK or Taiwan means you are not able to afford an apartment here and are probably struggling to survive like everyone else here. Zero advantage.
&#13;
在八十到九十年代，如果你是个来自香港或者台湾的男性，你可以和任何你想要的对象结婚，即使是出生名门的女孩也可以。如今，在我生活的上海，从香港或台湾来意味着你在上海连房都供不起，很可能像所有本地人一样在为生存而奋斗。没有任何优势。
&#13;
4. Up until around 2010, having an overseas Chinese background was still an advantage on the dating market. Today: Because property prices are so high and nearly everyone with any serious wealth here is a local, the value of an overseas background on the marriage market is at most 0, likely negative, especially if you don't speak Chinese well.
&#13;
直到2010年左右，具有海外华人背景在恋爱时仍然拥有优势。如今，由于房地产价格非常高，几乎所有拥有真正财富的都是本地人，在婚姻市场上海外背景的价值几乎为零，很可能还有负面影响，尤其是你中文都说不好的话。
&#13;
5. Up until around 2010, working for a big western company was a source of prestige and the pay was substantially higher than at a local company. Today: I don't know about other places, but EVEN in Shanghai, that's no longer the case. Top graduates today are flocking to local tech and finance companies and are actually avoiding western companies because they generally pay less than Chinese finance and tech companies and are seen as career dead ends. On average, I believe foreign companies still pay more than Chinese companies in general, but that is if you include low-pay industries like manufacturing and low-end service. Western companies have completely dropped out of the top echelon of professional prestige and huge pay. A recent Bloomberg article talks about the difficulties companies like Goldman Sachs and Morgan Stanley are having in attracting top talent in China.
&#13;
直到2010年左右，在大型西方公司供职是种声望资源，而且薪水也远比本地公司高得多。现在，其他地方我不了解，但即使在上海也再也没有这种情况了。优秀毕业生都纷纷涌向本地的科技和金融公司，由于比中国金融和科技公司的报酬低以及可预见的职业瓶颈，优秀的毕业生实际上对西方公司是有所回避的。就平均水平而言，我相信外企通常还是比中企的薪水要高，但这要包括制造业和低端服务等低薪行业。西方公司已经完全退出了职业声望及高薪的顶级梯队。彭博社最近的一篇文章谈到了高盛和摩根士丹利等公司在吸引中国顶尖人才方面遇到的困难。
&#13;
6. Up until maybe 2010 (?), if you were white, people automatically assumed you were rich and successful. Today: being white in Shanghai just means you can't afford a property here.
&#13;
大概直到2010年，如果你是个白人，人们会自然而然认为你富有而成功。如今，在上海的白人只能表明你在当地买不起房。
&#13;
7. Up until around 2012, with a good degree from a top American university, you could still get a good job relatively easily. Today: Not the case anymore. China's economy has changed from export-driven to domestically focused. Not knowing the local market is a decisive disadvantage. Having an Ivy league degree itself is no longer a ticket to a privileged position. You have to prove that you can offer more than a fancy degree and get in line with lots of highly competent locals competing for the same job.
&#13;
到2012年左右，凭借着美国顶尖高校的优秀学位，你仍然可以相当轻松的获得一份好工作。现在，不再是这样了，中国经济由出口驱动转变为专注内需。不了解本地市场是个决定性的劣势。拥有常春藤高校的学位本身不再是获得特权职位的直通票。你必须证明除了花哨的学位外还能贡献更多的价值，而且还要和许多高素质的本地人一起竞争同样的职位。
&#13;
8. The last two years: The above trends are accelerating. You can see changes happening in all facets of daily life. For example, the government is no longer happy about real estate developers giving residential communities western names. Videos and stories of locals being mistreated by foreigners go viral easily. More and more people feel that foreigners should not be treated differently than locals (that's obvious, but this was not how people used to think). Recently, a Rwandan guy who taught in Shanghai drowned in a river on a trip to a nearby province. For some reason, it was reported in the news and virtually single reaction was like "What is a guy from Rwanda doing teaching kids in Shanghai? What can a Rwandan guy teach the people in Shanghai?" I personally that's a bit unnecessary, but that's what's needed to de-colonize many people's mindset.
&#13;
最近两年，上述的趋势正在加速发生。你可以看到在日常生活的方方面面都发生着变化。例如，政府不再对房地产开发商用西方名称为住宅小区命名而感到高兴。外国人不公对待本地人的视频及故事很容易广泛传播。越来越多的民众觉得外国人的待遇不应该和本地人有什么不同（这是很明显的事情，但这并不是人们通常想的那样）。最近，有个在上海任教的卢旺达人在邻省旅行时淹死了。出于某些原因，新闻报道了这件事情，并且只是单单反应了诸如“一个卢旺达人在上海教小孩是怎么回事？”“一个卢旺达人在上海能教人们什么？”等问题。我个人觉得这没有任何必要，反而是需要对很多人的心态进行去殖民化。
&#13;
9. Today: If you are obviously a foreigner and you do something disrespectful in public, there is a serious chance that you will be confronted, possibly by a mob.
&#13;
如今，如果你是明显是个外国人而且在公共场所做了无礼的事情，那么你很有可能被暴民所针对。
&#13;
Don't get me wrong. I'm not suggesting China is becoming xenophobic, absolutely not. Nor am I saying white privilege has completely disappeared. No it hasn't. But China is becoming a normal country fast. That's a good thing.
&#13;
别误会我的意思。我并不是说中国变得排外了，绝对不是这样。我也没说白人特权在中国完全消失了。不，并没有。但中国正迅速变成一个正常的国家。这是好事情。
&#13;
评论翻译
&#13;
原创翻译：龙腾网 http://www.ltaaa.com 翻译：masterfang 转载请注明出处
&#13;
论坛地址：http://www.ltaaa.com/bbs/thread-488335-1-1.html
&#13;
CuckStalin
&#13;
I think you're missing the point. Chinese people stopped unconditionally admiring white and overseas people because it's no longer uncommon, and not as benefitial for business as before. But it's not because somehow China has advanced that it doesn't need overseas talent anymore. Ivy league degrees still get you far, as far as a qinghua or beida (I went to qinghua highschool and now at upenn). Overseas and foreign talent is still preferred, not due to privalige, but demand for language skills and international experience. Yes the privilege has faded, but that doesn't mean somehow everyone is equal in the job market. That is not to say domestic talent is inferior, simply one is more in demand compared to supply.
&#13;
​
&#13;
我想你漏掉了这点。中国人不再无条件的钦佩白人及海外人士是因为这种情况已经不再罕见，对商业而言也没有以前那么有利可图。但并不是因为中国已经领先到不再需要海外人才。拥有常春藤名校的学位仍然可以让你走的更远，就如清华和北大一样（我原来上的清华附中，现在在宾夕法尼亚大学）。海外及外国人才仍然是首选，不是因为特权，而是出于对语言技能和国际经验的需求。特权的情况确实在减少，但并不意味着所有人在就业市场上都平等。并不是说国内人才不行，只是海外人才更供不应求罢了。
&#13;
davidl321456（回复：CuckStalin）
&#13;
What you are saying was categorically true ten years ago. Today, it depends. I'm a member of an Ivy alum association in Shanghai. I know what I'm talking about.
&#13;
What I can tell you is that your Upenn degree is going to be worth far less in 20 years when you reach your peak career potential than a degree from THU or PKU. When you are in your 40s, how many Upenn alums are going to be in key positions in corporate business and politics IN CHINA? Not that many, that we can be 100% sure. How many high powered positions IN CHINA will be held by graduates of THU and PKU in China in 20 years? A lot. If you stay in the US where you Upenn will always be worth more than a Chinese degree, then you get the bamboo ceiling from day 1.
&#13;
If your dad is an official in the central gov, then forget what I said. Otherwise, I'm telling you the truth. Many of my friends with Ivy degrees who returned to work for once-prestigious western companies are now struggling with bamboo ceilings in China and plateaued careers.
&#13;
15 years ago, even an ABC with passable Chinese could probably waltz into a lucrative finance job in Shanghai or Beijing. Today, completion of high school in China is an implicit requirement at many PE shops for entry level positions. The trend is clear.
&#13;
你所说的在十年前绝对是真事。如今，要视情况而定。我是上海常春藤校友会的成员。我清楚我在说什么。
&#13;
我可以告诉你的是，在20年内当你到达你可能的职业巅峰时，你宾夕法尼亚大学学位的价值远低于清华或者北大的学位。当你40岁的时候，有多少宾大的校友会在中国坐到政企的关键位置？我们百分百确定，不会有很多。20年内在中国有多少高层职位会被清华和北大的毕业生把持？很多！如果你呆在美国那你宾大的学位永远会比中国的学位更有价值，但在入职的第一天你就会遇到无形的升职障碍（bamboo ceiling 注）。
&#13;
如果你爹是中央政府官员，那你当我没说。否则，我可以告诉你实话。我许多拥有常春藤名校学位的朋友回来后为享有盛名的西方公司工作，现在则在为突破中国的升职障碍并稳定其事业而奋斗。
&#13;
15年前，即使一个勉强算中国人的美籍华人也可以在上海或北京获得一份获利丰厚的金融工作。现在，
&#13;
完成中国的中学教育成了许多私募公司入门职位的一项隐含要求。这种趋势很明显。
&#13;
[译注]：bamboo ceiling(竹子天花板)，是指一种对于亚裔（尤其是东亚裔，主要是中日韩）而言，无形的升职障碍。
&#13;
YMRTZ
&#13;
As an overseas Chinese, I support this. We're all Chinese, so why should some of us get special treatment? And why should foreigners get special treatment?
&#13;
作为一名海外华人，我同意这个观点。我们都是中国人，那么为什么我们有些人可以获得特殊待遇？为什么外国人也可以获得特殊待遇？
&#13;
FlyFlygon
&#13;
Overseas Chinese privilege is still a thing. But it's more due to practicality. An overseas degree is still worth more than most domestic degrees.
&#13;
I've taught English in China and stayed in touch with some of the friends I've made since. Before, having a white teacher was highly sought after and people get very good compensation. It seems that compensation has lowered in recent years, but is still a very good chunk of change.
&#13;
Still, the requirements for English teaching has become a lot more stringent and supervisors are less tolerant of lazy teachers. White teachers have been downgraded from stars of the company to regular employees. So it certainly is moving a certain way.
&#13;
海外华人的特权依然存在。但这更多是取决于其实用性。一个国外的学位仍然比大多数国内的学位更有价值。
&#13;
我曾在中国教过英语，并一直和在中国交的一些朋友保持着联系。以前，白人教师十分抢手，而且薪水也非常丰厚。最近几年薪水似乎有所下降，但这仍是个非常好的改变。
&#13;
还有，对于英语教学的要求更加严格，而且主管人员对于懒惰的教师更不宽容。白人教师已经从公司的明星降级为普通员工。所以确实是往这个方向发展。
&#13;
davidl321456（回复：FlyFlygon）
&#13;
Overseas Chinese privilege is still a thing.
&#13;
No, it is not. Trust me. But by "privilege" if you mean being looked on with envy by some old square-dancing aunties in their 60's or 70's who think you are a fu'er'dai returning from abroad just because you are overseas Chinese, then yeah, maybe. That's not what privilege means to me though.
&#13;
If anything, overseas Chinese are in a rather unenviable situation here. If you speak perfect Chinese and can blend in, you are fine. If not, then you better have some in-demand skills. If you have no in-demand skills and have to teach English, life will suck for you.
&#13;
An overseas degree is still worth more than most domestic degrees.
&#13;
If you are talking about Ivy league vs an average university in China, yes. A second-tier American university, or an Australian, New Zealand, Canadian, Singaporean university vs a good university in China? Absolutely not. In fact, the value of a degree from most universities in Australia and New Zealand is already negative, as people assume you went there because you could not get into a good college in China.
&#13;
海外华人的特权仍然是个事。
&#13;
不存在的，相信我。但如果你所谓的“特权”是指被那些仅仅因为你是海外华人就以为你是归国“富二代”的六七十岁的广场舞大妈羡慕的看着，那么，也许是吧。对我而言那可不是什么特权。要说有什么的话，那就是海外华人在这的处境根本不值得羡慕。如果你中文说的很好并能融入当地，那你会过得不错。如果不是，你最好有一技之长。如果你没有一技之长只能教教英语，那就人艰不拆了。
&#13;
国外的学位仍然比大多数国内的学位更有价值。
&#13;
如果你说的是用常春藤联盟的名校和普通中国大学比较，那确实是。那用二流大美国大学或者澳大利亚、新西兰、加拿大、新加坡的大学和中国优秀的大学对比呢？结果绝对不是这样。事实上，大多数澳大利亚和新西兰大学的学位价值都已经被否定了，通常人们都认定你是因为进不了中国的好大学才去那种地方上学的。
&#13;
allinwonderornot
&#13;
Point 6 is very true. If you are an expat, you are assumed to be renting, which automatically puts you on second tier on the dating market.
&#13;
Also for point 3, 90s mainland hard rock/metal scene was far better than contemporary cookie cutter HK pop anyway.
&#13;
第6点非常正确。如果你是外籍人士，你就会被认定为正在租房住，在恋爱市场上自动就被划归为第二序列。第3点也是一样，九十年代大陆的硬摇滚和重金属摇滚远比香港千篇一律的流行音乐好多了。
&#13;
FENG_TI_MUO
&#13;
youre obviously not from the mainland. There are plenty of Chinese men with white women. (specifically russian and ukrainian brides) So much so that white supremacists sites have threads complaining about this shit
&#13;
你明显不是来自中国大陆。有许多中国男人和白人女**往。（特别是俄罗斯和乌克兰新娘）多到在白人至上主义的网站上都在喷这个事。
&#13;
FlyFlygon
&#13;
Russians are a recognized minority in China just like Mongols, Tibetans, Zhuang, Miao, and so on. They are legitimately white Chinese, just like the Tatars and Tajiks.
&#13;
Like this guy, this guy, this girl, this girl, these soldiers, they are 100% Chinese.
&#13;
It's not "Chinese men with white women". It's just "Chinese men with Chinese women".
&#13;
I'm Mongolian and it peeves me even Chinese people think Chinese all look the same.
&#13;
俄罗斯人是中国公认的少数民族，就像蒙古人，藏人，壮族，苗族等。他们是合法的白种中国人，就像鞑靼人和塔吉克人一样。
&#13;
（译注：评论者弄了些少数民族的图片链接）这些都是百分百的中国人。
&#13;
这不是“中国男人和白人女性在一起”。这仅仅是“中国男人和中国女性在一起”。
&#13;
我是蒙古人，但连中国人都认为所有中国人长得都一样，这种的观点让我很恼火。
&#13;
jorvis_nonof
&#13;
The gilding continues...
&#13;
这种虚假的表象仍在继续…
&#13;
Icm2（回复：FENG_TI_MUO）
&#13;
They're not common enough to regularly see on the street. It's one of those things everyone is semi-aware of but few people actually know someone who did it other than the "success stories" online.
&#13;
这种事情并不是在街头可以常常见到的，很少有人真正认识和外国人交往的人，而不只是像网上 “成功故事”里说的那样，对于大众来说这是件一知半解的事情。
&#13;
Medical_Officer
&#13;
This trend is even more amazing when you compare it to Japan and (to a lesser extent) South Korea.
&#13;
Both Japan and SK have higher average incomes than even Tier 1 cities in China. Yet their white worship hasn't dimmed a bit since 1945. Japanese women still trip over themselves banzai charging white man's you-know-what. It's not as bad in SK (Koreans tend to have more self-respect than Japanese... marginally) but it's still a thing.
&#13;
I mean, I get that the typical Japanese man makes the worst possible husband, but still, it's national embarrassment how a "developed" East Asian country can still white worship so hard.
&#13;
如果同日本和韩国（在较小程度上）进行比较，这种趋势更加惊人。日本和韩国的平均收入都比中国的一线城市要高。但自1945年开始，他们对白人的崇拜没有一点消退。日本女人仍然疯狂的想和白人男性做不可描述的事情。韩国的没有那么糟糕（韩国人稍微比日本人自爱一点）但依然有这样的情况。
&#13;
我的意思是，我认为典型的日本男人是最糟糕的丈夫，国家的尴尬在于为什么一个“发达”的东亚国家依然存在如此严重的白人崇拜。
&#13;
Breakdancing_DrZaius
&#13;
To be fair, they're practically American slaves since they're forced to host foreign soldiers on their soil. Those soldiers are rapists, murderers, and america isn't sending its best. Some I assume are good people.
&#13;
To host non-native foreign troops on your soil - effectively being a colony in the 21st century - is the equivalent to having your men neutered at birth. The strong implication being that your men aren't even able to defend themselves and require a foreign master to do so must really damage their collective psyches. Hence all the pathetic white worship.
&#13;
公平的讲，自从被迫让外国军队在自己的土地上驻军，他们实际上就成了美国人的奴隶。美国没有派驻他们最好的部队，这些士兵是强奸犯、杀人犯。有些我认为是好人。
&#13;
让外国军队在自己的土地上驻军，其实就是21世纪的殖民地，这相当于你们的男人在出生时就被阉割了。最严重的影响就是你们的男人甚至不能为自己辩护，而是需要外国主子帮忙。这必定会真正损害他们的集体意志。这一切就导致了可悲的白人崇拜。
&#13;
BayMind
&#13;
I would hope this to be the case for the #2 biggest economy in the world. But like japan, I fear china will continue to have massive caucasian worship brainwashing. Need to combat racist Hollywood media or actively influence hollywood media with more positive asian male images.
&#13;
我倒是希望在世界第二大经济体，消除白人特权可以成为现实。但像日本一样，我当心中国会继续存在大量的白人崇拜洗脑灌输。需要同种族主义的好莱坞媒体进行抗争，或者用正面的亚洲男性形象来积极影响好莱坞媒体。
&#13;
jorvis_nonof
&#13;
The Trade War and the reaction to the Hong Kong fiasco has awakened Chinese patriotism in a way that we've never seen before in our lifetimes...
&#13;
贸易战以及对HK惨败的反应唤醒了中国的爱国主义，这是我们一生中从未见过的方式......
&#13;
DragonSeed420
&#13;
I never thought I had much privilege when I lived in China back in 2010. Applying to jobs I got told I wasn’t Chinese enough to I was too Chinese. My Chinese is at HSK 5 too. I think all of it was just to low ball me on salary but w/e. Anyways, these comparison threads do nothing but entrench people’s prejudices. If money and privilege is what we ultimately seek then I’m afraid it’s not enough to confront the problems that Chinese society faces today.
&#13;
I think “overseas Chinese privilege” is something shitty fuerdai kids made up to console themselves after they’ve blown a fortune and flunked out of college.
&#13;
Life would be great for me if I didn’t have to share family wealth with 2 other siblings and I had a family business or properties to inherit. I could just hire an ABC to do all my work while I play dota2 all day. Mainlanders have it so easy man /s
&#13;
2010年当我在中国生活时，我从未想过到我有多少特权。在求职时，不够中国和太过中国我都被说过。我的中文也是汉语水平考试（HSK）5级。我想这一切都只是要压低我的薪水。无论如何，这种比较主题除了加深人们的偏见没有什么作用。如果金钱和特权是我们的根本追求，那么我担心它并不足以应对中国社会今天所面临的问题。
&#13;
我认为“海外华人特权”问题是些顽劣的富二代小孩在挥霍完财富还有考不进大学之后编造出来安慰自己的。
&#13;
如果我不用同其他2个兄弟姐妹来分享家庭财产，并且我有家族企业或财产可以继承，那么生活对我来说实在太美妙了。我可以雇个美籍华人来完成我所有的工作，我就整天耍耍dota2。大陆人中就是有这种拥有简单模式的人。</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>狒狗: </b><br>
<span>该不会就此结束 就此分手 爱却分明还没到尽头 会不会难...</span><br>
<span>Personal experience in China: Foreigner privilege dissipating fast in China.</span><br>
<span>在中国的个人体会：外国人在中国的特权迅速消散（正文及评论）</span><br>
<span>Given 10-15 more years max, it probably won't exist in any substantial form anymore. Overseas Chinese privilege has completely disappeared already.</span><br>
<span>最多还有10到15年，外国人在中国可能不会再有任何实质形式的特权。海外华人的特权现在已经完全没有了。</span><br>
<span>I'll begin by saying that White privilege still exists in China: when you see a white guy, there is a 50% chance that he's with a Chinese girl. But when you see a white woman, you almost never see a Chinese guy next to her. Ukrainian models still get paid more than Chinese models on average. OK. With that out of the way, let me tell you what I have observed on the ground:</span><br>
<span>我首先要说的是，在中国现在仍然存在着白人特权：如果你看到一个白人男子，那有50%的可能他会和一个中国女孩在一起。但你要是看到一个白人女性，那你几乎不会在她旁边看到一个中国男人。乌克兰模特得到的平均报酬仍然要比中国模特的高。好吧，我们先不谈这些，我来告诉你们我实地观察到的东西：</span><br>
<span>1. Back in the 80s-90s, if you were an overseas Chinese or from HK or TW, you literally got worshipped like a rock star. For example, back in the 80s, a Chinese American man who owned a restaurant in Boston became an advisor on economic development to the mayor of my hometown. He had no credentials and owned no other businesses other than his Chinese restaurant in Boston, and my hometown is a mega-city you've definitely heard of. Today: returnees with degrees from the Ivy league have a hard time competing with locals.</span><br>
<span>在上世纪八十到九十年代，如果你是一个来自香港或台湾的海外华人，毫不夸张的说你会受到像摇滚明星一样的崇拜。例如，在八十年代时，一个在波士顿开餐馆的美籍华人成了我家乡城市市长的经济发展顾问。这个人没有文凭，除了在波士顿的中餐馆也没有其他生意，而我的家乡是个你们肯定听说过的大城市。如今，拥有常春藤名校学位的海归也很难和本地人竞争。</span><br>
<span>2. In the 90s, pop culture in China was monopolized by HK entertainers, who were literally treated like gods. If HK changed its name to "Heaven" or "This is the life you want but can't have, poor mainlanders", people in China would have supported it because that's exactly what HK symbolized to every single mainlander in the 90s. Today: People see HK as a place in rapid decline, a place with no future, and when was the last blockbuster movie from HK? I don't remember.</span><br>
<span>九十年代时，中国的流行文化被香港艺人所垄断，不夸张的说他们被当作神来对待。如果香港把名字改成“天堂”或者“这是你们想拥有却没有的生活，可怜的大陆人”，中国的老百姓也会支持，因为在九十年代香港对于每个大陆人来说确实就是这样的象征。如今，人们把香港视为一个迅速衰落的地方，一个没有未来的地方，最近一部轰动的香港大片是什么时候？我是记不清了。</span><br>
<span>3. In the 80s - 90s, if you were a guy from HK or Taiwan, you could literally marry any woman you wanted, even girls from well-connected families. Today: in Shanghai where I live, being from HK or Taiwan means you are not able to afford an apartment here and are probably struggling to survive like everyone else here. Zero advantage.</span><br>
<span>在八十到九十年代，如果你是个来自香港或者台湾的男性，你可以和任何你想要的对象结婚，即使是出生名门的女孩也可以。如今，在我生活的上海，从香港或台湾来意味着你在上海连房都供不起，很可能像所有本地人一样在为生存而奋斗。没有任何优势。</span><br>
<span>4. Up until around 2010, having an overseas Chinese background was still an advantage on the dating market. Today: Because property prices are so high and nearly everyone with any serious wealth here is a local, the value of an overseas background on the marriage market is at most 0, likely negative, especially if you don't speak Chinese well.</span><br>
<span>直到2010年左右，具有海外华人背景在恋爱时仍然拥有优势。如今，由于房地产价格非常高，几乎所有拥有真正财富的都是本地人，在婚姻市场上海外背景的价值几乎为零，很可能还有负面影响，尤其是你中文都说不好的话。</span><br>
<span>5. Up until around 2010, working for a big western company was a source of prestige and the pay was substantially higher than at a local company. Today: I don't know about other places, but EVEN in Shanghai, that's no longer the case. Top graduates today are flocking to local tech and finance companies and are actually avoiding western companies because they generally pay less than Chinese finance and tech companies and are seen as career dead ends. On average, I believe foreign companies still pay more than Chinese companies in general, but that is if you include low-pay industries like manufacturing and low-end service. Western companies have completely dropped out of the top echelon of professional prestige and huge pay. A recent Bloomberg article talks about the difficulties companies like Goldman Sachs and Morgan Stanley are having in attracting top talent in China.</span><br>
<span>直到2010年左右，在大型西方公司供职是种声望资源，而且薪水也远比本地公司高得多。现在，其他地方我不了解，但即使在上海也再也没有这种情况了。优秀毕业生都纷纷涌向本地的科技和金融公司，由于比中国金融和科技公司的报酬低以及可预见的职业瓶颈，优秀的毕业生实际上对西方公司是有所回避的。就平均水平而言，我相信外企通常还是比中企的薪水要高，但这要包括制造业和低端服务等低薪行业。西方公司已经完全退出了职业声望及高薪的顶级梯队。彭博社最近的一篇文章谈到了高盛和摩根士丹利等公司在吸引中国顶尖人才方面遇到的困难。</span><br>
<span>6. Up until maybe 2010 (?), if you were white, people automatically assumed you were rich and successful. Today: being white in Shanghai just means you can't afford a property here.</span><br>
<span>大概直到2010年，如果你是个白人，人们会自然而然认为你富有而成功。如今，在上海的白人只能表明你在当地买不起房。</span><br>
<span>7. Up until around 2012, with a good degree from a top American university, you could still get a good job relatively easily. Today: Not the case anymore. China's economy has changed from export-driven to domestically focused. Not knowing the local market is a decisive disadvantage. Having an Ivy league degree itself is no longer a ticket to a privileged position. You have to prove that you can offer more than a fancy degree and get in line with lots of highly competent locals competing for the same job.</span><br>
<span>到2012年左右，凭借着美国顶尖高校的优秀学位，你仍然可以相当轻松的获得一份好工作。现在，不再是这样了，中国经济由出口驱动转变为专注内需。不了解本地市场是个决定性的劣势。拥有常春藤高校的学位本身不再是获得特权职位的直通票。你必须证明除了花哨的学位外还能贡献更多的价值，而且还要和许多高素质的本地人一起竞争同样的职位。</span><br>
<span>8. The last two years: The above trends are accelerating. You can see changes happening in all facets of daily life. For example, the government is no longer happy about real estate developers giving residential communities western names. Videos and stories of locals being mistreated by foreigners go viral easily. More and more people feel that foreigners should not be treated differently than locals (that's obvious, but this was not how people used to think). Recently, a Rwandan guy who taught in Shanghai drowned in a river on a trip to a nearby province. For some reason, it was reported in the news and virtually single reaction was like "What is a guy from Rwanda doing teaching kids in Shanghai? What can a Rwandan guy teach the people in Shanghai?" I personally that's a bit unnecessary, but that's what's needed to de-colonize many people's mindset.</span><br>
<span>最近两年，上述的趋势正在加速发生。你可以看到在日常生活的方方面面都发生着变化。例如，政府不再对房地产开发商用西方名称为住宅小区命名而感到高兴。外国人不公对待本地人的视频及故事很容易广泛传播。越来越多的民众觉得外国人的待遇不应该和本地人有什么不同（这是很明显的事情，但这并不是人们通常想的那样）。最近，有个在上海任教的卢旺达人在邻省旅行时淹死了。出于某些原因，新闻报道了这件事情，并且只是单单反应了诸如“一个卢旺达人在上海教小孩是怎么回事？”“一个卢旺达人在上海能教人们什么？”等问题。我个人觉得这没有任何必要，反而是需要对很多人的心态进行去殖民化。</span><br>
<span>9. Today: If you are obviously a foreigner and you do something disrespectful in public, there is a serious chance that you will be confronted, possibly by a mob.</span><br>
<span>如今，如果你是明显是个外国人而且在公共场所做了无礼的事情，那么你很有可能被暴民所针对。</span><br>
<span>Don't get me wrong. I'm not suggesting China is becoming xenophobic, absolutely not. Nor am I saying white privilege has completely disappeared. No it hasn't. But China is becoming a normal country fast. That's a good thing.</span><br>
<span>别误会我的意思。我并不是说中国变得排外了，绝对不是这样。我也没说白人特权在中国完全消失了。不，并没有。但中国正迅速变成一个正常的国家。这是好事情。</span><br>
<span>评论翻译</span><br>
<span>原创翻译：龙腾网 http://www.ltaaa.com 翻译：masterfang 转载请注明出处</span><br>
<span>论坛地址：http://www.ltaaa.com/bbs/thread-488335-1-1.html</span><br>
<span>CuckStalin</span><br>
<span>I think you're missing the point. Chinese people stopped unconditionally admiring white and overseas people because it's no longer uncommon, and not as benefitial for business as before. But it's not because somehow China has advanced that it doesn't need overseas talent anymore. Ivy league degrees still get you far, as far as a qinghua or beida (I went to qinghua highschool and now at upenn). Overseas and foreign talent is still preferred, not due to privalige, but demand for language skills and international experience. Yes the privilege has faded, but that doesn't mean somehow everyone is equal in the job market. That is not to say domestic talent is inferior, simply one is more in demand compared to supply.</span><br>
<span>​</span><br>
<span>我想你漏掉了这点。中国人不再无条件的钦佩白人及海外人士是因为这种情况已经不再罕见，对商业而言也没有以前那么有利可图。但并不是因为中国已经领先到不再需要海外人才。拥有常春藤名校的学位仍然可以让你走的更远，就如清华和北大一样（我原来上的清华附中，现在在宾夕法尼亚大学）。海外及外国人才仍然是首选，不是因为特权，而是出于对语言技能和国际经验的需求。特权的情况确实在减少，但并不意味着所有人在就业市场上都平等。并不是说国内人才不行，只是海外人才更供不应求罢了。</span><br>
<span>davidl321456（回复：CuckStalin）</span><br>
<span>What you are saying was categorically true ten years ago. Today, it depends. I'm a member of an Ivy alum association in Shanghai. I know what I'm talking about.</span><br>
<span>What I can tell you is that your Upenn degree is going to be worth far less in 20 years when you reach your peak career potential than a degree from THU or PKU. When you are in your 40s, how many Upenn alums are going to be in key positions in corporate business and politics IN CHINA? Not that many, that we can be 100% sure. How many high powered positions IN CHINA will be held by graduates of THU and PKU in China in 20 years? A lot. If you stay in the US where you Upenn will always be worth more than a Chinese degree, then you get the bamboo ceiling from day 1.</span><br>
<span>If your dad is an official in the central gov, then forget what I said. Otherwise, I'm telling you the truth. Many of my friends with Ivy degrees who returned to work for once-prestigious western companies are now struggling with bamboo ceilings in China and plateaued careers.</span><br>
<span>15 years ago, even an ABC with passable Chinese could probably waltz into a lucrative finance job in Shanghai or Beijing. Today, completion of high school in China is an implicit requirement at many PE shops for entry level positions. The trend is clear.</span><br>
<span>你所说的在十年前绝对是真事。如今，要视情况而定。我是上海常春藤校友会的成员。我清楚我在说什么。</span><br>
<span>我可以告诉你的是，在20年内当你到达你可能的职业巅峰时，你宾夕法尼亚大学学位的价值远低于清华或者北大的学位。当你40岁的时候，有多少宾大的校友会在中国坐到政企的关键位置？我们百分百确定，不会有很多。20年内在中国有多少高层职位会被清华和北大的毕业生把持？很多！如果你呆在美国那你宾大的学位永远会比中国的学位更有价值，但在入职的第一天你就会遇到无形的升职障碍（bamboo ceiling 注）。</span><br>
<span>如果你爹是中央政府官员，那你当我没说。否则，我可以告诉你实话。我许多拥有常春藤名校学位的朋友回来后为享有盛名的西方公司工作，现在则在为突破中国的升职障碍并稳定其事业而奋斗。</span><br>
<span>15年前，即使一个勉强算中国人的美籍华人也可以在上海或北京获得一份获利丰厚的金融工作。现在，</span><br>
<span>完成中国的中学教育成了许多私募公司入门职位的一项隐含要求。这种趋势很明显。</span><br>
<span>[译注]：bamboo ceiling(竹子天花板)，是指一种对于亚裔（尤其是东亚裔，主要是中日韩）而言，无形的升职障碍。</span><br>
<span>YMRTZ</span><br>
<span>As an overseas Chinese, I support this. We're all Chinese, so why should some of us get special treatment? And why should foreigners get special treatment?</span><br>
<span>作为一名海外华人，我同意这个观点。我们都是中国人，那么为什么我们有些人可以获得特殊待遇？为什么外国人也可以获得特殊待遇？</span><br>
<span>FlyFlygon</span><br>
<span>Overseas Chinese privilege is still a thing. But it's more due to practicality. An overseas degree is still worth more than most domestic degrees.</span><br>
<span>I've taught English in China and stayed in touch with some of the friends I've made since. Before, having a white teacher was highly sought after and people get very good compensation. It seems that compensation has lowered in recent years, but is still a very good chunk of change.</span><br>
<span>Still, the requirements for English teaching has become a lot more stringent and supervisors are less tolerant of lazy teachers. White teachers have been downgraded from stars of the company to regular employees. So it certainly is moving a certain way.</span><br>
<span>海外华人的特权依然存在。但这更多是取决于其实用性。一个国外的学位仍然比大多数国内的学位更有价值。</span><br>
<span>我曾在中国教过英语，并一直和在中国交的一些朋友保持着联系。以前，白人教师十分抢手，而且薪水也非常丰厚。最近几年薪水似乎有所下降，但这仍是个非常好的改变。</span><br>
<span>还有，对于英语教学的要求更加严格，而且主管人员对于懒惰的教师更不宽容。白人教师已经从公司的明星降级为普通员工。所以确实是往这个方向发展。</span><br>
<span>davidl321456（回复：FlyFlygon）</span><br>
<span>Overseas Chinese privilege is still a thing.</span><br>
<span>No, it is not. Trust me. But by "privilege" if you mean being looked on with envy by some old square-dancing aunties in their 60's or 70's who think you are a fu'er'dai returning from abroad just because you are overseas Chinese, then yeah, maybe. That's not what privilege means to me though.</span><br>
<span>If anything, overseas Chinese are in a rather unenviable situation here. If you speak perfect Chinese and can blend in, you are fine. If not, then you better have some in-demand skills. If you have no in-demand skills and have to teach English, life will suck for you.</span><br>
<span>An overseas degree is still worth more than most domestic degrees.</span><br>
<span>If you are talking about Ivy league vs an average university in China, yes. A second-tier American university, or an Australian, New Zealand, Canadian, Singaporean university vs a good university in China? Absolutely not. In fact, the value of a degree from most universities in Australia and New Zealand is already negative, as people assume you went there because you could not get into a good college in China.</span><br>
<span>海外华人的特权仍然是个事。</span><br>
<span>不存在的，相信我。但如果你所谓的“特权”是指被那些仅仅因为你是海外华人就以为你是归国“富二代”的六七十岁的广场舞大妈羡慕的看着，那么，也许是吧。对我而言那可不是什么特权。要说有什么的话，那就是海外华人在这的处境根本不值得羡慕。如果你中文说的很好并能融入当地，那你会过得不错。如果不是，你最好有一技之长。如果你没有一技之长只能教教英语，那就人艰不拆了。</span><br>
<span>国外的学位仍然比大多数国内的学位更有价值。</span><br>
<span>如果你说的是用常春藤联盟的名校和普通中国大学比较，那确实是。那用二流大美国大学或者澳大利亚、新西兰、加拿大、新加坡的大学和中国优秀的大学对比呢？结果绝对不是这样。事实上，大多数澳大利亚和新西兰大学的学位价值都已经被否定了，通常人们都认定你是因为进不了中国的好大学才去那种地方上学的。</span><br>
<span>allinwonderornot</span><br>
<span>Point 6 is very true. If you are an expat, you are assumed to be renting, which automatically puts you on second tier on the dating market.</span><br>
<span>Also for point 3, 90s mainland hard rock/metal scene was far better than contemporary cookie cutter HK pop anyway.</span><br>
<span>第6点非常正确。如果你是外籍人士，你就会被认定为正在租房住，在恋爱市场上自动就被划归为第二序列。第3点也是一样，九十年代大陆的硬摇滚和重金属摇滚远比香港千篇一律的流行音乐好多了。</span><br>
<span>FENG_TI_MUO</span><br>
<span>youre obviously not from the mainland. There are plenty of Chinese men with white women. (specifically russian and ukrainian brides) So much so that white supremacists sites have threads complaining about this shit</span><br>
<span>你明显不是来自中国大陆。有许多中国男人和白人女**往。（特别是俄罗斯和乌克兰新娘）多到在白人至上主义的网站上都在喷这个事。</span><br>
<span>FlyFlygon</span><br>
<span>Russians are a recognized minority in China just like Mongols, Tibetans, Zhuang, Miao, and so on. They are legitimately white Chinese, just like the Tatars and Tajiks.</span><br>
<span>Like this guy, this guy, this girl, this girl, these soldiers, they are 100% Chinese.</span><br>
<span>It's not "Chinese men with white women". It's just "Chinese men with Chinese women".</span><br>
<span>I'm Mongolian and it peeves me even Chinese people think Chinese all look the same.</span><br>
<span>俄罗斯人是中国公认的少数民族，就像蒙古人，藏人，壮族，苗族等。他们是合法的白种中国人，就像鞑靼人和塔吉克人一样。</span><br>
<span>（译注：评论者弄了些少数民族的图片链接）这些都是百分百的中国人。</span><br>
<span>这不是“中国男人和白人女性在一起”。这仅仅是“中国男人和中国女性在一起”。</span><br>
<span>我是蒙古人，但连中国人都认为所有中国人长得都一样，这种的观点让我很恼火。</span><br>
<span>jorvis_nonof</span><br>
<span>The gilding continues...</span><br>
<span>这种虚假的表象仍在继续…</span><br>
<span>Icm2（回复：FENG_TI_MUO）</span><br>
<span>They're not common enough to regularly see on the street. It's one of those things everyone is semi-aware of but few people actually know someone who did it other than the "success stories" online.</span><br>
<span>这种事情并不是在街头可以常常见到的，很少有人真正认识和外国人交往的人，而不只是像网上 “成功故事”里说的那样，对于大众来说这是件一知半解的事情。</span><br>
<span>Medical_Officer</span><br>
<span>This trend is even more amazing when you compare it to Japan and (to a lesser extent) South Korea.</span><br>
<span>Both Japan and SK have higher average incomes than even Tier 1 cities in China. Yet their white worship hasn't dimmed a bit since 1945. Japanese women still trip over themselves banzai charging white man's you-know-what. It's not as bad in SK (Koreans tend to have more self-respect than Japanese... marginally) but it's still a thing.</span><br>
<span>I mean, I get that the typical Japanese man makes the worst possible husband, but still, it's national embarrassment how a "developed" East Asian country can still white worship so hard.</span><br>
<span>如果同日本和韩国（在较小程度上）进行比较，这种趋势更加惊人。日本和韩国的平均收入都比中国的一线城市要高。但自1945年开始，他们对白人的崇拜没有一点消退。日本女人仍然疯狂的想和白人男性做不可描述的事情。韩国的没有那么糟糕（韩国人稍微比日本人自爱一点）但依然有这样的情况。</span><br>
<span>我的意思是，我认为典型的日本男人是最糟糕的丈夫，国家的尴尬在于为什么一个“发达”的东亚国家依然存在如此严重的白人崇拜。</span><br>
<span>Breakdancing_DrZaius</span><br>
<span>To be fair, they're practically American slaves since they're forced to host foreign soldiers on their soil. Those soldiers are rapists, murderers, and america isn't sending its best. Some I assume are good people.</span><br>
<span>To host non-native foreign troops on your soil - effectively being a colony in the 21st century - is the equivalent to having your men neutered at birth. The strong implication being that your men aren't even able to defend themselves and require a foreign master to do so must really damage their collective psyches. Hence all the pathetic white worship.</span><br>
<span>公平的讲，自从被迫让外国军队在自己的土地上驻军，他们实际上就成了美国人的奴隶。美国没有派驻他们最好的部队，这些士兵是强奸犯、杀人犯。有些我认为是好人。</span><br>
<span>让外国军队在自己的土地上驻军，其实就是21世纪的殖民地，这相当于你们的男人在出生时就被阉割了。最严重的影响就是你们的男人甚至不能为自己辩护，而是需要外国主子帮忙。这必定会真正损害他们的集体意志。这一切就导致了可悲的白人崇拜。</span><br>
<span>BayMind</span><br>
<span>I would hope this to be the case for the #2 biggest economy in the world. But like japan, I fear china will continue to have massive caucasian worship brainwashing. Need to combat racist Hollywood media or actively influence hollywood media with more positive asian male images.</span><br>
<span>我倒是希望在世界第二大经济体，消除白人特权可以成为现实。但像日本一样，我当心中国会继续存在大量的白人崇拜洗脑灌输。需要同种族主义的好莱坞媒体进行抗争，或者用正面的亚洲男性形象来积极影响好莱坞媒体。</span><br>
<span>jorvis_nonof</span><br>
<span>The Trade War and the reaction to the Hong Kong fiasco has awakened Chinese patriotism in a way that we've never seen before in our lifetimes...</span><br>
<span>贸易战以及对HK惨败的反应唤醒了中国的爱国主义，这是我们一生中从未见过的方式......</span><br>
<span>DragonSeed420</span><br>
<span>I never thought I had much privilege when I lived in China back in 2010. Applying to jobs I got told I wasn’t Chinese enough to I was too Chinese. My Chinese is at HSK 5 too. I think all of it was just to low ball me on salary but w/e. Anyways, these comparison threads do nothing but entrench people’s prejudices. If money and privilege is what we ultimately seek then I’m afraid it’s not enough to confront the problems that Chinese society faces today.</span><br>
<span>I think “overseas Chinese privilege” is something shitty fuerdai kids made up to console themselves after they’ve blown a fortune and flunked out of college.</span><br>
<span>Life would be great for me if I didn’t have to share family wealth with 2 other siblings and I had a family business or properties to inherit. I could just hire an ABC to do all my work while I play dota2 all day. Mainlanders have it so easy man /s</span><br>
<span>2010年当我在中国生活时，我从未想过到我有多少特权。在求职时，不够中国和太过中国我都被说过。我的中文也是汉语水平考试（HSK）5级。我想这一切都只是要压低我的薪水。无论如何，这种比较主题除了加深人们的偏见没有什么作用。如果金钱和特权是我们的根本追求，那么我担心它并不足以应对中国社会今天所面临的问题。</span><br>
<span>我认为“海外华人特权”问题是些顽劣的富二代小孩在挥霍完财富还有考不进大学之后编造出来安慰自己的。</span><br>
<span>如果我不用同其他2个兄弟姐妹来分享家庭财产，并且我有家族企业或财产可以继承，那么生活对我来说实在太美妙了。我可以雇个美籍华人来完成我所有的工作，我就整天耍耍dota2。大陆人中就是有这种拥有简单模式的人。</span><br>
</p><p><b>非喵碳: </b><br>
<span>废狗逐渐书记化， 书记搬知乎，废狗搬龙腾，大锅莫说二锅</span><br>
</p><p><b>mimighost: </b><br>
<span>总结，不如有房</span><br>
</p><p><b>Plague: </b><br>
<span>龙腾的辣鸡请不要往外野倒</span><br>
</p><p><b>机动妖精: </b><br>
<span>白菜毛妹哪里点击领取</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1854745[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
