<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>中国是不是太自信了？ 他们认为自己会战胜任何军事挑战？</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>中国是不是太自信了？ 他们认为自己会战胜任何军事挑战？</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 19:58:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>中国是不是太自信了？ 他们认为自己会战胜任何军事挑战？[100-150]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1837648-1-1.html</link>
      <description>中国是不是太自信了？ 他们认为自己会战胜任何军事挑战？&#13;
Overconfident? China Thinks Its Military Can Win in Almost Any Scenario
&#13;
是不是太自信了？ 中国认为本国军队可以在任何种情况下取得胜利
&#13;
http://img.ltaaa.com/uploadfile/thumb/2019/06/07//1559875626981.jpg
&#13;
Zachary Keck,The National Interest 10 hours ago 
&#13;
Zachary Keck
&#13;
Security,
&#13;
At least accoring to some polls. Can they be right? 
&#13;
Overconfident? China Thinks Its Military Can Win in Almost Any Scenario
&#13;
The vast majority of Chinese citizens believe the People’s Liberation Army (PLA) could seize islands in the East and South China Seas, even if the U.S. military were to intervene in the conflicts.
&#13;
绝大多数中国人认为，即使美国军队介入冲突，中国人民解放军也可以占领东海与南海的岛屿。
&#13;
No less than 87 percent of respondents said that the Chinese military already possessed the capability to take back the Diaoyu/Senkaku Islands from Japan, according to a recent public opinion poll. When asked whether they still believed the PLA could achieve this objective if the U.S. intervened in the conflict, 74 percent said yes.
&#13;
根据最近的一项民意调查，不少于87%的受访者表示，中国军队已经拥有从日本手中夺回钓鱼岛的能力。当被问及美国若介入冲突，他们是否仍然相信解放军能够实现这一目标时，74%的人给予了肯定答复。
&#13;
(This first appeared back in 2015.)
&#13;
The numbers were much the same for the South China Sea. When asked whether they believed the PLA could militarily take back disputed islands in the South China Sea, 85.6 percent of respondents said that China’s military could achieve this objective. Even if the U.S. military intervened on behalf of the Southeast Asian nations, about 73 percent of respondents said they still believed the Chinese military would prevail.
&#13;
中国南海的情况也大致相同。当被问及是否相信中国人民解放军能够以武力收复南海争议岛屿时，85.6%的受访者表示，中国军队能够实现这一目标。即使美国军方为东南亚国家利益出面进行干预，约73%的受访者也仍然表示，他们相信中国军方会取得胜利。
&#13;
评论翻译
&#13;
原创翻译：龙腾网 http://www.ltaaa.com 翻译：bluebit 转载请注明出处
&#13;
论坛地址：http://www.ltaaa.com/bbs/thread-486463-1-1.html
&#13;
Tony
&#13;
Tony43 minutes ago
&#13;
China would lose as the world would shut down its economy and trade.
&#13;
中国将会输能赢，因为世界会终止与它贸易。
&#13;
Matt
&#13;
Matt34 minutes ago
&#13;
China's recent real-world combat experience is next to nil. They employ sly cheap back-door tactics. If their confidence is based on some Huawei gadgets, its misplaced.
&#13;
近代中国实战经验几乎为零。他们利用狡诈取巧的策略。如果他们信心是建立在华为上，那就大错特错了。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/61/28661/comment-1.jpg
&#13;
PresidentFittu
&#13;
PresidentFittu54 minutes ago
&#13;
A land war probably, but they would never be able to transport their Army over water.
&#13;
可能是一场陆地战争，因为他们永远无法通过水路运送军队。
&#13;
John
&#13;
John3 hours ago
&#13;
China could not take the Diaoyu/Senkaku Islands from Japan even if the US did NOT intervene. The Japanese would destroy the Chinese if they ever tried.
&#13;
即使美国不去管，中国也无法从日本手中拿回钓鱼岛。如果日本想干掉中国，他们就会去做了。
&#13;
Anonymous
&#13;
Anonymous6 hours ago
&#13;
They would be very wrong, the Chinese Navy surface ships would be put down in less than 72 hours and their air force would be obliterated in about 1 weeks time. the only part that would take time to locate and destroy would be their submarines, and those realistically would be destroyed in about 2-3 weeks time in a true all out conflict, you can be sure they would have no penns to return to after USA struck their operating bases. Chinese military is the largest paper tiger in history, they have gone under former soviet premises which is quantity over quality. Lastly as someone who does "things" for Area 52, i can say that there are things that exist in USA military now, that if shown to the world, would frighten them so much that the world would unite against USA for war. There are 2 forces the USA has,..the nuclear/conventional forces and then the second secret army/toys hidden in USA in the event they must fight a world war or some fool gets the idea to attempt an invasion of USA mainland. Remember this,..in 1979 the USA black ops programs were using laser cannons to shoot down unmanned passenger airplanes(first technical drone if you will) for testing national shield defense. It's been 40 years.......what do you think exists today......
&#13;
大错特错，中国海军的水面舰艇72小时内就会被击沉，他们空军将在一周内即被消灭。唯一需要花点时间得就是定位摧毁他们的潜艇，儿这些潜艇也将在2-3周的时间内被消灭，在一场真正的全面冲突中，可以肯定的是，美国袭击他们军事基地后，他们啥也剩不下。中国军队是历史上最大的纸老虎，他们就是学前苏联完蛋的，那就是数量重于质量。最后，作为一个曾在52区做过“事情”的人，我可以说，现在美国军队中藏有的一些东西，如果向世界展示，就会吓到他们，但那样全世界就会团结起来反对美国。美国有…核弹与常规两股力量，然后是隐藏在美国的第二秘密军队和(那个）“玩具”，万一他们一定想打一场世界大战，或者一些傻瓜有入侵美国的想法。请记住，1979年，美国黑色行动计划用于测试国家防御系统的激光炮打掉过一架无人客机。四十年过去了，想想一下（这东西）现在能会怎么样。
&#13;
Matt
&#13;
Matt46 minutes ago
&#13;
Literally nobody in their massive military has ever fought in a war. They are shiny and look good on paper, but they are completely untested in war.
&#13;
他们军队庞大，几乎没人参加过战争。中国也就是纸上谈兵完全没有实战经验。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/61/28661/comment-2.jpg
&#13;
Reyes
&#13;
Reyes28 minutes ago
&#13;
I believe Panda Express is better than any Chinese food in China. That is fact.
&#13;
我相信熊猫快餐比中国的任何中餐都好吃。这是事实。
&#13;
Anonymous
&#13;
Anonymous1 hour ago
&#13;
No winners in a war. Lives and places will be destroyed.
&#13;
战争中没有赢家。只有摧毁生命与和平。
&#13;
dobey
&#13;
dobey35 minutes ago
&#13;
It might be what they say but I seriously doubt they are that naive and if they truly believed that they likely would’ve already tried to take Taiwan.
&#13;
这是他们以为的吧，但我严重怀疑他们是否天真，要是真认为可以，没准台湾早占领了。
&#13;
Ma Qin
&#13;
Ma Qin3 hours ago
&#13;
As the Korea and Vietnam wars demonstrared ,USA is definiteltly the biggest paper tiger ,unable to defeat even the weak opponents then and let alone the stronger ones.
&#13;
正如朝鲜战争和越南战争所证明的那样，美国无疑是最大的纸老虎，连弱小的对手都打不过，更不用说强大的对手了
&#13;
Shlomo
&#13;
Shlomo31 minutes ago
&#13;
America still hasn't won wars against Third World powers like Afghanistan &amp; Iraq after 16 years of trying. They have absolutely no hope of beating a superpower like China in a war.
&#13;
经过16年的努力，美国仍没赢得对阿富汗和伊拉克等**强国的战争。美国绝没希望通过一场战争打败像中国这样的超级大国了。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/62/28662/comment-1.jpg
&#13;
nik
&#13;
nik36 minutes ago
&#13;
It just shows you how much a brainwashed nation believes about its own Government's propaganda.
&#13;
它只是向你展示了一个被洗脑的国家是多么相信自己的政府宣传。
&#13;
Reply3
&#13;
WT
&#13;
WT22 minutes ago
&#13;
The rhetoric is absurd. A trade disagreement spirals into talk of military conflict? Nationalism is certainly alive and well on both sides of the Pacific. Fact is the US-China relationship since '79 has significantly benefited both countries and kept the Soviets in check. US-China is the single most important bi-lateral relationship in the world; nothing comes close. China has zero interest to engage the US in a military conflict. The war mongers in the US just looking for a fight having no successes since Grenada.
&#13;
这种诉说方式太荒诞了。贸易分歧升级为军事冲突?太平洋两岸的民族主义无疑是和谐的。事实上，自1979年以来，美中关系给两国带来了巨大的好处，并遏制了苏联。美中是世界上唯一最重要的双边关系;什么都比不上。中国对美国卷入的军事冲突毫无兴趣。美国的战争贩子只是在寻找一场自格林纳达以来毫无胜算的战争。
&#13;
Peter
&#13;
Peter55 minutes ago
&#13;
I seem to recall another Asian country that was all full of themselves, and they tried seizing islands across the Pacific theaters. They even got in a devastating sneak attack against the American Pacific fleet. But still, it didn't work out very well for them, and I don't see China doing much better!
&#13;
我好像记得另一个亚洲国家，他们充满自信，试图占领太平洋战场对面的岛屿。他们甚至对美国太平洋舰队发动了毁灭性的偷袭。但是，他们没做好，我不认为中国也能做的更好。
&#13;
Rex
&#13;
Rex1 hour ago
&#13;
Well, just dont underestimate your opponent. And keep in mind 350 nukes and the ability to deliver them is no joke. It ain't 7000 but still can wipe us out.
&#13;
嗯，不要低估你的对手。记住，350枚核弹可不是闹着玩的。虽然远不及7000，但还是可以足够毁灭我们。
&#13;
Joel
&#13;
Joel23 minutes ago
&#13;
The only other nation in the world that could even remotely compete with the US in terms of military might and experience is Russia, and even they are a very distant second.
&#13;
在军事实力与经验方面，世界上唯一能够与美国进行远距离竞争的国家是俄罗斯，即便是俄罗斯，也远落美国之后吧。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/62/28662/comment-2.jpg
&#13;
Sk
&#13;
Sk25 minutes ago
&#13;
There is zero reason to go to war other than the rich men in America are losing their relative strength to the rich men in Asia. There is no ideological difference? there is no animosity between any of the people if the world. This has everything to do with one side is losing wealth to the other side.
&#13;
除了美国富人输给亚洲富人外，毫无理由发动战争。意识形态有什么不同吗?世界上任何一个民族之间都没有仇恨。这一切都与一方财富流失到另一方有关。
&#13;
JT
&#13;
JT56 minutes ago
&#13;
Two to three weeks? We can’t even end the terrorists in the Middle East that don’t have nearly as much military power...
&#13;
两到三周?我们甚至消灭不了中东的恐怖分子，因为那里没有那么多的军事力量
&#13;
FuManchuJr
&#13;
FuManchuJr1 hour ago
&#13;
This is home ground advantage. 
&#13;
Crossing a sea to attack an enemy is tough enough but to cross an ocean to attack a country with more than 4.25 times their population size is plain suicidal.
&#13;
跨过大洋打击敌人就已经很困难了，跨过大洋海还要攻击一个人口超过美国4.25倍的国家，那简直就是自杀。
&#13;
Ted S
&#13;
Ted S24 minutes ago
&#13;
I suspect those islands that China has militarized just might cease to exist very quickly, thus nothing to take back.
&#13;
我怀疑那些中国军事化的岛屿可能很快就会不复存在，因为没了就没必要要了
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/62/28662/comment-3.jpg
&#13;
Obscure
&#13;
Obscure54 minutes ago
&#13;
In its backyards, it undoubtedly can and will obliterate any military in the world. China's main power is her highly advanced projectiles. They have millions of them. I mean millions literally
&#13;
在他们的地盘，毫无疑问，中国能够消灭世界上任何军队。中国的主要力量是其高度先进的导弹。他们有数百万。我的意思是数-百-万
&#13;
Jamie
&#13;
Jamiein 11 seconds
&#13;
China can not figure anything out themselves they steal technology because communist can not think for themselves
&#13;
中国自己什么都搞不懂，他们只有偷技术，因为中国人不会独立思考
&#13;
bene
&#13;
bene36 minutes ago
&#13;
Most Chinese would believe the earth is flat if their communist masters told them that.
&#13;
如果他们的GC主义主人告诉他们地球是平的，大多数中国人就会都信</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>鸟耶稣: </b><br>
<span>话说我爸就还真觉得解放军是纸老虎日本强无敌毛子不可战胜美帝至尊王者</span><br>
</p><p><b>weary10: </b><br>
<span>那你们16年为什么在南海怂了啊？</span><br>
</p><p><b>纸皮: </b><br>
<span>转这些垃圾是想麻痹我们吗！敌特行为！</span><br>
</p><p><b>pilipala: </b><br>
<span>半江瑟瑟半江红 发表于 2019-06-07 15:57:11</span><br>
<span>这是这篇垃圾帖子里最傻逼的一句话，没有之一</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HUAWEI LYA-AL10, Android 9上的v2.1.2 ...味觉失灵了吧</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>Yukine_Chris: </b><br>
<span>乃木坂裕人 发表于 2019-6-7 16:42</span><br>
<span>美国成立之后除了墨西哥和日本，好像就没国家打到过美国本土？</span><br>
<span>白宫是加拿大烧的，夏威夷不算本土</span><br>
</p><p><b>vandechine: </b><br>
<span>icefcold 发表于 2019-6-7 20:49</span><br>
<span>胜利本来就不大可能，军费和实战经验差距都是事实，但足够让美国付出葬送国际地位和未来的惨重代价，这楼里 ...</span><br>
<span>没必要觉得的必要，事实如此罢了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>阿萨托斯: </b><br>
<span>至少核弹灭纽约没问题</span><br>
</p><p><b>冷冷: </b><br>
<span>打仗有什么意思，应该放出双方战狼对咬</span><br>
</p><p><b>ysasz: </b><br>
<span>icefcold 发表于 2019-6-7 20:49</span><br>
<span>胜利本来就不大可能，军费和实战经验差距都是事实，但足够让美国付出葬送国际地位和未来的惨重代价，这楼里 ...</span><br>
<span>不觉得能赢，但是有拖着美帝和全世界一起死的能力。</span><br>
</p><p><b>jojohunter: </b><br>
<span>sdhf028397 发表于 2019-6-7 17:03</span><br>
<span>我是相信三十年前的nasa有一堆黑科技的现在？土星五号还造得出来么</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 ...</span><br>
<span>书记:我不管我不管美利坚就是领先tg五十年，spacex人类希望日本氢氧机无敌哒！</span><br>
</p><p><b>liens: </b><br>
<span>icefcold 发表于 2019-6-7 20:49</span><br>
<span>胜利本来就不大可能，军费和实战经验差距都是事实，但足够让美国付出葬送国际地位和未来的惨重代价，这楼里 ...</span><br>
<span>中国又不会对美国本土发起战争，区域防守你美本来就赢不了，扔核弹都赢不了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>ggg45g: </b><br>
<span>首先战争是双输，中国永远不会主动挑起战争。其次中国的自信是建立在建国前后与几次对外反击作战中的。最后中国在保留作战精神的同时拥有先进的武器水平</span><br>
</p><p><b>魔法酪饼: </b><br>
<span>icefcold 发表于 2019-6-7 20:49</span><br>
<span>胜利本来就不大可能，军费和实战经验差距都是事实，但足够让美国付出葬送国际地位和未来的惨重代价，这楼里 ...</span><br>
<span>如果是都不动核武器，美利坚打上门，我国打防御战，我觉得我国能赢。</span><br>
</p><p><b>redivan: </b><br>
<span>中国是不是太自信了？ 他们认为自己会战胜任何军事挑战？ </span><br>
<span>不，我们不会，但我们可以掀桌子。</span><br>
</p><p><b>redivan: </b><br>
<span>乃木坂裕人 发表于 2019-6-7 16:42</span><br>
<span>美国成立之后除了墨西哥和日本，好像就没国家打到过美国本土？</span><br>
<span>加拿大军曾把白宫烧了泄愤。</span><br>
</p><p><b>余桥: </b><br>
<span>龙腾好像删帖了</span><br>
</p><p><b>zhaoyanggolden: </b><br>
<span>如果他们是真的这么想，我还挺开心的。</span><br>
</p><p><b>fallout: </b><br>
<span>不是我们一定会赢是我们一定要赢啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>克拉苏: </b><br>
<span>regular 发表于 2019-6-7 20:58</span><br>
<span>那这样的话，下一问就该是：中国不服，美军没啥还不A上去？</span><br>
<span>美军是爱好和平的自由战士啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>南风森琉璃: </b><br>
<span>Chinese military is the largest paper tiger in history, they have gone under former soviet premises which is quantity over quality.</span><br>
<span>"Paper tiger" is a literal English translation of the Chinese phrase zhilaohu (纸老虎／紙老虎). The term refers to something or someone that claims or appears to be powerful and/or threatening, but is actually ineffectual and unable to withstand challenge.</span><br>
<span>神奇的出口转内销</span><br>
</p><p><b>坦克: </b><br>
<span>52区那个怕不是中二少年幻想过度烧坏脑子了。。。</span><br>
</p><p><b>废狗: </b><br>
<span>坦克 发表于 2019-6-7 22:38</span><br>
<span>52区那个怕不是中二少年幻想过度烧坏脑子了。。。</span><br>
<span>反串黑？</span><br>
</p><p><b>13102587870: </b><br>
<span>icefcold 发表于 2019-6-7 20:49</span><br>
<span>胜利本来就不大可能，军费和实战经验差距都是事实，但足够让美国付出葬送国际地位和未来的惨重代价，这楼里 ...</span><br>
<span>距离的暴政呗，嘉手纳的F-22能在中导下活下来几架，关岛的F-22能飞到台海的又有几架，美国军费再怎么多，也撑不住在台海玩猛禽墙吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>血满沙场: </b><br>
<span>南风森琉璃 发表于 2019-6-7 22:32</span><br>
<span>Chinese military is the largest paper tiger in history, they have gone under former soviet premises...</span><br>
<span>说paper tiger的那位ID是ma qin，可能是战乎局外勤。</span><br>
</p><p><b>KA0827: </b><br>
<span>milkon 发表于 2019-6-7 15:58</span><br>
<span>在，看看朝鲜战争？</span><br>
<span>我猜是不是很多美国人根本不知道朝鲜战争和中国有什么关系</span><br>
</p><p><b>phyc: </b><br>
<span>血满沙场 发表于 2019-6-7 22:51</span><br>
<span>说paper tiger的那位ID是ma qin，可能是战乎局外勤。</span><br>
<span>用力过猛</span><br>
</p><p><b>银鍠吞佛: </b><br>
<span>只能说外国的战忽局也是有干活的</span><br>
</p><p><b>初音比良坂: </b><br>
<span>icefcold 发表于 2019-6-7 20:49</span><br>
<span>胜利本来就不大可能，军费和实战经验差距都是事实，但足够让美国付出葬送国际地位和未来的惨重代价，这楼里 ...</span><br>
<span>不是全面战争而是第一岛链的局部战争的话，中国不说赢，但我也不觉得美帝能赢。全面开片，中美又不是傻子，那只会便宜了其他国家</span><br>
</p><p><b>qratosone: </b><br>
<span>icefcold 发表于 2019-6-7 20:49</span><br>
<span>胜利本来就不大可能，军费和实战经验差距都是事实，但足够让美国付出葬送国际地位和未来的惨重代价，这楼里 ...</span><br>
<span>在几个主要预设战场，比如第一岛链、南海，中国认真打的话基本上能确保局部打赢。而对于泥川宣战万国的今天，美国刚开始打输了，然后就没有然后了——由此带来的多米诺骨牌效应足以自发推倒美国霸权。</span><br>
</p><p><b>688i: </b><br>
<span>KA0827 发表于 2019-6-7 22:57</span><br>
<span>我猜是不是很多美国人根本不知道朝鲜战争和中国有什么关系</span><br>
<span>知道一些的，美军损失3万，屠杀100万PLA那种。南朝鲜当然不是人。</span><br>
</p><p><b>688i: </b><br>
<span>坦克 发表于 2019-6-7 22:38</span><br>
<span>52区那个怕不是中二少年幻想过度烧坏脑子了。。。</span><br>
<span>未必，这个帖子如果是最近发的话，那位中二少年大概看了很久前一个美国专家的发言，那位公然宣称美国巨大的技术优势，现在台面上这些不过是技术和资金妥协的产物，如果美国真受到威胁，保险箱里技术拿出来立刻吊打全世界10年以上。</span><br>
</p><p><b>青年A: </b><br>
<span>战忽局做过头了，你看中国人都信了</span><br>
<span>— from samsung SM-G930F, Android 8.0.0 of S1 Next Goose v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>Kozakai: </b><br>
<span>kabunsan 发表于 2019-6-7 16:45</span><br>
<span>据说加拿大烧过白宫？</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Essential Products PH-1, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2 ...</span><br>
<span>两次，当时还没独立，是自治领</span><br>
</p><p><b>普雷尔公: </b><br>
<span>04年美军中央司令部司令在国会做的总结发言，简直就是刚从大魔王萨达姆手上拯救了全世界的态度</span><br>
</p><p><b>kpkxyshlyj: </b><br>
<span>icefcold 发表于 2019-6-7 20:49</span><br>
<span>胜利本来就不大可能，军费和实战经验差距都是事实，但足够让美国付出葬送国际地位和未来的惨重代价，这楼里 ...</span><br>
<span>算得上大国的国家之间的常规战争已经很久没打过了… 美国人也一直是虐菜而已</span><br>
<span>其实连现在用的这套主战兵器都是脑补理论和战场情况发展出来的 实际打起来到底是什么样 谁也不知道 </span><br>
</p><p><b>林拓: </b><br>
<span>中国可能战胜不了，你来战胜中国试试呗~</span><br>
</p><p><b>chickensoup: </b><br>
<span>688i 发表于 2019-06-07 23:10:23</span><br>
<span>未必，这个帖子如果是最近发的话，那位中二少年大概看了很久前一个美国专家的发言，那位公然宣称美国巨大 ...保险箱里有5G技术吗？原来华为的5G技术真的是从美帝偷的啊？</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>samsoncheng: </b><br>
<span>icefcold 发表于 2019-6-7 20:49</span><br>
<span>胜利本来就不大可能，军费和实战经验差距都是事实，但足够让美国付出葬送国际地位和未来的惨重代价，这楼里 ...</span><br>
<span>第一岛链内的防御作战不至于你说的那样</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 nubia NX595J, Android 7.1.1上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>chia7: </b><br>
<span>弱小和无知不是生存的障碍，傲慢才是</span><br>
</p><p><b>坦克: </b><br>
<span>688i 发表于 2019-6-7 23:10</span><br>
<span>未必，这个帖子如果是最近发的话，那位中二少年大概看了很久前一个美国专家的发言，那位公然宣称美国巨大 ...</span><br>
<span>不是，正常来说，美帝压箱底的技术储备拿出来领先中国十年这种事情认真想一下也是完全合乎逻辑的，但那位中二少年的发言很明显就是那种自己参加了最新型高达的开发但是被封口了虽然啥都知道但就是不能说的语气呀</span><br>
</p><p><b>kazuma: </b><br>
<span>泥潭咬钩的傻鱼真多</span><br>
</p><p><b>KUSOSO: </b><br>
<span>就是</span><br>
</p><p><b>gkstill: </b><br>
<span>kazuma 发表于 2019-6-8 02:56</span><br>
<span>泥潭咬钩的傻鱼真多</span><br>
<span>哪有鱼啊，我看都是渔夫在水里打架。</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Sony G8142, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1837648[100-150]</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>中国是不是太自信了？ 他们认为自己会战胜任何军事挑战？[50-100]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1837648-1-1.html</link>
      <description>中国是不是太自信了？ 他们认为自己会战胜任何军事挑战？&#13;
Overconfident? China Thinks Its Military Can Win in Almost Any Scenario
&#13;
是不是太自信了？ 中国认为本国军队可以在任何种情况下取得胜利
&#13;
http://img.ltaaa.com/uploadfile/thumb/2019/06/07//1559875626981.jpg
&#13;
Zachary Keck,The National Interest 10 hours ago 
&#13;
Zachary Keck
&#13;
Security,
&#13;
At least accoring to some polls. Can they be right? 
&#13;
Overconfident? China Thinks Its Military Can Win in Almost Any Scenario
&#13;
The vast majority of Chinese citizens believe the People’s Liberation Army (PLA) could seize islands in the East and South China Seas, even if the U.S. military were to intervene in the conflicts.
&#13;
绝大多数中国人认为，即使美国军队介入冲突，中国人民解放军也可以占领东海与南海的岛屿。
&#13;
No less than 87 percent of respondents said that the Chinese military already possessed the capability to take back the Diaoyu/Senkaku Islands from Japan, according to a recent public opinion poll. When asked whether they still believed the PLA could achieve this objective if the U.S. intervened in the conflict, 74 percent said yes.
&#13;
根据最近的一项民意调查，不少于87%的受访者表示，中国军队已经拥有从日本手中夺回钓鱼岛的能力。当被问及美国若介入冲突，他们是否仍然相信解放军能够实现这一目标时，74%的人给予了肯定答复。
&#13;
(This first appeared back in 2015.)
&#13;
The numbers were much the same for the South China Sea. When asked whether they believed the PLA could militarily take back disputed islands in the South China Sea, 85.6 percent of respondents said that China’s military could achieve this objective. Even if the U.S. military intervened on behalf of the Southeast Asian nations, about 73 percent of respondents said they still believed the Chinese military would prevail.
&#13;
中国南海的情况也大致相同。当被问及是否相信中国人民解放军能够以武力收复南海争议岛屿时，85.6%的受访者表示，中国军队能够实现这一目标。即使美国军方为东南亚国家利益出面进行干预，约73%的受访者也仍然表示，他们相信中国军方会取得胜利。
&#13;
评论翻译
&#13;
原创翻译：龙腾网 http://www.ltaaa.com 翻译：bluebit 转载请注明出处
&#13;
论坛地址：http://www.ltaaa.com/bbs/thread-486463-1-1.html
&#13;
Tony
&#13;
Tony43 minutes ago
&#13;
China would lose as the world would shut down its economy and trade.
&#13;
中国将会输能赢，因为世界会终止与它贸易。
&#13;
Matt
&#13;
Matt34 minutes ago
&#13;
China's recent real-world combat experience is next to nil. They employ sly cheap back-door tactics. If their confidence is based on some Huawei gadgets, its misplaced.
&#13;
近代中国实战经验几乎为零。他们利用狡诈取巧的策略。如果他们信心是建立在华为上，那就大错特错了。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/61/28661/comment-1.jpg
&#13;
PresidentFittu
&#13;
PresidentFittu54 minutes ago
&#13;
A land war probably, but they would never be able to transport their Army over water.
&#13;
可能是一场陆地战争，因为他们永远无法通过水路运送军队。
&#13;
John
&#13;
John3 hours ago
&#13;
China could not take the Diaoyu/Senkaku Islands from Japan even if the US did NOT intervene. The Japanese would destroy the Chinese if they ever tried.
&#13;
即使美国不去管，中国也无法从日本手中拿回钓鱼岛。如果日本想干掉中国，他们就会去做了。
&#13;
Anonymous
&#13;
Anonymous6 hours ago
&#13;
They would be very wrong, the Chinese Navy surface ships would be put down in less than 72 hours and their air force would be obliterated in about 1 weeks time. the only part that would take time to locate and destroy would be their submarines, and those realistically would be destroyed in about 2-3 weeks time in a true all out conflict, you can be sure they would have no penns to return to after USA struck their operating bases. Chinese military is the largest paper tiger in history, they have gone under former soviet premises which is quantity over quality. Lastly as someone who does "things" for Area 52, i can say that there are things that exist in USA military now, that if shown to the world, would frighten them so much that the world would unite against USA for war. There are 2 forces the USA has,..the nuclear/conventional forces and then the second secret army/toys hidden in USA in the event they must fight a world war or some fool gets the idea to attempt an invasion of USA mainland. Remember this,..in 1979 the USA black ops programs were using laser cannons to shoot down unmanned passenger airplanes(first technical drone if you will) for testing national shield defense. It's been 40 years.......what do you think exists today......
&#13;
大错特错，中国海军的水面舰艇72小时内就会被击沉，他们空军将在一周内即被消灭。唯一需要花点时间得就是定位摧毁他们的潜艇，儿这些潜艇也将在2-3周的时间内被消灭，在一场真正的全面冲突中，可以肯定的是，美国袭击他们军事基地后，他们啥也剩不下。中国军队是历史上最大的纸老虎，他们就是学前苏联完蛋的，那就是数量重于质量。最后，作为一个曾在52区做过“事情”的人，我可以说，现在美国军队中藏有的一些东西，如果向世界展示，就会吓到他们，但那样全世界就会团结起来反对美国。美国有…核弹与常规两股力量，然后是隐藏在美国的第二秘密军队和(那个）“玩具”，万一他们一定想打一场世界大战，或者一些傻瓜有入侵美国的想法。请记住，1979年，美国黑色行动计划用于测试国家防御系统的激光炮打掉过一架无人客机。四十年过去了，想想一下（这东西）现在能会怎么样。
&#13;
Matt
&#13;
Matt46 minutes ago
&#13;
Literally nobody in their massive military has ever fought in a war. They are shiny and look good on paper, but they are completely untested in war.
&#13;
他们军队庞大，几乎没人参加过战争。中国也就是纸上谈兵完全没有实战经验。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/61/28661/comment-2.jpg
&#13;
Reyes
&#13;
Reyes28 minutes ago
&#13;
I believe Panda Express is better than any Chinese food in China. That is fact.
&#13;
我相信熊猫快餐比中国的任何中餐都好吃。这是事实。
&#13;
Anonymous
&#13;
Anonymous1 hour ago
&#13;
No winners in a war. Lives and places will be destroyed.
&#13;
战争中没有赢家。只有摧毁生命与和平。
&#13;
dobey
&#13;
dobey35 minutes ago
&#13;
It might be what they say but I seriously doubt they are that naive and if they truly believed that they likely would’ve already tried to take Taiwan.
&#13;
这是他们以为的吧，但我严重怀疑他们是否天真，要是真认为可以，没准台湾早占领了。
&#13;
Ma Qin
&#13;
Ma Qin3 hours ago
&#13;
As the Korea and Vietnam wars demonstrared ,USA is definiteltly the biggest paper tiger ,unable to defeat even the weak opponents then and let alone the stronger ones.
&#13;
正如朝鲜战争和越南战争所证明的那样，美国无疑是最大的纸老虎，连弱小的对手都打不过，更不用说强大的对手了
&#13;
Shlomo
&#13;
Shlomo31 minutes ago
&#13;
America still hasn't won wars against Third World powers like Afghanistan &amp; Iraq after 16 years of trying. They have absolutely no hope of beating a superpower like China in a war.
&#13;
经过16年的努力，美国仍没赢得对阿富汗和伊拉克等**强国的战争。美国绝没希望通过一场战争打败像中国这样的超级大国了。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/62/28662/comment-1.jpg
&#13;
nik
&#13;
nik36 minutes ago
&#13;
It just shows you how much a brainwashed nation believes about its own Government's propaganda.
&#13;
它只是向你展示了一个被洗脑的国家是多么相信自己的政府宣传。
&#13;
Reply3
&#13;
WT
&#13;
WT22 minutes ago
&#13;
The rhetoric is absurd. A trade disagreement spirals into talk of military conflict? Nationalism is certainly alive and well on both sides of the Pacific. Fact is the US-China relationship since '79 has significantly benefited both countries and kept the Soviets in check. US-China is the single most important bi-lateral relationship in the world; nothing comes close. China has zero interest to engage the US in a military conflict. The war mongers in the US just looking for a fight having no successes since Grenada.
&#13;
这种诉说方式太荒诞了。贸易分歧升级为军事冲突?太平洋两岸的民族主义无疑是和谐的。事实上，自1979年以来，美中关系给两国带来了巨大的好处，并遏制了苏联。美中是世界上唯一最重要的双边关系;什么都比不上。中国对美国卷入的军事冲突毫无兴趣。美国的战争贩子只是在寻找一场自格林纳达以来毫无胜算的战争。
&#13;
Peter
&#13;
Peter55 minutes ago
&#13;
I seem to recall another Asian country that was all full of themselves, and they tried seizing islands across the Pacific theaters. They even got in a devastating sneak attack against the American Pacific fleet. But still, it didn't work out very well for them, and I don't see China doing much better!
&#13;
我好像记得另一个亚洲国家，他们充满自信，试图占领太平洋战场对面的岛屿。他们甚至对美国太平洋舰队发动了毁灭性的偷袭。但是，他们没做好，我不认为中国也能做的更好。
&#13;
Rex
&#13;
Rex1 hour ago
&#13;
Well, just dont underestimate your opponent. And keep in mind 350 nukes and the ability to deliver them is no joke. It ain't 7000 but still can wipe us out.
&#13;
嗯，不要低估你的对手。记住，350枚核弹可不是闹着玩的。虽然远不及7000，但还是可以足够毁灭我们。
&#13;
Joel
&#13;
Joel23 minutes ago
&#13;
The only other nation in the world that could even remotely compete with the US in terms of military might and experience is Russia, and even they are a very distant second.
&#13;
在军事实力与经验方面，世界上唯一能够与美国进行远距离竞争的国家是俄罗斯，即便是俄罗斯，也远落美国之后吧。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/62/28662/comment-2.jpg
&#13;
Sk
&#13;
Sk25 minutes ago
&#13;
There is zero reason to go to war other than the rich men in America are losing their relative strength to the rich men in Asia. There is no ideological difference? there is no animosity between any of the people if the world. This has everything to do with one side is losing wealth to the other side.
&#13;
除了美国富人输给亚洲富人外，毫无理由发动战争。意识形态有什么不同吗?世界上任何一个民族之间都没有仇恨。这一切都与一方财富流失到另一方有关。
&#13;
JT
&#13;
JT56 minutes ago
&#13;
Two to three weeks? We can’t even end the terrorists in the Middle East that don’t have nearly as much military power...
&#13;
两到三周?我们甚至消灭不了中东的恐怖分子，因为那里没有那么多的军事力量
&#13;
FuManchuJr
&#13;
FuManchuJr1 hour ago
&#13;
This is home ground advantage. 
&#13;
Crossing a sea to attack an enemy is tough enough but to cross an ocean to attack a country with more than 4.25 times their population size is plain suicidal.
&#13;
跨过大洋打击敌人就已经很困难了，跨过大洋海还要攻击一个人口超过美国4.25倍的国家，那简直就是自杀。
&#13;
Ted S
&#13;
Ted S24 minutes ago
&#13;
I suspect those islands that China has militarized just might cease to exist very quickly, thus nothing to take back.
&#13;
我怀疑那些中国军事化的岛屿可能很快就会不复存在，因为没了就没必要要了
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/62/28662/comment-3.jpg
&#13;
Obscure
&#13;
Obscure54 minutes ago
&#13;
In its backyards, it undoubtedly can and will obliterate any military in the world. China's main power is her highly advanced projectiles. They have millions of them. I mean millions literally
&#13;
在他们的地盘，毫无疑问，中国能够消灭世界上任何军队。中国的主要力量是其高度先进的导弹。他们有数百万。我的意思是数-百-万
&#13;
Jamie
&#13;
Jamiein 11 seconds
&#13;
China can not figure anything out themselves they steal technology because communist can not think for themselves
&#13;
中国自己什么都搞不懂，他们只有偷技术，因为中国人不会独立思考
&#13;
bene
&#13;
bene36 minutes ago
&#13;
Most Chinese would believe the earth is flat if their communist masters told them that.
&#13;
如果他们的GC主义主人告诉他们地球是平的，大多数中国人就会都信</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>半江瑟瑟半江红: </b><br>
<span>JWJking 发表于 2019-6-7 16:41</span><br>
<span>但我觉得Panda Express真的很好吃啊，甜甜的，还不贵，就是种类太少了</span><br>
<span>就是劣化咕咾肉作法做出来的鸡肉，喜欢吃酸甜口国内咕咾肉不更好吃嘛</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HUAWEI LYA-AL10, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>传奇820: </b><br>
<span>魔法酪饼 发表于 2019-6-7 16:01</span><br>
<span>这贴不是挺有用的么。。。</span><br>
<span>证明美国群众已经无法理性的面对面前的情况，宁愿用一些荒谬的想法来欺骗自己来 ...</span><br>
<span>这是一方面·······同时老美民众对中国的实际实力和发展程度几乎一无所知吧全是他们媒体片面报道</span><br>
</p><p><b>我要金坷垃i: </b><br>
<span>看乐了，战忽局的工作还是很到位的</span><br>
<span>但是贬中餐的就不能忍了</span><br>
</p><p><b>你妈的为什么: </b><br>
<span>半江瑟瑟半江红 发表于 2019-6-7 15:57</span><br>
<span>这是这篇垃圾帖子里最傻逼的一句话，没有之一</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HUAWEI LYA-AL10, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v ...</span><br>
<span>我觉得是表现最好的巨魔嘲讽啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>風駿: </b><br>
<span>说起来，国外有没有这种特地搬运中国网民评论并翻译成英文给网民看的情况？</span><br>
</p><p><b>alerbe: </b><br>
<span>卡缪911 发表于 2019-6-7 16:59</span><br>
<span>吃过panda express的咕佬肉和糖醋肉，觉得二者没任何区别，只有甜味。</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1 ...</span><br>
<span>区别只有酱汁，问题是两种酱吃起来也差不多。其实美式中餐里最搞笑的就是超市里卖的那种四川酱了，拿来炒炒就是各种四川xx</span><br>
</p><p><b>sdhf028397: </b><br>
<span>我是相信三十年前的nasa有一堆黑科技的现在？土星五号还造得出来么</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>luang: </b><br>
<span>之所以没有立刻开始武统军事上的考量其实是次要的吧</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>thewingz: </b><br>
<span>luang 发表于 2019-6-7 17:04</span><br>
<span>之所以没有立刻开始武统军事上的考量其实是次要的吧</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端 ...</span><br>
<span>老大早就定调了啊，中国人不打中国人，只要对岸不独立，那就是中国人</span><br>
</p><p><b>菲特妹: </b><br>
<span>红夜殇雨 发表于 2019-6-7 16:54</span><br>
<span>也证明了你至今不知道美国纽约地铁连2G信号都没有，拿我国和第三个世界基建国家比的被洗脑事实。</span><br>
<span> ...</span><br>
<span>可是我想说的是，这贴主楼里面的美国人证明了一个被洗脑的国家是多么相信自己的政府宣传。</span><br>
</p><p><b>zyc1629: </b><br>
<span>nik</span><br>
<span>nik36 minutes ago</span><br>
<span>It just shows you how much a brainwashed nation believes about its own Government's propaganda.</span><br>
<span>它只是向你展示了一个被洗脑的国家是多么相信自己的政府宣传。</span><br>
<span>And why beholdest thou the mote that is in thy brother's eye, but considerest not the beam that is in thine own eye?</span><br>
</p><p><b>zyc1629: </b><br>
<span>红夜殇雨 发表于 2019-6-7 16:54</span><br>
<span>也证明了你至今不知道美国纽约地铁连2G信号都没有，拿我国和第三个世界基建国家比的被洗脑事实。</span><br>
<span> ...</span><br>
<span>老细你这个语文不行啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>ののワ: </b><br>
<span>大错特错，中国海军的水面舰艇72小时内就会被击沉，他们空军将在一周内即被消灭。唯一需要花点时间得就是定位摧毁他们的潜艇，儿这些潜艇也将在2-3周的时间内被消灭，在一场真正的全面冲突中，可以肯定的是，美国袭击他们军事基地后，他们啥也剩不下。中国军队是历史上最大的纸老虎，他们就是学前苏联完蛋的，那就是数量重于质量。最后，作为一个曾在52区做过“事情”的人，我可以说，现在美国军队中藏有的一些东西，如果向世界展示，就会吓到他们，但那样全世界就会团结起来反对美国。美国有…核弹与常规两股力量，然后是隐藏在美国的第二秘密军队和(那个）“玩具”，万一他们一定想打一场世界大战，或者一些傻瓜有入侵美国的想法。请记住，1979年，美国黑色行动计划用于测试国家防御系统的激光炮打掉过一架无人客机。四十年过去了，想想一下（这东西）现在能会怎么样。操喷了美国知乎这说话方式跟中国知乎完全一模一样</span><br>
</p><p><b>rhubarb: </b><br>
<span>老美民众原来被洗脑成这样了</span><br>
</p><p><b>wind319415: </b><br>
<span>戏谑二次元 发表于 2019-6-7 16:01</span><br>
<span>反正制定政策的不会是这些傻逼</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 Android客户端 ...</span><br>
<span>现在看也未必，傻逼老了变成了老傻逼</span><br>
</p><p><b>韶华白首: </b><br>
<span>民众都是愚蠢的，我想起很久以前翻译美军在阿富汗的评论，如出一辙，换汤不换药</span><br>
</p><p><b>韶华白首: </b><br>
<span>乔伊 发表于 2019-6-7 16:58</span><br>
<span>米帝对内的战忽局实在太厉害</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
<span>论如何洗脑，美国人说第一没人敢说第二。</span><br>
</p><p><b>Okumur: </b><br>
<span>中国和美国都觉得另一方被自己政府洗脑了，而且都觉得自己比对方更了解彼此的国家。</span><br>
<span>洗脑真是个好词，应该是中文对英语逆向输出的所有词汇中，频率最高/使用最广/接受度最深/最喜闻乐见的非专有名词了</span><br>
</p><p><b>Processed: </b><br>
<span>rhubarb 发表于 2019-6-7 17:26</span><br>
<span>老美民众原来被洗脑成这样了</span><br>
<span>毕竟美国是从根子上毁灭了普通群众的阅读能力</span><br>
</p><p><b>韶华白首: </b><br>
<span>ののワ 发表于 2019-6-7 17:26</span><br>
<span>操喷了美国知乎这说话方式跟中国知乎完全一模一样</span><br>
<span>逼呼的留学党不要太多。</span><br>
</p><p><b>悲伤的风中云: </b><br>
<span>I believe Panda Express is better than any Chinese food in China. That is fact.</span><br>
<span>我爱死这句话了 这是我今天下午的笑点</span><br>
<span>----发送自 STAGE1 App for Android.</span><br>
</p><p><b>pkuworm: </b><br>
<span>52区笑翻了</span><br>
</p><p><b>霜叶舞影: </b><br>
<span>ののワ 发表于 2019-6-7 17:26</span><br>
<span>操喷了美国知乎这说话方式跟中国知乎完全一模一样</span><br>
<span>这人是cod忠实玩家吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>lhyxw: </b><br>
<span>戏谑二次元 发表于 2019-6-7 16:01</span><br>
<span>反正制定政策的不会是这些傻逼</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 Android客户端 ...</span><br>
<span>你是说特朗普团队吗？</span><br>
</p><p><b>御坂MKII: </b><br>
<span>China hasn't done too well in conflicts (with anyone stronger than peasants) in the past several centuries</span><br>
</p><p><b>御坂MKII: </b><br>
<span> 看完了 整个水平也太低了 还是转点儿比较正常的评论吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>Sliark: </b><br>
<span>cpuisme 发表于 2019-6-7 16:20</span><br>
<span>本来战争就是双输。</span><br>
<span>中国群众有信心的是解放军守卫国土的决心。</span><br>
<span>不惜代价的决心。</span><br>
<span>如果美国（在军事上）被揍了</span><br>
<span>那它还有个锤子资本搞禁运，谁听它的</span><br>
</p><p><b>falloutboy29: </b><br>
<span>为毛我有一种在看ww留言的错觉？</span><br>
</p><p><b>11酱: </b><br>
<span>看看外国论坛还挺有意思的 感谢搬运</span><br>
</p><p><b>一三五七九: </b><br>
<span>大部分美国人都坚信中国人全都带着斗笠住在唐人街里</span><br>
</p><p><b>第八协奏曲: </b><br>
<span>请不要转垃圾</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Meizu 16th Plus, Android 8.1.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>FML: </b><br>
<span>如果把微博和公知整体照样搬到美国</span><br>
<span>会是如何盛况</span><br>
</p><p><b>smdzh2: </b><br>
<span>I believe Panda Express is better than any Chinese food in China. That is fact.</span><br>
<span>我相信熊猫快餐比中国的任何中餐都好吃。这是事实。</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>火流星: </b><br>
<span>再次证明了川破天有着广泛的群众基础，网上反川破天的是一小撮民主党的败犬非国民！</span><br>
</p><p><b>nereus: </b><br>
<span>52区我觉得是反串的。</span><br>
</p><p><b>ccow: </b><br>
<span>卧槽，打不过就放弃挣扎了吗。强盗逻辑。</span><br>
</p><p><b>firefatfox: </b><br>
<span>不是说禁止洋垃圾进海关吗？</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能手机投票的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>cubesun: </b><br>
<span>看发言我还以为是印度网友评论。。。。</span><br>
<span>原来美国人已经低落成这样了？</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>天堂蜘蛛: </b><br>
<span>乃木坂裕人 发表于 2019-6-7 16:42</span><br>
<span>美国成立之后除了墨西哥和日本，好像就没国家打到过美国本土？</span><br>
<span>严格来说太战那会儿，夏威夷也算不上美国本土</span><br>
</p><p><b>豪福: </b><br>
<span>一国老百姓对本国军队投出信任票难道不对吗</span><br>
</p><p><b>dark_templar: </b><br>
<span>戏谑二次元 发表于 2019-6-7 16:01</span><br>
<span>反正制定政策的不会是这些傻逼</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 Android客户端 ...</span><br>
<span>布什和奥巴马时期的白宫经济顾问去年参与了上千人的联名信，反对贸易战</span><br>
<span>所以问题来了，要么他们是傻逼，要么纳瓦罗是</span><br>
</p><p><b>wuxan94: </b><br>
<span>已经拥有从日本手中夺回钓鱼岛的能力</span><br>
<span>海自：多大仇～</span><br>
</p><p><b>shiwenbaobao: </b><br>
<span>开开眼界挺好的，感谢搬运</span><br>
</p><p><b>尼克芭菲: </b><br>
<span>完全胜利不敢说，但是让对手付出极大代价还是可以的。。。</span><br>
<span>大不了种蘑菇喽</span><br>
</p><p><b>八代一: </b><br>
<span>这是美国战忽局，骗不到我的！</span><br>
</p><p><b>ycwind: </b><br>
<span>涉及钓鱼岛的是不是japs在回复，美国佬那地理知识知道钓鱼岛在哪？</span><br>
</p><p><b>响音: </b><br>
<span>戏谑二次元 发表于 2019-6-7 16:01</span><br>
<span>反正制定政策的不会是这些傻逼</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 Android客户端 ...</span><br>
<span>你确定？</span><br>
<span>美国国会山号称一个懂中文的都没有，会外语的不到15%</span><br>
<span>白宫里一群冷战活化石，究竟谁在面对中国的时候蠢点真不好说</span><br>
<span>毕竟就连反应最快的五角大楼在18年才吧主要威胁由毛子换成兔子</span><br>
</p><p><b>icefcold: </b><br>
<span>胜利本来就不大可能，军费和实战经验差距都是事实，但足够让美国付出葬送国际地位和未来的惨重代价，这楼里的人真觉得能赢怎的？</span><br>
</p><p><b>solitaryx: </b><br>
<span>中国是很久没打仗了没错，但是除了中东现在的菜鸡互啄，能和中美俄势均力敌的战场根本没有好吧</span><br>
<span>美国打菜鸡打出了朱姆沃尔特，打出了面对正规军先扫雷等对面炮击，美国自己多少年没打过正规大战了，自己的科技都点歪了</span><br>
</p><p><b>regular: </b><br>
<span>那这样的话，下一问就该是：中国不服，美军没啥还不A上去？</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1837648[50-100]</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>中国是不是太自信了？ 他们认为自己会战胜任何军事挑战？[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1837648-1-1.html</link>
      <description>中国是不是太自信了？ 他们认为自己会战胜任何军事挑战？&#13;
Overconfident? China Thinks Its Military Can Win in Almost Any Scenario
&#13;
是不是太自信了？ 中国认为本国军队可以在任何种情况下取得胜利
&#13;
http://img.ltaaa.com/uploadfile/thumb/2019/06/07//1559875626981.jpg
&#13;
Zachary Keck,The National Interest 10 hours ago 
&#13;
Zachary Keck
&#13;
Security,
&#13;
At least accoring to some polls. Can they be right? 
&#13;
Overconfident? China Thinks Its Military Can Win in Almost Any Scenario
&#13;
The vast majority of Chinese citizens believe the People’s Liberation Army (PLA) could seize islands in the East and South China Seas, even if the U.S. military were to intervene in the conflicts.
&#13;
绝大多数中国人认为，即使美国军队介入冲突，中国人民解放军也可以占领东海与南海的岛屿。
&#13;
No less than 87 percent of respondents said that the Chinese military already possessed the capability to take back the Diaoyu/Senkaku Islands from Japan, according to a recent public opinion poll. When asked whether they still believed the PLA could achieve this objective if the U.S. intervened in the conflict, 74 percent said yes.
&#13;
根据最近的一项民意调查，不少于87%的受访者表示，中国军队已经拥有从日本手中夺回钓鱼岛的能力。当被问及美国若介入冲突，他们是否仍然相信解放军能够实现这一目标时，74%的人给予了肯定答复。
&#13;
(This first appeared back in 2015.)
&#13;
The numbers were much the same for the South China Sea. When asked whether they believed the PLA could militarily take back disputed islands in the South China Sea, 85.6 percent of respondents said that China’s military could achieve this objective. Even if the U.S. military intervened on behalf of the Southeast Asian nations, about 73 percent of respondents said they still believed the Chinese military would prevail.
&#13;
中国南海的情况也大致相同。当被问及是否相信中国人民解放军能够以武力收复南海争议岛屿时，85.6%的受访者表示，中国军队能够实现这一目标。即使美国军方为东南亚国家利益出面进行干预，约73%的受访者也仍然表示，他们相信中国军方会取得胜利。
&#13;
评论翻译
&#13;
原创翻译：龙腾网 http://www.ltaaa.com 翻译：bluebit 转载请注明出处
&#13;
论坛地址：http://www.ltaaa.com/bbs/thread-486463-1-1.html
&#13;
Tony
&#13;
Tony43 minutes ago
&#13;
China would lose as the world would shut down its economy and trade.
&#13;
中国将会输能赢，因为世界会终止与它贸易。
&#13;
Matt
&#13;
Matt34 minutes ago
&#13;
China's recent real-world combat experience is next to nil. They employ sly cheap back-door tactics. If their confidence is based on some Huawei gadgets, its misplaced.
&#13;
近代中国实战经验几乎为零。他们利用狡诈取巧的策略。如果他们信心是建立在华为上，那就大错特错了。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/61/28661/comment-1.jpg
&#13;
PresidentFittu
&#13;
PresidentFittu54 minutes ago
&#13;
A land war probably, but they would never be able to transport their Army over water.
&#13;
可能是一场陆地战争，因为他们永远无法通过水路运送军队。
&#13;
John
&#13;
John3 hours ago
&#13;
China could not take the Diaoyu/Senkaku Islands from Japan even if the US did NOT intervene. The Japanese would destroy the Chinese if they ever tried.
&#13;
即使美国不去管，中国也无法从日本手中拿回钓鱼岛。如果日本想干掉中国，他们就会去做了。
&#13;
Anonymous
&#13;
Anonymous6 hours ago
&#13;
They would be very wrong, the Chinese Navy surface ships would be put down in less than 72 hours and their air force would be obliterated in about 1 weeks time. the only part that would take time to locate and destroy would be their submarines, and those realistically would be destroyed in about 2-3 weeks time in a true all out conflict, you can be sure they would have no penns to return to after USA struck their operating bases. Chinese military is the largest paper tiger in history, they have gone under former soviet premises which is quantity over quality. Lastly as someone who does "things" for Area 52, i can say that there are things that exist in USA military now, that if shown to the world, would frighten them so much that the world would unite against USA for war. There are 2 forces the USA has,..the nuclear/conventional forces and then the second secret army/toys hidden in USA in the event they must fight a world war or some fool gets the idea to attempt an invasion of USA mainland. Remember this,..in 1979 the USA black ops programs were using laser cannons to shoot down unmanned passenger airplanes(first technical drone if you will) for testing national shield defense. It's been 40 years.......what do you think exists today......
&#13;
大错特错，中国海军的水面舰艇72小时内就会被击沉，他们空军将在一周内即被消灭。唯一需要花点时间得就是定位摧毁他们的潜艇，儿这些潜艇也将在2-3周的时间内被消灭，在一场真正的全面冲突中，可以肯定的是，美国袭击他们军事基地后，他们啥也剩不下。中国军队是历史上最大的纸老虎，他们就是学前苏联完蛋的，那就是数量重于质量。最后，作为一个曾在52区做过“事情”的人，我可以说，现在美国军队中藏有的一些东西，如果向世界展示，就会吓到他们，但那样全世界就会团结起来反对美国。美国有…核弹与常规两股力量，然后是隐藏在美国的第二秘密军队和(那个）“玩具”，万一他们一定想打一场世界大战，或者一些傻瓜有入侵美国的想法。请记住，1979年，美国黑色行动计划用于测试国家防御系统的激光炮打掉过一架无人客机。四十年过去了，想想一下（这东西）现在能会怎么样。
&#13;
Matt
&#13;
Matt46 minutes ago
&#13;
Literally nobody in their massive military has ever fought in a war. They are shiny and look good on paper, but they are completely untested in war.
&#13;
他们军队庞大，几乎没人参加过战争。中国也就是纸上谈兵完全没有实战经验。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/61/28661/comment-2.jpg
&#13;
Reyes
&#13;
Reyes28 minutes ago
&#13;
I believe Panda Express is better than any Chinese food in China. That is fact.
&#13;
我相信熊猫快餐比中国的任何中餐都好吃。这是事实。
&#13;
Anonymous
&#13;
Anonymous1 hour ago
&#13;
No winners in a war. Lives and places will be destroyed.
&#13;
战争中没有赢家。只有摧毁生命与和平。
&#13;
dobey
&#13;
dobey35 minutes ago
&#13;
It might be what they say but I seriously doubt they are that naive and if they truly believed that they likely would’ve already tried to take Taiwan.
&#13;
这是他们以为的吧，但我严重怀疑他们是否天真，要是真认为可以，没准台湾早占领了。
&#13;
Ma Qin
&#13;
Ma Qin3 hours ago
&#13;
As the Korea and Vietnam wars demonstrared ,USA is definiteltly the biggest paper tiger ,unable to defeat even the weak opponents then and let alone the stronger ones.
&#13;
正如朝鲜战争和越南战争所证明的那样，美国无疑是最大的纸老虎，连弱小的对手都打不过，更不用说强大的对手了
&#13;
Shlomo
&#13;
Shlomo31 minutes ago
&#13;
America still hasn't won wars against Third World powers like Afghanistan &amp; Iraq after 16 years of trying. They have absolutely no hope of beating a superpower like China in a war.
&#13;
经过16年的努力，美国仍没赢得对阿富汗和伊拉克等**强国的战争。美国绝没希望通过一场战争打败像中国这样的超级大国了。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/62/28662/comment-1.jpg
&#13;
nik
&#13;
nik36 minutes ago
&#13;
It just shows you how much a brainwashed nation believes about its own Government's propaganda.
&#13;
它只是向你展示了一个被洗脑的国家是多么相信自己的政府宣传。
&#13;
Reply3
&#13;
WT
&#13;
WT22 minutes ago
&#13;
The rhetoric is absurd. A trade disagreement spirals into talk of military conflict? Nationalism is certainly alive and well on both sides of the Pacific. Fact is the US-China relationship since '79 has significantly benefited both countries and kept the Soviets in check. US-China is the single most important bi-lateral relationship in the world; nothing comes close. China has zero interest to engage the US in a military conflict. The war mongers in the US just looking for a fight having no successes since Grenada.
&#13;
这种诉说方式太荒诞了。贸易分歧升级为军事冲突?太平洋两岸的民族主义无疑是和谐的。事实上，自1979年以来，美中关系给两国带来了巨大的好处，并遏制了苏联。美中是世界上唯一最重要的双边关系;什么都比不上。中国对美国卷入的军事冲突毫无兴趣。美国的战争贩子只是在寻找一场自格林纳达以来毫无胜算的战争。
&#13;
Peter
&#13;
Peter55 minutes ago
&#13;
I seem to recall another Asian country that was all full of themselves, and they tried seizing islands across the Pacific theaters. They even got in a devastating sneak attack against the American Pacific fleet. But still, it didn't work out very well for them, and I don't see China doing much better!
&#13;
我好像记得另一个亚洲国家，他们充满自信，试图占领太平洋战场对面的岛屿。他们甚至对美国太平洋舰队发动了毁灭性的偷袭。但是，他们没做好，我不认为中国也能做的更好。
&#13;
Rex
&#13;
Rex1 hour ago
&#13;
Well, just dont underestimate your opponent. And keep in mind 350 nukes and the ability to deliver them is no joke. It ain't 7000 but still can wipe us out.
&#13;
嗯，不要低估你的对手。记住，350枚核弹可不是闹着玩的。虽然远不及7000，但还是可以足够毁灭我们。
&#13;
Joel
&#13;
Joel23 minutes ago
&#13;
The only other nation in the world that could even remotely compete with the US in terms of military might and experience is Russia, and even they are a very distant second.
&#13;
在军事实力与经验方面，世界上唯一能够与美国进行远距离竞争的国家是俄罗斯，即便是俄罗斯，也远落美国之后吧。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/62/28662/comment-2.jpg
&#13;
Sk
&#13;
Sk25 minutes ago
&#13;
There is zero reason to go to war other than the rich men in America are losing their relative strength to the rich men in Asia. There is no ideological difference? there is no animosity between any of the people if the world. This has everything to do with one side is losing wealth to the other side.
&#13;
除了美国富人输给亚洲富人外，毫无理由发动战争。意识形态有什么不同吗?世界上任何一个民族之间都没有仇恨。这一切都与一方财富流失到另一方有关。
&#13;
JT
&#13;
JT56 minutes ago
&#13;
Two to three weeks? We can’t even end the terrorists in the Middle East that don’t have nearly as much military power...
&#13;
两到三周?我们甚至消灭不了中东的恐怖分子，因为那里没有那么多的军事力量
&#13;
FuManchuJr
&#13;
FuManchuJr1 hour ago
&#13;
This is home ground advantage. 
&#13;
Crossing a sea to attack an enemy is tough enough but to cross an ocean to attack a country with more than 4.25 times their population size is plain suicidal.
&#13;
跨过大洋打击敌人就已经很困难了，跨过大洋海还要攻击一个人口超过美国4.25倍的国家，那简直就是自杀。
&#13;
Ted S
&#13;
Ted S24 minutes ago
&#13;
I suspect those islands that China has militarized just might cease to exist very quickly, thus nothing to take back.
&#13;
我怀疑那些中国军事化的岛屿可能很快就会不复存在，因为没了就没必要要了
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/62/28662/comment-3.jpg
&#13;
Obscure
&#13;
Obscure54 minutes ago
&#13;
In its backyards, it undoubtedly can and will obliterate any military in the world. China's main power is her highly advanced projectiles. They have millions of them. I mean millions literally
&#13;
在他们的地盘，毫无疑问，中国能够消灭世界上任何军队。中国的主要力量是其高度先进的导弹。他们有数百万。我的意思是数-百-万
&#13;
Jamie
&#13;
Jamiein 11 seconds
&#13;
China can not figure anything out themselves they steal technology because communist can not think for themselves
&#13;
中国自己什么都搞不懂，他们只有偷技术，因为中国人不会独立思考
&#13;
bene
&#13;
bene36 minutes ago
&#13;
Most Chinese would believe the earth is flat if their communist masters told them that.
&#13;
如果他们的GC主义主人告诉他们地球是平的，大多数中国人就会都信</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>废狗: </b><br>
<span>中国是不是太自信了？ 他们认为自己会战胜任何军事挑战？</span><br>
<span>Overconfident? China Thinks Its Military Can Win in Almost Any Scenario</span><br>
<span>是不是太自信了？ 中国认为本国军队可以在任何种情况下取得胜利</span><br>
<img src="http://img.ltaaa.com/uploadfile/thumb/2019/06/07//1559875626981.jpg" title="http://img.ltaaa.com/uploadfile/thumb/2019/06/07//1559875626981.jpg"><br>
<span>Zachary Keck,The National Interest 10 hours ago </span><br>
<span>Zachary Keck</span><br>
<span>Security,</span><br>
<span>At least accoring to some polls. Can they be right? </span><br>
<span>Overconfident? China Thinks Its Military Can Win in Almost Any Scenario</span><br>
<span>The vast majority of Chinese citizens believe the People’s Liberation Army (PLA) could seize islands in the East and South China Seas, even if the U.S. military were to intervene in the conflicts.</span><br>
<span>绝大多数中国人认为，即使美国军队介入冲突，中国人民解放军也可以占领东海与南海的岛屿。</span><br>
<span>No less than 87 percent of respondents said that the Chinese military already possessed the capability to take back the Diaoyu/Senkaku Islands from Japan, according to a recent public opinion poll. When asked whether they still believed the PLA could achieve this objective if the U.S. intervened in the conflict, 74 percent said yes.</span><br>
<span>根据最近的一项民意调查，不少于87%的受访者表示，中国军队已经拥有从日本手中夺回钓鱼岛的能力。当被问及美国若介入冲突，他们是否仍然相信解放军能够实现这一目标时，74%的人给予了肯定答复。</span><br>
<span>(This first appeared back in 2015.)</span><br>
<span>The numbers were much the same for the South China Sea. When asked whether they believed the PLA could militarily take back disputed islands in the South China Sea, 85.6 percent of respondents said that China’s military could achieve this objective. Even if the U.S. military intervened on behalf of the Southeast Asian nations, about 73 percent of respondents said they still believed the Chinese military would prevail.</span><br>
<span>中国南海的情况也大致相同。当被问及是否相信中国人民解放军能够以武力收复南海争议岛屿时，85.6%的受访者表示，中国军队能够实现这一目标。即使美国军方为东南亚国家利益出面进行干预，约73%的受访者也仍然表示，他们相信中国军方会取得胜利。</span><br>
<span>评论翻译</span><br>
<span>原创翻译：龙腾网 http://www.ltaaa.com 翻译：bluebit 转载请注明出处</span><br>
<span>论坛地址：http://www.ltaaa.com/bbs/thread-486463-1-1.html</span><br>
<span>Tony</span><br>
<span>Tony43 minutes ago</span><br>
<span>China would lose as the world would shut down its economy and trade.</span><br>
<span>中国将会输能赢，因为世界会终止与它贸易。</span><br>
<span>Matt</span><br>
<span>Matt34 minutes ago</span><br>
<span>China's recent real-world combat experience is next to nil. They employ sly cheap back-door tactics. If their confidence is based on some Huawei gadgets, its misplaced.</span><br>
<span>近代中国实战经验几乎为零。他们利用狡诈取巧的策略。如果他们信心是建立在华为上，那就大错特错了。</span><br>
<img src="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/61/28661/comment-1.jpg" title="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/61/28661/comment-1.jpg"><br>
<span>PresidentFittu</span><br>
<span>PresidentFittu54 minutes ago</span><br>
<span>A land war probably, but they would never be able to transport their Army over water.</span><br>
<span>可能是一场陆地战争，因为他们永远无法通过水路运送军队。</span><br>
<span>John</span><br>
<span>John3 hours ago</span><br>
<span>China could not take the Diaoyu/Senkaku Islands from Japan even if the US did NOT intervene. The Japanese would destroy the Chinese if they ever tried.</span><br>
<span>即使美国不去管，中国也无法从日本手中拿回钓鱼岛。如果日本想干掉中国，他们就会去做了。</span><br>
<span>Anonymous</span><br>
<span>Anonymous6 hours ago</span><br>
<span>They would be very wrong, the Chinese Navy surface ships would be put down in less than 72 hours and their air force would be obliterated in about 1 weeks time. the only part that would take time to locate and destroy would be their submarines, and those realistically would be destroyed in about 2-3 weeks time in a true all out conflict, you can be sure they would have no penns to return to after USA struck their operating bases. Chinese military is the largest paper tiger in history, they have gone under former soviet premises which is quantity over quality. Lastly as someone who does "things" for Area 52, i can say that there are things that exist in USA military now, that if shown to the world, would frighten them so much that the world would unite against USA for war. There are 2 forces the USA has,..the nuclear/conventional forces and then the second secret army/toys hidden in USA in the event they must fight a world war or some fool gets the idea to attempt an invasion of USA mainland. Remember this,..in 1979 the USA black ops programs were using laser cannons to shoot down unmanned passenger airplanes(first technical drone if you will) for testing national shield defense. It's been 40 years.......what do you think exists today......</span><br>
<span>大错特错，中国海军的水面舰艇72小时内就会被击沉，他们空军将在一周内即被消灭。唯一需要花点时间得就是定位摧毁他们的潜艇，儿这些潜艇也将在2-3周的时间内被消灭，在一场真正的全面冲突中，可以肯定的是，美国袭击他们军事基地后，他们啥也剩不下。中国军队是历史上最大的纸老虎，他们就是学前苏联完蛋的，那就是数量重于质量。最后，作为一个曾在52区做过“事情”的人，我可以说，现在美国军队中藏有的一些东西，如果向世界展示，就会吓到他们，但那样全世界就会团结起来反对美国。美国有…核弹与常规两股力量，然后是隐藏在美国的第二秘密军队和(那个）“玩具”，万一他们一定想打一场世界大战，或者一些傻瓜有入侵美国的想法。请记住，1979年，美国黑色行动计划用于测试国家防御系统的激光炮打掉过一架无人客机。四十年过去了，想想一下（这东西）现在能会怎么样。</span><br>
<span>Matt</span><br>
<span>Matt46 minutes ago</span><br>
<span>Literally nobody in their massive military has ever fought in a war. They are shiny and look good on paper, but they are completely untested in war.</span><br>
<span>他们军队庞大，几乎没人参加过战争。中国也就是纸上谈兵完全没有实战经验。</span><br>
<img src="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/61/28661/comment-2.jpg" title="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/61/28661/comment-2.jpg"><br>
<span>Reyes</span><br>
<span>Reyes28 minutes ago</span><br>
<span>I believe Panda Express is better than any Chinese food in China. That is fact.</span><br>
<span>我相信熊猫快餐比中国的任何中餐都好吃。这是事实。</span><br>
<span>Anonymous</span><br>
<span>Anonymous1 hour ago</span><br>
<span>No winners in a war. Lives and places will be destroyed.</span><br>
<span>战争中没有赢家。只有摧毁生命与和平。</span><br>
<span>dobey</span><br>
<span>dobey35 minutes ago</span><br>
<span>It might be what they say but I seriously doubt they are that naive and if they truly believed that they likely would’ve already tried to take Taiwan.</span><br>
<span>这是他们以为的吧，但我严重怀疑他们是否天真，要是真认为可以，没准台湾早占领了。</span><br>
<span>Ma Qin</span><br>
<span>Ma Qin3 hours ago</span><br>
<span>As the Korea and Vietnam wars demonstrared ,USA is definiteltly the biggest paper tiger ,unable to defeat even the weak opponents then and let alone the stronger ones.</span><br>
<span>正如朝鲜战争和越南战争所证明的那样，美国无疑是最大的纸老虎，连弱小的对手都打不过，更不用说强大的对手了</span><br>
<span>Shlomo</span><br>
<span>Shlomo31 minutes ago</span><br>
<span>America still hasn't won wars against Third World powers like Afghanistan & Iraq after 16 years of trying. They have absolutely no hope of beating a superpower like China in a war.</span><br>
<span>经过16年的努力，美国仍没赢得对阿富汗和伊拉克等**强国的战争。美国绝没希望通过一场战争打败像中国这样的超级大国了。</span><br>
<img src="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/62/28662/comment-1.jpg" title="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/62/28662/comment-1.jpg"><br>
<span>nik</span><br>
<span>nik36 minutes ago</span><br>
<span>It just shows you how much a brainwashed nation believes about its own Government's propaganda.</span><br>
<span>它只是向你展示了一个被洗脑的国家是多么相信自己的政府宣传。</span><br>
<span>Reply3</span><br>
<span>WT</span><br>
<span>WT22 minutes ago</span><br>
<span>The rhetoric is absurd. A trade disagreement spirals into talk of military conflict? Nationalism is certainly alive and well on both sides of the Pacific. Fact is the US-China relationship since '79 has significantly benefited both countries and kept the Soviets in check. US-China is the single most important bi-lateral relationship in the world; nothing comes close. China has zero interest to engage the US in a military conflict. The war mongers in the US just looking for a fight having no successes since Grenada.</span><br>
<span>这种诉说方式太荒诞了。贸易分歧升级为军事冲突?太平洋两岸的民族主义无疑是和谐的。事实上，自1979年以来，美中关系给两国带来了巨大的好处，并遏制了苏联。美中是世界上唯一最重要的双边关系;什么都比不上。中国对美国卷入的军事冲突毫无兴趣。美国的战争贩子只是在寻找一场自格林纳达以来毫无胜算的战争。</span><br>
<span>Peter</span><br>
<span>Peter55 minutes ago</span><br>
<span>I seem to recall another Asian country that was all full of themselves, and they tried seizing islands across the Pacific theaters. They even got in a devastating sneak attack against the American Pacific fleet. But still, it didn't work out very well for them, and I don't see China doing much better!</span><br>
<span>我好像记得另一个亚洲国家，他们充满自信，试图占领太平洋战场对面的岛屿。他们甚至对美国太平洋舰队发动了毁灭性的偷袭。但是，他们没做好，我不认为中国也能做的更好。</span><br>
<span>Rex</span><br>
<span>Rex1 hour ago</span><br>
<span>Well, just dont underestimate your opponent. And keep in mind 350 nukes and the ability to deliver them is no joke. It ain't 7000 but still can wipe us out.</span><br>
<span>嗯，不要低估你的对手。记住，350枚核弹可不是闹着玩的。虽然远不及7000，但还是可以足够毁灭我们。</span><br>
<span>Joel</span><br>
<span>Joel23 minutes ago</span><br>
<span>The only other nation in the world that could even remotely compete with the US in terms of military might and experience is Russia, and even they are a very distant second.</span><br>
<span>在军事实力与经验方面，世界上唯一能够与美国进行远距离竞争的国家是俄罗斯，即便是俄罗斯，也远落美国之后吧。</span><br>
<img src="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/62/28662/comment-2.jpg" title="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/62/28662/comment-2.jpg"><br>
<span>Sk</span><br>
<span>Sk25 minutes ago</span><br>
<span>There is zero reason to go to war other than the rich men in America are losing their relative strength to the rich men in Asia. There is no ideological difference? there is no animosity between any of the people if the world. This has everything to do with one side is losing wealth to the other side.</span><br>
<span>除了美国富人输给亚洲富人外，毫无理由发动战争。意识形态有什么不同吗?世界上任何一个民族之间都没有仇恨。这一切都与一方财富流失到另一方有关。</span><br>
<span>JT</span><br>
<span>JT56 minutes ago</span><br>
<span>Two to three weeks? We can’t even end the terrorists in the Middle East that don’t have nearly as much military power...</span><br>
<span>两到三周?我们甚至消灭不了中东的恐怖分子，因为那里没有那么多的军事力量</span><br>
<span>FuManchuJr</span><br>
<span>FuManchuJr1 hour ago</span><br>
<span>This is home ground advantage. </span><br>
<span>Crossing a sea to attack an enemy is tough enough but to cross an ocean to attack a country with more than 4.25 times their population size is plain suicidal.</span><br>
<span>跨过大洋打击敌人就已经很困难了，跨过大洋海还要攻击一个人口超过美国4.25倍的国家，那简直就是自杀。</span><br>
<span>Ted S</span><br>
<span>Ted S24 minutes ago</span><br>
<span>I suspect those islands that China has militarized just might cease to exist very quickly, thus nothing to take back.</span><br>
<span>我怀疑那些中国军事化的岛屿可能很快就会不复存在，因为没了就没必要要了</span><br>
<img src="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/62/28662/comment-3.jpg" title="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/62/28662/comment-3.jpg"><br>
<span>Obscure</span><br>
<span>Obscure54 minutes ago</span><br>
<span>In its backyards, it undoubtedly can and will obliterate any military in the world. China's main power is her highly advanced projectiles. They have millions of them. I mean millions literally</span><br>
<span>在他们的地盘，毫无疑问，中国能够消灭世界上任何军队。中国的主要力量是其高度先进的导弹。他们有数百万。我的意思是数-百-万</span><br>
<span>Jamie</span><br>
<span>Jamiein 11 seconds</span><br>
<span>China can not figure anything out themselves they steal technology because communist can not think for themselves</span><br>
<span>中国自己什么都搞不懂，他们只有偷技术，因为中国人不会独立思考</span><br>
<span>bene</span><br>
<span>bene36 minutes ago</span><br>
<span>Most Chinese would believe the earth is flat if their communist masters told them that.</span><br>
<span>如果他们的GC主义主人告诉他们地球是平的，大多数中国人就会都信</span><br>
</p><p><b>wzk3232: </b><br>
<span>请不要乱倒垃圾，国外的垃圾也是垃圾</span><br>
</p><p><b>macoy0: </b><br>
<span> I believe Panda Express is better than any Chinese food in China. That is fact.</span><br>
</p><p><b>考茨基: </b><br>
<span>这种一抬屁股就知道放什么屁的玩意有啥好看的，多转点美少女，谁有空看外国宅宅空骚</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>不科学的瘦子: </b><br>
<span>别倒垃圾</span><br>
</p><p><b>roger_goodell: </b><br>
<span>多放一些nsfw好不好</span><br>
</p><p><b>梨花: </b><br>
<span>今天份的傻吊图在吗</span><br>
</p><p><b>半江瑟瑟半江红: </b><br>
<span>macoy0 发表于 2019-6-7 15:48</span><br>
<span>I believe Panda Express is better than any Chinese food in China. That is fact.</span><br>
<span>这是这篇垃圾帖子里最傻逼的一句话，没有之一</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HUAWEI LYA-AL10, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>macoy0: </b><br>
<span>半江瑟瑟半江红 发表于 2019-6-7 15:57</span><br>
<span>这是这篇垃圾帖子里最傻逼的一句话，没有之一</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HUAWEI LYA-AL10, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v ...</span><br>
<span>应该是巨魔反串</span><br>
</p><p><b>milkon: </b><br>
<span>在，看看朝鲜战争？</span><br>
</p><p><b>杨松: </b><br>
<span>考茨基 发表于 2019-6-7 15:49</span><br>
<span>这种一抬屁股就知道放什么屁的玩意有啥好看的，多转点美少女，谁有空看外国宅宅空骚</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 S ...</span><br>
<span>不敢相信“美”少女，多来点毛子女仆吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>keures: </b><br>
<span>美国人讲的自信和中国人的不一样。前者是盲目的，不盲目就不像自信了。而中国人的自信建立在现实之上。</span><br>
</p><p><b>天才我心: </b><br>
<span>pandaexpress除了orangechicken能吃之外其它都不好吃</span><br>
</p><p><b>魔法酪饼: </b><br>
<span>这贴不是挺有用的么。。。</span><br>
<span>证明美国群众已经无法理性的面对面前的情况，宁愿用一些荒谬的想法来欺骗自己来让自身情绪安定。</span><br>
<span>换句话说，恐惧已经深入了他们的心灵。</span><br>
</p><p><b>戏谑二次元: </b><br>
<span>反正制定政策的不会是这些傻逼</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>SK-II: </b><br>
<span>不是自信 在这个集权的话语权里一句话的执行力就是强</span><br>
</p><p><b>シャル: </b><br>
<span>我怀疑这些低智商白皮认为中国和阿富汗一样大</span><br>
</p><p><b>izumlily: </b><br>
<span>52区那个真把我逗笑了</span><br>
</p><p><b>cools: </b><br>
<span>倒垃圾</span><br>
</p><p><b>cloudcc: </b><br>
<span>戏谑二次元 发表于 2019-6-7 16:01</span><br>
<span>反正制定政策的不会是这些傻逼</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 Android客户端 ...</span><br>
<span>你觉得纳瓦罗博尔顿阿川会比这些人强到哪里去？</span><br>
<span>醒醒</span><br>
<span>温和狗都已经被干掉了好不好233</span><br>
</p><p><b>alerbe: </b><br>
<span>熊猫快餐除了看起来像中餐之外其他并不如福建人开的中餐馆好吃</span><br>
</p><p><b>菲特妹: </b><br>
<span>这帖子证明了这句话</span><br>
<span>It just shows you how much a brainwashed nation believes about its own Government's propaganda.</span><br>
<span>它只是向你展示了一个被洗脑的国家是多么相信自己的政府宣传。</span><br>
<span>----发送自 STAGE1 App for Android.</span><br>
</p><p><b>Narrative: </b><br>
<span>这是美国丈育红脖论坛的回复吗</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 samsung SM-G9730, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>Lamic: </b><br>
<span>南海仲裁案才过去没多久，看不到中国在那填了多少个岛么</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HUAWEI BKL-AL20, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>本异末同: </b><br>
<span>52区那个是认真的吗？</span><br>
</p><p><b>czs13: </b><br>
<span>战忽局做过头了？</span><br>
</p><p><b>Sculpey: </b><br>
<span>真是巨魔丛生的世界啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>cpuisme: </b><br>
<span>本来战争就是双输。</span><br>
<span>中国群众有信心的是解放军守卫国土的决心。</span><br>
<span>不惜代价的决心。</span><br>
<span>就像之前咱们看到的，</span><br>
<span>假如美国被揍了，</span><br>
<span>但他借战争借口，</span><br>
<span>抹黑中国，搞技术禁运的话。</span><br>
<span>咱们很多底层东西就没了，</span><br>
<span>芯片，科技产品，电子系统。</span><br>
<span>所以至少现在，</span><br>
<span>任何开战的举动，</span><br>
<span>对国内经济和咱们每个人的影响，</span><br>
<span>都是很难承受的。</span><br>
<span>所以我衷心希望特朗普能在位更久一点，</span><br>
<span>等他把美国鼓吹的国际秩序假面都撕毁，</span><br>
<span>舆论就不那么容易洗脑了</span><br>
</p><p><b>melvin95: </b><br>
<span>这个巨魔沙雕站前几天还洗福岛呢</span><br>
</p><p><b>melvin95: </b><br>
<span>alerbe 发表于 2019-6-7 16:05</span><br>
<span>熊猫快餐除了看起来像中餐之外其他并不如福建人开的中餐馆好吃</span><br>
<span>根本就是能和wagamama比谁更屎了</span><br>
</p><p><b>StrangerJ: </b><br>
<span>Lastly as someone who does "things" for Area 52, i can say that there are things that exist in USA military now, that if shown to the world, would frighten them so much that the world would unite against USA for war. </span><br>
<span>请不要倒这种弱智垃圾，很无聊</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MIX 2S, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>chnyang: </b><br>
<span> 想吃熊猫快餐? 把想吃的人 用**脚镣锁起来扔进成年大熊猫的园子里</span><br>
</p><p><b>东方萃梦想: </b><br>
<span>最后一个回复挺有趣的</span><br>
<span>Most Chinese would believe the earth is flat if their communist masters told them that.</span><br>
<span>如果他们的GC主义主人告诉他们地球是平的，大多数中国人就会都信</span><br>
<span>然后美国是世界上地平论者最多的国家</span><br>
</p><p><b>エマシ—ン: </b><br>
<span>戏谑二次元 发表于 2019-6-7 16:01</span><br>
<span>反正制定政策的不会是这些傻逼</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 Android客户端 ...</span><br>
<span>不同意，你看看特朗普，就是这个水平</span><br>
</p><p><b>JWJking: </b><br>
<span>但我觉得Panda Express真的很好吃啊，甜甜的，还不贵，就是种类太少了</span><br>
</p><p><b>乃木坂裕人: </b><br>
<span>美国成立之后除了墨西哥和日本，好像就没国家打到过美国本土？</span><br>
</p><p><b>炽十二翼: </b><br>
<span>战忽局工作开展得不错</span><br>
</p><p><b>kabunsan: </b><br>
<span>乃木坂裕人 发表于 2019-6-7 16:42</span><br>
<span>美国成立之后除了墨西哥和日本，好像就没国家打到过美国本土？</span><br>
<span>据说加拿大烧过白宫？</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Essential Products PH-1, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>十全吕布: </b><br>
<span>老祖宗都知道兵不厌诈，灯塔国硬推猛咋还被个蓝装弟弟撵出鸭绿江了呢。</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 6, Android 8.0.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>十点半: </b><br>
<span>乃木坂裕人 发表于 2019-06-07 16:42:14</span><br>
<span>美国成立之后除了墨西哥和日本，好像就没国家打到过美国本土？美国建国后被英国殖民地加拿大烧过白宫</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>丁春秋: </b><br>
<span>不是自信 是事实</span><br>
</p><p><b>红夜殇雨: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 红夜殇雨 于 2019-6-7 16:58 编辑 </span><br>
<span>菲特妹 发表于 2019-6-7 16:05</span><br>
<span>这帖子证明了这句话</span><br>
<span>It just shows you how much a brainwashed nation believes about its own Government ...</span><br>
<span>也证明了你至今不知道美国纽约地铁连2G信号都没有，拿我国和第三个世界基建国家比的被洗脑事实。</span><br>
<span>要是你在三国蜀汉荆州方，肯定支持孙权和关羽联姻的孙权反间计不管，中了计的刘备不顾隆中对让关羽北伐，蜀汉封建统治者刘备会怎么想他俩结亲。要不就支持子午谷，让魏延提前几百年成为安禄山的祖宗</span><br>
<span>毕竟台湾人也喜欢刘禅还做个轩辕剑污名化丞相的吗，你这种和敌人互相理解范和台湾人挺像。</span><br>
</p><p><b>小黑鱼: </b><br>
<span>国外的军坛对TG的军事水平评价程度基本和其专业度成正比</span><br>
</p><p><b>卡缪911: </b><br>
<span>I believe Panda Express is better than any Chinese food in China. That is fact.</span><br>
<span>只能了。</span><br>
<span>作为肥宅还是喜欢无限续杯的M记</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>乔伊: </b><br>
<span>米帝对内的战忽局实在太厉害</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>alerbe: </b><br>
<span>JWJking 发表于 2019-6-7 16:41</span><br>
<span>但我觉得Panda Express真的很好吃啊，甜甜的，还不贵，就是种类太少了</span><br>
<span>如果他们旁边开一个普通的中餐快餐店，就是照顾美国人口味那种，你肯定就不会去熊猫快餐吃了，做的东西都差不多，味道还是不如。</span><br>
</p><p><b>Thermo: </b><br>
<span>美国战狼</span><br>
</p><p><b>星隐月明: </b><br>
<span>不得不感慨，当初打朝鲜战争这个决定真是正确无比</span><br>
</p><p><b>卡缪911: </b><br>
<span>JWJking 发表于 2019-06-07 16:41:13</span><br>
<span>但我觉得Panda Express真的很好吃啊，甜甜的，还不贵，就是种类太少了吃过panda express的咕佬肉和糖醋肉，觉得二者没任何区别，只有甜味。</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>田多宇光: </b><br>
<span>漂洋过海洋垃圾</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1837648[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
