<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>非死不可在硅谷的总部发现沙林毒气邮包炸弹</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>非死不可在硅谷的总部发现沙林毒气邮包炸弹</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 19:21:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>非死不可在硅谷的总部发现沙林毒气邮包炸弹[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1843648-1-1.html</link>
      <description>非死不可在硅谷的总部发现沙林毒气邮包炸弹&#13;
 本帖最后由 李恭暔 于 2019-7-2 05:43 编辑 

多家外媒报道
&#13;
两名员工暴露
&#13;
没必要找原文看屁信息都没
&#13;
来来去去就那几句空洞套话
&#13;
用来练高考英语都嫌没营养
&#13;
https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/104101103-GettyImages-621183242.jpg?v=1532563988&amp;w=1910</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>李恭暔: </b><br>
<span>非死不可在硅谷的总部发现沙林毒气邮包炸弹</span><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 李恭暔 于 2019-7-2 05:43 编辑 </span><br>
<span>多家外媒报道</span><br>
<span>两名员工暴露</span><br>
<span>没必要找原文看屁信息都没</span><br>
<span>来来去去就那几句空洞套话</span><br>
<span>用来练高考英语都嫌没营养</span><br>
<span>https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/104101103-GettyImages-621183242.jpg?v=1532563988&w=1910</span><br>
</p><p><b>Inquisitor: </b><br>
<span>引用第0楼李恭暔于2019-07-02 05:39发表的:</span><br>
<span>多家外媒报道</span><br>
<span>两名员工暴露</span><br>
<span>没必要找原文看屁信息都没</span><br>
<span>来来去去就那几句空洞套话</span><br>
<span>用来练高考英语都嫌没营养</span><br>
<span>@李恭暔</span><br>
<span>说人话</span><br>
<span>----发送自 STAGE1 App for Android.</span><br>
</p><p><b>nicebody: </b><br>
<span>李恭暔 发表于 2019-7-2 05:39</span><br>
<span>多家外媒报道</span><br>
<span>两名员工暴露</span><br>
<span>煞笔当性格？</span><br>
</p><p><b>tfcatus: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 tfcatus 于 2019-7-2 07:30 编辑 </span><br>
<span>目前就找到这么一篇，剩下的都是去年11月的新闻，凑合着看吧</span><br>
<span>Facebook office evacuated after suspicious package identifiedA machine at the social network's mail-sorting facility warned of a toxic substance. The FBI is involved.</span><br>
<span>BY [*]IAN SHERR,</span><br>
<span> [*]QUEENIE WONG</span><br>
<span>JULY 1, 2019 2:05 PM PDT</span><br>
<span>Facebook may have been the target of an attack after a machine at one of the social network's mail-sorting facilities warned of a possible toxic substance.</span><br>
<span>Menlo Park Fire District said a hazardous materials team is on the scene at the building, which normally has about five or six people working there. Both NBC News Bay Area and KRON 4, which at first said the substance may have been sarin, said no employees were exposed, though initially there were indications two people may have been. </span><br>
<span>Facebook, in a statement, said a package delivered to one of its mail rooms was "deemed suspicious" around 11 a.m. PT, without providing additional details.</span><br>
<span>"We evacuated four buildings and are conducting a thorough investigation in coordination with local authorities," a Facebook spokesman said in a statement, adding that the substance has not yet been identified. "As of now, three of the evacuated buildings have been cleared for repopulation. The safety of our employees is our top priority and we will share additional information when it is available." </span><br>
<span>The possible attack at Facebook and the response highlight the increasing concerns tech companies have over security, which is spilling over into their home communities.</span><br>
<span>In April 2018, a woman shot three people at YouTube's headquarters, about 20 minutes south of San Francisco, before turning the gun on herself. In that case, the shooter appeared to be angry at how YouTube had handled her channels and videos.</span><br>
<span>And in December of last year, Facebook evacuated its headquarters after receiving an anonymous bomb threat that turned out to be a false alarm.</span><br>
<span>Business Insider said an MPFD official said Monday that sarin was detected in a mail bag at Facebook during a routine test, and that its detection may have been a false positive. So far, no one was showing symptoms of exposure.</span><br>
<span>CBS News confirmed that the Federal Bureau of Investigation is responding to Facebook's headquarters at the request of the hazmat team.</span><br>
<span>The FBI didn't immediately respond to a request for comment.</span><br>
</p><p><b>海克托尔: </b><br>
<span>用户组:        腐宅</span><br>
<span>在线时间:        196 小时</span><br>
<span>注册时间:        2019-4-17 18:35</span><br>
<span>看来是幼齿巨魔啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>jjyycy: </b><br>
<span>https://www.businessinsider.com/sarin-poison-detected-in-facebook-mail-menlo-park-california-2019-7</span><br>
</p><p><b>m10086288: </b><br>
<span>李恭暔 发表于 2019-7-2 05:39</span><br>
<span>多家外媒报道</span><br>
<span>两名员工暴露</span><br>
<span>您这内容倒是精炼的简洁明快</span><br>
<span>真当自己维生素片了？</span><br>
</p><p><b>佛里德姆: </b><br>
<span>妙啊，自己先把转的一句话新闻批判一番，这样楼里的人就没法当批判新闻第一人了，只能转向人身批判了</span><br>
</p><p><b>セリア=キルミン: </b><br>
<span>幼齿有点色情</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MIX, Android 8.0.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1843648[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
