<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>印度一男子强奸19岁女儿并将其斩首</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>印度一男子强奸19岁女儿并将其斩首</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 18:12:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>印度一男子强奸19岁女儿并将其斩首[50-100]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1854634-1-1.html</link>
      <description>印度一男子强奸19岁女儿并将其斩首&#13;
Gorakhpur man arrested for raping, beheading 19-year-old daughter戈勒克布尔一男子奸杀19岁女儿并将其斩首，现已被捕GORAKHPUR: A man was arrested on Saturday for allegedly raping and beheading her 19-year-old daughter in Bathbuzurg village of Gorakhpur.戈勒克布尔：周六，戈勒克布尔Bathbuzurg村一名男子因涉嫌强奸19岁女儿并将其斩首而被捕。The arrest was made on the complaint of the elder daughter of the accused.被告的大女儿报案后，警方将凶手逮捕归案。http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/e3e8f136fd25908173e5a6844ce41a31.pngPolice said the accused, Jai Prakash Gupta had been allegedly raping his younger daughter for the last two years. During interrogation, Gupta told the police that on July 26 night, he raped his daughter and beheaded her.警方表示，被告贾伊·普拉卡什·古普塔涉嫌在过去两年多次强奸其小女儿。在审讯过程中，古普塔告诉警方，7月26日晚，他强奸了自己的女儿，并将其斩首。He buried the head in Urwa area of the district and threw the lower part of the body in Kachna Nulla in Harpurbudhat. Police recovered the body on the basis of the information provided by the accused.他把砍下的头颅埋在乌尔瓦地区，把下半身扔在哈普巴德哈特的Kachna Nulla。警方根据被告提供的信息找到了尸体。Gupta admitted that he had been raping his daughter for the last two years.古普塔承认，在过去两年中他多次强奸其女儿。His wife died about 15 years ago and after the marriage of his elder daughter in 2015, Gupta and his younger daughter had been living in the house.古普塔的妻子在15年前去世，2015年大女儿结婚后，古普塔和小女儿一直住在这栋房子里。Senior superintendent of police Sunil Gupta said, "The accused has accepted that he raped and killed his daughter and the police have recovered the body parts. A case of rape and murder has been registered against the accused."高级警司苏尼尔·古普塔称:“被告已经承认奸杀了女儿，警方已经找到了尸体。凶手被控强奸和谋杀罪，已立案。”印度时报读者的评论：译文来源：三泰虎http://www.santaihu.com/48267.html   译者：Jessica.Wu外文：https://timesofindia.indiatimes.comHindustani•19 hours agosad to say.. but its time has come for us ..we hindu need some serious law..this is going out of control悲哀啊，制定严厉的法律吧。强奸这个问题已经失控了。
&#13;
Karun Chakma•19 hours agoWhat''s the fault of the daughter? Her misfortune that she was born to a Inhuman worst animal like person.他女儿犯了什么错? 真不幸，她的父亲是一个畜生
&#13;
Indian•India•23 hours agowe have to know that it''s just a normal thing.这事儿很平常
&#13;
Ullatt Subhas•Kochi•1 day agoDon’t bring Religion into this tragedy as it is commonly happening all over the world in many families and because of shame and guilt feelings it’s never brought to the open and it’s shamefully covered up.不要把宗教扯进这场悲剧中。这种事情，在世界各地都算普遍，只不过碍于羞耻和内疚，从来没有公开过而已，都被掩盖了。
&#13;
Durga Dass•1 day agoVery sad, you all are linking this criminal act of an individual with religion.Let us be realistic. Condemn the act of accused.,Don''t link it with anything else. Go scientifically and pathologically to study the anatomy of perverted minds of human beings.悲哀的是，大家都把这种个人犯罪行为和宗教联系在一起。实事求是一点，谴责被告的行为，不要把它和其他事情联系起来。要从科学和病理学的角度来剖析变态心理。
&#13;
Mumtaz Hussain•Dubai, UAE•1 day agoSexual assault, as we all know, is an appalling and unlawful act that has to be prosecuted. Rapists can be held back if they fear that they would be punished rigorously without the discrimination and leniency. It is essential to enforce capital punishment and rigorous imprisonment for the criminals involved in rapes and sexual assaults. The capital and severe laws are the most powerful methods / tools to curb the crimes everywhere in the world. The punishment should be prominent and a precedent for criminals in particular and for the public in general.众所周知，性侵犯是一种令人震惊的违法行为，必须起诉强奸犯。对强奸犯和性侵犯，务必执行死刑和监禁。严惩能起到震慑作用，可以防止类似案件的发生。死刑和监禁是遏制犯罪的最有力的方法。必须严惩，杀鸡儆猴，给其他罪犯和公众树一个先例。
&#13;
Tompok•Far East•1 day agoTime overdue for a revamp of the outdated law and judiciary system. These kind of criminals must be eliminated without wasting anybody''s time and money of the taxpayers.早就该修改法律，改革司法体系。
&#13;
Allwyn•1 day agoFather daughter relationship has been shamed by this man. Where is the society heading.父女关系被这个男人玷污了。这个社会何去何从？
&#13;
Just Only•1 day agoToday I can say that Hindus are champion in rape and murder. No one can beat them in this.论强奸和谋杀，印度人是冠军，在这方面没有人能超过他们。
&#13;
sunil kumar•Noida•1 day agoI m Hindu. My head bow with shame. Horrible henious crime. Unfortunate girl . We only talk big our national leaders of boasting, dreaming whereas on ground out little girls are not safe in their homes. What a shame. Dont send satellite do not dream big, my earnest request to my national Leader is to just make India rape free.作为印度人，我羞愧得低下了头。这个罪行令人发指，女孩太不幸了。我们成天夸夸其谈，我们国家领导人只会吹牛。女孩在自己家里都不安全，真丢人啊。别发射卫星了，别做美梦了，我对国家领导人的殷切要求，就是让印度不再发生强奸案。
&#13;
Samuel Thomas•1 day agoWe need to introduce public executions in some cases where they will serve as a deterrent to others. Cases of extreme cruelty such as this one needs to be punished exemplary and general public needs to witness it.对于某些案子，我们要实行公开处决，这样才有震慑作用。像这类极端残忍的案件，必须严惩，要让公众亲眼目睹行刑过程。
&#13;
Tiger Shabs•1 day agoTake him as a procedure on PCR within 2 days he will provide hard cash take it as bribe and leave the culprit on bail free for life as long as haftah keeps coming in . Shame on the countries law , why such people cannot be immediately hanged to death. In this scenario father rapes her own daughter for 2 years and the beheads her and police and law does nothing INSANE贿赂一下警察，2天内他就能获得保释。父亲在2年里多次强奸自己的女儿并将其斩首，警方什么都没做。要疯了。。
&#13;
Dilip•1 day agoDO WE NEED COURT TO HEAR HIS CASE, DO WE NEED A LAWYER TO FIGHT HIS CASE, WE NEED A ROPE TO HANG HIM OR A GUN TO SHOOT HIM NOW TODAY这个案子还需要庭审吗？需要律师为他辩护吗？直接拿根绳子绞死他，或者一枪毙了。
&#13;
typsygypsy gypsytypsy•Gods Green Earth•1 day ago... disgraceful .... the murderer should be hung pronto可耻。立即绞死这个杀人犯。
&#13;
Kamil Tisekar•1 day agoHe would have married again. Too low that man went. He should be hanged.他本可以再娶一个老婆的。绞死他。
&#13;
Jaihind•Unknown•1 day agoWhat a country, what a religion of falsehood, what kind of governance India is having? the most stupid, scumbags, literate worst beasts are living in this country B j piiigg ssss.....will offer him ticket to become NETA... f**** nnnggg hindutva goons celebrate your new neta has born...印度是个什么样的国家，是怎么治理的？这个国家生活着最愚蠢、最卑鄙、最没有文化的畜生。love chaganti• Jaihind•3 hours agoDear friend never say bad about our country or in particular my country , if you cannot like it please leave. You should be shameful to right like this , you are eating this countries food and breathing the Air and drinking the indian water and living in India亲，不要说我们国家的坏话，如果你不喜欢，就请离开。你生活在印度，吃着印度的饭菜，呼吸着印度的空气，喝着印度的水。说出这种话，你应该感到羞耻，
&#13;
Anil Kumar Tripathi• Jaihind•23 hours agoIdiot. ..its nothing to do with the religion or politics.....its the sick mentality of that person ....这与宗教或政治无关……这男的心理变态……
&#13;
Rajesh Singh• Jaihind•20 hours agoIndia is one of the most hootiya countries in the world. Hai hind.印度是全球最受欢迎的国家之一。印度必胜
&#13;
Mouni Baba•1 day agoNever mind! He is innocent. NOTHING will happen to him because in modern India, ALL RAPISTS AND BTUTAL MURDERERS ARE PROTECTED while every female live in constant fear of her life.,Have you ever heard of a SINGLE RAPIST OR MURDERER BEING HANGED? Nor they will ever be. In INdia, they are protected by the government.,What the country needs is a revolution wherr all politicians and all rapists are tied up to trees and burnt alive.他不会受到惩罚的。在印度，所有强奸犯和杀人犯都受到保护，而每个女性都生活在恐惧中，你听说过强奸犯或杀人犯被绞死的吗?永远不会的。在印度，他们受到政府的保护。这个国家需要的是一场革命，在这场革命中，所有的政客和强奸犯都将被绑在树上活活烧死。
&#13;
SJ•1 day agoHe should be publicly executed.应该公开处决这个男的。
&#13;
Sunitha Nair•1 day agoShame on humanity...What is India becoming a haven for rapists...Really really Sick country...Bloody hell印度是强奸犯的天堂，是个非常病态的国家…
&#13;
Nationcomesfirst• Sunitha Nair•Mother INDIA•19 hours agoHello sunitha Nair ..Rapists r everywhere in every part of the world. Iam talking about real world. Eastern, western, African, etc..It''s just few sick individuals with severe mental illness do these crimes.世界各地都有强奸犯，东方国家、西方国家、非洲等等。只有少数患有严重精神病的病人才会犯下这种罪行。
&#13;
Bittoo•1 day agoReally horrible.. How can a father rape and then murder his own daughter...shame on...太可怕了. .父亲怎么能奸杀自己的女儿……可耻……</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>mintpie: </b><br>
<span>中国建国以来民族问题是越来越大的，印度建国以来民族问题是越来越小的，这个看法我是支持的。你不能因为现在中国6分印度4分就忽略了中国是从8分降到6分，印度从1分涨到4分的事实。</span><br>
</p><p><b>FuManchu: </b><br>
<span>在印度教传统里，女性就是一物件，完全受男方支配。绿教好歹承认女性是和男性平等的人类，虽然权利不太完整。</span><br>
</p><p><b>fn_herstal: </b><br>
<span>天网 发表于 2019-8-20 13:29</span><br>
<span>以牙还压 ×</span><br>
<span>社会、司法各方面不惯着、偏袒某族群 √</span><br>
<span>你是说印度吗？</span><br>
<span>那没办法，印度可是个联邦，人家绿绿可是作为一个族群基本上“拥有”一些邦的，甚至主要的绿绿区域早几十年都独立成为了巴基斯坦，中央政府有能力给他们更高的待遇吗？</span><br>
</p><p><b>光荣的小学生: </b><br>
<span>mintpie 发表于 2019-8-20 13:38</span><br>
<span>中国建国以来民族问题是越来越大的，印度建国以来民族问题是越来越小的，这个看法我是支持的。你不能因为现 ...</span><br>
<span>呵呵，你不会以为以前看不到民族矛盾就没有民族矛盾了吧</span><br>
<span>互联网发达了，看来对你政治素养大有好处了</span><br>
<span>建议去新疆霍尔果斯体验一下什么叫少数民族和解放军</span><br>
</p><p><b>yenvy: </b><br>
<span>jai hind的麻将脸被下了么</span><br>
</p><p><b>马猴肥宅√: </b><br>
<span>很像十年前的微博评论……</span><br>
</p><p><b>马猴肥宅√: </b><br>
<span>天网 发表于 2019-8-20 12:45</span><br>
<span>三哥把七零八落、一堆土邦、主体民族不占多数、语言割裂的一陀地理概念渐渐捏合成一个有血有肉的民族国家 ...</span><br>
<span>对对对，跟cia没有一点关系</span><br>
</p><p><b>siwang26: </b><br>
<span>竟然没人把锅甩给国大党</span><br>
<span>JAI HIND！</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能手机投票的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>hcmn: </b><br>
<span>三泰虎有条评论真能说明印度人的心态，也就他们以为这种事情在世界各地都算普遍</span><br>
</p><p><b>皮卡丘跑快快: </b><br>
<span>亲，不要说我们国家的坏话，如果你不喜欢，就请离开。你生活在印度，吃着印度的饭菜，呼吸着印度的空气，喝着印度的水。说出这种话，你应该感到羞耻，</span><br>
</p><p><b>stmule: </b><br>
<span>印度必胜是不是新的波兰不会亡？</span><br>
</p><p><b>sjax001: </b><br>
<span>tillnight 发表于 2019-8-20 12:38</span><br>
<span>？？？你知不知道为什么印度在经常项目大额赤字的情况仍然能保持外汇储备？因为侨汇。恨国？ ...</span><br>
<span>恨国和爱自己家人有什么关系</span><br>
<span>喀啦啦就是靠侨汇养活的邦，执政的国大党和（已经沦落成二流在野党）的共产党恨不得bjp和印度中央政府死全家，手里的侨汇少拿了?</span><br>
</p><p><b>sjax001: </b><br>
<span>fn_herstal 发表于 2019-8-20 13:47</span><br>
<span>你是说印度吗？</span><br>
<span>那没办法，印度可是个联邦，人家绿绿可是作为一个族群基本上“拥有”一些邦的，甚至主要 ...</span><br>
<span>拥有哪个邦啊？穆斯林最多的西北和中央地区是bjp的基本盘，西孟的穆斯林还得指望草根国大不要翻脸给点活路，喀拉拉的穆斯林先把基督教干翻再说吧。至于克什米尔，过几天不搞人走地留就算好的了。印度没任何一个邦现在绿绿能说上话的，轮得到锡克教拜火教也轮不到他们。</span><br>
</p><p><b>大哀之君: </b><br>
<span>天网 发表于 2019-08-20 13:29:16</span><br>
<span>以牙还压 ×</span><br>
<span>社会、司法各方面不惯着、偏袒某族群 √不惯着个屁。没人惯着印度的穆斯林人口是怎么从印巴分治时的接近0%暴涨到今天的16%？照你自己的理论推导这国家都快完了你还闭眼胡吹，笑死个人</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能手机投票的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>放眼大世界: </b><br>
<span>据说全世界发生“荣誉谋杀”最多的国家，不是某一个伊斯兰国家而是印度</span><br>
</p><p><b>放眼大世界: </b><br>
<span>天网 发表于 2019-8-20 12:45</span><br>
<span>三哥把七零八落、一堆土邦、主体民族不占多数、语言割裂的一陀地理概念渐渐捏合成一个有血有肉的民族国家 ...</span><br>
<span>你不会是龙空来的吧，啥屁事都往民族问题上转进</span><br>
</p><p><b>天网: </b><br>
<span>大哀之君 发表于 2019-8-20 15:31</span><br>
<span>不惯着个屁。没人惯着印度的穆斯林人口是怎么从印巴分治时的接近0%暴涨到今天的16%？照你自己的理论推导这 ...</span><br>
<span>0%？提供个来源吧，穆斯林一开始是比较少，但不会这么0%。</span><br>
<span>印度教徒的生育率很低的，整个印度的出生率也快到接近时代更替线了，都是穆斯林生得多。我说的是在“司法和社会”上，老仙就是靠处理穆斯林和印度教的矛盾上压倒性地偏向印度教上位的。穆斯林生育意愿高有什么能提现惯着不惯着的，上门绝育才叫不惯着？</span><br>
</p><p><b>天网: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 天网 于 2019-8-20 15:47 编辑 </span><br>
<span>放眼大世界 发表于 2019-8-20 15:37</span><br>
<span>你不会是龙空来的吧，啥屁事都往民族问题上转进</span><br>
<span>#27：印度恨国党不少</span><br>
<span>#28：通过侨汇说明他们很爱国</span><br>
<span>我引用#28：印度恨国党比中国少很多。继而感叹一个拼凑起来的主体民族不占主体的多民族国家在同化和民族感情上凝聚力。比底牌好的中国,打出了相对自己底牌而言更好的效果。</span><br>
<span>这不是很自然啊。你们不回应话题直接立场攻击，什么我什么开小号给自己加鹅，你不是xx来的吧，我也莫名其妙呢</span><br>
</p><p><b>放眼大世界: </b><br>
<span>奶油小吉 发表于 2019-8-20 12:53</span><br>
<span>？？？？？，三哥10分天朝负分？印度教经常杀绿绿、东北邦那块经常有反政府游击队袭击警察这样也是一个有 ...</span><br>
<span>以前经常看到说日本人韩国人比中国人更爱国更有凝聚力，但这真是第一次看到有人说印度比中国更爱国更有凝聚力的</span><br>
</p><p><b>放眼大世界: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 放眼大世界 于 2019-8-20 16:06 编辑 </span><br>
<span>天网 发表于 2019-8-20 15:43</span><br>
<span>#27：印度恨国党不少</span><br>
<span>#28：通过侨汇说明他们很爱国</span><br>
<span>我引用#28：印度恨国党比中国少很多。继而感叹一个拼凑 ...</span><br>
<span>主贴说的是印度的一起强奸亲生女儿的案件，跟什么民族问题宗教问题国家认同问题绿教问题丝毫没有关系，你却莫名其妙的扯这些问题，而且得出的什么“三哥10分中国负分”的结论荒谬无比，当然要对你的动机产生的怀疑！</span><br>
<span>还有对于侨汇这一点，这能说明什么？当年抗美援朝的时候可是人人踊跃捐款捐物为志愿军提供支持的，连在监狱里的溥仪都受到感染，捐出了私藏的宝物，之前还是“一盘散沙”的中国人，怎么这么有凝聚力了呢？</span><br>
</p><p><b>哈桑: </b><br>
<span>奶油小吉 发表于 2019-8-20 12:53</span><br>
<span> ？？？？？，三哥10分天朝负分？印度教经常杀绿绿、东北邦那块经常有反政府游击队袭击警察这样也是一个有 ...</span><br>
<span>都打得血肉横飞了还不叫有血有肉？</span><br>
</p><p><b>蝶梦魂: </b><br>
<span>Indian•India•23 hours ago we have to know that it''s just a normal thing.                  Ullatt Subhas•Kochi•1 day ago Don’t bring Religion into this tragedy as it is commonly happening all over the world in many families and because of shame and guilt feelings it’s never brought to the open and it’s shamefully covered up.    行吧，印必胜</span><br>
</p><p><b>蝶梦魂: </b><br>
<span>天网 发表于 2019-8-20 12:45</span><br>
<span>三哥把七零八落、一堆土邦、主体民族不占多数、语言割裂的一陀地理概念渐渐捏合成一个有血有肉的民族国家 ...</span><br>
<span>阁下主基地是龙空还是北朝？   这个转进法很眼熟啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>荒南君: </b><br>
<span>鬼父在全世界都有，因为总有人的理智无法战胜兽欲</span><br>
<span>……但斩首绝对是特色吧！</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 8 Lite, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>放眼大世界: </b><br>
<span>光荣的小学生 发表于 2019-8-20 13:56</span><br>
<span>呵呵，你不会以为以前看不到民族矛盾就没有民族矛盾了吧</span><br>
<span>互联网发达了，看来对你政治素养大有好处了</span><br>
<span>跟你分享个故事吧，这故事时常被国粉拿来论证“相较于TG，常公的屁股更偏向汉人”</span><br>
<span>民国时期，几个少数民族的酋长一类的人来到上海想见识下现代化的生活，结果被抓起来关到笼子里作为“落后民族样板”拉去进行展览，气的这些人回去就找了当地的红军投了TG</span><br>
</p><p><b>天网: </b><br>
<span>放眼大世界 发表于 2019-8-20 15:58</span><br>
<span>主贴说的是印度的一起强奸亲生女儿的案件，跟什么民族问题宗教问题国家认同问题绿教问题丝毫没有关系，你 ...</span><br>
<span>#31 我的论据是：建国95%是汉族的国家玩了60年把民族问题玩成了第一大内患。同样汉族占多数的特别行政区政策也是乏善可陈，越舔越对立。这是一败。</span><br>
<span>而印度可以把根本不是印度传统地区的占领区，根本没有主体民族占多数多地区（胁迫加入印度的土绑、果阿、锡金）转换成自己的地区。这次的克什米尔取消自治权亦是行动迅速、对局势判断准确、手腕果断的典范。这是一成。</span><br>
<span>为什么这一点你一直在无视，一直把话题转到什么什么抗美援朝华侨乱七八糟的东西少呢。为什么你一直不回应我的核心论据。老在给我安乱七八糟的帽子呢。</span><br>
</p><p><b>天网: </b><br>
<span>放眼大世界 发表于 2019-8-20 15:58</span><br>
<span>主贴说的是印度的一起强奸亲生女儿的案件，跟什么民族问题宗教问题国家认同问题绿教问题丝毫没有关系，你 ...</span><br>
<span>我也不知道为什么强奸案会扯到印度恨国党、侨汇上，你问问前面几楼？</span><br>
</p><p><b>卡奥斯·克斯拉: </b><br>
<span>放眼大世界 发表于 2019-8-20 15:58</span><br>
<span>主贴说的是印度的一起强奸亲生女儿的案件，跟什么民族问题宗教问题国家认同问题绿教问题丝毫没有关系，你 ...</span><br>
<span>大梵天也干了不过代价是被砍掉一个头（5-1）</span><br>
</p><p><b>放眼大世界: </b><br>
<span>天网 发表于 2019-8-20 16:14</span><br>
<span>#31 我的论据是：建国95%是汉族的国家玩了60年把民族问题玩成了第一大内患。同样汉族占多数的特别行政区 ...</span><br>
<span>https://www.bilibili.com/video/av18375176</span><br>
<span>自己看看去吧，人家可是在印度待过的，我想他们比你有发言权，现在印度连度量衡都没统一，说句你不喜欢听的话，现在印度的凝聚力还没秦始皇时候的中国高</span><br>
<span>至于为什么无视你，那是因为你说的东西和本帖应该讨论的内容屁点关系没有，好比语文考试你写了篇离题的作文，那么批卷老师也没必要细看直接给低分了</span><br>
</p><p><b>天网: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 天网 于 2019-8-20 16:39 编辑 </span><br>
<span>放眼大世界 发表于 2019-8-20 16:23</span><br>
<span>https://www.bilibili.com/video/av18375176</span><br>
<span>自己看看去吧，人家可是在印度待过的，我想他们比你有发言权 ...</span><br>
<span>所以你一直在给我安帽子啊，我说印度这一个七零八落的国家在吸收新地区上很有政策和手腕。而中国这个几千年大一统的国家却在处理这些问题上与自己的段位不配。这就代表我说过“印度凝聚力比中国强了”？原来独立时候几百个土邦根本不是印度传统地盘，现有领土一半是强行并进去的。现在都会一起高呼jai hind了。我判断一下印度的民族国家意识正在形成也没问题吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>卡奥斯·克斯拉: </b><br>
<span>天网 发表于 2019-8-20 16:28</span><br>
<span>所以你一直在给我安帽子啊，我说印度这一个七零八落的国家在吸收新地区上很有政策和手腕。而中国这 ...</span><br>
<span>通过宗教认同替换的国家认同更容易极端化</span><br>
</p><p><b>氪金萌新: </b><br>
<span>恋想花火 发表于 2019-8-20 11:48</span><br>
<span>love chaganti• Jaihind•3 hours ago</span><br>
<span>Dear friend never say bad about our country or in particular my ...</span><br>
<span>印度版的阴阳怪气？</span><br>
</p><p><b>鲭saba: </b><br>
<span>安娜导函数 发表于 2019-8-20 11:58</span><br>
<span>这种算荣誉谋杀么？？ 我女儿和她丈夫以外的人发生关系，为了保护家族荣誉将她斩首这种？ ...</span><br>
<span>我也是这么想的</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 OnePlus ONEPLUS A5010, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>top2000: </b><br>
<span>鬼父倒是哪里都有 砍头是不是印度特色</span><br>
<span>— from HMD Global Nokia 7 plus, Android 9 of S1 Next Goose v2.0.4-play</span><br>
</p><p><b>放眼大世界: </b><br>
<span>天网 发表于 2019-8-20 16:28</span><br>
<span>所以你一直在给我安帽子啊，我说印度这一个七零八落的国家在吸收新地区上很有政策和手腕。而中国这 ...</span><br>
<span>是谁先扯跟主贴完全无关的东西的？</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1854634[50-100]</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>印度一男子强奸19岁女儿并将其斩首[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1854634-1-1.html</link>
      <description>印度一男子强奸19岁女儿并将其斩首&#13;
Gorakhpur man arrested for raping, beheading 19-year-old daughter戈勒克布尔一男子奸杀19岁女儿并将其斩首，现已被捕GORAKHPUR: A man was arrested on Saturday for allegedly raping and beheading her 19-year-old daughter in Bathbuzurg village of Gorakhpur.戈勒克布尔：周六，戈勒克布尔Bathbuzurg村一名男子因涉嫌强奸19岁女儿并将其斩首而被捕。The arrest was made on the complaint of the elder daughter of the accused.被告的大女儿报案后，警方将凶手逮捕归案。http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/e3e8f136fd25908173e5a6844ce41a31.pngPolice said the accused, Jai Prakash Gupta had been allegedly raping his younger daughter for the last two years. During interrogation, Gupta told the police that on July 26 night, he raped his daughter and beheaded her.警方表示，被告贾伊·普拉卡什·古普塔涉嫌在过去两年多次强奸其小女儿。在审讯过程中，古普塔告诉警方，7月26日晚，他强奸了自己的女儿，并将其斩首。He buried the head in Urwa area of the district and threw the lower part of the body in Kachna Nulla in Harpurbudhat. Police recovered the body on the basis of the information provided by the accused.他把砍下的头颅埋在乌尔瓦地区，把下半身扔在哈普巴德哈特的Kachna Nulla。警方根据被告提供的信息找到了尸体。Gupta admitted that he had been raping his daughter for the last two years.古普塔承认，在过去两年中他多次强奸其女儿。His wife died about 15 years ago and after the marriage of his elder daughter in 2015, Gupta and his younger daughter had been living in the house.古普塔的妻子在15年前去世，2015年大女儿结婚后，古普塔和小女儿一直住在这栋房子里。Senior superintendent of police Sunil Gupta said, "The accused has accepted that he raped and killed his daughter and the police have recovered the body parts. A case of rape and murder has been registered against the accused."高级警司苏尼尔·古普塔称:“被告已经承认奸杀了女儿，警方已经找到了尸体。凶手被控强奸和谋杀罪，已立案。”印度时报读者的评论：译文来源：三泰虎http://www.santaihu.com/48267.html   译者：Jessica.Wu外文：https://timesofindia.indiatimes.comHindustani•19 hours agosad to say.. but its time has come for us ..we hindu need some serious law..this is going out of control悲哀啊，制定严厉的法律吧。强奸这个问题已经失控了。
&#13;
Karun Chakma•19 hours agoWhat''s the fault of the daughter? Her misfortune that she was born to a Inhuman worst animal like person.他女儿犯了什么错? 真不幸，她的父亲是一个畜生
&#13;
Indian•India•23 hours agowe have to know that it''s just a normal thing.这事儿很平常
&#13;
Ullatt Subhas•Kochi•1 day agoDon’t bring Religion into this tragedy as it is commonly happening all over the world in many families and because of shame and guilt feelings it’s never brought to the open and it’s shamefully covered up.不要把宗教扯进这场悲剧中。这种事情，在世界各地都算普遍，只不过碍于羞耻和内疚，从来没有公开过而已，都被掩盖了。
&#13;
Durga Dass•1 day agoVery sad, you all are linking this criminal act of an individual with religion.Let us be realistic. Condemn the act of accused.,Don''t link it with anything else. Go scientifically and pathologically to study the anatomy of perverted minds of human beings.悲哀的是，大家都把这种个人犯罪行为和宗教联系在一起。实事求是一点，谴责被告的行为，不要把它和其他事情联系起来。要从科学和病理学的角度来剖析变态心理。
&#13;
Mumtaz Hussain•Dubai, UAE•1 day agoSexual assault, as we all know, is an appalling and unlawful act that has to be prosecuted. Rapists can be held back if they fear that they would be punished rigorously without the discrimination and leniency. It is essential to enforce capital punishment and rigorous imprisonment for the criminals involved in rapes and sexual assaults. The capital and severe laws are the most powerful methods / tools to curb the crimes everywhere in the world. The punishment should be prominent and a precedent for criminals in particular and for the public in general.众所周知，性侵犯是一种令人震惊的违法行为，必须起诉强奸犯。对强奸犯和性侵犯，务必执行死刑和监禁。严惩能起到震慑作用，可以防止类似案件的发生。死刑和监禁是遏制犯罪的最有力的方法。必须严惩，杀鸡儆猴，给其他罪犯和公众树一个先例。
&#13;
Tompok•Far East•1 day agoTime overdue for a revamp of the outdated law and judiciary system. These kind of criminals must be eliminated without wasting anybody''s time and money of the taxpayers.早就该修改法律，改革司法体系。
&#13;
Allwyn•1 day agoFather daughter relationship has been shamed by this man. Where is the society heading.父女关系被这个男人玷污了。这个社会何去何从？
&#13;
Just Only•1 day agoToday I can say that Hindus are champion in rape and murder. No one can beat them in this.论强奸和谋杀，印度人是冠军，在这方面没有人能超过他们。
&#13;
sunil kumar•Noida•1 day agoI m Hindu. My head bow with shame. Horrible henious crime. Unfortunate girl . We only talk big our national leaders of boasting, dreaming whereas on ground out little girls are not safe in their homes. What a shame. Dont send satellite do not dream big, my earnest request to my national Leader is to just make India rape free.作为印度人，我羞愧得低下了头。这个罪行令人发指，女孩太不幸了。我们成天夸夸其谈，我们国家领导人只会吹牛。女孩在自己家里都不安全，真丢人啊。别发射卫星了，别做美梦了，我对国家领导人的殷切要求，就是让印度不再发生强奸案。
&#13;
Samuel Thomas•1 day agoWe need to introduce public executions in some cases where they will serve as a deterrent to others. Cases of extreme cruelty such as this one needs to be punished exemplary and general public needs to witness it.对于某些案子，我们要实行公开处决，这样才有震慑作用。像这类极端残忍的案件，必须严惩，要让公众亲眼目睹行刑过程。
&#13;
Tiger Shabs•1 day agoTake him as a procedure on PCR within 2 days he will provide hard cash take it as bribe and leave the culprit on bail free for life as long as haftah keeps coming in . Shame on the countries law , why such people cannot be immediately hanged to death. In this scenario father rapes her own daughter for 2 years and the beheads her and police and law does nothing INSANE贿赂一下警察，2天内他就能获得保释。父亲在2年里多次强奸自己的女儿并将其斩首，警方什么都没做。要疯了。。
&#13;
Dilip•1 day agoDO WE NEED COURT TO HEAR HIS CASE, DO WE NEED A LAWYER TO FIGHT HIS CASE, WE NEED A ROPE TO HANG HIM OR A GUN TO SHOOT HIM NOW TODAY这个案子还需要庭审吗？需要律师为他辩护吗？直接拿根绳子绞死他，或者一枪毙了。
&#13;
typsygypsy gypsytypsy•Gods Green Earth•1 day ago... disgraceful .... the murderer should be hung pronto可耻。立即绞死这个杀人犯。
&#13;
Kamil Tisekar•1 day agoHe would have married again. Too low that man went. He should be hanged.他本可以再娶一个老婆的。绞死他。
&#13;
Jaihind•Unknown•1 day agoWhat a country, what a religion of falsehood, what kind of governance India is having? the most stupid, scumbags, literate worst beasts are living in this country B j piiigg ssss.....will offer him ticket to become NETA... f**** nnnggg hindutva goons celebrate your new neta has born...印度是个什么样的国家，是怎么治理的？这个国家生活着最愚蠢、最卑鄙、最没有文化的畜生。love chaganti• Jaihind•3 hours agoDear friend never say bad about our country or in particular my country , if you cannot like it please leave. You should be shameful to right like this , you are eating this countries food and breathing the Air and drinking the indian water and living in India亲，不要说我们国家的坏话，如果你不喜欢，就请离开。你生活在印度，吃着印度的饭菜，呼吸着印度的空气，喝着印度的水。说出这种话，你应该感到羞耻，
&#13;
Anil Kumar Tripathi• Jaihind•23 hours agoIdiot. ..its nothing to do with the religion or politics.....its the sick mentality of that person ....这与宗教或政治无关……这男的心理变态……
&#13;
Rajesh Singh• Jaihind•20 hours agoIndia is one of the most hootiya countries in the world. Hai hind.印度是全球最受欢迎的国家之一。印度必胜
&#13;
Mouni Baba•1 day agoNever mind! He is innocent. NOTHING will happen to him because in modern India, ALL RAPISTS AND BTUTAL MURDERERS ARE PROTECTED while every female live in constant fear of her life.,Have you ever heard of a SINGLE RAPIST OR MURDERER BEING HANGED? Nor they will ever be. In INdia, they are protected by the government.,What the country needs is a revolution wherr all politicians and all rapists are tied up to trees and burnt alive.他不会受到惩罚的。在印度，所有强奸犯和杀人犯都受到保护，而每个女性都生活在恐惧中，你听说过强奸犯或杀人犯被绞死的吗?永远不会的。在印度，他们受到政府的保护。这个国家需要的是一场革命，在这场革命中，所有的政客和强奸犯都将被绑在树上活活烧死。
&#13;
SJ•1 day agoHe should be publicly executed.应该公开处决这个男的。
&#13;
Sunitha Nair•1 day agoShame on humanity...What is India becoming a haven for rapists...Really really Sick country...Bloody hell印度是强奸犯的天堂，是个非常病态的国家…
&#13;
Nationcomesfirst• Sunitha Nair•Mother INDIA•19 hours agoHello sunitha Nair ..Rapists r everywhere in every part of the world. Iam talking about real world. Eastern, western, African, etc..It''s just few sick individuals with severe mental illness do these crimes.世界各地都有强奸犯，东方国家、西方国家、非洲等等。只有少数患有严重精神病的病人才会犯下这种罪行。
&#13;
Bittoo•1 day agoReally horrible.. How can a father rape and then murder his own daughter...shame on...太可怕了. .父亲怎么能奸杀自己的女儿……可耻……</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>狒狗: </b><br>
<span>印度一男子强奸19岁女儿并将其斩首</span><br>
<span>Gorakhpur man arrested for raping, beheading 19-year-old daughter戈勒克布尔一男子奸杀19岁女儿并将其斩首，现已被捕GORAKHPUR: A man was arrested on Saturday for allegedly raping and beheading her 19-year-old daughter in Bathbuzurg village of Gorakhpur.戈勒克布尔：周六，戈勒克布尔Bathbuzurg村一名男子因涉嫌强奸19岁女儿并将其斩首而被捕。The arrest was made on the complaint of the elder daughter of the accused.被告的大女儿报案后，警方将凶手逮捕归案。http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/e3e8f136fd25908173e5a6844ce41a31.pngPolice said the accused, Jai Prakash Gupta had been allegedly raping his younger daughter for the last two years. During interrogation, Gupta told the police that on July 26 night, he raped his daughter and beheaded her.警方表示，被告贾伊·普拉卡什·古普塔涉嫌在过去两年多次强奸其小女儿。在审讯过程中，古普塔告诉警方，7月26日晚，他强奸了自己的女儿，并将其斩首。He buried the head in Urwa area of the district and threw the lower part of the body in Kachna Nulla in Harpurbudhat. Police recovered the body on the basis of the information provided by the accused.他把砍下的头颅埋在乌尔瓦地区，把下半身扔在哈普巴德哈特的Kachna Nulla。警方根据被告提供的信息找到了尸体。Gupta admitted that he had been raping his daughter for the last two years.古普塔承认，在过去两年中他多次强奸其女儿。His wife died about 15 years ago and after the marriage of his elder daughter in 2015, Gupta and his younger daughter had been living in the house.古普塔的妻子在15年前去世，2015年大女儿结婚后，古普塔和小女儿一直住在这栋房子里。Senior superintendent of police Sunil Gupta said, "The accused has accepted that he raped and killed his daughter and the police have recovered the body parts. A case of rape and murder has been registered against the accused."高级警司苏尼尔·古普塔称:“被告已经承认奸杀了女儿，警方已经找到了尸体。凶手被控强奸和谋杀罪，已立案。”印度时报读者的评论：译文来源：三泰虎http://www.santaihu.com/48267.html   译者：Jessica.Wu外文：https://timesofindia.indiatimes.comHindustani•19 hours agosad to say.. but its time has come for us ..we hindu need some serious law..this is going out of control悲哀啊，制定严厉的法律吧。强奸这个问题已经失控了。</span><br>
<span>Karun Chakma•19 hours agoWhat''s the fault of the daughter? Her misfortune that she was born to a Inhuman worst animal like person.他女儿犯了什么错? 真不幸，她的父亲是一个畜生</span><br>
<span>Indian•India•23 hours agowe have to know that it''s just a normal thing.这事儿很平常</span><br>
<span>Ullatt Subhas•Kochi•1 day agoDon’t bring Religion into this tragedy as it is commonly happening all over the world in many families and because of shame and guilt feelings it’s never brought to the open and it’s shamefully covered up.不要把宗教扯进这场悲剧中。这种事情，在世界各地都算普遍，只不过碍于羞耻和内疚，从来没有公开过而已，都被掩盖了。</span><br>
<span>Durga Dass•1 day agoVery sad, you all are linking this criminal act of an individual with religion.Let us be realistic. Condemn the act of accused.,Don''t link it with anything else. Go scientifically and pathologically to study the anatomy of perverted minds of human beings.悲哀的是，大家都把这种个人犯罪行为和宗教联系在一起。实事求是一点，谴责被告的行为，不要把它和其他事情联系起来。要从科学和病理学的角度来剖析变态心理。</span><br>
<span>Mumtaz Hussain•Dubai, UAE•1 day agoSexual assault, as we all know, is an appalling and unlawful act that has to be prosecuted. Rapists can be held back if they fear that they would be punished rigorously without the discrimination and leniency. It is essential to enforce capital punishment and rigorous imprisonment for the criminals involved in rapes and sexual assaults. The capital and severe laws are the most powerful methods / tools to curb the crimes everywhere in the world. The punishment should be prominent and a precedent for criminals in particular and for the public in general.众所周知，性侵犯是一种令人震惊的违法行为，必须起诉强奸犯。对强奸犯和性侵犯，务必执行死刑和监禁。严惩能起到震慑作用，可以防止类似案件的发生。死刑和监禁是遏制犯罪的最有力的方法。必须严惩，杀鸡儆猴，给其他罪犯和公众树一个先例。</span><br>
<span>Tompok•Far East•1 day agoTime overdue for a revamp of the outdated law and judiciary system. These kind of criminals must be eliminated without wasting anybody''s time and money of the taxpayers.早就该修改法律，改革司法体系。</span><br>
<span>Allwyn•1 day agoFather daughter relationship has been shamed by this man. Where is the society heading.父女关系被这个男人玷污了。这个社会何去何从？</span><br>
<span>Just Only•1 day agoToday I can say that Hindus are champion in rape and murder. No one can beat them in this.论强奸和谋杀，印度人是冠军，在这方面没有人能超过他们。</span><br>
<span>sunil kumar•Noida•1 day agoI m Hindu. My head bow with shame. Horrible henious crime. Unfortunate girl . We only talk big our national leaders of boasting, dreaming whereas on ground out little girls are not safe in their homes. What a shame. Dont send satellite do not dream big, my earnest request to my national Leader is to just make India rape free.作为印度人，我羞愧得低下了头。这个罪行令人发指，女孩太不幸了。我们成天夸夸其谈，我们国家领导人只会吹牛。女孩在自己家里都不安全，真丢人啊。别发射卫星了，别做美梦了，我对国家领导人的殷切要求，就是让印度不再发生强奸案。</span><br>
<span>Samuel Thomas•1 day agoWe need to introduce public executions in some cases where they will serve as a deterrent to others. Cases of extreme cruelty such as this one needs to be punished exemplary and general public needs to witness it.对于某些案子，我们要实行公开处决，这样才有震慑作用。像这类极端残忍的案件，必须严惩，要让公众亲眼目睹行刑过程。</span><br>
<span>Tiger Shabs•1 day agoTake him as a procedure on PCR within 2 days he will provide hard cash take it as bribe and leave the culprit on bail free for life as long as haftah keeps coming in . Shame on the countries law , why such people cannot be immediately hanged to death. In this scenario father rapes her own daughter for 2 years and the beheads her and police and law does nothing INSANE贿赂一下警察，2天内他就能获得保释。父亲在2年里多次强奸自己的女儿并将其斩首，警方什么都没做。要疯了。。</span><br>
<span>Dilip•1 day agoDO WE NEED COURT TO HEAR HIS CASE, DO WE NEED A LAWYER TO FIGHT HIS CASE, WE NEED A ROPE TO HANG HIM OR A GUN TO SHOOT HIM NOW TODAY这个案子还需要庭审吗？需要律师为他辩护吗？直接拿根绳子绞死他，或者一枪毙了。</span><br>
<span>typsygypsy gypsytypsy•Gods Green Earth•1 day ago... disgraceful .... the murderer should be hung pronto可耻。立即绞死这个杀人犯。</span><br>
<span>Kamil Tisekar•1 day agoHe would have married again. Too low that man went. He should be hanged.他本可以再娶一个老婆的。绞死他。</span><br>
<span>Jaihind•Unknown•1 day agoWhat a country, what a religion of falsehood, what kind of governance India is having? the most stupid, scumbags, literate worst beasts are living in this country B j piiigg ssss.....will offer him ticket to become NETA... f**** nnnggg hindutva goons celebrate your new neta has born...印度是个什么样的国家，是怎么治理的？这个国家生活着最愚蠢、最卑鄙、最没有文化的畜生。love chaganti• Jaihind•3 hours agoDear friend never say bad about our country or in particular my country , if you cannot like it please leave. You should be shameful to right like this , you are eating this countries food and breathing the Air and drinking the indian water and living in India亲，不要说我们国家的坏话，如果你不喜欢，就请离开。你生活在印度，吃着印度的饭菜，呼吸着印度的空气，喝着印度的水。说出这种话，你应该感到羞耻，</span><br>
<span>Anil Kumar Tripathi• Jaihind•23 hours agoIdiot. ..its nothing to do with the religion or politics.....its the sick mentality of that person ....这与宗教或政治无关……这男的心理变态……</span><br>
<span>Rajesh Singh• Jaihind•20 hours agoIndia is one of the most hootiya countries in the world. Hai hind.印度是全球最受欢迎的国家之一。印度必胜</span><br>
<span>Mouni Baba•1 day agoNever mind! He is innocent. NOTHING will happen to him because in modern India, ALL RAPISTS AND BTUTAL MURDERERS ARE PROTECTED while every female live in constant fear of her life.,Have you ever heard of a SINGLE RAPIST OR MURDERER BEING HANGED? Nor they will ever be. In INdia, they are protected by the government.,What the country needs is a revolution wherr all politicians and all rapists are tied up to trees and burnt alive.他不会受到惩罚的。在印度，所有强奸犯和杀人犯都受到保护，而每个女性都生活在恐惧中，你听说过强奸犯或杀人犯被绞死的吗?永远不会的。在印度，他们受到政府的保护。这个国家需要的是一场革命，在这场革命中，所有的政客和强奸犯都将被绑在树上活活烧死。</span><br>
<span>SJ•1 day agoHe should be publicly executed.应该公开处决这个男的。</span><br>
<span>Sunitha Nair•1 day agoShame on humanity...What is India becoming a haven for rapists...Really really Sick country...Bloody hell印度是强奸犯的天堂，是个非常病态的国家…</span><br>
<span>Nationcomesfirst• Sunitha Nair•Mother INDIA•19 hours agoHello sunitha Nair ..Rapists r everywhere in every part of the world. Iam talking about real world. Eastern, western, African, etc..It''s just few sick individuals with severe mental illness do these crimes.世界各地都有强奸犯，东方国家、西方国家、非洲等等。只有少数患有严重精神病的病人才会犯下这种罪行。</span><br>
<span>Bittoo•1 day agoReally horrible.. How can a father rape and then murder his own daughter...shame on...太可怕了. .父亲怎么能奸杀自己的女儿……可耻……</span><br>
</p><p><b>soulogic: </b><br>
<span>Jai Hind ！</span><br>
</p><p><b>pockem: </b><br>
<span>Don’t bring Religion into this tragedy as it is commonly happening all over the world in many families and because of shame and guilt feelings it’s never brought to the open and it’s shamefully covered up.</span><br>
<span>不要把宗教扯进这场悲剧中。这种事情，在世界各地都算普遍，只不过碍于羞耻和内疚，从来没有公开过而已，都被掩盖了。</span><br>
<span>翻译成常见句型：哪都有好人和坏人，哪都有鬼父，这个人不能代表印度人。我有个朋友……</span><br>
</p><p><b>Pinchbeck: </b><br>
<span>能养到19岁才...在硬度人里是不是算挺难得的</span><br>
</p><p><b>米缸: </b><br>
<span>这种事情，在世界各地都算普遍。</span><br>
<span>是么？那真的牛逼。</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Google Pixel XL, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.0</span><br>
</p><p><b>红都剧院24排4号: </b><br>
<span>印度恨国党VS印度粉红吗，说话的腔调都和泥潭差不多</span><br>
</p><p><b>恋想花火: </b><br>
<span>love chaganti• Jaihind•3 hours ago</span><br>
<span>Dear friend never say bad about our country or in particular my country , if you cannot like it please leave. You should be shameful to right like this , you are eating this countries food and breathing the Air and drinking the indian water and living in India</span><br>
<span>亲，不要说我们国家的坏话，如果你不喜欢，就请离开。你生活在印度，吃着印度的饭菜，呼吸着印度的空气，喝着印度的水。说出这种话，你应该感到羞耻。</span><br>
<span>嗯？？？？？？？？？？？？？？？？？？？？</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能手机投票的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>产丿丿丿: </b><br>
<span>Rajesh Singh• Jaihind•20 hours ago</span><br>
<span>India is one of the most hootiya countries in the world. Hai hind.</span><br>
<span>印度是全球最受欢迎的国家之一。印度必胜</span><br>
</p><p><b>丹德里恩: </b><br>
<span>印度必胜</span><br>
</p><p><b>popeacg: </b><br>
<span>这种事情，在世界各地都算普遍，只不过碍于羞耻和内疚，从来没有公开过而已，都被掩盖了。</span><br>
<span>jail hindi</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 OnePlus ONEPLUS A5010, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>无敌大法师: </b><br>
<span>哇 厉害</span><br>
</p><p><b>jzsgtx: </b><br>
<span>Jai hind！</span><br>
</p><p><b>逃离学校: </b><br>
<span>这评论这么有既视感</span><br>
</p><p><b>你妈的为什么: </b><br>
<span>Hai hind！</span><br>
<span>Jaihind！</span><br>
<span>jail hind！</span><br>
</p><p><b>nanrendu: </b><br>
<span>还是有很正常的回复啊，这几年感觉印度网民越来越正常了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>安娜导函数: </b><br>
<span>这种算荣誉谋杀么？？ 我女儿和她丈夫以外的人发生关系，为了保护家族荣誉将她斩首这种？</span><br>
</p><p><b>zxlice: </b><br>
<span>印度人的贤者时间这么可怕？</span><br>
</p><p><b>狒狗: </b><br>
<span>安娜导函数 发表于 2019-8-20 11:58</span><br>
<span>这种算荣誉谋杀么？？ 我女儿和她丈夫以外的人发生关系，为了保护家族荣誉将她斩首这种？ ...</span><br>
<span>荣誉谋杀？</span><br>
<span>看清楚新闻内容哦</span><br>
</p><p><b>掉过脑袋: </b><br>
<span>世界各地都很普遍</span><br>
<span>人头滚滚的世界么</span><br>
</p><p><b>luy3244213: </b><br>
<span>恋想花火 发表于 2019-8-20 11:48</span><br>
<span>love chaganti• Jaihind•3 hours ago</span><br>
<span>Dear friend never say bad about our country or in particular my ...</span><br>
<span>印度洋没加盖，不服你游出去</span><br>
</p><p><b>hsyg: </b><br>
<span>Dont send satellite do not dream big, my earnest request to my national Leader is to just make India rape free.</span><br>
<span>别发射卫星了，别做美梦了，我对国家领导人的殷切要求，就是让印度不再发生强奸案。</span><br>
<span>魔笛：那个这位朋友，我们还是来继续讨论登陆火星吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>poppin: </b><br>
<span>把底下的评论安到国内恶性杀人案新闻下面都没有任何违和感</span><br>
</p><p><b>perfaceNext: </b><br>
<span>luy3244213 发表于 2019-8-20 12:08</span><br>
<span>印度洋没加盖，不服你游出去</span><br>
<span>走过去都可以啊，为啥要游泳</span><br>
</p><p><b>ualiant: </b><br>
<span>nanrendu 发表于 2019-8-20 11:57</span><br>
<span>还是有很正常的回复啊，这几年感觉印度网民越来越正常了。</span><br>
<span>回帖的明显不全是阿三啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>铁神: </b><br>
<span>JS不算稀奇，但斩首我只能联系到你们的习俗了，抱歉</span><br>
</p><p><b>weary10: </b><br>
<span>jail hind!!!</span><br>
</p><p><b>yexuning: </b><br>
<span>ualiant 发表于 2019-8-20 12:31</span><br>
<span>回帖的明显不全是阿三啊</span><br>
<span>阿三的恨国党一点也不少，不然干嘛那么多移民了美国</span><br>
</p><p><b>tillnight: </b><br>
<span>yexuning 发表于 2019-8-20 12:34</span><br>
<span>阿三的恨国党一点也不少，不然干嘛那么多移民了美国</span><br>
<span>？？？你知不知道为什么印度在经常项目大额赤字的情况仍然能保持外汇储备？因为侨汇。恨国？</span><br>
</p><p><b>loveoniji: </b><br>
<span>阿三那边的强奸案往往都伴随着谋杀，并且有相当数量是斩首，他们为啥如此偏爱斩首？</span><br>
</p><p><b>性欲モンスター: </b><br>
<span>建议把鬼父的丁丁斩首，如果他失血过多昏迷还能活的话就判终生监禁，死了的话就判死刑。</span><br>
</p><p><b>天网: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 天网 于 2019-8-20 12:53 编辑 </span><br>
<span>tillnight 发表于 2019-8-20 12:38</span><br>
<span>？？？你知不知道为什么印度在经常项目大额赤字的情况仍然能保持外汇储备？因为侨汇。恨国？ ...</span><br>
<span>三哥把七零八落、一堆土邦、主体民族不占多数、语言割裂的一陀地理概念渐渐捏合成一个有血有肉的民族国家卓有成效。烂牌打出了10分。天朝10分牌打成了负分。建国95%是汉族的国家玩了60年把民族问题玩成了第一大内患，史诗级成就了。香港台湾和大陆间对立也是史诗级的，乃至朝鲜和韩国的同民族认同都比港台大陆强点。</span><br>
</p><p><b>我真的很變態: </b><br>
<span> जय हिन्द！</span><br>
</p><p><b>细雨湿流光: </b><br>
<span>天网 发表于 2019-8-20 12:45</span><br>
<span>三哥把七零八落、一堆土邦、主体民族不占多数、语言割裂的一陀地理概念渐渐捏合成一个有血有肉的民族国家 ...</span><br>
<span>Jail hind</span><br>
</p><p><b>yexuning: </b><br>
<span>天网 发表于 2019-8-20 12:45</span><br>
<span>三哥把七零八落、一堆土邦、主体民族不占多数、语言割裂的一陀地理概念渐渐捏合成一个有血有肉的民族国家 ...</span><br>
<span>最主要的原因还是印度对西方构不成威胁</span><br>
</p><p><b>奶油小吉: </b><br>
<span>天网 发表于 2019-8-20 12:45</span><br>
<span>三哥把七零八落、一堆土邦、主体民族不占多数、语言割裂的一陀地理概念渐渐捏合成一个有血有肉的民族国家 ...</span><br>
<span>？？？？？，三哥10分天朝负分？印度教经常杀绿绿、东北邦那块经常有反政府游击队袭击警察这样也是一个有血有肉的民族国家？我再看一下你的注册时间是8月3日却有61战斗力你是养一堆小号给自己加的吧这样的话你的发言就能说明很多问题了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>离谱兰斯基: </b><br>
<span>loveoniji 发表于 2019-8-20 12:39</span><br>
<span>阿三那边的强奸案往往都伴随着谋杀，并且有相当数量是斩首，他们为啥如此偏爱斩首？ ...</span><br>
<span>可能比较浪漫吧，斩首明显比掐死，捅死高级</span><br>
</p><p><b>安娜导函数: </b><br>
<span>狒狗 发表于 2019-8-20 12:01</span><br>
<span>荣誉谋杀？</span><br>
<span>看清楚新闻内容哦</span><br>
<span>看了啊 ，女儿被丈夫以外的人（她爹）强上了，难道不算失节？对付失节的女儿荣誉谋杀不是很合理</span><br>
</p><p><b>crabwar: </b><br>
<span>奶油小吉 发表于 2019-8-20 12:53</span><br>
<span>？？？？？，三哥10分天朝负分？印度教经常杀绿绿、东北邦那块经常有反政府游击队袭击警察这样也是一个有 ...</span><br>
<span>你不反斥他后半句嘛？</span><br>
</p><p><b>爱与和平的道化者: </b><br>
<span>红都剧院24排4号 发表于 2019-8-20 11:46</span><br>
<span>印度恨国党VS印度粉红吗，说话的腔调都和泥潭差不多</span><br>
<span>虽然都说了操你妈，但我们说的是革命口号，他们说的是反动口号，能一样吗？能一样吗？</span><br>
</p><p><b>奶油小吉: </b><br>
<span>crabwar 发表于 2019-8-20 12:58</span><br>
<span>你不反斥他后半句嘛？</span><br>
<span>我回的时候他还没改后面改的那段纯粹是想钓鱼。</span><br>
</p><p><b>依然荏苒: </b><br>
<span>你们这文章都是龙腾转来的么</span><br>
</p><p><b>天网: </b><br>
<span>奶油小吉 发表于 2019-8-20 12:53</span><br>
<span>？？？？？，三哥10分天朝负分？印度教经常杀绿绿、东北邦那块经常有反政府游击队袭击警察这样也是一个有 ...</span><br>
<span>我说的是渐渐捏合成，还在进行时候，但已经很有成效了</span><br>
<span>独立时还是一个地理概念，现在印度人对印度认同、爱国心、强烈的自豪心是世界前几，这你也要装瞎。为什么其他国家都是绿绿砍主体民族、而到了印度就变成绿绿被砍、不敢吭声呢。镇压强烈的地方本来就不是印度的地盘，但结果上印度就可以把它们完全吞并下来，果阿，锡金，下一个就是东北诸邦，现在黄种人早就不是主体了</span><br>
</p><p><b>传奇820: </b><br>
<span>Ullatt Subhas•Kochi•1 day ago</span><br>
<span>Don’t bring Religion into this tragedy as it is commonly happening all over the world in many families and because of shame and guilt feelings it’s never brought to the open and it’s shamefully covered up.</span><br>
<span>不要把宗教扯进这场悲剧中。这种事情，在世界各地都算普遍，只不过碍于羞耻和内疚，从来没有公开过而已，都被掩盖了。</span><br>
<span>===============</span><br>
<span>这是泥潭巨魔吧 </span><br>
</p><p><b>奶油小吉: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 奶油小吉 于 2019-8-20 13:16 编辑 </span><br>
<span>天网 发表于 2019-8-20 13:02</span><br>
<span>我说的是渐渐捏合成，还在进行时候，但已经很有成效了</span><br>
<span>独立时还是一个地理概念，现在印度人对印度认同、 ...</span><br>
<span>我也觉得中国是渐渐合成这几年在内地意识形态统一度非常高比起90年代到2008期间年高了不知多少倍，还有你觉得内地的中国人爱国心民族自豪感输给印度了？另外印度的国际环境比中国好不知多少倍印度发生的事在中国发生一遍西方早就把中国打成纳粹了虽然现在也好不了多少，那印度发生的事为什么西方会睁一只眼闭一只眼呢说穿了还不是印度对现在的西方没有威胁懒得干涉你，印度哪一天开始对西方产生威胁了我保证印度境内百花齐开比中国热闹百倍。</span><br>
</p><p><b>asakura: </b><br>
<span>在泥潭看帖感觉新北比印度牛逼多了</span><br>
</p><p><b>fn_herstal: </b><br>
<span>天网 发表于 2019-8-20 13:02</span><br>
<span>我说的是渐渐捏合成，还在进行时候，但已经很有成效了</span><br>
<span>独立时还是一个地理概念，现在印度人对印度认同、 ...</span><br>
<span>真有人发自内心觉得以牙还牙是好事的啊……</span><br>
</p><p><b>天网: </b><br>
<span>fn_herstal 发表于 2019-8-20 13:25</span><br>
<span>真有人发自内心觉得以牙还牙是好事的啊……</span><br>
<span>以牙还压 ×</span><br>
<span>社会、司法各方面不惯着、偏袒某族群 √</span><br>
</p><p><b>cdy111222: </b><br>
<span>居……居然……不是新北！</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>江户川恩维: </b><br>
<span>鬼父就算了（单纯就稀有度而言，不是说这就不是畜生行为），斩首这。。。</span><br>
</p><p><b>zanber: </b><br>
<span>cdy111222 发表于 2019-8-20 13:32</span><br>
<span>居……居然……不是新北！</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
<span>新北顶多是色孽信徒，这种四神神选只有印度才能有</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1854634[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
