<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>印度女人更偏爱白肤色的男人吗</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>印度女人更偏爱白肤色的男人吗</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 17:45:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>印度女人更偏爱白肤色的男人吗[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1858831-1-1.html</link>
      <description>印度女人更偏爱白肤色的男人吗&#13;
Do Indian women prefer fair-skinned men over dark men?印度女人更偏爱白皮肤的男人吗？以下是Quora读者的评论：AnonymousInteresting discussion. As for me, I love dark skinned men. I am a fair skinned lady and I cannot even think of being touched by a fair skinned guy. I don’t get aroused, nor stimulated. So I had two divorces - both were fair skinned guys; but their looks did not have anything to do with it. At the same time, we did not have great physical stuff. Now I am happily wed to a south indian dark man, and we are very attracted to each other. During my second divorce, I met a social scientist and a psychologist online. She told me that even in the animal kingdom, a female animal is subconsciously attracted to a dark male animal.Theoretically, it is about day and night. During day, predators don’t come out. During night they come out. Even ghosts and paranormal activity happens during night. So right from the start all creatures are frightened and intimidated by the absence of light. Therefore, the absence of “light” is also “dark”. Dark is then synonymous with danger. Therefore woman find “dark” men dangerous. And this is a turn-on for them because they also find “dark” men as “protectors” because they are dangerous and fearless.Over the years, because of evolution, the female species became the nurturer and the male species became the one who went out and fought for space, food, and social status. So the male was supposed to be “outside” the home, and the female was supposed to be “inside” the home. So someone who is constantly outside the home is under the Sun and looks dark and weathered. Someone who is constantly inside the home is lighter. Therefore “dark” men look “outdoorsy” and fair men look “indoorsy”.这个讨论有趣。对我而言，我喜欢深肤色的男人。我是一个皮肤白皙的女人，我甚至无法想象自己被一个皮肤白皙的男人碰触会是什么样。我离过两次婚，对方都是肤色较白的人；但他们的长相与此无关。我们也没有太多的身体接触。现在我幸福地嫁给了一个南印度的黑皮肤男人，我们对彼此都很有吸引力。第二次离婚时，我在网上遇到了一位社会学家和一位心理学家。她告诉我，即使在动物王国里，雌性动物也会下意识地被深色的雄性动物所吸引。从理论上讲，这跟昼夜更替有关。白天，捕食者不会出来。到了晚上，他们出来活动。就连鬼魂和超自然现象也会在夜晚发生。所以从一开始，所有的生物都因为没有光线而受到惊吓。因此，没有“光”也就意味着“黑暗”。黑暗就是危险的同义词。因此，女人觉得“黑皮肤”男人很危险。这对她们来说是一种刺激，因为她们也会发现“黑皮肤”男人是“保护者”，因为他们有威胁性，勇敢无畏。多年来，由于进化，雌性物种成为养育者，而雄性物种成为外出为空间、食物和社会地位而拼搏的人。因此，男性主外，而女性主内。所以经常在外头奔忙的人总能见阳光，看起来皮肤较黑、饱经风霜。而经常呆在家里的人肤色较白。因此，“黑皮肤”男人看起来“喜欢户外活动”，而“白皮肤”男人看起来“喜欢室内活动”。Even evolution has made “dark” men stronger than “light skinned” men. “Dark” means more melanin content in the skin, and therefore more protection from the Sun, and it could equate to better health, better bone structure, stronger muscles. An example is African men, who are “dark and strong” and hence the stereotype or subconscious belief was established.Therefore, for a woman, a “dark skinned man” is “outdoorsy”, “virile”, “energetic”, “healthy”, “strong”, “protector” and “macho”.There could be some women who do prefer fair skin men. But this is very very rarely a biological preference. Nearly “All Women Biologically Prefer Dark Males” is what science has confirmed. So when would a woman prefer a fair skinned male? These are the cases:甚至进化也让“黑皮肤”的男人比“白皮肤”的男人更强壮。“黑皮肤”意味着皮肤中含有更多的黑色素，因此可以更好地保护皮肤免受阳光的伤害，也即等同于更好的健康，更好的骨骼结构，更强壮的肌肉。举个例子，非洲男人，他们“又黑又壮”，因此就形成了这种刻板印象或潜意识里的信念。因此，对于女人来说，“黑皮肤男人”就是“喜欢户外活动”、“阳刚”、“精力充沛”、“健康”、“强壮”、“保护神”和“大男子主义”。可能有些女人更喜欢白皮肤的男人。但在生物学上，这是很少见的偏好。科学已经证实，几乎“所有女性在生理上都更喜欢黑皮肤男性”。那么，女人什么时候会更喜欢白皮肤的男人呢？以下是一些例子：1.The woman is intimidated by the virility, energy of a dark man, and she feels she could get over-possessive of him or too intense over him. It could also be that she might find dark men aggressive which might not complement her behavior, which too could be temperamental. So with such a preconceived notion, she prefers fair skinned men, who look harmless.2.The woman wants to be the “dominant” person in the relationship. She feels at a disadvantage or perceives that she cannot be the dominant one in a relationship with a dark skinned man. So she goes for a fair skinned man.3.Racial issues. Some women are hard-pressed to conserve racial lineage.1.这个女人被一个黑皮肤男人的男子气概和能量吓到，她觉得她可能会对他有过度的占有欲，或者对他太过紧张。也有可能是她发现黑皮肤的男人有攻击性，这可能与她的行为不符，因为她的行为也可能是喜怒无常的。因此，带着这样一种先入为主的观念，她会更喜欢皮肤白皙、看上去比较无害的男人。2.女人想要在这段关系中占据主导地位。她觉得自己处于劣势，或者觉得自己无法在与一个黑皮肤男人的关系中处于主导地位。因此她会转而喜欢白皮肤的男人。3.种族问题。有些妇女被迫保持种族血统。4.Lack of hormones. Some women lack the necessary hormones that makes a woman “womanly”. They could have a bit of both - lots of testosterone in addition to oestrogen. So due to a hormonal imbalance, they “think like men” and choose fair skinned males.5.Exacting revenge on other men. Some women might have been in bad relationships with either fair skinned men or dark skinned men. They might have been dumped or hurt in previous relationships. So they want to subconsciously exact revenge on their previous partners by choosing men that might “make their previous partners jealous”.6.Inexperience. Girls who have not had experiences such as intimate relationships with at least two men in their lives do not understand what they want. That is why you see young girls or young adults who are relatively inexperienced go for fair skinned men after watching movies that show fair skinned men as the heroes. But just ask “experienced” women whom they like? They have been with men, and now they understand what they want. All of them - at least 95% percent of them want a dark man.4.缺乏激素。一些女性缺乏必要的荷尔蒙，令其“充满女人味儿”。她们可能两者兼而有之—除了雌激素外，还有大量的睾丸激素。因此，由于荷尔蒙失衡，她们“像男人一样思考”，选择皮肤白皙的男性。5.对别人进行报复。有些女人可能和白皮肤的男人或黑皮肤的男人关系不好。她们可能在之前的关系中被甩过或受到过伤害。因此，她们希望通过选择可能“让前任嫉妒”的男人，在潜意识里报复前任。6.缺乏经验。在她们的生活中，如果没有与至少两个男人发生过亲密关系之类的经历，她们就不会明白自己想要什么。这就是为什么你会看到比较没有经验的年轻女孩或年轻的成年人，去追求白皮肤的男人，把白皮肤的男人视为英雄。但问问“有经验”的女性，看她们喜欢谁？她们和男人相处时间长，现在已经明白自己想要什么了。她们中所有人——至少95%的人都想找一个黑皮肤的男人。译文来源：三泰虎 http://www.santaihu.com/48565.html 译者：Joyceliu7.Accessorizing and shallowness. Women want to “show off” their men sometimes. So that their value increases in society. But internally they might not have any kind of attraction. But externally they want to show off and increase their own self worth in the society.8.Wanting fair skinned children. In sub-continent countries, most parents struggle to marry-off their “dark skinned daughters.” So a woman entering into marriage does not want a dark skinned daughter to avoid such problems in the future. So she thinks marrying a fair skinned man can give her fair skinned children. But the truth is that genetically 90% of the human population inherit the skin tone from their mothers. I have four children and all are my skin tone!7.显摆和浅薄。女人有时想要“炫耀”她们的男人。增加她们在社会中的价值。内心里，她们可能没有任何吸引力。但在外表上，她们想要在社会上炫耀和增加自我价值。8.想要皮肤白皙的孩子。在南亚次大陆国家，大多数父母都很难把自己的“黑皮肤女儿”嫁出去。因此，步入婚姻的女性不希望自己的女儿是黑皮肤，以避免将来出现这样的问题。所以她认为嫁给白皮肤的男人可以生出一个白皮肤的孩子。但事实是，90%的人都会遗传母亲的肤色。我有四个孩子，肤色都跟我一样!
&#13;
I have lived in the US for a decade, and also places such as Romania, Hungary. I have seen more lesbians and bisexual women in these countries. The numbers are more in these countries than in countries where there are darker men. This is because when a woman is compelled to be attracted to fair skin men in such countries because there are not many dark skin men around, they have to stifle their inherent biological urges to be with dark men. They have to subconsciously mould their mind to be attracted to fair skin men because of unavailability of dark skin men. So whilst doing so, they become “less of women, and more of men”. That is why it is easy for them to become lesbians, and be attracted to other women.我在美国生活了10年，也在罗马尼亚、匈牙利等地生活过。我在这些国家看到了更多的女**和双性恋女性。这些国家中，女**和双性恋女性的数字比肤色较深的国家要多。这是因为在这样的国家，当一个女人因为周围没有很多黑皮肤的男人而被迫被白皮肤的男人吸引时，她们不得不抑制自己与生俱来的与黑皮肤男人在一起的生理冲动。因为没有深色皮肤的男人，她们不得不在潜意识里把自己的思想塑造成被白皙皮肤的男人。因此，与此同时，她们变成了“越来越少不女性化，越来越男性化”。这就是为什么她们很容易成为女**，并被其他女人所吸引的原因。
&#13;
AnonymousMy dad is an Indian from Gujarat and my mom is Irish. I have lived all around the world until I came to India. Right from an early age when I was in England and then when I went to South Africa, I have been in several relationships, but the most fulfilling ones were with the men who were intelligent, creative, honest - skin color hardly mattered. One of my exes was even an African black man. The darker they are, the more I am attracted to them. I saw a post that stated that Indian women don’t like the really dark ones. Actually in my opinion, the darker they are, the more manly they look. I personally like the dark ones.In fact I think most women don’t even care about the skin color of the man. This kind of question does not make sense to a woman because a woman hardly thinks on physical lines like a man. A woman thinks emotionally, her feelings for the man is based on what he speaks, how he treats her etc.So you might say why is that all the hot women have fair and handsome men as boyfriends or husbands. I feel it is because the fair skinned men approach women more than the darker ones, especially in India. I feel dark skin men in India are down in the south and they are either too busy to be at parties or already married! But in the west, if you notice, it is the black men that approach all the white women without a moment’s hesitation! And trust me - it’s a beautiful feeling when a really nice even skinned dusky dark man with a nice smile approaches a woman!我爸爸是来自古吉拉特邦的印度人，我妈妈是爱尔兰人。在我来到印度之前，我一直在世界各地生活。我很小的时候在英国，后来去了南非，我有过几段恋情，但最令人满意的是那些聪明、有创造力、诚实的男人——肤色并不重要。我的一个前任还是非洲黑人。他们的肤色越黑，我就越容易被他们吸引。我看到一个帖子说印度女人不喜欢真正的黑皮肤。事实上，在我看来，肤色越深，越有男人味。我个人喜欢黑皮肤的男人。事实上，我认为大多数女人并不关心男人的肤色。这类问题对女人来说毫无意义，因为女人几乎不像男人用身体思考。女人用情绪思考，她对男人的感觉是基于他说过什么话，他如何对待她等等。所以你可能会说为什么所有性感的女人都能找到漂亮帅气的男人当男朋友或丈夫。我觉得这是因为白皮肤的男人比黑皮肤的男人更容易接近女人，尤其是在印度。我觉得印度的黑皮肤男人都住在南方，他们要么太忙，没时间参加派对，要么已经结婚了！但是在西方，如果你留意，就会发现是黑人男性主动地接近所有白人女性！相信我——当一个皮肤黝黑、面带微笑的男人走近一个女人时，那是一种多么美妙的感觉!
&#13;
AnonymousI personally prefer guys that are a little dark. The look of fair guys doesn't appeal to me much. The skin color doesn't matter much if the guy is well groomed and behaves nicely. I'm more attracted to people from south than from north.Now if we see popular menI find these guys hotterThan them:Girls like guys who take care of themselves and are physically attracted to them quickly. This does not mean that the guys who don't take care of themselves are looked down upon but we are not that easily attracted to them.P.S: This is my personal opinion and others opinion can differ.我个人更喜欢肤色有点黑的男生。我不太喜欢白皮肤男生的长相。如果一个男人打扮得体，举止得体，他的肤色并不重要。我更喜欢南方人而不是北方人。如果我们看看受欢迎的男人，我发现这些家伙:http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-10-10/c2604f6d6efc471b05f65a4d8871c915.jpghttp://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-10-10/61450a1aa9ed0276fbbd91d181fec241.jpg比他们更性感http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-10-10/a7a021483c538ec67b9037a655fac864.jpg女孩喜欢注重外表的男人，而且很快就会被他们的外表所吸引。这并不意味着那些不会收拾自己的男人会被人看不起，但我们并不那么容易被他们吸引。PS:这是我个人的看法，其他人的看法可能不同。
&#13;
AnonymousHonestly, I find darker shades much more hot, to the extend that I have a thing for it, sexually. My fantasies are full of them. Especially South Indian and Bengali men.This isn't directly related to the question but since you mentioned India's obsession with fair skin, I've met a lot of people who think I would choose a fair skinned guy because I am fair skinned too, some think that I "should". These are same set of people for whom marriage isn't a relationship but of love but more like give and take.说实话，我觉得深色皮肤更有吸引力，就我对它的迷恋而言，就是性感的同义词。我满脑子都是幻想。特别是南印度人和孟加拉人。这和这个问题没有直接关系，但既然你提到印度对白皮肤的痴迷，我遇到过很多认为我会选择白皮肤对象的人，因为我也是白皮肤，有些人认为我“应该”喜欢白皮肤。对这些人来说，婚姻不是一种关系，而是爱，更像是给予和索取。
&#13;
AnonymousNo.Have you ever heard of tall dark handsome? There were lots of fair skinned guys in my school and college but none attracted me. Sure, they look good but sexually I am not attracted to them.Whenever I see a confident dark handsome guy with a dashing smile, I go weak between my legs. Yes, the brown skin is precious. It is synonymous with sexiness. I am going anonymous because lots of my friends are on quora and I don't want to get trolled by them lol.Bottomline :I will only marry a brown skinned guy because I am so very attracted to them. Brown skin is sexiness y’all. I myself is brown skinned.不。你听说过高黑帅的人吗？在我的学校和大学里有很多皮肤白皙的男生，但没有一个能吸引我。当然，他们长得不错，但在性方面，我对他们不感兴趣。每当我看到一个自信、黝黑、英俊、带着潇洒微笑的小伙子时，我都忍不住两腿发软。是的，棕色的皮肤很珍贵。它是性感的同义词。我要匿名，因为我的很多朋友都会逛Quora，我不想被他们嘲笑。归根结底：我只想嫁给棕色皮肤的男人，因为我很喜欢他们。棕色皮肤很性感。我自己是棕色皮肤。
&#13;
Rohit Vaidyaboth black skin and white skin are good i will tell you why.first of all black is color of energy ,strength, power hence black men and women are energetic and strongand white color symbolises purity and peace thats why white people are seen as good and sweetso both are goodthare is no superior and inferior in this its just diffrent qualities黑皮肤和白皮肤都很好，我来告诉你为什么。首先，黑色是象征能量、力量、权力的颜色，因此黑人男性和女性都精力充沛、十分强壮。白色象征着纯洁和和平，这就是为什么白皮肤的人会被视为善良、甜美。所以两者都很不错。在这方面并无优劣之分，只是特征不同而已。
&#13;
Anonymousindian girl here, most girls I know have a strong preference for fair skin.Most don’t admit it openly but they definitely do have a strong preference.When it comes for marriage most indian women I know don’t take looks as criteria, because that’s not what creates a healthy relationship .But when it comes to dating and one night stands you go for your instincts.For example I know a girl from a liberal hindu family who went after a Kashmiri muslim guy.The guy was an islammist, he even said on many occasions that women who don’t cover up are asking for it.But still he was very attractive fair skin light brown eyesmy friend immediately fell for him.She eventually converted to islam at marriage.这里的印度女孩，我认识的大多数女孩都非常喜欢白皙的皮肤。大多数人不会公开承认，但她们确实有强烈的偏好。说到婚姻，我认识的大多数印度女性都不以长相为标准，因为长相并不能带来健康的关系。例如，我认识一个来自自由派印度家庭的女孩，她追求一个克什米尔男子。这名男子是一名岛民。但他仍然很有吸引力，白皙的皮肤，浅棕色的眼睛，我的朋友立刻爱上了他。她最终在结婚时皈依了伊斯兰教。
&#13;
RoarflinguyIndian women prefer fair skinned men. It is just a preference like how Indian men prefer fair skinned women over dark ones. You shouldn't be whining about that because you are dark and want a fair skin girl. U don't prefer dark skinned woman.(you may reply "no, I like dark skinned women more blah blah blah"). If you don't want dark skinned woman why should women want dark skinned guy like you......it is all tit for ta印度女人更喜欢白皮肤男人。这只是一种偏好，就像印度男人更喜欢白皮肤的女人一样。你不应该抱怨，因为你是黑皮肤，想找白皮肤的女孩。你不想选黑皮肤的女人。(你可以回答“不，我更喜欢黑皮肤的女人等等等等”)。如果你不想要黑皮肤的女人，为什么女人要选择像你这样的黑皮肤男人。
&#13;
Cath QueenI absolutely love semi dark skin tone on men. Especially those who mixed race ( half Brits and African cause they look hot as f and the accent kills me) and exotic features (like green, hazel or blue eyes and jaws). Tall and average muscles are fine with me. But the man should cook cause there's nothing as delicious as a half naked man cooking with an apron on him.我绝对喜欢男人的半黑肤色。尤其是那些混血儿(一半英国人，一半非洲人，因为他们看起来太性感了，而且他们的口音秒杀了我)和具有异国情调的外貌特征(如绿色，淡褐色或蓝色眼睛和下巴)。个头高，肌肉普通的男人对我来说也可以。但是男人应该做饭，因为没有什么比半裸的男人系着围裙做饭更秀色可餐的了。
&#13;
Nakul Singh, Area Manager (2018-present)No thats not the case first of all majority of i dian men are dusky not dark some are dark some are fair okay . my best friend is dark good looking guy he never faced difficulty attracting women some features are essential for guys attractivness they are不，不是这样的，首先，大多数的印度男人皮肤较暗，不是黑皮肤，有些人是黑皮肤，有些人是白皮肤。我最好的朋友是黑色好看的家伙，他从来没有遇到过困难，吸引女人的一些特征是必不可少的，对男人的吸引力，他们是1 Long height 6 feet best height if you have you wont find difficulty attracting women2 Jawline3 Muscular build4 Status5 Money6 Thick hairs on head7 Clean skin8 Good maxillar bones9 small eyes with canthal tilt10 Large robust skull11 compact midface12 Strong brow ridges13 See europeon white men are preferred not because of pale skin colour but because of their facial bone structure and long height with light eyes many white men are tanned also who looks very good14 High cheekbones15 Low bodyfat .1最佳身高6英尺，如果你有这个身高，你会发现吸引女人并不难2下颌线3肌肉4身份5钱6头发浓密7肌肤干净8上颌骨好看9 丹凤眼10强健的头骨11紧凑的五官12突出的眉骨13欧洲白人男性更受欢迎，不是因为他们的肤色苍白，而是因为他们的面部骨骼结构好，个头高，眼睛明亮14颧骨高15体脂低。I am fairskinned with blue eyes i didn’t get any favours from society nor girls give me any extra attention so its just a misconception okay good looking man can be of any skin he should be masculine. I only got relationship with teo girls in college and i made the move but my friend a dusky complexioned a kind of tanned with light eyes git proposals from girls okay so shed this fear out of your mind yaa. See i am telling truth that fair skin guys has no edge over dusky guys i am fair skinned you can see in my dP and with blue eyes .And remember There is a saying Tall , Dark handsome not tall fair and handsome thats the bullshit brand promoted by bollywood but yes fairness matters in girlsPersonal Views based on my experience我白皮肤，蓝眼睛，我没有得到任何青睐，也没有女孩给我额外的关注，所以这只是一个误解，好的，长得漂亮的男人什么肤色都行，但要有男人味儿。我只在大学里和女生谈过恋爱，但是我一个朋友，肤色黝黑，浅色眼睛，被女孩主动求婚了，好吧，把你心里的恐惧赶走吧。你看，我说的是实话，白皮肤的人跟黑皮肤的人相比，并没有优势。记住，有句话是这么说的，高黑帅，而非高白帅，这是宝莱坞宣扬的屁话，但是对女孩来说，基于我的个人经验，肤色白皙还是挺重要的。</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>狒狗: </b><br>
<span>印度女人更偏爱白肤色的男人吗</span><br>
<span>Do Indian women prefer fair-skinned men over dark men?印度女人更偏爱白皮肤的男人吗？以下是Quora读者的评论：AnonymousInteresting discussion. As for me, I love dark skinned men. I am a fair skinned lady and I cannot even think of being touched by a fair skinned guy. I don’t get aroused, nor stimulated. So I had two divorces - both were fair skinned guys; but their looks did not have anything to do with it. At the same time, we did not have great physical stuff. Now I am happily wed to a south indian dark man, and we are very attracted to each other. During my second divorce, I met a social scientist and a psychologist online. She told me that even in the animal kingdom, a female animal is subconsciously attracted to a dark male animal.Theoretically, it is about day and night. During day, predators don’t come out. During night they come out. Even ghosts and paranormal activity happens during night. So right from the start all creatures are frightened and intimidated by the absence of light. Therefore, the absence of “light” is also “dark”. Dark is then synonymous with danger. Therefore woman find “dark” men dangerous. And this is a turn-on for them because they also find “dark” men as “protectors” because they are dangerous and fearless.Over the years, because of evolution, the female species became the nurturer and the male species became the one who went out and fought for space, food, and social status. So the male was supposed to be “outside” the home, and the female was supposed to be “inside” the home. So someone who is constantly outside the home is under the Sun and looks dark and weathered. Someone who is constantly inside the home is lighter. Therefore “dark” men look “outdoorsy” and fair men look “indoorsy”.这个讨论有趣。对我而言，我喜欢深肤色的男人。我是一个皮肤白皙的女人，我甚至无法想象自己被一个皮肤白皙的男人碰触会是什么样。我离过两次婚，对方都是肤色较白的人；但他们的长相与此无关。我们也没有太多的身体接触。现在我幸福地嫁给了一个南印度的黑皮肤男人，我们对彼此都很有吸引力。第二次离婚时，我在网上遇到了一位社会学家和一位心理学家。她告诉我，即使在动物王国里，雌性动物也会下意识地被深色的雄性动物所吸引。从理论上讲，这跟昼夜更替有关。白天，捕食者不会出来。到了晚上，他们出来活动。就连鬼魂和超自然现象也会在夜晚发生。所以从一开始，所有的生物都因为没有光线而受到惊吓。因此，没有“光”也就意味着“黑暗”。黑暗就是危险的同义词。因此，女人觉得“黑皮肤”男人很危险。这对她们来说是一种刺激，因为她们也会发现“黑皮肤”男人是“保护者”，因为他们有威胁性，勇敢无畏。多年来，由于进化，雌性物种成为养育者，而雄性物种成为外出为空间、食物和社会地位而拼搏的人。因此，男性主外，而女性主内。所以经常在外头奔忙的人总能见阳光，看起来皮肤较黑、饱经风霜。而经常呆在家里的人肤色较白。因此，“黑皮肤”男人看起来“喜欢户外活动”，而“白皮肤”男人看起来“喜欢室内活动”。Even evolution has made “dark” men stronger than “light skinned” men. “Dark” means more melanin content in the skin, and therefore more protection from the Sun, and it could equate to better health, better bone structure, stronger muscles. An example is African men, who are “dark and strong” and hence the stereotype or subconscious belief was established.Therefore, for a woman, a “dark skinned man” is “outdoorsy”, “virile”, “energetic”, “healthy”, “strong”, “protector” and “macho”.There could be some women who do prefer fair skin men. But this is very very rarely a biological preference. Nearly “All Women Biologically Prefer Dark Males” is what science has confirmed. So when would a woman prefer a fair skinned male? These are the cases:甚至进化也让“黑皮肤”的男人比“白皮肤”的男人更强壮。“黑皮肤”意味着皮肤中含有更多的黑色素，因此可以更好地保护皮肤免受阳光的伤害，也即等同于更好的健康，更好的骨骼结构，更强壮的肌肉。举个例子，非洲男人，他们“又黑又壮”，因此就形成了这种刻板印象或潜意识里的信念。因此，对于女人来说，“黑皮肤男人”就是“喜欢户外活动”、“阳刚”、“精力充沛”、“健康”、“强壮”、“保护神”和“大男子主义”。可能有些女人更喜欢白皮肤的男人。但在生物学上，这是很少见的偏好。科学已经证实，几乎“所有女性在生理上都更喜欢黑皮肤男性”。那么，女人什么时候会更喜欢白皮肤的男人呢？以下是一些例子：1.The woman is intimidated by the virility, energy of a dark man, and she feels she could get over-possessive of him or too intense over him. It could also be that she might find dark men aggressive which might not complement her behavior, which too could be temperamental. So with such a preconceived notion, she prefers fair skinned men, who look harmless.2.The woman wants to be the “dominant” person in the relationship. She feels at a disadvantage or perceives that she cannot be the dominant one in a relationship with a dark skinned man. So she goes for a fair skinned man.3.Racial issues. Some women are hard-pressed to conserve racial lineage.1.这个女人被一个黑皮肤男人的男子气概和能量吓到，她觉得她可能会对他有过度的占有欲，或者对他太过紧张。也有可能是她发现黑皮肤的男人有攻击性，这可能与她的行为不符，因为她的行为也可能是喜怒无常的。因此，带着这样一种先入为主的观念，她会更喜欢皮肤白皙、看上去比较无害的男人。2.女人想要在这段关系中占据主导地位。她觉得自己处于劣势，或者觉得自己无法在与一个黑皮肤男人的关系中处于主导地位。因此她会转而喜欢白皮肤的男人。3.种族问题。有些妇女被迫保持种族血统。4.Lack of hormones. Some women lack the necessary hormones that makes a woman “womanly”. They could have a bit of both - lots of testosterone in addition to oestrogen. So due to a hormonal imbalance, they “think like men” and choose fair skinned males.5.Exacting revenge on other men. Some women might have been in bad relationships with either fair skinned men or dark skinned men. They might have been dumped or hurt in previous relationships. So they want to subconsciously exact revenge on their previous partners by choosing men that might “make their previous partners jealous”.6.Inexperience. Girls who have not had experiences such as intimate relationships with at least two men in their lives do not understand what they want. That is why you see young girls or young adults who are relatively inexperienced go for fair skinned men after watching movies that show fair skinned men as the heroes. But just ask “experienced” women whom they like? They have been with men, and now they understand what they want. All of them - at least 95% percent of them want a dark man.4.缺乏激素。一些女性缺乏必要的荷尔蒙，令其“充满女人味儿”。她们可能两者兼而有之—除了雌激素外，还有大量的睾丸激素。因此，由于荷尔蒙失衡，她们“像男人一样思考”，选择皮肤白皙的男性。5.对别人进行报复。有些女人可能和白皮肤的男人或黑皮肤的男人关系不好。她们可能在之前的关系中被甩过或受到过伤害。因此，她们希望通过选择可能“让前任嫉妒”的男人，在潜意识里报复前任。6.缺乏经验。在她们的生活中，如果没有与至少两个男人发生过亲密关系之类的经历，她们就不会明白自己想要什么。这就是为什么你会看到比较没有经验的年轻女孩或年轻的成年人，去追求白皮肤的男人，把白皮肤的男人视为英雄。但问问“有经验”的女性，看她们喜欢谁？她们和男人相处时间长，现在已经明白自己想要什么了。她们中所有人——至少95%的人都想找一个黑皮肤的男人。译文来源：三泰虎 http://www.santaihu.com/48565.html 译者：Joyceliu7.Accessorizing and shallowness. Women want to “show off” their men sometimes. So that their value increases in society. But internally they might not have any kind of attraction. But externally they want to show off and increase their own self worth in the society.8.Wanting fair skinned children. In sub-continent countries, most parents struggle to marry-off their “dark skinned daughters.” So a woman entering into marriage does not want a dark skinned daughter to avoid such problems in the future. So she thinks marrying a fair skinned man can give her fair skinned children. But the truth is that genetically 90% of the human population inherit the skin tone from their mothers. I have four children and all are my skin tone!7.显摆和浅薄。女人有时想要“炫耀”她们的男人。增加她们在社会中的价值。内心里，她们可能没有任何吸引力。但在外表上，她们想要在社会上炫耀和增加自我价值。8.想要皮肤白皙的孩子。在南亚次大陆国家，大多数父母都很难把自己的“黑皮肤女儿”嫁出去。因此，步入婚姻的女性不希望自己的女儿是黑皮肤，以避免将来出现这样的问题。所以她认为嫁给白皮肤的男人可以生出一个白皮肤的孩子。但事实是，90%的人都会遗传母亲的肤色。我有四个孩子，肤色都跟我一样!</span><br>
<span>I have lived in the US for a decade, and also places such as Romania, Hungary. I have seen more lesbians and bisexual women in these countries. The numbers are more in these countries than in countries where there are darker men. This is because when a woman is compelled to be attracted to fair skin men in such countries because there are not many dark skin men around, they have to stifle their inherent biological urges to be with dark men. They have to subconsciously mould their mind to be attracted to fair skin men because of unavailability of dark skin men. So whilst doing so, they become “less of women, and more of men”. That is why it is easy for them to become lesbians, and be attracted to other women.我在美国生活了10年，也在罗马尼亚、匈牙利等地生活过。我在这些国家看到了更多的女**和双性恋女性。这些国家中，女**和双性恋女性的数字比肤色较深的国家要多。这是因为在这样的国家，当一个女人因为周围没有很多黑皮肤的男人而被迫被白皮肤的男人吸引时，她们不得不抑制自己与生俱来的与黑皮肤男人在一起的生理冲动。因为没有深色皮肤的男人，她们不得不在潜意识里把自己的思想塑造成被白皙皮肤的男人。因此，与此同时，她们变成了“越来越少不女性化，越来越男性化”。这就是为什么她们很容易成为女**，并被其他女人所吸引的原因。</span><br>
<span>AnonymousMy dad is an Indian from Gujarat and my mom is Irish. I have lived all around the world until I came to India. Right from an early age when I was in England and then when I went to South Africa, I have been in several relationships, but the most fulfilling ones were with the men who were intelligent, creative, honest - skin color hardly mattered. One of my exes was even an African black man. The darker they are, the more I am attracted to them. I saw a post that stated that Indian women don’t like the really dark ones. Actually in my opinion, the darker they are, the more manly they look. I personally like the dark ones.In fact I think most women don’t even care about the skin color of the man. This kind of question does not make sense to a woman because a woman hardly thinks on physical lines like a man. A woman thinks emotionally, her feelings for the man is based on what he speaks, how he treats her etc.So you might say why is that all the hot women have fair and handsome men as boyfriends or husbands. I feel it is because the fair skinned men approach women more than the darker ones, especially in India. I feel dark skin men in India are down in the south and they are either too busy to be at parties or already married! But in the west, if you notice, it is the black men that approach all the white women without a moment’s hesitation! And trust me - it’s a beautiful feeling when a really nice even skinned dusky dark man with a nice smile approaches a woman!我爸爸是来自古吉拉特邦的印度人，我妈妈是爱尔兰人。在我来到印度之前，我一直在世界各地生活。我很小的时候在英国，后来去了南非，我有过几段恋情，但最令人满意的是那些聪明、有创造力、诚实的男人——肤色并不重要。我的一个前任还是非洲黑人。他们的肤色越黑，我就越容易被他们吸引。我看到一个帖子说印度女人不喜欢真正的黑皮肤。事实上，在我看来，肤色越深，越有男人味。我个人喜欢黑皮肤的男人。事实上，我认为大多数女人并不关心男人的肤色。这类问题对女人来说毫无意义，因为女人几乎不像男人用身体思考。女人用情绪思考，她对男人的感觉是基于他说过什么话，他如何对待她等等。所以你可能会说为什么所有性感的女人都能找到漂亮帅气的男人当男朋友或丈夫。我觉得这是因为白皮肤的男人比黑皮肤的男人更容易接近女人，尤其是在印度。我觉得印度的黑皮肤男人都住在南方，他们要么太忙，没时间参加派对，要么已经结婚了！但是在西方，如果你留意，就会发现是黑人男性主动地接近所有白人女性！相信我——当一个皮肤黝黑、面带微笑的男人走近一个女人时，那是一种多么美妙的感觉!</span><br>
<span>AnonymousI personally prefer guys that are a little dark. The look of fair guys doesn't appeal to me much. The skin color doesn't matter much if the guy is well groomed and behaves nicely. I'm more attracted to people from south than from north.Now if we see popular menI find these guys hotterThan them:Girls like guys who take care of themselves and are physically attracted to them quickly. This does not mean that the guys who don't take care of themselves are looked down upon but we are not that easily attracted to them.P.S: This is my personal opinion and others opinion can differ.我个人更喜欢肤色有点黑的男生。我不太喜欢白皮肤男生的长相。如果一个男人打扮得体，举止得体，他的肤色并不重要。我更喜欢南方人而不是北方人。如果我们看看受欢迎的男人，我发现这些家伙:http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-10-10/c2604f6d6efc471b05f65a4d8871c915.jpghttp://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-10-10/61450a1aa9ed0276fbbd91d181fec241.jpg比他们更性感http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-10-10/a7a021483c538ec67b9037a655fac864.jpg女孩喜欢注重外表的男人，而且很快就会被他们的外表所吸引。这并不意味着那些不会收拾自己的男人会被人看不起，但我们并不那么容易被他们吸引。PS:这是我个人的看法，其他人的看法可能不同。</span><br>
<span>AnonymousHonestly, I find darker shades much more hot, to the extend that I have a thing for it, sexually. My fantasies are full of them. Especially South Indian and Bengali men.This isn't directly related to the question but since you mentioned India's obsession with fair skin, I've met a lot of people who think I would choose a fair skinned guy because I am fair skinned too, some think that I "should". These are same set of people for whom marriage isn't a relationship but of love but more like give and take.说实话，我觉得深色皮肤更有吸引力，就我对它的迷恋而言，就是性感的同义词。我满脑子都是幻想。特别是南印度人和孟加拉人。这和这个问题没有直接关系，但既然你提到印度对白皮肤的痴迷，我遇到过很多认为我会选择白皮肤对象的人，因为我也是白皮肤，有些人认为我“应该”喜欢白皮肤。对这些人来说，婚姻不是一种关系，而是爱，更像是给予和索取。</span><br>
<span>AnonymousNo.Have you ever heard of tall dark handsome? There were lots of fair skinned guys in my school and college but none attracted me. Sure, they look good but sexually I am not attracted to them.Whenever I see a confident dark handsome guy with a dashing smile, I go weak between my legs. Yes, the brown skin is precious. It is synonymous with sexiness. I am going anonymous because lots of my friends are on quora and I don't want to get trolled by them lol.Bottomline :I will only marry a brown skinned guy because I am so very attracted to them. Brown skin is sexiness y’all. I myself is brown skinned.不。你听说过高黑帅的人吗？在我的学校和大学里有很多皮肤白皙的男生，但没有一个能吸引我。当然，他们长得不错，但在性方面，我对他们不感兴趣。每当我看到一个自信、黝黑、英俊、带着潇洒微笑的小伙子时，我都忍不住两腿发软。是的，棕色的皮肤很珍贵。它是性感的同义词。我要匿名，因为我的很多朋友都会逛Quora，我不想被他们嘲笑。归根结底：我只想嫁给棕色皮肤的男人，因为我很喜欢他们。棕色皮肤很性感。我自己是棕色皮肤。</span><br>
<span>Rohit Vaidyaboth black skin and white skin are good i will tell you why.first of all black is color of energy ,strength, power hence black men and women are energetic and strongand white color symbolises purity and peace thats why white people are seen as good and sweetso both are goodthare is no superior and inferior in this its just diffrent qualities黑皮肤和白皮肤都很好，我来告诉你为什么。首先，黑色是象征能量、力量、权力的颜色，因此黑人男性和女性都精力充沛、十分强壮。白色象征着纯洁和和平，这就是为什么白皮肤的人会被视为善良、甜美。所以两者都很不错。在这方面并无优劣之分，只是特征不同而已。</span><br>
<span>Anonymousindian girl here, most girls I know have a strong preference for fair skin.Most don’t admit it openly but they definitely do have a strong preference.When it comes for marriage most indian women I know don’t take looks as criteria, because that’s not what creates a healthy relationship .But when it comes to dating and one night stands you go for your instincts.For example I know a girl from a liberal hindu family who went after a Kashmiri muslim guy.The guy was an islammist, he even said on many occasions that women who don’t cover up are asking for it.But still he was very attractive fair skin light brown eyesmy friend immediately fell for him.She eventually converted to islam at marriage.这里的印度女孩，我认识的大多数女孩都非常喜欢白皙的皮肤。大多数人不会公开承认，但她们确实有强烈的偏好。说到婚姻，我认识的大多数印度女性都不以长相为标准，因为长相并不能带来健康的关系。例如，我认识一个来自自由派印度家庭的女孩，她追求一个克什米尔男子。这名男子是一名岛民。但他仍然很有吸引力，白皙的皮肤，浅棕色的眼睛，我的朋友立刻爱上了他。她最终在结婚时皈依了伊斯兰教。</span><br>
<span>RoarflinguyIndian women prefer fair skinned men. It is just a preference like how Indian men prefer fair skinned women over dark ones. You shouldn't be whining about that because you are dark and want a fair skin girl. U don't prefer dark skinned woman.(you may reply "no, I like dark skinned women more blah blah blah"). If you don't want dark skinned woman why should women want dark skinned guy like you......it is all tit for ta印度女人更喜欢白皮肤男人。这只是一种偏好，就像印度男人更喜欢白皮肤的女人一样。你不应该抱怨，因为你是黑皮肤，想找白皮肤的女孩。你不想选黑皮肤的女人。(你可以回答“不，我更喜欢黑皮肤的女人等等等等”)。如果你不想要黑皮肤的女人，为什么女人要选择像你这样的黑皮肤男人。</span><br>
<span>Cath QueenI absolutely love semi dark skin tone on men. Especially those who mixed race ( half Brits and African cause they look hot as f and the accent kills me) and exotic features (like green, hazel or blue eyes and jaws). Tall and average muscles are fine with me. But the man should cook cause there's nothing as delicious as a half naked man cooking with an apron on him.我绝对喜欢男人的半黑肤色。尤其是那些混血儿(一半英国人，一半非洲人，因为他们看起来太性感了，而且他们的口音秒杀了我)和具有异国情调的外貌特征(如绿色，淡褐色或蓝色眼睛和下巴)。个头高，肌肉普通的男人对我来说也可以。但是男人应该做饭，因为没有什么比半裸的男人系着围裙做饭更秀色可餐的了。</span><br>
<span>Nakul Singh, Area Manager (2018-present)No thats not the case first of all majority of i dian men are dusky not dark some are dark some are fair okay . my best friend is dark good looking guy he never faced difficulty attracting women some features are essential for guys attractivness they are不，不是这样的，首先，大多数的印度男人皮肤较暗，不是黑皮肤，有些人是黑皮肤，有些人是白皮肤。我最好的朋友是黑色好看的家伙，他从来没有遇到过困难，吸引女人的一些特征是必不可少的，对男人的吸引力，他们是1 Long height 6 feet best height if you have you wont find difficulty attracting women2 Jawline3 Muscular build4 Status5 Money6 Thick hairs on head7 Clean skin8 Good maxillar bones9 small eyes with canthal tilt10 Large robust skull11 compact midface12 Strong brow ridges13 See europeon white men are preferred not because of pale skin colour but because of their facial bone structure and long height with light eyes many white men are tanned also who looks very good14 High cheekbones15 Low bodyfat .1最佳身高6英尺，如果你有这个身高，你会发现吸引女人并不难2下颌线3肌肉4身份5钱6头发浓密7肌肤干净8上颌骨好看9 丹凤眼10强健的头骨11紧凑的五官12突出的眉骨13欧洲白人男性更受欢迎，不是因为他们的肤色苍白，而是因为他们的面部骨骼结构好，个头高，眼睛明亮14颧骨高15体脂低。I am fairskinned with blue eyes i didn’t get any favours from society nor girls give me any extra attention so its just a misconception okay good looking man can be of any skin he should be masculine. I only got relationship with teo girls in college and i made the move but my friend a dusky complexioned a kind of tanned with light eyes git proposals from girls okay so shed this fear out of your mind yaa. See i am telling truth that fair skin guys has no edge over dusky guys i am fair skinned you can see in my dP and with blue eyes .And remember There is a saying Tall , Dark handsome not tall fair and handsome thats the bullshit brand promoted by bollywood but yes fairness matters in girlsPersonal Views based on my experience我白皮肤，蓝眼睛，我没有得到任何青睐，也没有女孩给我额外的关注，所以这只是一个误解，好的，长得漂亮的男人什么肤色都行，但要有男人味儿。我只在大学里和女生谈过恋爱，但是我一个朋友，肤色黝黑，浅色眼睛，被女孩主动求婚了，好吧，把你心里的恐惧赶走吧。你看，我说的是实话，白皮肤的人跟黑皮肤的人相比，并没有优势。记住，有句话是这么说的，高黑帅，而非高白帅，这是宝莱坞宣扬的屁话，但是对女孩来说，基于我的个人经验，肤色白皙还是挺重要的。</span><br>
</p><p><b>0330: </b><br>
<span>是你，真正的肥狗！咖喱味！</span><br>
</p><p><b>狒狗: </b><br>
<span>0330 发表于 2019-10-10 20:40</span><br>
<span>是你，真正的肥狗！咖喱味！</span><br>
</p><p><b>无攻不受鹿: </b><br>
<span>古天乐有话说</span><br>
</p><p><b>muzimuzhen: </b><br>
<span>不够咖喱，越白就约接近婆罗门，咖喱女自然越喜欢。</span><br>
<span>不过班里有个磨砂黑的印度妹很漂亮，但是没有人去追她，估计是太黑了。</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1858831[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
