<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>【翻译】有多少美国人每日生活水平在2刀以下？</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>【翻译】有多少美国人每日生活水平在2刀以下？</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 19:36:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>【翻译】有多少美国人每日生活水平在2刀以下？[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1841255-1-1.html</link>
      <description>【翻译】有多少美国人每日生活水平在2刀以下？&#13;
How many Americans live on $2 a day?
&#13;
有多少美国人每日生活水平在2刀以下？
&#13;
Far fewer than previously thought, according to new research
&#13;
一项新的调查显示，贫困人口比例较先前大幅下降
&#13;
AS AMERICA’S economy continues its recovery from the Great Recession, the official poverty rate has fallen—from 15.9% of the population to 13.4% in 2017. This is still a couple of percentage points higher than it was a decade ago. But in another hopeful sign, new measures of extreme poverty—defined as living on $2 a day or less—suggest it is much lower than previously thought. This is inconvenient for those on both the left and the right. It suggests that the welfare reform of the 1990s did not, as previously believed, much increase extreme poverty and that America’s safety net works better than is often argued. It also suggests arguments that poverty at home is as bad as poverty elsewhere in the world are overblown.
&#13;
美国的经济在大衰退（指08年金融危机）后持续恢复，美国官方给出的贫困率也在下降——从2017年人口的15.9%下降到目前的13.4%。这个比率仍比十年前高出几个百分点。但从另一个角度来说，今天以新的标准（每日生活水平在两刀及以下）来界定极端贫困时，贫困率仍比之前所设想的要少。美国左右两派都对这个数据感到尴尬。这个数据表明90年代的福利制度改革不像以前人们所相信的那样，极大增加了贫困人口的数量，同时也表明美国的社会安全网要比人们通常认为的要更有效。这个数据还显示出美国的贫困率和世界其他地区的贫困率一样糟糕是一种被夸大的论调。
&#13;
Previous estimates of extreme poverty have suggested it was concentrated amongst single parent families. These households bore the brunt of a major bipartisan reform in 1996, which made welfare payments conditional on recipients trying to find work and ruled that no one could receive them for more than five years. According to Kathryn Edin and Luke Schaefer, sociologists, survey evidence suggests the number of households with children living on less than $2 cash per person per day climbed from 600,000 in 1997 to more than 1.4m in 2010. Even including the Supplemental Nutritional Assistance Programme, once known as food stamps, which was designed to ensure that poor American families have enough to eat, the numbers appeared to have increased from below half a million in 1996 to 800,000 in 2010.
&#13;
先前对极端贫困状况的估计认为极端贫困多发于单亲家庭中。这些家庭在96年的两党改革中首当其冲，因为改革要求这些家庭必须找到工作才能领取社会福利，而且不许任何资方雇佣他们超过五年。Kathryn Edin和Luke Schaefer两位社会学家的研究表明，每人每天生活水平低于2刀的家庭从1997年的60万上升到2010年的140多万。即使考虑到营养补充援助计划（SNAP，也称食物券计划）的帮助，本应得到足够食物的贫困美国家庭，其数量仍在1996年到2010年间从不足50万上升到80万。
&#13;
The $2 poverty line is broadly comparable to the World Bank’s global $1.90 “extreme poverty line.” It is a fraction of the official, income-based, poverty line in America, which is set at $21,330 for a family of three—or about $19 a day. Those earlier estimates of extreme poverty, suggestive of widespread destitution, prompted Angus Deaton, a Nobel prize-winning economist, to propose redirecting US foreign aid to America’s poorest people.
&#13;
2刀的贫困线与世界银行的1.9刀“极端贫困线”大致相当。不过这个数据只是美国官方认定的，基于收入的贫困线的一小部分，基于收入的贫困线要求三口之家年收入低于21330刀，或者说，每天19刀。先前对极端贫困率的估计暗示了美国存在普遍的贫困问题，让诺贝尔经济学奖得主Angus Deaton倡议美国政府将外援重新导向到美国最贫困的人群里。
&#13;
The new poverty estimates, by Carla Medalia from the Census Bureau and Bruce Meyer from the University of Chicago, tell a rather different story. They combine data from surveys and from government agencies. That helps overcome two problems from estimates that use survey data alone: respondents often under-report the benefits they get and sometimes they mis-report other income.
&#13;
新的贫困估测数据来自美国人口调查局的Carla Medalia和来自芝加哥大学的Bruce Meyer，他们给出了不一样的视角，两人将来自调查和政府机构的数据合并，克服了估测中单独使用某方数据时可能出现的两个问题：受访者通常低估他们的救济金，有时也会误报其他收入。
&#13;
Looking at all individuals’ survey-reported household income, about 2.6% report living on less than $2 a day. But when other benefits, under-reported earnings and other assets are factored in, that falls to 0.57%. Add in data from programme administrators on under-reported transfers including the earned income tax credit, social security payments, housing assistance and the Supplemental Nutritional Assistance Programme and the proportion falls to 0.11% percent, or around 336,000 people.
&#13;
从所有独立的调查报告来看，大概有2.6%的受访者每日生活水平在2刀以下。但考虑到其他救济金，瞒报的收入和其余因素时，这个比率降到了0.57%。再加上从计划管理方获得的瞒报数据，包括税收减免，社会保障金，住房援助计划和营养援助计划后，这一比例再降至0.11%，也就是说约有33万6千人生活在贫困线以下。
&#13;
The adjustments also suggest extreme poverty isn’t concentrated among families. On a survey-reported basis that excludes in-kind payments households with children make up the considerable majority of the extreme poor. But once the adjustments are made, poverty is almost exclusively concentrated amongst single, childless households.
&#13;
这项调整也表明极端贫困并不以家庭为中心分布。以调查报告为基础时，除了有实物支付（即派发）的，那些有孩子的家庭占据了极端贫困占大多数。但进行上述的调整后，贫困几乎完全集中于单身无子的家庭中。
&#13;
While the additional data sources certainly make the numbers more reliable, the analysis, as with previous estimates, excludes the homeless—half a million or more Americans. And some of the assumptions regarding data adjustments are arguable—including that benefits are worth the same as cash, that hours worked will necessarily pay at least the minimum wage and that households with considerable asset wealth will not be income-poor. On the other hand, the results exclude administrative data on some big transfer programmes including unemployment insurance, veteran’s benefits and worker’s compensation, which collectively spend over $200bn a year.
&#13;
虽然额外的材料确实能使这些数字更可靠，但和之前的估测一样，无家可归的美国人被排除在统计之外——大概有50万以上的美国人。而且关于数据调整所做的一些假设仍有争议，如简单地把救济金与现金等同，假设小时工必然能领到等价的最低工资，假设拥有一定资产的家庭不会在收入上贫困。另一方面，这个结果也未包括一些大型的政府财政转移计划，如失业保险，退伍军人福利和工人赔偿金，这些计划每年共花费超过2000亿美元。
&#13;
The new evidence is important for two reasons. First, it suggests that extreme poverty cannot have risen significantly after welfare reform. The numbers living on $2 a day remain low and are not amongst those targeted by the reform measures. Second, the big gap between market income and consumption spending thrown up by the new research suggests that safety net programmes are doing their job of keeping people from utter destitution.
&#13;
有两个原因使新的数据更重要。首先，它表明极端贫困不可能在福利改革后明显上升。每日生活水平在2刀以下的家庭数量保持较低水平并不是改革的目标。其次，新研究所展示的市场收入与消费支出间的巨大差距表明，社会安全网正在尽其所能，避免人们陷入到贫困的境地中。
&#13;
The overall impact of welfare reform continues to be debated. Research by Hilary Hoynes and Diane Schanzenbach, economists, suggests safety-net spending on families with incomes below the official poverty line has fallen from 87% of the total in 1990 to 56% in 2015, while per-child spending on families without earnings has declined since 1990. And even if the number of Americans living on $2 a day is in the thousands, rather than over 1m, it is still too high.
&#13;
福利改革的总体后果直到今天还在争论不休。由两位经济学家，Hilary Hoynes和Diane Schanzenbach所做的研究表明，社会安全网在低于官方贫困线的家庭中总花费比例从1990年的87%下降到2015年的56%，但无收入家庭对每个孩子的支出从1990年就一直在下降。就算美国每日生活条件在两刀以下的人口只有几十万，不到一百万，这个值还是太高了。
&#13;
原文链接：https://www.economist.com/democr ... ans-live-on-2-a-day</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>chenpony: </b><br>
<span>【翻译】有多少美国人每日生活水平在2刀以下？</span><br>
<span>How many Americans live on $2 a day?</span><br>
<span>有多少美国人每日生活水平在2刀以下？</span><br>
<span>Far fewer than previously thought, according to new research</span><br>
<span>一项新的调查显示，贫困人口比例较先前大幅下降</span><br>
<span>AS AMERICA’S economy continues its recovery from the Great Recession, the official poverty rate has fallen—from 15.9% of the population to 13.4% in 2017. This is still a couple of percentage points higher than it was a decade ago. But in another hopeful sign, new measures of extreme poverty—defined as living on $2 a day or less—suggest it is much lower than previously thought. This is inconvenient for those on both the left and the right. It suggests that the welfare reform of the 1990s did not, as previously believed, much increase extreme poverty and that America’s safety net works better than is often argued. It also suggests arguments that poverty at home is as bad as poverty elsewhere in the world are overblown.</span><br>
<span>美国的经济在大衰退（指08年金融危机）后持续恢复，美国官方给出的贫困率也在下降——从2017年人口的15.9%下降到目前的13.4%。这个比率仍比十年前高出几个百分点。但从另一个角度来说，今天以新的标准（每日生活水平在两刀及以下）来界定极端贫困时，贫困率仍比之前所设想的要少。美国左右两派都对这个数据感到尴尬。这个数据表明90年代的福利制度改革不像以前人们所相信的那样，极大增加了贫困人口的数量，同时也表明美国的社会安全网要比人们通常认为的要更有效。这个数据还显示出美国的贫困率和世界其他地区的贫困率一样糟糕是一种被夸大的论调。</span><br>
<span>Previous estimates of extreme poverty have suggested it was concentrated amongst single parent families. These households bore the brunt of a major bipartisan reform in 1996, which made welfare payments conditional on recipients trying to find work and ruled that no one could receive them for more than five years. According to Kathryn Edin and Luke Schaefer, sociologists, survey evidence suggests the number of households with children living on less than $2 cash per person per day climbed from 600,000 in 1997 to more than 1.4m in 2010. Even including the Supplemental Nutritional Assistance Programme, once known as food stamps, which was designed to ensure that poor American families have enough to eat, the numbers appeared to have increased from below half a million in 1996 to 800,000 in 2010.</span><br>
<span>先前对极端贫困状况的估计认为极端贫困多发于单亲家庭中。这些家庭在96年的两党改革中首当其冲，因为改革要求这些家庭必须找到工作才能领取社会福利，而且不许任何资方雇佣他们超过五年。Kathryn Edin和Luke Schaefer两位社会学家的研究表明，每人每天生活水平低于2刀的家庭从1997年的60万上升到2010年的140多万。即使考虑到营养补充援助计划（SNAP，也称食物券计划）的帮助，本应得到足够食物的贫困美国家庭，其数量仍在1996年到2010年间从不足50万上升到80万。</span><br>
<span>The $2 poverty line is broadly comparable to the World Bank’s global $1.90 “extreme poverty line.” It is a fraction of the official, income-based, poverty line in America, which is set at $21,330 for a family of three—or about $19 a day. Those earlier estimates of extreme poverty, suggestive of widespread destitution, prompted Angus Deaton, a Nobel prize-winning economist, to propose redirecting US foreign aid to America’s poorest people.</span><br>
<span>2刀的贫困线与世界银行的1.9刀“极端贫困线”大致相当。不过这个数据只是美国官方认定的，基于收入的贫困线的一小部分，基于收入的贫困线要求三口之家年收入低于21330刀，或者说，每天19刀。先前对极端贫困率的估计暗示了美国存在普遍的贫困问题，让诺贝尔经济学奖得主Angus Deaton倡议美国政府将外援重新导向到美国最贫困的人群里。</span><br>
<span>The new poverty estimates, by Carla Medalia from the Census Bureau and Bruce Meyer from the University of Chicago, tell a rather different story. They combine data from surveys and from government agencies. That helps overcome two problems from estimates that use survey data alone: respondents often under-report the benefits they get and sometimes they mis-report other income.</span><br>
<span>新的贫困估测数据来自美国人口调查局的Carla Medalia和来自芝加哥大学的Bruce Meyer，他们给出了不一样的视角，两人将来自调查和政府机构的数据合并，克服了估测中单独使用某方数据时可能出现的两个问题：受访者通常低估他们的救济金，有时也会误报其他收入。</span><br>
<span>Looking at all individuals’ survey-reported household income, about 2.6% report living on less than $2 a day. But when other benefits, under-reported earnings and other assets are factored in, that falls to 0.57%. Add in data from programme administrators on under-reported transfers including the earned income tax credit, social security payments, housing assistance and the Supplemental Nutritional Assistance Programme and the proportion falls to 0.11% percent, or around 336,000 people.</span><br>
<span>从所有独立的调查报告来看，大概有2.6%的受访者每日生活水平在2刀以下。但考虑到其他救济金，瞒报的收入和其余因素时，这个比率降到了0.57%。再加上从计划管理方获得的瞒报数据，包括税收减免，社会保障金，住房援助计划和营养援助计划后，这一比例再降至0.11%，也就是说约有33万6千人生活在贫困线以下。</span><br>
<span>The adjustments also suggest extreme poverty isn’t concentrated among families. On a survey-reported basis that excludes in-kind payments households with children make up the considerable majority of the extreme poor. But once the adjustments are made, poverty is almost exclusively concentrated amongst single, childless households.</span><br>
<span>这项调整也表明极端贫困并不以家庭为中心分布。以调查报告为基础时，除了有实物支付（即派发）的，那些有孩子的家庭占据了极端贫困占大多数。但进行上述的调整后，贫困几乎完全集中于单身无子的家庭中。</span><br>
<span>While the additional data sources certainly make the numbers more reliable, the analysis, as with previous estimates, excludes the homeless—half a million or more Americans. And some of the assumptions regarding data adjustments are arguable—including that benefits are worth the same as cash, that hours worked will necessarily pay at least the minimum wage and that households with considerable asset wealth will not be income-poor. On the other hand, the results exclude administrative data on some big transfer programmes including unemployment insurance, veteran’s benefits and worker’s compensation, which collectively spend over $200bn a year.</span><br>
<span>虽然额外的材料确实能使这些数字更可靠，但和之前的估测一样，无家可归的美国人被排除在统计之外——大概有50万以上的美国人。而且关于数据调整所做的一些假设仍有争议，如简单地把救济金与现金等同，假设小时工必然能领到等价的最低工资，假设拥有一定资产的家庭不会在收入上贫困。另一方面，这个结果也未包括一些大型的政府财政转移计划，如失业保险，退伍军人福利和工人赔偿金，这些计划每年共花费超过2000亿美元。</span><br>
<span>The new evidence is important for two reasons. First, it suggests that extreme poverty cannot have risen significantly after welfare reform. The numbers living on $2 a day remain low and are not amongst those targeted by the reform measures. Second, the big gap between market income and consumption spending thrown up by the new research suggests that safety net programmes are doing their job of keeping people from utter destitution.</span><br>
<span>有两个原因使新的数据更重要。首先，它表明极端贫困不可能在福利改革后明显上升。每日生活水平在2刀以下的家庭数量保持较低水平并不是改革的目标。其次，新研究所展示的市场收入与消费支出间的巨大差距表明，社会安全网正在尽其所能，避免人们陷入到贫困的境地中。</span><br>
<span>The overall impact of welfare reform continues to be debated. Research by Hilary Hoynes and Diane Schanzenbach, economists, suggests safety-net spending on families with incomes below the official poverty line has fallen from 87% of the total in 1990 to 56% in 2015, while per-child spending on families without earnings has declined since 1990. And even if the number of Americans living on $2 a day is in the thousands, rather than over 1m, it is still too high.</span><br>
<span>福利改革的总体后果直到今天还在争论不休。由两位经济学家，Hilary Hoynes和Diane Schanzenbach所做的研究表明，社会安全网在低于官方贫困线的家庭中总花费比例从1990年的87%下降到2015年的56%，但无收入家庭对每个孩子的支出从1990年就一直在下降。就算美国每日生活条件在两刀以下的人口只有几十万，不到一百万，这个值还是太高了。</span><br>
<span>原文链接：https://www.economist.com/democr ... ans-live-on-2-a-day</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1841255[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
