<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>莫迪总理：印度5万亿美元的经济目标具有挑战，但可以实现</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>莫迪总理：印度5万亿美元的经济目标具有挑战，但可以实现</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 19:36:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>莫迪总理：印度5万亿美元的经济目标具有挑战，但可以实现[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1841151-1-1.html</link>
      <description>莫迪总理：印度5万亿美元的经济目标具有挑战，但可以实现&#13;
Making India $5 trillion economy challenging but achievable: PM Modi莫迪总理：印度5万亿美元的经济目标具有挑战，但可以实现NEW DELHI: Prime Minister Narendra Modi on Saturday said the goal of making India a $5 trillion economy by 2024 is challenging but surely achievable, as he asked states to focus on their core competencies and work towards increasing the GDP right from the district level.Addressing the fifth meeting of the Governing Council of Niti Aayog, Modi also announced setting up of a high-powered committee comprising some chief ministers and Union ministers on structural reforms in agriculture.The meeting which held in a "very positive atmosphere" was attended by senior Union ministers and almost all the chief ministers, except for Mamata Banerjee (West Bengal) and K Chandrashekhar Rao (Telangana).Punjab chief minister Amarinder Singh could not attend the meeting due to health reasons. Himachal Pradesh chief minister Jairam Thakur too could not attend the meeting as he was in Germany.莫迪总理周六表示，到2024年印度经济规模实现5万亿美元的目标具有挑战性，但肯定是可以实现的，他要求各邦专注于自己的核心竞争力，努力提高各地区的GDP。莫迪在尼提阿约格理事会第五次会议上发表讲话时，还宣布将成立一个由一些首席部长和联盟部长组成的关于农业结构改革的高层委员会。这次会议在“非常积极的气氛”中进行，除了Mamata Banerjee(西孟加拉邦)和K Chandrashekhar Rao(泰伦加纳邦)以外，高级联盟部长和几乎所有首席部长都出席了会议。旁遮普省首席部长辛格由于健康原因无法出席会议。喜马偕尔邦首席部长塔库尔(Jairam Thakur)因为人在德国也没能出席会议。Banerjee had earlier said she would not attend the meeting saying Niti Aayog is a "fruitless" body as it has no financial powers. Rao did not come as he was busy with preparations for the launch of the ambitious Rs 80,000 crore Kaleshwaram lift irrigation project that would end water woes in the state.After the meeting, Niti Aayog Vice-Chairman Rajiv Kumar told reporters that composition and terms of reference about the high powered committee on agriculture reforms would be announced in the next few days. The committee, he added, would be submitting its report in two-three months.班纳吉早些时候曾表示她不会参加这次会议，她说尼提·阿约格因为没有财政权力，所以是一个“不会有成果”的机构。拉奥没有来，因为他正忙于启动雄心勃勃的8万卢比的灌溉项目，该项目将结束印度的水资源困境。会后，尼提·阿约格副主席拉吉夫·库马尔告诉记者，农业改革高级委员会的成立和职权范围将在未来几天内正式宣布。他补充说，该委员会将在两三个月内提交报告。On the absence of the Bengal chief minister, Kumar said it is regrettable that she did not come as her contribution to the meeting would have been helpful.In his inaugural address, the Prime Minister also underlined the need for taking effective steps to tackle drought in various parts of the country.According to an official release, Modi recalled the recent General Election as the world's largest democratic exercise and said that it is now time for everyone to work for the development of India. He spoke of a collective fight against poverty, unemployment, drought, flood, pollution, corruption and violence.孟加拉邦首席部长缺席会议，库马尔说，她没有出席会议令人遗憾，因为她本来会对会议做出一定贡献的。在就职演说中，总理还强调了采取有效措施解决该国各地干旱问题的必要性。据官方发布的消息，莫迪称最近的大选是世界上规模最大的皿煮运动，现在是每个人为印度发展而努力的时候了。他谈到了与贫困、失业、干旱、洪水、污染、腐败和暴力进行的集体斗争。The Prime Minister said that everyone has a common goal of achieving a New India by 2022.Stressing that the focus should be on collective responsibility for achieving short-term and long-term goals, Modi said the goal to make India a $5 trillion economy by 2024, is "challenging, but can surely be achieved".The size of India's economy was estimated at $2.75 trillion at end-March 2019.总理说，每个人都有一个共同的目标，那就是在2022年前打造一个全新的印度。莫迪强调，重点应放在实现短期和长期目标的集体责任上。他说，到2024年使印度经济规模达到5万亿美元的目标“具有挑战性，但肯定可以实现”。到2019年3月底，印度经济规模约为2.75万亿美元。States, he added, should recognise their core competence, and work towards raising GDP targets right from the district level.He also stressed on increasing exports from the country.Amid drought-like situation in several parts of the country, Modi called for effective steps to tackle drought and emphasised that "per-drop, more-crop" strategy should be promoted.India has faced deficit monsoon rains for the last five years and water management has become a major issue.他补充称，各邦应认识到自己的核心竞争力，并从努力提高各邦的GDP目标。他还强调要增加出口总额。在印度部分地区出现类似干旱的情况下，莫迪呼吁采取有效措施应对干旱，并强调应推广“水滴增产”战略。印度在过去五年中面临季风雨不足的困难，水资源管理已成为一个主要问题。The release further said Modi reiterated the Union Government's commitment to double incomes of farmers by 2022. To achieve this, he said there should be a focus on fisheries, animal husbandry, horticulture, fruits and vegetables.Noting the importance of structural reforms in agriculture, PM Modi spoke of the need to boost corporate investment, strengthen logistics, and provide ample market support. He said the food processing sector should grow at a faster pace than foodgrain production.Giving further details about the meeting, the Niti Aayog Vice-Chairman said the stress was on boosting the agriculture sector and many of the states suggested a review of the agricultural produce market committees and norms related to essential commodities law.声明还说，莫迪重申了联邦政府对2022年实现农民收入翻番的承诺。他说，要实现这一目标，应该把重点放在渔业、畜牧业、园艺业、水果和蔬菜上。莫迪总理指出农业结构改革的重要性，指出必须促进企业投资，加强物流，并提供充足的市场支持。他说，食品加工业的增长速度应该快于粮食生产。关于会议的进一步细节，副主席Niti Aayog说，重点是大力发展农业部门，许多邦建议审查农产品市场委员会和与基本商品法有关的规范。He also said the issue related to Jammu and Kashmir too came up for discussion and Governor Satya Pal Malik informed the gathering that there was a marked improvement in the law and order situation in the state.The problem of Naxalism was being contained because there has been better coordination and information sharing among affected states.Kumar said several states made many suggestions regarding the forthcoming Union Budget. He said the suggestions would help in budget making.He also said devolution of funds from the Centre to states has almost doubled to Rs 41 lakh crore in the past four years.他还说，会上还讨论了查谟和克什米尔的有关问题，地方长官萨提亚·帕尔·马利克通知与会者说，查谟和克什米尔的法律和秩序状况有了明显改善。纳萨尔主义的问题得到了控制，因为受到影响的印度邦之间有更好的协调和信息共享。库马尔说，几个邦对即将到来的联邦预算提出了许多建议。他说这些建议将有助于预算的制定。他还说，在过去四年里，中央向各邦下放的资金几乎翻了一番，达到4100亿卢比。以下是印度时报读者的评论：译文来源：三泰虎http://www.santaihu.com/47870.html 译者：Joyceliu外文：http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/Rohan•india•17 hours agobut achievable but Jumla. But bodies of 13 dead Air man is not traceable.可以实现，就是个笑话。13名飞行员的尸体至今下落不明。
&#13;
Arun Mehta•mumbai•1 day agoWhy Modi educational qualifications (degrees) are under stay?为什么莫迪的学历(学位)还能留任?
&#13;
Syed Masood Hassan•1 day agoIt''s really heartening to note that our GDP will be double in the next 5 years. For a progressive country like India, this target, even though could be a challenge but definitely possible provided we citizens of this great nation join together. First action from Government, Govt. means all three levels of Govt. Central, State and Local self Govt. All these Govt. agencies should (1) Evaluate through experts the invaluable hyper potentials of our great nation (2) Plan as to how effectively and ef ... Read More我们的国内生产总值在今后五年内将翻一番，这真是令人鼓舞。对于印度这样一个发展中国家来说，这一目标虽然可能是个挑战，但只要我们这个伟大国家的公民团结起来，这一目标绝对是可能实现的。首先，政府的行动意味着中央、邦和地方三个层次的政府行动起来。所有这些政府机构都应该(1)通过专家评估我们伟大国家的巨大潜力；(2) 高效地规划。
&#13;
Rohan•india•1 day agochallenging, but achievable: This time he has become a bit wiser. He is not promising to achieve it. Any one may hope to achieve any thing !具有挑战性，但可以实现：这一次他变得更明智了。他并没有承诺一定会实现这一目标。任何人都有希望做成任何事!
&#13;
Bhushan•1 day agoYes it is very much achievable. But for that need to concentrate on rural india.是的，这是很容易实现的。但要实现这一目标，就必须把重点放在印度农村地区。
&#13;
Prabhakar Rallabhandi•1 day agoCalculations show that to reach 5 trillion USD by 2024 means an annual growth rate of about 13% per anum. India crossed 9 % on only 3 occasions in last 20 years. This is certainly ( over) ambitious and since the average growth has been about 7 % for many years . While stretch targets are desirable, they should not be impractical. Modi Govt should target 10% growth and achieve it consistently.统计表明，到2024年达到5万亿美元意味着每年的增长率约为13%。印度在过去20年中只有3次超过9%。这个目标过于雄心勃勃，因为多年来GDP平均增长率一直在7%左右。尽管弹性目标是可取的，但也不应不切实际。莫迪政府应该把经济增长目标定在10%，努力实现这一目标。
&#13;
King_maker69•1 day agoBJP &amp; Feku's cyber dogs people are uniting against the EVM rigging done by feku in the last elections.,They are planning protest soon please go out on the streets and start barking and biting them to save your master,Come on you can do it semi literates.印度人民党和印度联邦储备银行的网上忠犬们团结起来，反对印度联邦储备银行在上次选举中操纵EVM。他们正在筹划㢟抗议活动，请走到街上，冲着他们大叫、狠咬他们来拯救你的主人，来吧，你们这些半文盲可以做到的。
&#13;
srinivas•1 day agoElectric vehicles, self employment, financing the skilled youth, increase exports,and farm products,and afforestation are the sure ways to reach that goal in no time.电动汽车、自主创业、为有技能的年轻人提供资金、增加出口、农产品和植树造林，这些都是迅速实现这一目标的可靠途径。
&#13;
Valerian Pereira•india•1 day agoInvite all over seas Branded cos to set up ventures in india.邀请所有的海外公司在印度建立合资企业。
&#13;
Anurag•1 day agoaction to be taken 1. focus in jobs and economic growth ,2 psu shall be recapitalized and start lending , structural changes to be done in bank management otherwise more npa will be created , assets and personal property of all defaulters shall be sold 3. every year we have drought in part of India and flood in other part of India, river water to be diverted from flood prone areas to drought prone areas ( no need to spend tax payment money on bullet train or statues ) etc应采取的行动：1.以就业和经济增长为重点；2. 进行资本重组并开始放贷，对银行管理进行结构性改革；3. 每年，印度部分地区都会发生干旱，印度其他地区也会发生洪水，河水会从容易发生洪水的地区流向容易发生干旱的地区(不需要为高铁或雕像缴税)，等等
&#13;
Anurag• Anurag Garg•1 day agoall these to be done be,without increase in taxes on middle class , they are taxed very heavily , 30% income tax , 18% gst , rest of money gone for paying home loan EMI. in lieu of all these taxes do not get any freebie ( no subsidy, not covered in aayushman yozna ) from government .所有这些都要做，而且不要增加中产阶级的税收负担，他们的税赋很重，30%的所得税，18%的消费税，剩下的钱用来支付房贷了。
&#13;
Gadkari•1 day agoOn an average of 1 Pakoda Stall=1000 Dollars, Country will need 5 Billion Pakoda Stalls for 5 Trillion Dollar Economy.如果平均1个帕可达煎饼摊位=1000美元，印度得需要50亿个帕可达摊位才能实现5万亿美元的经济规模。
&#13;
BIG Indian•world•1 day agoIndian mouth is the biggest. hail Modi印度的口气之大天下无敌。莫迪万岁。</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>废狗: </b><br>
<span>莫迪总理：印度5万亿美元的经济目标具有挑战，但可以实现</span><br>
<span>Making India $5 trillion economy challenging but achievable: PM Modi莫迪总理：印度5万亿美元的经济目标具有挑战，但可以实现NEW DELHI: Prime Minister Narendra Modi on Saturday said the goal of making India a $5 trillion economy by 2024 is challenging but surely achievable, as he asked states to focus on their core competencies and work towards increasing the GDP right from the district level.Addressing the fifth meeting of the Governing Council of Niti Aayog, Modi also announced setting up of a high-powered committee comprising some chief ministers and Union ministers on structural reforms in agriculture.The meeting which held in a "very positive atmosphere" was attended by senior Union ministers and almost all the chief ministers, except for Mamata Banerjee (West Bengal) and K Chandrashekhar Rao (Telangana).Punjab chief minister Amarinder Singh could not attend the meeting due to health reasons. Himachal Pradesh chief minister Jairam Thakur too could not attend the meeting as he was in Germany.莫迪总理周六表示，到2024年印度经济规模实现5万亿美元的目标具有挑战性，但肯定是可以实现的，他要求各邦专注于自己的核心竞争力，努力提高各地区的GDP。莫迪在尼提阿约格理事会第五次会议上发表讲话时，还宣布将成立一个由一些首席部长和联盟部长组成的关于农业结构改革的高层委员会。这次会议在“非常积极的气氛”中进行，除了Mamata Banerjee(西孟加拉邦)和K Chandrashekhar Rao(泰伦加纳邦)以外，高级联盟部长和几乎所有首席部长都出席了会议。旁遮普省首席部长辛格由于健康原因无法出席会议。喜马偕尔邦首席部长塔库尔(Jairam Thakur)因为人在德国也没能出席会议。Banerjee had earlier said she would not attend the meeting saying Niti Aayog is a "fruitless" body as it has no financial powers. Rao did not come as he was busy with preparations for the launch of the ambitious Rs 80,000 crore Kaleshwaram lift irrigation project that would end water woes in the state.After the meeting, Niti Aayog Vice-Chairman Rajiv Kumar told reporters that composition and terms of reference about the high powered committee on agriculture reforms would be announced in the next few days. The committee, he added, would be submitting its report in two-three months.班纳吉早些时候曾表示她不会参加这次会议，她说尼提·阿约格因为没有财政权力，所以是一个“不会有成果”的机构。拉奥没有来，因为他正忙于启动雄心勃勃的8万卢比的灌溉项目，该项目将结束印度的水资源困境。会后，尼提·阿约格副主席拉吉夫·库马尔告诉记者，农业改革高级委员会的成立和职权范围将在未来几天内正式宣布。他补充说，该委员会将在两三个月内提交报告。On the absence of the Bengal chief minister, Kumar said it is regrettable that she did not come as her contribution to the meeting would have been helpful.In his inaugural address, the Prime Minister also underlined the need for taking effective steps to tackle drought in various parts of the country.According to an official release, Modi recalled the recent General Election as the world's largest democratic exercise and said that it is now time for everyone to work for the development of India. He spoke of a collective fight against poverty, unemployment, drought, flood, pollution, corruption and violence.孟加拉邦首席部长缺席会议，库马尔说，她没有出席会议令人遗憾，因为她本来会对会议做出一定贡献的。在就职演说中，总理还强调了采取有效措施解决该国各地干旱问题的必要性。据官方发布的消息，莫迪称最近的大选是世界上规模最大的皿煮运动，现在是每个人为印度发展而努力的时候了。他谈到了与贫困、失业、干旱、洪水、污染、腐败和暴力进行的集体斗争。The Prime Minister said that everyone has a common goal of achieving a New India by 2022.Stressing that the focus should be on collective responsibility for achieving short-term and long-term goals, Modi said the goal to make India a $5 trillion economy by 2024, is "challenging, but can surely be achieved".The size of India's economy was estimated at $2.75 trillion at end-March 2019.总理说，每个人都有一个共同的目标，那就是在2022年前打造一个全新的印度。莫迪强调，重点应放在实现短期和长期目标的集体责任上。他说，到2024年使印度经济规模达到5万亿美元的目标“具有挑战性，但肯定可以实现”。到2019年3月底，印度经济规模约为2.75万亿美元。States, he added, should recognise their core competence, and work towards raising GDP targets right from the district level.He also stressed on increasing exports from the country.Amid drought-like situation in several parts of the country, Modi called for effective steps to tackle drought and emphasised that "per-drop, more-crop" strategy should be promoted.India has faced deficit monsoon rains for the last five years and water management has become a major issue.他补充称，各邦应认识到自己的核心竞争力，并从努力提高各邦的GDP目标。他还强调要增加出口总额。在印度部分地区出现类似干旱的情况下，莫迪呼吁采取有效措施应对干旱，并强调应推广“水滴增产”战略。印度在过去五年中面临季风雨不足的困难，水资源管理已成为一个主要问题。The release further said Modi reiterated the Union Government's commitment to double incomes of farmers by 2022. To achieve this, he said there should be a focus on fisheries, animal husbandry, horticulture, fruits and vegetables.Noting the importance of structural reforms in agriculture, PM Modi spoke of the need to boost corporate investment, strengthen logistics, and provide ample market support. He said the food processing sector should grow at a faster pace than foodgrain production.Giving further details about the meeting, the Niti Aayog Vice-Chairman said the stress was on boosting the agriculture sector and many of the states suggested a review of the agricultural produce market committees and norms related to essential commodities law.声明还说，莫迪重申了联邦政府对2022年实现农民收入翻番的承诺。他说，要实现这一目标，应该把重点放在渔业、畜牧业、园艺业、水果和蔬菜上。莫迪总理指出农业结构改革的重要性，指出必须促进企业投资，加强物流，并提供充足的市场支持。他说，食品加工业的增长速度应该快于粮食生产。关于会议的进一步细节，副主席Niti Aayog说，重点是大力发展农业部门，许多邦建议审查农产品市场委员会和与基本商品法有关的规范。He also said the issue related to Jammu and Kashmir too came up for discussion and Governor Satya Pal Malik informed the gathering that there was a marked improvement in the law and order situation in the state.The problem of Naxalism was being contained because there has been better coordination and information sharing among affected states.Kumar said several states made many suggestions regarding the forthcoming Union Budget. He said the suggestions would help in budget making.He also said devolution of funds from the Centre to states has almost doubled to Rs 41 lakh crore in the past four years.他还说，会上还讨论了查谟和克什米尔的有关问题，地方长官萨提亚·帕尔·马利克通知与会者说，查谟和克什米尔的法律和秩序状况有了明显改善。纳萨尔主义的问题得到了控制，因为受到影响的印度邦之间有更好的协调和信息共享。库马尔说，几个邦对即将到来的联邦预算提出了许多建议。他说这些建议将有助于预算的制定。他还说，在过去四年里，中央向各邦下放的资金几乎翻了一番，达到4100亿卢比。以下是印度时报读者的评论：译文来源：三泰虎http://www.santaihu.com/47870.html 译者：Joyceliu外文：http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/Rohan•india•17 hours agobut achievable but Jumla. But bodies of 13 dead Air man is not traceable.可以实现，就是个笑话。13名飞行员的尸体至今下落不明。</span><br>
<span>Arun Mehta•mumbai•1 day agoWhy Modi educational qualifications (degrees) are under stay?为什么莫迪的学历(学位)还能留任?</span><br>
<span>Syed Masood Hassan•1 day agoIt''s really heartening to note that our GDP will be double in the next 5 years. For a progressive country like India, this target, even though could be a challenge but definitely possible provided we citizens of this great nation join together. First action from Government, Govt. means all three levels of Govt. Central, State and Local self Govt. All these Govt. agencies should (1) Evaluate through experts the invaluable hyper potentials of our great nation (2) Plan as to how effectively and ef ... Read More我们的国内生产总值在今后五年内将翻一番，这真是令人鼓舞。对于印度这样一个发展中国家来说，这一目标虽然可能是个挑战，但只要我们这个伟大国家的公民团结起来，这一目标绝对是可能实现的。首先，政府的行动意味着中央、邦和地方三个层次的政府行动起来。所有这些政府机构都应该(1)通过专家评估我们伟大国家的巨大潜力；(2) 高效地规划。</span><br>
<span>Rohan•india•1 day agochallenging, but achievable: This time he has become a bit wiser. He is not promising to achieve it. Any one may hope to achieve any thing !具有挑战性，但可以实现：这一次他变得更明智了。他并没有承诺一定会实现这一目标。任何人都有希望做成任何事!</span><br>
<span>Bhushan•1 day agoYes it is very much achievable. But for that need to concentrate on rural india.是的，这是很容易实现的。但要实现这一目标，就必须把重点放在印度农村地区。</span><br>
<span>Prabhakar Rallabhandi•1 day agoCalculations show that to reach 5 trillion USD by 2024 means an annual growth rate of about 13% per anum. India crossed 9 % on only 3 occasions in last 20 years. This is certainly ( over) ambitious and since the average growth has been about 7 % for many years . While stretch targets are desirable, they should not be impractical. Modi Govt should target 10% growth and achieve it consistently.统计表明，到2024年达到5万亿美元意味着每年的增长率约为13%。印度在过去20年中只有3次超过9%。这个目标过于雄心勃勃，因为多年来GDP平均增长率一直在7%左右。尽管弹性目标是可取的，但也不应不切实际。莫迪政府应该把经济增长目标定在10%，努力实现这一目标。</span><br>
<span>King_maker69•1 day agoBJP & Feku's cyber dogs people are uniting against the EVM rigging done by feku in the last elections.,They are planning protest soon please go out on the streets and start barking and biting them to save your master,Come on you can do it semi literates.印度人民党和印度联邦储备银行的网上忠犬们团结起来，反对印度联邦储备银行在上次选举中操纵EVM。他们正在筹划㢟抗议活动，请走到街上，冲着他们大叫、狠咬他们来拯救你的主人，来吧，你们这些半文盲可以做到的。</span><br>
<span>srinivas•1 day agoElectric vehicles, self employment, financing the skilled youth, increase exports,and farm products,and afforestation are the sure ways to reach that goal in no time.电动汽车、自主创业、为有技能的年轻人提供资金、增加出口、农产品和植树造林，这些都是迅速实现这一目标的可靠途径。</span><br>
<span>Valerian Pereira•india•1 day agoInvite all over seas Branded cos to set up ventures in india.邀请所有的海外公司在印度建立合资企业。</span><br>
<span>Anurag•1 day agoaction to be taken 1. focus in jobs and economic growth ,2 psu shall be recapitalized and start lending , structural changes to be done in bank management otherwise more npa will be created , assets and personal property of all defaulters shall be sold 3. every year we have drought in part of India and flood in other part of India, river water to be diverted from flood prone areas to drought prone areas ( no need to spend tax payment money on bullet train or statues ) etc应采取的行动：1.以就业和经济增长为重点；2. 进行资本重组并开始放贷，对银行管理进行结构性改革；3. 每年，印度部分地区都会发生干旱，印度其他地区也会发生洪水，河水会从容易发生洪水的地区流向容易发生干旱的地区(不需要为高铁或雕像缴税)，等等</span><br>
<span>Anurag• Anurag Garg•1 day agoall these to be done be,without increase in taxes on middle class , they are taxed very heavily , 30% income tax , 18% gst , rest of money gone for paying home loan EMI. in lieu of all these taxes do not get any freebie ( no subsidy, not covered in aayushman yozna ) from government .所有这些都要做，而且不要增加中产阶级的税收负担，他们的税赋很重，30%的所得税，18%的消费税，剩下的钱用来支付房贷了。</span><br>
<span>Gadkari•1 day agoOn an average of 1 Pakoda Stall=1000 Dollars, Country will need 5 Billion Pakoda Stalls for 5 Trillion Dollar Economy.如果平均1个帕可达煎饼摊位=1000美元，印度得需要50亿个帕可达摊位才能实现5万亿美元的经济规模。</span><br>
<span>BIG Indian•world•1 day agoIndian mouth is the biggest. hail Modi印度的口气之大天下无敌。莫迪万岁。</span><br>
</p><p><b>dark_templar: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 dark_templar 于 2019-6-21 13:06 编辑 </span><br>
<span>反正可以修改GDP统计方法嘛，大不了说牛粪是纯天然无污染比化肥高到不知道哪里去了所以算进GDP里的价值可以再加一倍</span><br>
</p><p><b>废狗: </b><br>
<span>dark_templar 发表于 2019-6-21 13:04</span><br>
<span>反正可以修改GDP统计方法嘛</span><br>
<span>美元正开始回流，印度18-19财年（至今年3月31）吸收外资总额出现下降，通讯业下降57%、建筑业下降61%、制药业下降73%</span><br>
</p><p><b>左道: </b><br>
<span>BIG Indian•world•1 day ago</span><br>
<span>Indian mouth is the biggest. hail Modi</span><br>
<span>印度的口气之大天下无敌。莫迪万岁。</span><br>
<img src="https://avatar.saraba1st.com/data/avatar/000/03/09/11_avatar_middle.jpg" title="https://avatar.saraba1st.com/data/avatar/000/03/09/11_avatar_middle.jpg"><br>
</p><p><b>Okumur: </b><br>
<span>美：自住房算虚拟房租计入GDP</span><br>
<span>欧：**与非法毒品交易活动计入GDP</span><br>
<span>他 山 之 石，可 以 攻 玉</span><br>
</p><p><b>pzgr43: </b><br>
<span>Gadkari•1 day ago</span><br>
<span>On an average of 1 Pakoda Stall=1000 Dollars, Country will need 5 Billion Pakoda Stalls for 5 Trillion Dollar Economy.</span><br>
<span>如果平均1个帕可达煎饼摊位=1000美元，印度得需要50亿个帕可达摊位才能实现5万亿美元的经济规模。</span><br>
</p><p><b>dark_templar: </b><br>
<span>废狗 发表于 2019-6-21 13:07</span><br>
<span>美元正开始回流，印度18-19财年（至今年3月31）吸收外资总额出现下降，通讯业下降57%、建筑业下降61%、制 ...</span><br>
<span>要相信印度统计局的水平，办法多得是</span><br>
<span>比如还可以这么干</span><br>
<span>打个比方说，中国造了条高铁，2年修完，产生1000亿刀增加值，平均每年就是500亿刀</span><br>
<span>中国都能每条高铁每年500亿，那么阿三第一条高铁自然也能每年500亿</span><br>
<span>这样是不是很Jai hind?</span><br>
</p><p><b>放下自在: </b><br>
<span>Jai hind！</span><br>
</p><p><b>佐塚間桐: </b><br>
<span>印度人安心搞基建的话也许还有希望</span><br>
</p><p><b>意大利面: </b><br>
<span>佐塚間桐 发表于 2019-6-21 13:45</span><br>
<span>印度人安心搞基建的话也许还有希望</span><br>
<span>兔子大搞基建的年代也没有一年13个点的增长，还是举国效率的前提下，印度要不打上月球，不然如何实现年均13个点增长</span><br>
</p><p><b>火烧云: </b><br>
<span>可以建厕所，一个厕所1000美刀，只需要50亿个厕所</span><br>
</p><p><b>佐塚間桐: </b><br>
<span>意大利面 发表于 2019-6-21 14:05</span><br>
<span>兔子大搞基建的年代也没有一年13个点的增长，还是举国效率的前提下，印度要不打上月球，不然如何实现年均 ...</span><br>
<span>本世纪初那几年都是两位数增长。那阵子经常听到的是经济过热</span><br>
</p><p><b>意大利面: </b><br>
<span>佐塚間桐 发表于 2019-6-21 14:36</span><br>
<span>本世纪初那几年都是两位数增长。那阵子经常听到的是经济过热</span><br>
<span>然后你觉得印度能”过热“5年不成……</span><br>
</p><p><b>bluescope: </b><br>
<span>5年，每年12.7%的GDP增速</span><br>
</p><p><b>Ursa: </b><br>
<span>废狗 发表于 2019-6-21 13:07</span><br>
<span>美元正开始回流，印度18-19财年（至今年3月31）吸收外资总额出现下降，通讯业下降57%、建筑业下降61%、制 ...</span><br>
<span>印度很依赖外国投资的吧，真经济指标下降这么严重，印度国内没点反应的？</span><br>
</p><p><b>废狗: </b><br>
<span>Ursa 发表于 2019-6-21 15:12</span><br>
<span>印度很依赖外国投资的吧，真经济指标下降这么严重，印度国内没点反应的？ ...</span><br>
<span>有的</span><br>
<span>http://www.santaihu.com/47787.html</span><br>
<span>为了刺激经济和增加就业，莫迪总理设立两个内阁小组</span><br>
</p><p><b>Dmitryeav: </b><br>
<span>13%是名义增长还是实际增长？如果是名义的话才有一点点可行性</span><br>
<span>----发送自 OPPO OPPO A33,Android 5.1.1</span><br>
</p><p><b>蓝川文和: </b><br>
<span>有点扯，这就是中国高速发展能到10，我们肯定比中国强，的这种幻想吧…</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>シャスタ: </b><br>
<span>贫困的地方多,还有富的地方带,高速发展是肯定的.就是有没有吹得这么多的问题.</span><br>
</p><p><b>thewingz: </b><br>
<span>Dmitryeav 发表于 2019-6-21 15:19</span><br>
<span>13%是名义增长还是实际增长？如果是名义的话才有一点点可行性</span><br>
<span>----发送自 OPPO OPPO A33,Android 5.1.1 ...</span><br>
<span>三哥之前不是每年都修改基准年么，致使名义增长=实际增长</span><br>
</p><p><b>03e7: </b><br>
<span>恒河水可以換算多少GDP</span><br>
</p><p><b>Lozs: </b><br>
<span>只能jai hind了</span><br>
</p><p><b>fore_long: </b><br>
<span>大干快上，赶美超英，坂上飞饼的日子已经到啦</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1841151[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
