<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>【ZT】中国并非美国经济问题的根源，企业的贪婪才是</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>【ZT】中国并非美国经济问题的根源，企业的贪婪才是</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 20:10:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>【ZT】中国并非美国经济问题的根源，企业的贪婪才是[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1835636-1-1.html</link>
      <description>【ZT】中国并非美国经济问题的根源，企业的贪婪才是&#13;
 本帖最后由 撒撒 于 2019-5-30 16:58 编辑 

中文翻译：肖准（译） 财经园地（公众号）
&#13;
（原作：杰弗里·萨克斯）
&#13;
中国不是美国的敌人。中国是一个试图通过教育、国际贸易、基础设施投资和改进技术来提高生活水平的国家。简单来说，它（中国）正在做的事，是任何国家在面对贫穷且远远落后于更强大国家的历史现实时应做之事。然而，特朗普政府现在的目标是阻止中国的发展，这可能对美国和整个世界都是灾难性的。
&#13;
中国正在成为美国不平等加剧的替罪羊。虽然美国与中国的贸易关系多年来一直是互惠互利的，但一些美国工人却产生了失落感，特别是中西部工厂的工人由于生产力提高和中国的劳动力成本相对较低（虽然也在上升）而面临竞争。我们不应该将这种正常的市场竞争所带来的后果归咎于中国，而应该对本国的跨国公司高涨的企业利润征税，并把税收用于帮助工薪阶层家庭，重建摇摇欲坠的基础设施，帮助工人掌握新的工作技能，并投资于尖端科技。
&#13;
我们应该明白，在遭遇长期地缘政治挫折以及经济发展失利后，中国只是在努力弥补失去的时间。这一重要的历史背景，有助于理解中国过去40年的经济发展。
&#13;
1839年，英国攻打中国，因为它拒绝允许英国商人继续向中国人提供成瘾的 鸦 片 。英国占了上风，使中国在1842年结束的第一次 鸦 片 战争中蒙受失败的耻辱，并在一定程度上促成反抗清朝统治的大规模起义，史称太平天国起义，这场起义最终导致超过2000万人死亡。随后抗击英法的第二次 鸦 片 战争从根本上动摇了中国政权和内部稳定。
&#13;
到了19世纪末，中国在一场战争（甲午战争）中输给了刚刚工业化的日本，并被迫接受了欧洲和美国对贸易更多单方面的要求。这些耻辱导致了另一场反抗（义和团运动），随后又遭到外国势力的镇压。
&#13;
中国的清朝政府于1911年垮台，此后中国又罹患军阀、内乱和日本1931年对中国的入侵。第二次世界大战结束后，随之而来的是内战，1949年中华人民共和国成立，然后毛泽东思想给中国带来了剧变，其间发生了大跃进中上百万人死于饥馑（1960年代初期结束），以及之后的群众运动，其余波一直持续到1977年。
&#13;
因此，中国以市场为基础的快速发展始于1978年，当时邓小平开始担任领导工作并开展了全面的经济改革。虽然中国经济在过去四十年中取得了令人难以置信的增长，但一个多世纪以来的贫穷、动荡、外敌入侵和外来威胁的后患仍然不时萦绕在中国人的心头。中国领导人希望这次能公平地解决贸易争端，这意味着他们不愿再次向美国或其他西方国家屈服。
&#13;
如果GDP按市场价格计算，中国现在是世界第二大经济体。然而，中国仍是一个正在摆脱贫困的国家。1980年，根据国际货币基金组织的数据，中国人均GDP仅为美国的2.5%，到2018年仅为美国的15.3%。如按购买力平价计算，通过使用一组相同的“国际价格”来衡量各国的国内生产总值，中国2018年的人均收入略高于美国的28.9％。
&#13;
中国大致遵循与日本、韩国、台湾、香港和新加坡相同的发展战略。从经济的角度来看，对于一个正在追赶的国家来说，中国并没有做什么特别不寻常的事情。美国一再重申中国“窃取”技术，这是非常幼稚的。
&#13;
相对落后国家要想进行技术升级，往往会通过学习、模仿、购买、兼并、外国投资、广泛使用非专利技术以及复制等多种方法。而随着科技飞速变化，在知识产权问题上总是会产生争端。即使如今的美国公司同样会出现这样的情况——这种竞争只是全球经济体系的一部分。技术引领者们都知道，他们应通过不断创新，而不是保护（现有技术）来保持领先地位。
&#13;
美国在19世纪初就坚持采用英国的技术。当任何一个国家想要缩小技术差距时，它都会从国外引进专门技术。众所周知，美国的弹道导弹计划是在二战后被招募到美国的前纳粹火箭科学家的帮助下完成的。
&#13;
如果中国是一个人口较少的亚洲国家，比如韩国，只有5000多万人，那么美国仅仅把它誉为一个了不起的发展成功故事 - 当然事实也是这样。但由于中国的体量如此之大，它不啻击碎了美国统治世界的玻璃心。毕竟，美国仅占世界人口的4.2％，不到中国的四分之一。事实是，由于专业技术知识在全球范围内的传播速度比以往任何时候都快，因此这两个国家都无法主宰当今世界。
&#13;
与中国的贸易为美国提供了低成本的消费品和更高质量的产品。它还会导致与中国直接竞争的制造业等部门的失业。这就是贸易的必然结果。单方面指责中国不公平贸易行为是错误的——许多美国公司已经从中国制造业或中国的出口商品中获益。由于中国的廉价商品，美国消费者享有更高的生活水平。美国和中国应该继续就完善双边和多边贸易规则进行谈判和阐释各自的意见，而不是用单方面的威胁和过分的指责来引发贸易战。
&#13;
贸易理论、实践和政策的最主要教训不是停止贸易 - 这将导致生活水平下降、经济危机和冲突。相反，我们应该分享经济增长带来的好处，这样获利的赢家就可以补偿输家。
&#13;
然而，在美国资本主义制度下，由于长期缺乏（罗斯福）新政时期的合作精神，如今的赢家们都不愿分享他们的胜利果实。由于不愿分享，美国政治总会在贸易问题上产生冲突。企业的贪婪全面支配着华盛顿政策。
&#13;
美国真正的战斗不是与中国，而是与美国自己的大企业。这些大企业中，许多都在赚大钱的同时，没有给自己的员工支付体面的薪水。美国的商业领袖和超级富豪努力争取减税、更多的垄断力量和产业转移——总之一切可以获取更多利润的东西——同时却拒绝任何可以促使美国社会更加公平的政策。
&#13;
特朗普正在抨击中国，自信中国会再次屈服于西方的力量。它试图通过突然和单方面地改变国际贸易规则来蓄意挤压像华为这样成功公司的生存空间。过去40年来，中国一直遵循西方的规则，逐渐步入美国亚洲盟国过去的发展道路。现在，美国正试图通过发动新的冷战对中国釜底抽薪。
&#13;
除非理性能够占据上风，否则我们可能会首先在经济上与中国发生冲突，随后是在地缘政治和军事层面上，这将给所有人带来一场的灾难。在这样的冲突中不会有赢家。而正是由于今天美国政治的极度肤浅和腐败，才使我们走上了这条路。
&#13;
与中国的贸易战无法解决我们的经济问题。相反，我们的经济问题需要“本土”的解决方案：负担得起的医疗保健、优质的学校、现代化的基础设施、提高最低工资标准和严惩企业的贪婪。在这个过程中，我们才会认识到，通过与中国合作，而非鲁莽不公的挑衅，才能让美国获得更多。
&#13;
（资料来源：美国有线电视新闻网（CNN））
&#13;
英文原文 ：微博
&#13;
Jeffrey Sachs is a professor and director of the Center for Sustainable Development at Columbia University. The opinions expressed in this commentary are those of the author; view more opinion articles on CNN. （May 27，2019）
&#13;
(CNN)China is not an enemy. It is a nation trying to raise its living standards through education, international trade, infrastructure investment, and improved technologies. In short, it is doing what any country should do when confronted with the historical reality of being poor and far behind more powerful countries. Yet the Trump administration is now aiming to stop China's development, which could prove to be disastrous for both the United States and the entire world.Jeffrey SachsJeffrey SachsChina is being made a scapegoat for rising inequality in the United States. While US trade relations with China have been mutually beneficial over the years, some US workers have been left behind, notably Midwestern factory workers facing competition due to rising productivity and comparatively low (though rising) labor costs in China. Instead of blaming China for this normal phenomenon of market competition, we should be taxing the soaring corporate profits of our own multinational corporations and using the revenues to help working-class households, rebuild crumbling infrastructure, promote new job skills and invest in cutting-edge science and technology.We should understand that China is merely trying to make up for lost time after a very long period of geopolitical setbacks and related economic failures. Here is important historical background that is useful to understand China's economic development in the past 40 years.In 1839, Britain attacked China because it refused to allow British traders to continue providing Chinese people with addictive opium. Britain prevailed, and the humiliation of China's defeat in the First Opium War, ending in 1842, contributed in part to a mass uprising against the Qing Dynasty called the Taiping Rebellion that ended up causing more than 20 million deaths. A Second Opium War against Britain and France ultimately led to the continued erosion of China's power and internal stability.Toward the end of the 19th century, China lost a war to the newly industrializing Japan, and was subjected to yet more one-sided demands by Europe and the United States for trade. These humiliations led to another rebellion, followed by yet another defeat,at the hands of foreign powers.ADVERTISINGinRead invented by TeadsChina's Qing Dynasty fell in 1911, after which China quickly succumbed to warlords, internal strife and Japan's invasion of China beginning in 1931. The end of World War II was followed by civil war, the creation of the People's Republic of China in 1949 and then the upheavals of Maoism, including millions of deaths from famine in the Great Leap Forward, which ended in the early 1960s, and the mass destabilization of the Cultural Revolutionand its aftermath until 1977.
&#13;
China's rapid development on a market basis therefore started only in 1978, when Deng Xiaoping came to power and launched sweeping economic reforms. While China has seen incredible growth in the past four decades, the legacy of more than a century of poverty, instability, invasion and foreign threats still looms large. Chinese leaders would like to get things right this time, and that means they are unwilling to bow to the United States or other Western powers again.China is now the second-largest economy in the world, when GDP is measured at market prices. Yet it is a country still in the process of catching up from poverty. In 1980, according toIMF data, China's GDP per capita was a mere 2.5% of the United States, and by 2018 had reached only 15.3% of the US level. When GDP is measured in purchasing-power-parity terms, by using a common set of "international prices" to value GDP in all countries, China's income per capita in 2018 was a bit higher at 28.9% of the United States. China has roughly followed the same development strategy as Japan, Korea, Taiwan, Hong Kong and Singapore before it. From an economic standpoint, it is not doing anything particularly unusual for a country that is playing catch up.The constant US refrain that China "steals" technologies is highly simplistic.Countries that are lagging behind upgrade their technologies in many ways, through study, imitation, purchases, mergers, foreign investments, extensive use of off-patent knowledge and, yes, copying. And with any fast-changing technologies, there are always running battles over intellectual property. That's true even among US companies today -- this kind of competition is simply a part of the global economic system. Technology leaders know they shouldn't count on keeping their lead through protection, but through continued innovation.
&#13;
The United States relentlessly adopted British technologies in the early 19th century. And when any country wants to close a technology gap, it recruits know-how from abroad. The US ballistic missile program, as it is well known, was built with the help of former Nazi rocket scientists recruited to the United States after World War II. If China were a less populous Asian country, say like South Korea, with a little more than 50 million people, it would simply be hailed by the United States as a great development success story -- which it is. But because it is so big, China refutes America's pretensions to run the world. The United States, after all, is a mere 4.2% of the world's population, less than a fourth of China's. The truth is that neither country is in a position to dominate the world today, as technologies and know-how are spreading more quickly across the globe than ever before.Trade with China provides the United States with low-cost consumer goods and increasingly high-quality products. It also causes job losses in sectors such as manufacturing that compete directly with China. That is how trade works. To accuse China of unfairness in this is wrong -- plenty of American companies have reaped the benefits of manufacturing in China or exporting goods there. And US consumers enjoy higher living standards as a result of China's low-cost goods. The US and China should continue to negotiate and develop improved rules for bilateral and multilateral trade instead of stoking a trade war with one-sided threats and over-the-top accusations. The most basic lesson of trade theory, practice and policy is not to stop trade -- which would lead to falling living standards, economic crisis and conflict. Instead, we should share the benefits of economic growth so that the winners who benefit compensate the losers.Yet under American capitalism, which has long strayed from the cooperative spirit of the New Deal era, today's winners flat-out reject sharing their winnings. As a result of this lack of sharing, American politics are fraught with conflicts over trade. Greed comprehensively dominates Washington policies.The real battle is not with China but with America's own giant companies, many of which are raking in fortunes while failing to pay their own workers decent wages. America's business leaders and the mega-rich push for tax cuts, more monopoly power and offshoring -- anything to make a bigger profit -- while rejecting any policies to make American society fairer.
&#13;
Trump is lashing out against China, ostensibly believing that it will once again bow to a Western power. It is willfully trying to crush successful companies like Huawei by changing the rules of international trade abruptly and unilaterally. China has been playing by Western rules for the past 40 years, gradually catching up the way that America's Asian allies did in the past. Now the United States is trying to pull the rug out from under China by launching a new Cold War.Unless some greater wisdom prevails, we could spin toward conflict with China, first economically, then geopolitically and militarily, with utter disaster for all. There will be no winners in such a conflict. Yet such is the profound shallowness and corruption of US politics today that we are on such a path.A trade war with China won't solve our economic problems. Instead we need homegrown solutions: affordable health care, better schools, modernized infrastructure, higher minimum wages and a crackdown on corporate greed. In the process, we would also learn that we have far more to gain through cooperation with China rather than reckless and unfair provocation.​​​​                        </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>撒撒: </b><br>
<span>【ZT】中国并非美国经济问题的根源，企业的贪婪才是</span><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 撒撒 于 2019-5-30 16:58 编辑 </span><br>
<span>中文翻译：肖准（译） 财经园地（公众号）</span><br>
<span>（原作：杰弗里·萨克斯）</span><br>
<span>中国不是美国的敌人。中国是一个试图通过教育、国际贸易、基础设施投资和改进技术来提高生活水平的国家。简单来说，它（中国）正在做的事，是任何国家在面对贫穷且远远落后于更强大国家的历史现实时应做之事。然而，特朗普政府现在的目标是阻止中国的发展，这可能对美国和整个世界都是灾难性的。</span><br>
<span>中国正在成为美国不平等加剧的替罪羊。虽然美国与中国的贸易关系多年来一直是互惠互利的，但一些美国工人却产生了失落感，特别是中西部工厂的工人由于生产力提高和中国的劳动力成本相对较低（虽然也在上升）而面临竞争。我们不应该将这种正常的市场竞争所带来的后果归咎于中国，而应该对本国的跨国公司高涨的企业利润征税，并把税收用于帮助工薪阶层家庭，重建摇摇欲坠的基础设施，帮助工人掌握新的工作技能，并投资于尖端科技。</span><br>
<span>我们应该明白，在遭遇长期地缘政治挫折以及经济发展失利后，中国只是在努力弥补失去的时间。这一重要的历史背景，有助于理解中国过去40年的经济发展。</span><br>
<span>1839年，英国攻打中国，因为它拒绝允许英国商人继续向中国人提供成瘾的 鸦 片 。英国占了上风，使中国在1842年结束的第一次 鸦 片 战争中蒙受失败的耻辱，并在一定程度上促成反抗清朝统治的大规模起义，史称太平天国起义，这场起义最终导致超过2000万人死亡。随后抗击英法的第二次 鸦 片 战争从根本上动摇了中国政权和内部稳定。</span><br>
<span>到了19世纪末，中国在一场战争（甲午战争）中输给了刚刚工业化的日本，并被迫接受了欧洲和美国对贸易更多单方面的要求。这些耻辱导致了另一场反抗（义和团运动），随后又遭到外国势力的镇压。</span><br>
<span>中国的清朝政府于1911年垮台，此后中国又罹患军阀、内乱和日本1931年对中国的入侵。第二次世界大战结束后，随之而来的是内战，1949年中华人民共和国成立，然后毛泽东思想给中国带来了剧变，其间发生了大跃进中上百万人死于饥馑（1960年代初期结束），以及之后的群众运动，其余波一直持续到1977年。</span><br>
<span>因此，中国以市场为基础的快速发展始于1978年，当时邓小平开始担任领导工作并开展了全面的经济改革。虽然中国经济在过去四十年中取得了令人难以置信的增长，但一个多世纪以来的贫穷、动荡、外敌入侵和外来威胁的后患仍然不时萦绕在中国人的心头。中国领导人希望这次能公平地解决贸易争端，这意味着他们不愿再次向美国或其他西方国家屈服。</span><br>
<span>如果GDP按市场价格计算，中国现在是世界第二大经济体。然而，中国仍是一个正在摆脱贫困的国家。1980年，根据国际货币基金组织的数据，中国人均GDP仅为美国的2.5%，到2018年仅为美国的15.3%。如按购买力平价计算，通过使用一组相同的“国际价格”来衡量各国的国内生产总值，中国2018年的人均收入略高于美国的28.9％。</span><br>
<span>中国大致遵循与日本、韩国、台湾、香港和新加坡相同的发展战略。从经济的角度来看，对于一个正在追赶的国家来说，中国并没有做什么特别不寻常的事情。美国一再重申中国“窃取”技术，这是非常幼稚的。</span><br>
<span>相对落后国家要想进行技术升级，往往会通过学习、模仿、购买、兼并、外国投资、广泛使用非专利技术以及复制等多种方法。而随着科技飞速变化，在知识产权问题上总是会产生争端。即使如今的美国公司同样会出现这样的情况——这种竞争只是全球经济体系的一部分。技术引领者们都知道，他们应通过不断创新，而不是保护（现有技术）来保持领先地位。</span><br>
<span>美国在19世纪初就坚持采用英国的技术。当任何一个国家想要缩小技术差距时，它都会从国外引进专门技术。众所周知，美国的弹道导弹计划是在二战后被招募到美国的前纳粹火箭科学家的帮助下完成的。</span><br>
<span>如果中国是一个人口较少的亚洲国家，比如韩国，只有5000多万人，那么美国仅仅把它誉为一个了不起的发展成功故事 - 当然事实也是这样。但由于中国的体量如此之大，它不啻击碎了美国统治世界的玻璃心。毕竟，美国仅占世界人口的4.2％，不到中国的四分之一。事实是，由于专业技术知识在全球范围内的传播速度比以往任何时候都快，因此这两个国家都无法主宰当今世界。</span><br>
<span>与中国的贸易为美国提供了低成本的消费品和更高质量的产品。它还会导致与中国直接竞争的制造业等部门的失业。这就是贸易的必然结果。单方面指责中国不公平贸易行为是错误的——许多美国公司已经从中国制造业或中国的出口商品中获益。由于中国的廉价商品，美国消费者享有更高的生活水平。美国和中国应该继续就完善双边和多边贸易规则进行谈判和阐释各自的意见，而不是用单方面的威胁和过分的指责来引发贸易战。</span><br>
<span>贸易理论、实践和政策的最主要教训不是停止贸易 - 这将导致生活水平下降、经济危机和冲突。相反，我们应该分享经济增长带来的好处，这样获利的赢家就可以补偿输家。</span><br>
<span>然而，在美国资本主义制度下，由于长期缺乏（罗斯福）新政时期的合作精神，如今的赢家们都不愿分享他们的胜利果实。由于不愿分享，美国政治总会在贸易问题上产生冲突。企业的贪婪全面支配着华盛顿政策。</span><br>
<span>美国真正的战斗不是与中国，而是与美国自己的大企业。这些大企业中，许多都在赚大钱的同时，没有给自己的员工支付体面的薪水。美国的商业领袖和超级富豪努力争取减税、更多的垄断力量和产业转移——总之一切可以获取更多利润的东西——同时却拒绝任何可以促使美国社会更加公平的政策。</span><br>
<span>特朗普正在抨击中国，自信中国会再次屈服于西方的力量。它试图通过突然和单方面地改变国际贸易规则来蓄意挤压像华为这样成功公司的生存空间。过去40年来，中国一直遵循西方的规则，逐渐步入美国亚洲盟国过去的发展道路。现在，美国正试图通过发动新的冷战对中国釜底抽薪。</span><br>
<span>除非理性能够占据上风，否则我们可能会首先在经济上与中国发生冲突，随后是在地缘政治和军事层面上，这将给所有人带来一场的灾难。在这样的冲突中不会有赢家。而正是由于今天美国政治的极度肤浅和腐败，才使我们走上了这条路。</span><br>
<span>与中国的贸易战无法解决我们的经济问题。相反，我们的经济问题需要“本土”的解决方案：负担得起的医疗保健、优质的学校、现代化的基础设施、提高最低工资标准和严惩企业的贪婪。在这个过程中，我们才会认识到，通过与中国合作，而非鲁莽不公的挑衅，才能让美国获得更多。</span><br>
<span>（资料来源：美国有线电视新闻网（CNN））</span><br>
<span>英文原文 ：微博</span><br>
<span>Jeffrey Sachs is a professor and director of the Center for Sustainable Development at Columbia University. The opinions expressed in this commentary are those of the author; view more opinion articles on CNN. （May 27，2019）</span><br>
<span>(CNN)China is not an enemy. It is a nation trying to raise its living standards through education, international trade, infrastructure investment, and improved technologies. In short, it is doing what any country should do when confronted with the historical reality of being poor and far behind more powerful countries. Yet the Trump administration is now aiming to stop China's development, which could prove to be disastrous for both the United States and the entire world.Jeffrey SachsJeffrey SachsChina is being made a scapegoat for rising inequality in the United States. While US trade relations with China have been mutually beneficial over the years, some US workers have been left behind, notably Midwestern factory workers facing competition due to rising productivity and comparatively low (though rising) labor costs in China. Instead of blaming China for this normal phenomenon of market competition, we should be taxing the soaring corporate profits of our own multinational corporations and using the revenues to help working-class households, rebuild crumbling infrastructure, promote new job skills and invest in cutting-edge science and technology.We should understand that China is merely trying to make up for lost time after a very long period of geopolitical setbacks and related economic failures. Here is important historical background that is useful to understand China's economic development in the past 40 years.In 1839, Britain attacked China because it refused to allow British traders to continue providing Chinese people with addictive opium. Britain prevailed, and the humiliation of China's defeat in the First Opium War, ending in 1842, contributed in part to a mass uprising against the Qing Dynasty called the Taiping Rebellion that ended up causing more than 20 million deaths. A Second Opium War against Britain and France ultimately led to the continued erosion of China's power and internal stability.Toward the end of the 19th century, China lost a war to the newly industrializing Japan, and was subjected to yet more one-sided demands by Europe and the United States for trade. These humiliations led to another rebellion, followed by yet another defeat,at the hands of foreign powers.ADVERTISINGinRead invented by TeadsChina's Qing Dynasty fell in 1911, after which China quickly succumbed to warlords, internal strife and Japan's invasion of China beginning in 1931. The end of World War II was followed by civil war, the creation of the People's Republic of China in 1949 and then the upheavals of Maoism, including millions of deaths from famine in the Great Leap Forward, which ended in the early 1960s, and the mass destabilization of the Cultural Revolutionand its aftermath until 1977.</span><br>
<span>China's rapid development on a market basis therefore started only in 1978, when Deng Xiaoping came to power and launched sweeping economic reforms. While China has seen incredible growth in the past four decades, the legacy of more than a century of poverty, instability, invasion and foreign threats still looms large. Chinese leaders would like to get things right this time, and that means they are unwilling to bow to the United States or other Western powers again.China is now the second-largest economy in the world, when GDP is measured at market prices. Yet it is a country still in the process of catching up from poverty. In 1980, according toIMF data, China's GDP per capita was a mere 2.5% of the United States, and by 2018 had reached only 15.3% of the US level. When GDP is measured in purchasing-power-parity terms, by using a common set of "international prices" to value GDP in all countries, China's income per capita in 2018 was a bit higher at 28.9% of the United States. China has roughly followed the same development strategy as Japan, Korea, Taiwan, Hong Kong and Singapore before it. From an economic standpoint, it is not doing anything particularly unusual for a country that is playing catch up.The constant US refrain that China "steals" technologies is highly simplistic.Countries that are lagging behind upgrade their technologies in many ways, through study, imitation, purchases, mergers, foreign investments, extensive use of off-patent knowledge and, yes, copying. And with any fast-changing technologies, there are always running battles over intellectual property. That's true even among US companies today -- this kind of competition is simply a part of the global economic system. Technology leaders know they shouldn't count on keeping their lead through protection, but through continued innovation.</span><br>
<span>The United States relentlessly adopted British technologies in the early 19th century. And when any country wants to close a technology gap, it recruits know-how from abroad. The US ballistic missile program, as it is well known, was built with the help of former Nazi rocket scientists recruited to the United States after World War II. If China were a less populous Asian country, say like South Korea, with a little more than 50 million people, it would simply be hailed by the United States as a great development success story -- which it is. But because it is so big, China refutes America's pretensions to run the world. The United States, after all, is a mere 4.2% of the world's population, less than a fourth of China's. The truth is that neither country is in a position to dominate the world today, as technologies and know-how are spreading more quickly across the globe than ever before.Trade with China provides the United States with low-cost consumer goods and increasingly high-quality products. It also causes job losses in sectors such as manufacturing that compete directly with China. That is how trade works. To accuse China of unfairness in this is wrong -- plenty of American companies have reaped the benefits of manufacturing in China or exporting goods there. And US consumers enjoy higher living standards as a result of China's low-cost goods. The US and China should continue to negotiate and develop improved rules for bilateral and multilateral trade instead of stoking a trade war with one-sided threats and over-the-top accusations. The most basic lesson of trade theory, practice and policy is not to stop trade -- which would lead to falling living standards, economic crisis and conflict. Instead, we should share the benefits of economic growth so that the winners who benefit compensate the losers.Yet under American capitalism, which has long strayed from the cooperative spirit of the New Deal era, today's winners flat-out reject sharing their winnings. As a result of this lack of sharing, American politics are fraught with conflicts over trade. Greed comprehensively dominates Washington policies.The real battle is not with China but with America's own giant companies, many of which are raking in fortunes while failing to pay their own workers decent wages. America's business leaders and the mega-rich push for tax cuts, more monopoly power and offshoring -- anything to make a bigger profit -- while rejecting any policies to make American society fairer.</span><br>
<span>Trump is lashing out against China, ostensibly believing that it will once again bow to a Western power. It is willfully trying to crush successful companies like Huawei by changing the rules of international trade abruptly and unilaterally. China has been playing by Western rules for the past 40 years, gradually catching up the way that America's Asian allies did in the past. Now the United States is trying to pull the rug out from under China by launching a new Cold War.Unless some greater wisdom prevails, we could spin toward conflict with China, first economically, then geopolitically and militarily, with utter disaster for all. There will be no winners in such a conflict. Yet such is the profound shallowness and corruption of US politics today that we are on such a path.A trade war with China won't solve our economic problems. Instead we need homegrown solutions: affordable health care, better schools, modernized infrastructure, higher minimum wages and a crackdown on corporate greed. In the process, we would also learn that we have far more to gain through cooperation with China rather than reckless and unfair provocation.​​​​                        </span><br>
</p><p><b>kuanyesine: </b><br>
<span>川皇能想得明白，就不会现在这样了</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 samsung SM-N9600, Android 8.1.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>TuzDoDez: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 TuzDoDez 于 2019-5-30 16:49 编辑 </span><br>
<span>这个作者是很清醒的，可惜这篇文章几乎把美国人都得罪光了，明白说就是资本家贪婪，民众愚昧，政客媚选票，唯一没有得罪的就是中国人。</span><br>
</p><p><b>SoulSpenser: </b><br>
<span>CNN </span><br>
</p><p><b>cishta: </b><br>
<span>川黄要fire他！</span><br>
</p><p><b>faust123: </b><br>
<span>其实咱们这何尝不是</span><br>
<span>这一制裁，都没人提996了</span><br>
<span>都是草台~</span><br>
</p><p><b>scourge411: </b><br>
<span>越来越多的人开始意识到，拯救当今世界的唯一手段是杀资本家</span><br>
</p><p><b>ivanwhite2: </b><br>
<span>scourge411 发表于 2019-5-30 17:00</span><br>
<span>越来越多的人开始意识到，拯救当今世界的唯一手段是杀资本家</span><br>
<span>一个幽灵</span><br>
</p><p><b>点点杠: </b><br>
<span>资本家就是坏有什么好说得</span><br>
</p><p><b>张绣: </b><br>
<span>美国必须大大的战败一次，然后华尔街那批遥控美国国家机器的犹太佬必须被清理一次，否则美国周期性想吸外国血的臭毛病改不了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>Kozakai: </b><br>
<span>还记得马克思是怎么说资本家的么</span><br>
</p><p><b>yych0611: </b><br>
<span>罗斯福当年到第三个任期和独裁者也没啥区别了，怎么有的比……</span><br>
</p><p><b>ydd-319: </b><br>
<span>TuzDoDez 发表于 2019-5-30 16:46</span><br>
<span>这个作者是很清醒的，可惜这篇文章几乎把美国人都得罪光了，明白说就是资本家贪婪，民众愚昧，政客媚选票， ...</span><br>
<span>资本家贪婪，民众愚昧</span><br>
<span>这两条放之四海。。。</span><br>
</p><p><b>有口皆悲: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 有口皆悲 于 2019-5-30 17:11 编辑 </span><br>
<span>主楼特地强调了新中国刚成立就陷入了maoism动乱中，maoism是新中国前三十年贫困的万恶之源，还是怕鹅们杀资本家。鼓励的是资本家杀资本家。</span><br>
</p><p><b>咲衣憧: </b><br>
<span>这文章我真怀疑是不是美国人写的</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HUAWEI VCE-AL00, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>fenugreek: </b><br>
<span>把资本家吊路灯是全球共识，现在才知道列宁主义宝贵，晚了</span><br>
</p><p><b>敖轩: </b><br>
<span>《GTAV》里老麦推那个富豪下悬崖之前怎么说的？</span><br>
<span>“2样东西毁掉了美国：跨境利润和外包。”</span><br>
</p><p><b>饿梦: </b><br>
<span>问题是现在不仅是特朗普这样想，普通美国佬也是这样想，甚至全世界的白皮都这样想</span><br>
</p><p><b>關羽: </b><br>
<span>萨克斯可惜了。经常来中国进行访问交流，对中国改开以来说经验比较了解的美国人了，可惜美国现在能冷静听下去的人不多了。有这群媒体我估计也不会让这群民粹冷静。</span><br>
</p><p><b>杨松: </b><br>
<span>张绣 发表于 2019-5-30 17:04</span><br>
<span>美国必须大大的战败一次，然后华尔街那批遥控美国国家机器的犹太佬必须被清理一次，否则美国周期性想吸外国 ...</span><br>
<span>换句话说是当年元首干得不够漂亮</span><br>
</p><p><b>pilipala: </b><br>
<span>ydd-319 发表于 2019-05-30 17:07:10</span><br>
<span>资本家贪婪，民众愚昧</span><br>
<span>这两条放之四海。。。再加一个，官僚颟顸</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>powwow: </b><br>
<span>在全员狂热中，这么清醒的美国人真是太难得</span><br>
</p><p><b>にまぴ: </b><br>
<span>powwow 发表于 2019-5-30 21:38</span><br>
<span>在全员狂热中，这么清醒的美国人真是太难得</span><br>
<span>搜了一下，他是休克疗法的发明人，不一样的啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>alerbe: </b><br>
<span>にまぴ 发表于 2019-5-30 21:41</span><br>
<span>搜了一下，他是休克疗法的发明人，不一样的啊</span><br>
<span>休克疗法不是需要额外的资金吗，波兰拿到了，俄罗斯么就没给吧。</span><br>
</p><p><b>にまぴ: </b><br>
<span>alerbe 发表于 2019-5-30 21:48</span><br>
<span>休克疗法不是需要额外的资金吗，波兰拿到了，俄罗斯么就没给吧。</span><br>
<span>对啊。所以别的国家成功了，就俄罗斯暴死了</span><br>
</p><p><b>mu1: </b><br>
<span>很清醒的文，然而连人家一美国人都了解义和团是中国人内部的愤怒反抗的本质，泥潭却还有一群人见义和团就喷的</span><br>
</p><p><b>nuick: </b><br>
<span>TuzDoDez 发表于 2019-5-30 16:46</span><br>
<span>这个作者是很清醒的，可惜这篇文章几乎把美国人都得罪光了，明白说就是资本家贪婪，民众愚昧，政客媚选票， ...</span><br>
<span>可是中国的资本家更坏更贪婪阿</span><br>
</p><p><b>瘦猫标题学: </b><br>
<span>萨克斯在休克疗法这事上被欧美联合坑了一把以后就跟美国政府各种不对付，他算是难得的，站在中国这边的经济学家</span><br>
</p><p><b>日照: </b><br>
<span>所以我认为川普班农这些人都是共产分子，最大的特征否定私人财产比如工作机会、企业利益，用一个虚假的借口（你们的工作被中国人抢走了）来制造矛盾对立和冲突，以此挑动斗争获取政治利益，跟土改完全如出一辙。这些人若是成功，将是美国精神西方价值的重大失败。</span><br>
</p><p><b>kpkxyshlyj: </b><br>
<span>其实就这么回事儿 中美贸易大部分收益被美国资本家拿走 然后不拿回美国国内进行再分配 搞得我们又苦逼打工没多少钱赚又背锅拉仇恨 然后为了"与国际水平看齐" 我们还得动不动减税让利 真是有毒</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi Mi MIX 2, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>aoick: </b><br>
<span>所以说有生之年我们还能看到吊资本家路灯吗</span><br>
</p><p><b>pilipala: </b><br>
<span>aoick 发表于 2019-5-30 23:03</span><br>
<span>所以说有生之年我们还能看到吊资本家路灯吗</span><br>
<span>上面的大佬需要资本家。</span><br>
<span>毕竟靠下面一群官僚来管企业，实在太不靠谱啦！</span><br>
</p><p><b>hellgate22: </b><br>
<span>nuick 发表于 2019-5-30 21:53</span><br>
<span>可是中国的资本家更坏更贪婪阿</span><br>
<span>全球资本家都一样草菅人命，没看出来中国的资本家有什么更坏的地方</span><br>
</p><p><b>KUSOSO: </b><br>
<span>啊，这个人看的透彻啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>dlboy1981: </b><br>
<span>古代杀资本家容易，现在难喽</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1835636[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
