<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>雄性长颈鹿中竟有94％个体为同♂性恋？</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>雄性长颈鹿中竟有94％个体为同♂性恋？</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 20:20:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>雄性长颈鹿中竟有94％个体为同♂性恋？[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1833999-1-1.html</link>
      <description>雄性长颈鹿中竟有94％个体为同♂性恋？&#13;
长颈鹿是陆地上最高的动物，因其长而优美的颈部而著称。传统观念认为，长颈鹿的颈部是其展示力量及地位的重要部分。雄性间会通过用颈部互相撕打，以争夺交配权。

吸引异性、繁衍后代是自然界中雄性斗争的永恒主题。不同的是，很多情况下，经过一番激烈战斗后，两只雄性长颈鹿会进行交配。

据观察，雄性长颈鹿之间最常见的关系是颈部摩擦及肛♂交。

在一份报告中，研究人员花费3200小时在坦桑尼亚野外观察长颈鹿行为。他们一共记录到16例雄性间发生性行为的例子。

由于雄长颈鹿与雌长颈鹿通常各自组成群体生活，而同性性行为一般发生在雄性中。研究人员最初认为这是群体间彰显地位的象征，类似于猴群中地位底下个体会主动向高地位个体抓挠虱子，然而没有充分证据证明。

同一时期，研究人员只看到一对雌雄长颈鹿发生交配行为。该报告认为，约有94%的雄性长颈鹿具有同性倾向。

值得指出，观察期间，该地区一共新生22只小长颈鹿。证明有许多交配行为被遗漏。从比例而言，意味着有更多的雄性长颈鹿同性♂恋案例未被记录。

研究发现，雄性长颈鹿很少主动向雌性长颈鹿寻求交配。只有在发情期时，雌性长颈鹿尿液会散发出一种性激素，吸引附近的雄性靠近。这些雄长颈鹿会尾随雌性几天，直到它从中选择一名合适的配偶。

即使处于严谨的科学角度，也可以确定的说，绝大多数雄性长颈鹿是“男同性♂恋者”。

自然界中的同性性行为显然是一种有意义的行为，并非建立在雌性缺乏或群体压制上。尽管我们对此原理了解并不多。

许多物种身上都观察过同性性行为；绿头鸭、野牛、亚马逊河豚、绵羊、海豚、企鹅、倭黑猩猩、灰雁等等。来自长颈鹿上的发现并不稀奇，但长颈鹿可能是已知“同性♂恋率”最高的动物。

“同性♂恋”的确是进化上的谜团，有关研究其背后的动机尚未清楚。可以确信的是，这种行为已经在自然界存在很长一段时间，且并没被淘汰。

一部分观点认为，同性关系会带给雄性间坚实的纽带，使得它们在与其他雄性竞争时更具有优势，也能够获得更多的交配机会，将基因传递给后代。

另一部分观点提出，自然界中的同性♂恋实际上是一种“亲缘选择”。同性伴侣可能通过一系列特定的行为；如抚养其他同类后代、保护群体免受捕食者的伤害等，实现基因上的延续。即一部分个体放弃自身繁育权，以提高整体成活率，通过兄弟姐妹的后代，将自身基因传递。</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>牙髓坏死: </b><br>
<span>雄性长颈鹿中竟有94％个体为同♂性恋？</span><br>
<span>长颈鹿是陆地上最高的动物，因其长而优美的颈部而著称。传统观念认为，长颈鹿的颈部是其展示力量及地位的重要部分。雄性间会通过用颈部互相撕打，以争夺交配权。</span><br>
<span>吸引异性、繁衍后代是自然界中雄性斗争的永恒主题。不同的是，很多情况下，经过一番激烈战斗后，两只雄性长颈鹿会进行交配。</span><br>
<span>据观察，雄性长颈鹿之间最常见的关系是颈部摩擦及肛♂交。</span><br>
<span>在一份报告中，研究人员花费3200小时在坦桑尼亚野外观察长颈鹿行为。他们一共记录到16例雄性间发生性行为的例子。</span><br>
<span>由于雄长颈鹿与雌长颈鹿通常各自组成群体生活，而同性性行为一般发生在雄性中。研究人员最初认为这是群体间彰显地位的象征，类似于猴群中地位底下个体会主动向高地位个体抓挠虱子，然而没有充分证据证明。</span><br>
<span>同一时期，研究人员只看到一对雌雄长颈鹿发生交配行为。该报告认为，约有94%的雄性长颈鹿具有同性倾向。</span><br>
<span>值得指出，观察期间，该地区一共新生22只小长颈鹿。证明有许多交配行为被遗漏。从比例而言，意味着有更多的雄性长颈鹿同性♂恋案例未被记录。</span><br>
<span>研究发现，雄性长颈鹿很少主动向雌性长颈鹿寻求交配。只有在发情期时，雌性长颈鹿尿液会散发出一种性激素，吸引附近的雄性靠近。这些雄长颈鹿会尾随雌性几天，直到它从中选择一名合适的配偶。</span><br>
<span>即使处于严谨的科学角度，也可以确定的说，绝大多数雄性长颈鹿是“男同性♂恋者”。</span><br>
<span>自然界中的同性性行为显然是一种有意义的行为，并非建立在雌性缺乏或群体压制上。尽管我们对此原理了解并不多。</span><br>
<span>许多物种身上都观察过同性性行为；绿头鸭、野牛、亚马逊河豚、绵羊、海豚、企鹅、倭黑猩猩、灰雁等等。来自长颈鹿上的发现并不稀奇，但长颈鹿可能是已知“同性♂恋率”最高的动物。</span><br>
<span>“同性♂恋”的确是进化上的谜团，有关研究其背后的动机尚未清楚。可以确信的是，这种行为已经在自然界存在很长一段时间，且并没被淘汰。</span><br>
<span>一部分观点认为，同性关系会带给雄性间坚实的纽带，使得它们在与其他雄性竞争时更具有优势，也能够获得更多的交配机会，将基因传递给后代。</span><br>
<span>另一部分观点提出，自然界中的同性♂恋实际上是一种“亲缘选择”。同性伴侣可能通过一系列特定的行为；如抚养其他同类后代、保护群体免受捕食者的伤害等，实现基因上的延续。即一部分个体放弃自身繁育权，以提高整体成活率，通过兄弟姐妹的后代，将自身基因传递。</span><br>
</p><p><b>七月飞沙: </b><br>
<span>动物根本就没有恋这个概念好吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>神秘男子A: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 神秘男子A 于 2019-5-24 12:24 编辑 </span><br>
<span>统计群落的问题。拿猴子举例，我记得之前看过一个纪录片，中心群落的猴王占据了大部分的母猴，周边群落里面有健壮的雄性公猴和次等的母猴作为卫戍护卫集团。然后边缘是被赶出的年轻公猴组成的最低级团体，只能以捡拾垃圾为食。</span><br>
<span>那种年轻公猴卢瑟群体是不会有母猴的，一般都是偷袭落单的母猴而且很快会被赶出。这样的群体中，公猴会由于交配繁殖的欲望而攻击同性并发生行为。</span><br>
<span>我觉得这个观察就是只盯着这种特殊卢瑟群体然后得出的不正确结论。最好是能提供研究原文，统计方法统计数据，甚至研究赞助机构。</span><br>
</p><p><b>古屋敷由良: </b><br>
<span>这长颈鹿是古罗马式吧，雌性只管生育，雄性互相施放斗争欲和性欲</span><br>
</p><p><b>传说级死亡爪: </b><br>
<span>牙髓坏死 发表于 2019-5-24 12:12</span><br>
<span>长颈鹿是陆地上最高的动物，因其长而优美的颈部而著称。传统观念认为，长颈鹿的颈部是其展示力量及地位的重 ...</span><br>
<span>搞兔子不是长颈鹿他想搞兔子，而是不得不搞兔子</span><br>
</p><p><b>烤烤鱼ω: </b><br>
<span>神秘男子A 发表于 2019-5-24 12:21</span><br>
<span>统计群落的问题。拿猴子举例，我记得之前看过一个纪录片，中心群落的猴王占据了大部分的母猴，周边群落里面 ...</span><br>
<span>这个研究考虑了你的观点，“并非建立在雌性缺乏或群体压制上”</span><br>
</p><p><b>跃渊: </b><br>
<span>动物只是被性欲驱使才会去交配的吧，只有人类才是把生殖作为交配的主要目的的(传统观念)，那么只要能解决性欲，动物才不会管它干的是雄性还是咬掉头的鲑鱼呢</span><br>
</p><p><b>Sliark: </b><br>
<span>わかります？</span><br>
</p><p><b>木棉: </b><br>
<span>我懂了</span><br>
</p><p><b>冰冻火柴: </b><br>
<span>怪不得长颈鹿这么懂</span><br>
</p><p><b>神秘男子A: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 神秘男子A 于 2019-5-24 13:13 编辑 </span><br>
<span>烤烤鱼ω 发表于 2019-5-24 12:53</span><br>
<span>这个研究考虑了你的观点，“并非建立在雌性缺乏或群体压制上”</span><br>
<span>原文提供一下</span><br>
<span>原文如下：自然界中的同性性行为显然是一种有意义的行为，并非建立在雌性缺乏或群体压制上。尽管我们对此原理了解并不多。</span><br>
<span>但这句话不是针对该项研究报告的说明。请提供该研究报告原文，研究过程方式，以及研究经费来源方式。</span><br>
</p><p><b>烤烤鱼ω: </b><br>
<span>神秘男子A 发表于 2019-5-24 13:09</span><br>
<span>原文提供一下</span><br>
<span>原文如下：自然界中的同性性行为显然是一种有意义的行为，并非建立在雌性缺乏或群体压制上。 ...</span><br>
<span>hmmm，我当他是说明才这么说的。认真要找的话，才注意到没名没姓没出处，看来有点可疑。暂时也没找到别的相关报道。倒是发现有种叫长颈鹿的亚文化圈是高个gay的</span><br>
</p><p><b>talesof213: </b><br>
<span>看到这个标题莫名其妙地想到生化6</span><br>
</p><p><b>韩子: </b><br>
<span>所以那个有名的长颈鹿用脖子打架gif，其实不是打架，而是在亲热………？</span><br>
</p><p><b>gstsg: </b><br>
<span>烤烤鱼ω 发表于 2019-5-24 12:53</span><br>
<span>这个研究考虑了你的观点，“并非建立在雌性缺乏或群体压制上”</span><br>
<span>你好，“并非建立在雌性缺乏或群体压制上”这句指的应该是“自然界中的同性性行为显然是一种有意义的行为”而非文章所具体观察的长颈鹿群落吧。</span><br>
</p><p><b>烤烤鱼ω: </b><br>
<span>gstsg 发表于 2019-5-24 21:57</span><br>
<span>你好，“并非建立在雌性缺乏或群体压制上”这句指的应该是“自然界中的同性性行为显然是一种有意义的行为 ...</span><br>
<span>唔，仔细看，你说的是对的，这句比较泛指。不过紧跟着上面谈到的长颈鹿性行为，是把长颈鹿作为一种例证吧。如果他们只在发情期才去找雌鹿，那平时的行为是应该跟雌性缺乏关系不大了。</span><br>
<span>我找这个的出处，目前在一个问答网站找到</span><br>
<span>https://skeptics.stackexchange.com/questions/8420/is-94-of-male-giraffe-sexual-behaviour-homosexual</span><br>
<span>00年或是99年出版的一本书，Biological Exuberance: Animal Homosexuality and Natural Diversity，作者Bruce Bagemihl，可以下到epub或mobi版。34页有一段</span><br>
<span>Three different species exemplify some of the issues that are involved in just one measure of frequency, the proportion of activity that is homosexual. Observed versus actually occurring behaviors in Giraffes, seasonal variations in sexual activity in Mountain Sheep, and alternative standards of reference in Gray Herons complicate the calculation of homosexual frequency in each of these species. During an exhaustive study of Giraffes in the Arush and Tarangire National Parks of Tanzania, researchers recorded 17 homosexual mounts and 1 heterosexual mount in more than a year (and 3,200 hours) of observation. Thus, 94 percent of all observed mounting activity was same-sex. Does this reflect the actual proportion of homosexual activity in Giraffes? Certainly more than on heterosexual mating occurred during that time, since over 20 calves were born that year in one population alone. However, these populations did have relatively low birth rates, and heterosexual mating appeared to be genuinely rare. In addition, if heterosexual matings were missed by the observers, probably homosexual ones were as well.</span><br>
<span>有一条脚注提到更早的文献</span><br>
<span>Giraffe (Pratt and Anderson 1985, 1982, 1979). In a study of another population of giraffes, only three mounts between males were recorded, but only 400 hours of observation were involved (Dagg and Foster 1976:124).</span><br>
</p><p><b>妖刀斩红玥: </b><br>
<span>我day到了</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>rubicon: </b><br>
<span>会得艾滋病吗</span><br>
</p><p><b>Megumiillusion: </b><br>
<span>我就知道肯定有少歌梗</span><br>
</p><p><b>神秘男子A: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 神秘男子A 于 2019-5-26 08:12 编辑 </span><br>
<span>烤烤鱼ω 发表于 2019-5-25 18:33</span><br>
<span>唔，仔细看，你说的是对的，这句比较泛指。不过紧跟着上面谈到的长颈鹿性行为，是把长颈鹿作为一种例证吧 ...</span><br>
<span>I looked up the sources mentioned above:</span><br>
<span>Pratt DM and VH Anderson. 1982. Population, distribution and behavior of giraffe in the Arusha National Park, Tanzania. Journal of Natural History 16 pp481-489</span><br>
<span>This article is about population data collected over a year of observation. It mentions there have been 22 births in that year, a low birth rate considering the population included 172 females. It says nothing about mating or homosexual behavior.</span><br>
<span>Pratt DM and VH Anderson. 1985. Giraffe social behavior. Journal of Natural History 19 pp771-781.</span><br>
<span>This article summarizes the authors' observations and statistics of social interaction in giraffes, collected in three separate national parks in Northen Tanzania, over about 3 years of total (non-consecutive) observations, more precisely 3264 hours of observation. They mention that they integrate findings from the '79 and the '82 articles in this summary article.</span><br>
<span>They say that sparring bouts, which usually involve "necking", when giraffes swing their necks and hit each other with them, sometimes included one male attempting to mount another. "We saw this eight times in the Arusha Park and eight times at Tarangire. In nine of these 16 events, the animal attempting to mount had his penis unsheathed. [...] In no case did a bull try to mount another male as large as himself. Intent observation and detailed recording of positions and movements failed to show that this act was an expression of dominance (which we initially surmised); we never saw any indications---e.g., behavioural, postural--of submission in bulls mounted."</span><br>
<span>The article goes on to discuss courtship and mating. It appears that it's very rare for giraffes to actually mate. The female is in heat only one day out of every two weeks. The males test females for readiness by sniffing their urine, but the female can choose who to give this data (by choosing to urinate or not when the male lowers his head to her rump). When a male giraffe senses that a female is in the right condition, they may proceed to courtship, which involved 1-2 days worth of following her closely and occasionally attempting to mount, which the female usually frustrates by just walking forward. When the female chooses to stand still, the mounting will proceed. The researchers note with some exasperation that over their 3 years of observation, they only saw one successful mounting, out of 46 courtship attempts and 304 urine-sniffing attempts. In light of the fact that in one of these years 22 calves were born as discussed in the previous article, they must have missed many - but of course they could also miss many homosexual mounting attempts.</span><br>
<span>Dagg, AI and Foester JB. 1976. The giraffe, its biology, behavior and ecology. New York, Van Nostrand Reinhold.</span><br>
<span>This book briefly mentions that homosexual mounting was frequent (no numbers) in one park where the number of females was unusually low, about 30%; in another park with approximate parity between the sexes, it was much more rare, and they only saw 3 attempts in 400 hours of observation.</span><br>
<span>"Necking" is not treated as homosexual behavior by any of these sources; they mention that necking is reserved only for males, and seems related to dominance relationships between males.</span><br>
<span>My conclusion from all this is that although it's arithmetically true that in 3 years of observation, the authors of the '85 source saw 16 homosexual mountings and just one mating, it might be misleading to summarize that as "94% of sexual activity is homosexual". First, the observation apparently missed the vast majority of matings, and probably of homosexual mounting as well. Second, the male giraffes seemed interested in much more coupling, but the menstrual cycle and female refusal combined to give them only incredibly rare opportunities.</span><br>
<span>Bagemihl cites 3 sources of which bibliographic particulars were not available. I believe it is:</span><br>
<span>Pratt DM and VH Anderson. 1982. Population, distribution and behavior of giraffe in the Arusha National Park, Tanzania. Journal of Natural History 16 pp481-489</span><br>
<span>Pratt DM and VH Anderson. 1985. Giraffe social behavior. Journal of Natural History 19 pp771-781. I do not see an article by Pratt and anderson in 1979.</span><br>
<span>Dagg, AI and Foester JB. 1976. The giraffe, its biology, behavior and ecology. New York, Van Nostrand Reinhold.</span><br>
<span>The source:</span><br>
<span>Simmons RE and Scheepers L. 1996. Winning by a neck: sexual selection in the evolution of Giraffe. The American Naturalist 148(5) pp781-786.</span><br>
<span>The figure of 94% may be in the 3 articles, but I do not have access to it. Logic tells me that no species of which sexual behaviour is 94% homosexual will survive. The observations were simply inadequate. Further, Simmons and Scheepers propose that the giraffe's long neck originates from intrasexual competition and not from the alternative theory of feeding behaviour. Males with the sturdiest and longest necks passed their genes on. For them, necking is agonistic and not affiliative behaviour.</span><br>
<span>原文中无此数据，该数据是通过推断得出的，而且推断过程非常搞笑，观察到很多次同性间行为的意思就是观察样本100%为同性间行为？所以，Biological Exuberance: Animal Homosexuality and Natural Diversity，作者Bruce Bagemihl，这本书的作者就是炮制这个数据的源头。</span><br>
</p><p><b>死亡之夜: </b><br>
<span>该被烧死</span><br>
</p><p><b>钢琴男: </b><br>
<span>搞不好背后有彩虹资金搞鬼</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>临界点: </b><br>
<span>最多算双性恋吧   真都是**那还不灭绝了？</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1833999[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
