<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>诺华CEO今天说新冠肺炎疫苗至少需要1年时间</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>诺华CEO今天说新冠肺炎疫苗至少需要1年时间</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 16:30:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>诺华CEO今天说新冠肺炎疫苗至少需要1年时间[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1911425-1-1.html</link>
      <description>诺华CEO今天说新冠肺炎疫苗至少需要1年时间&#13;
 本帖最后由 aiplus 于 2020-1-30 19:36 编辑 

“The reality is, it will take over a year in my expectation to really find a new vaccine for this so, we need to really use epidemiological controls to really get this situation in a better place,” 
&#13;
“One of the challenges is when these epidemics happen, or these situations happen, there is a lot of interest and there is a lot activity but then we go back to a place where they are not happening anymore and everyone kind of loses interest and the investment then flows out.”
&#13;
“So, the question is: How do you keep the investment in place in the troughs of interest in pandemics and these kinds of outbreaks? That’s a challenge.”
&#13;
“I continue to believe governments need to maintain high levels of preparedness, regardless of whether we have one of these outbreaks or not,” Narasimhan said.
&#13;
https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/29/novartis-ceo-warns-finding-a-coronavirus-vaccine-will-take-over-a-year.html
&#13;
其实1年都算是极乐观的估计了
&#13;
而且疫情转好之后，甚至病毒消失了，疫苗研发就不得不中断了</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>aiplus: </b><br>
<span>诺华CEO今天说新冠肺炎疫苗至少需要1年时间</span><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 aiplus 于 2020-1-30 19:36 编辑 </span><br>
<span>“The reality is, it will take over a year in my expectation to really find a new vaccine for this so, we need to really use epidemiological controls to really get this situation in a better place,” </span><br>
<span>“One of the challenges is when these epidemics happen, or these situations happen, there is a lot of interest and there is a lot activity but then we go back to a place where they are not happening anymore and everyone kind of loses interest and the investment then flows out.”</span><br>
<span>“So, the question is: How do you keep the investment in place in the troughs of interest in pandemics and these kinds of outbreaks? That’s a challenge.”</span><br>
<span>“I continue to believe governments need to maintain high levels of preparedness, regardless of whether we have one of these outbreaks or not,” Narasimhan said.</span><br>
<span>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/29/novartis-ceo-warns-finding-a-coronavirus-vaccine-will-take-over-a-year.html</span><br>
<span>其实1年都算是极乐观的估计了</span><br>
<span>而且疫情转好之后，甚至病毒消失了，疫苗研发就不得不中断了</span><br>
</p><p><b>aiplus: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 aiplus 于 2020-1-30 19:32 编辑 </span><br>
<span>https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2020/01/scientists-are-moving-record-speed-create-new-coronavirus-vaccines-they-may-come-too</span><br>
<span>Science的这篇文章介绍了三家公司/机构的疫苗研发进程</span><br>
<span> Moderna makes vaccines by converting viral sequences into messenger RNA (mRNA). When injected into the body, the mRNA causes the body to produce a viral protein that can trigger the desired immune response. Moderna already has nine vaccines in clinical trials that use the mRNA “platform,” says Stéphane Bancel, Moderna’s CEO. “It was a really, really hard scientific challenge to make the first one, but once you get the first one working, the next one becomes really easy: You get the sequence, and this is just another one,” Bancel says. “It’s the same manufacturing process by the same group in the same room.”</span><br>
<span>Inovio, another company working on a 2019-nCoV vaccine with help from CEPI, began its project that same Saturday morning. Inovio produces vaccines made of DNA. It also has a MERS vaccine—which is further along than Moderna’s, already having entered human trials—that also relies on the spike protein. “Our team worked around the clock and was able to design a spike-focused vaccine by that Sunday night,” says CEO J. Joseph Kim.</span><br>
<span>Both Moderna and Inovio say they could have enough vaccine produced 1 month from now to begin animal testing. Kim says he’s looking forward to the race. “We’re starting at the exact same time and this is a great opportunity for us to go mano a mano with Moderna,” Kim says. “I like our chances.”</span><br>
<span>CEPI’s third grant is going to researchers at the University of Queensland. They are developing a vaccine consisting of viral proteins produced in cell cultures, an older technology. Molecular virologist Keith Chappell, one of the project’s leaders, says the “aspirational goal” is to have a candidate vaccine ready for human tests 16 weeks from now. “This is incredibly ambitious and we can provide no guarantee that we can meet this target,” Chappell says. “Our team is working as hard and fast as we possibly can. It is reassuring to us that we are not the only team tasked with a response.”</span><br>
<span>总结一下：</span><br>
<span>Moderna通过将病毒序列转化为信使核糖核酸（mRNA）来生产疫苗</span><br>
<span> Inovio的是DNA疫苗</span><br>
<span>昆士兰大学的则是传统的基因工程改造细胞来表达抗原，从而生产疫苗</span><br>
</p><p><b>yyccq: </b><br>
<span>这几天国内各种公司跳出来，什么40天出样品3个月上临床都来了。我就寻思这国内药品研发那么强怎么平时都看不出来啊？</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1911425[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
