<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>求助Ocarina of Time Item Randomizer这个东西怎么用啊</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>求助Ocarina of Time Item Randomizer这个东西怎么用啊</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 11:06:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>求助Ocarina of Time Item Randomizer这个东西怎么用啊[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1905957-1-1.html</link>
      <description>求助Ocarina of Time Item Randomizer这个东西怎么用啊&#13;
据说是个能使时之笛的道具随机出现的hack工具
&#13;
有可能你商店里直接卖boss key，也有可能装关键道具的宝箱里只是几个卢比
&#13;
我用这个工具给rom打了补丁，但是用模拟器打不开
&#13;
谁玩过这个啊，求助解决方法
&#13;
还有那个把塞尔达传说：三角力量和超级银河战士hack到一起的游戏，有谁有rom啊，林克可以拿到空间跳，萨姆斯拿到心之碎片，切换两个游戏完成解密</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>dreamquest: </b><br>
<span>求助Ocarina of Time Item Randomizer这个东西怎么用啊</span><br>
<span>据说是个能使时之笛的道具随机出现的hack工具</span><br>
<span>有可能你商店里直接卖boss key，也有可能装关键道具的宝箱里只是几个卢比</span><br>
<span>我用这个工具给rom打了补丁，但是用模拟器打不开</span><br>
<span>谁玩过这个啊，求助解决方法</span><br>
<span>还有那个把塞尔达传说：三角力量和超级银河战士hack到一起的游戏，有谁有rom啊，林克可以拿到空间跳，萨姆斯拿到心之碎片，切换两个游戏完成解密</span><br>
</p><p><b>000000: </b><br>
<span>How to:</span><br>
<span>Use the Seed Generator below to create an OoT Randomizer Seed with your preferred settings, logic options and cosmetic touches. An Ocarina of Time 1.0 NTSC-U / NTSC-J rom is needed.</span><br>
<span>OoTRandomizer.com and ZeldaSpeedRuns.com do not distribute any copyrighted material.</span><br>
<span>Hit the Generate Seed button to start the generation process.</span><br>
<span>The Generate Race Seed button will disable the spoiler log, enable rom encryption, and set a random seed.</span><br>
<span>You will be added to the queue. The bot will only handle a few generation requests at a time, so bear in mind that the generation might take a minute (or more for Multiworld)</span><br>
<span>The cosmetic settings selected on generation can be overruled on the seed page itself, but will get set as default for this seed. Your own cosmetic choices are saved for next time.</span><br>
<span>After the seed is generated, you will be forwarded to the seed page where you can check the generated settings, the spoiler log (given you didn't generate a race seed), and also adjust the cosmetic and targeting settings.</span><br>
<span>Afterwards, enter the required file information and select your generation mode.</span><br>
<span>Then hit Patch Rom to generate your randomized OoT rom.</span><br>
<span>Please note that rom compression is a rather resource heavy process. To be able to run the OoT Web Randomizer smoothly, we recommend</span><br>
<span>A multi core CPU (at least 2 cores)</span><br>
<span>At least 1.5 GB of RAM (possibly more)</span><br>
<span>An updated Browser (Chrome v69+, Firefox v63+, Edge (Chromium branch only), Opera v56+, Safari 10+)</span><br>
<span>A 64 Bit system is preferred, 32 Bit support cannot be guaranteed</span><br>
<span>Mobile Devices are supported, but will slow down the patching process (Android phones with 2GB+ RAM, iPhone 5 or newer (iOS 10) supported)</span><br>
<span>Note: If your device barely fulfills the requirements, the patching process can take up to 90 seconds.</span><br>
</p><p><b>000000: </b><br>
<span>https://discordapp.com/invite/ootrandomizer</span><br>
</p><p><b>dreamquest: </b><br>
<span>000000 发表于 2019-12-27 18:21</span><br>
<span>How to:</span><br>
<span>Use the Seed Generator below to create an OoT Randomizer Seed with your preferred settings,...</span><br>
<span>能不能说国语啊</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1905957[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
