<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>宝可梦nuzlocke玩法是真的好玩</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>宝可梦nuzlocke玩法是真的好玩</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 16:51:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>宝可梦nuzlocke玩法是真的好玩[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1867003-1-1.html</link>
      <description>宝可梦nuzlocke玩法是真的好玩&#13;
看到泥潭有人推荐，就去搜索了一下，然后自我规制玩了一晚上……感觉发现了新世界，这才是真正的宝可梦。
&#13;
感觉宝可梦一下子从少儿休闲游戏变成了提心吊胆挑战的roguelike游戏了。配合rom随机修改工具，以前一些老rom也都焕发青春了。
&#13;
每次抵达新地区都有种开包开箱般的快感，打随机道馆和宿敌真的有boss战的紧张感，牺牲了伙伴的惨胜充分感受到了宝可梦世界观 少年兵、角斗士、生存试炼 这样的黑暗感。</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>最美人贩子: </b><br>
<span>宝可梦nuzlocke玩法是真的好玩</span><br>
<span>看到泥潭有人推荐，就去搜索了一下，然后自我规制玩了一晚上……感觉发现了新世界，这才是真正的宝可梦。</span><br>
<span>感觉宝可梦一下子从少儿休闲游戏变成了提心吊胆挑战的roguelike游戏了。配合rom随机修改工具，以前一些老rom也都焕发青春了。</span><br>
<span>每次抵达新地区都有种开包开箱般的快感，打随机道馆和宿敌真的有boss战的紧张感，牺牲了伙伴的惨胜充分感受到了宝可梦世界观 少年兵、角斗士、生存试炼 这样的黑暗感。</span><br>
</p><p><b>萝卜片: </b><br>
<span>在别的贴子也看到过有人提这个nuzlocke，能简单介绍下具体规则或者给个入门介绍文章吗</span><br>
</p><p><b>注册一个: </b><br>
<span>萝卜片 发表于 2019-11-21 12:52</span><br>
<span>在别的贴子也看到过有人提这个nuzlocke，能简单介绍下具体规则或者给个入门介绍文章吗 ...</span><br>
<span>The most basic Nuzlocke rules, as they were first introduced, are as follows:Any Pokémon that faints is considered dead, and must be released or put in the Pokémon Storage System permanently. The player may only catch the first Pokémon encountered in each area, and none else. If the first Pokémon encountered faints or flees, there are no second chances. If the first encounter in the area is a Double Battle in dark grass, the player may choose which of the two Pokémon they would like to catch. If there's a static encounter in the area, the player is allowed to capture them despite already capturing a Pokémon in that area. Shiny Pokémon also do not apply to this rule. Other near-universally used rules include:The general consensus is that players must also nickname all of their Pokémon, for the sake of forming stronger emotional bonds. The general consensus is that a black out/white out is considered to be "game over", even if there are Pokémon left in the PC, however it may be adjusted that other Pokémon in the PC can be used to continue, should this happen. Strongly implied, though not explicitly mentioned in the comic, is the stipulation that the player can use only Pokémon they have captured themselves, meaning traded Pokémon, mystery gifts, etc., are prohibited. Trading and retrading the same Pokémon (for the purpose of evolving a Graveler, for example) is something of a gray area, and may fall under optional rules. As of White: Hard-Mode Episode 3, it is implied that the player can accept Pokémon that are received freely from NPCs. Also strongly implied is a prohibition against voluntarily resetting and reloading the game when things go wrong. Being able to do so would render all of the other rules pointless.</span><br>
</p><p><b>helix: </b><br>
<span>萝卜片 发表于 2019-11-21 12:52</span><br>
<span>在别的贴子也看到过有人提这个nuzlocke，能简单介绍下具体规则或者给个入门介绍文章吗 ...</span><br>
<span>简单来说就是到达一个新区域之后只能抓遇到的第一只PM，战斗中如果濒死了就当做死亡，这次游戏中就不能再用了</span><br>
<span>其它还有些可选规则，比如必须起昵称啥的</span><br>
</p><p><b>johan·liebert: </b><br>
<span>就原版那难度，即使如此也没什么刺激可言</span><br>
</p><p><b>Lump: </b><br>
<span>我一直希望正作能有小畜生斗鸡失败永久死亡机制</span><br>
</p><p><b>战术核辣条: </b><br>
<span>Lump 发表于 2019-11-21 13:29</span><br>
<span>我一直希望正作能有小畜生斗鸡失败永久死亡机制</span><br>
<span>那怕是要动保警告了</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 OnePlus ONEPLUS A6000, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.2.0.1</span><br>
</p><p><b>whzfjk: </b><br>
<span>Lump 发表于 2019-11-21 13:29</span><br>
<span>我一直希望正作能有小畜生斗鸡失败永久死亡机制</span><br>
<span>火纹都废死了</span><br>
</p><p><b>最美人贩子: </b><br>
<span>johan·liebert 发表于 2019-11-21 13:07</span><br>
<span>就原版那难度，即使如此也没什么刺激可言</span><br>
<span>所以还要配合rom修改工具，全口袋池进行随机，有时会遇到压倒性强大/令人哭笑不得的组合。总之就像roguelike一样！由于宝可梦数量有限，boss战又没有退路，死了一只真的能体会到紫苑塔的祭祀者那样的伤感！</span><br>
</p><p><b>最美人贩子: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 最美人贩子 于 2019-11-21 22:29 编辑 </span><br>
<span>回错楼了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>最美人贩子: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 最美人贩子 于 2019-11-21 22:41 编辑 </span><br>
<span>萝卜片 发表于 2019-11-21 12:52</span><br>
<span>在别的贴子也看到过有人提这个nuzlocke，能简单介绍下具体规则或者给个入门介绍文章吗 ...</span><br>
<span>宝可梦不能复活，死了就是死了。</span><br>
<span>每个区域只有一次机会抓到第一只宝可梦。</span><br>
<span>如果遇到闪光宝可梦，则不受此限制。</span><br>
<span>每个城市只能用中心恢复体力2次。</span><br>
<span>不能其他方式获得宝可梦，但化石这类用道具、做任务得宝可梦的可以。</span><br>
<span>随机规则：</span><br>
<span>使用rom修改器修改rom</span><br>
<span>各区域宝可梦前几个世代随机。</span><br>
<span>各NPC宝可梦随机。</span><br>
<span>宿敌每次见面除了御三家以外队伍随机。</span><br>
<span>全部宝可梦招式随机，但不会随到它无法获得的招式。</span><br>
<span>全部技能机器随机，可能得到原本没有的技能机器，比如素描！</span><br>
<span>rom底子推荐心金魂银，操作方面。</span><br>
<span>如此改完就是一个全新的游戏了，感觉可以玩很久。</span><br>
</p><p><b>苏西踩到我了: </b><br>
<span>有种tome4的味道，真想试试看肉鸽味的宝可梦</span><br>
</p><p><b>最美人贩子: </b><br>
<span>苏西踩到我了 发表于 2019-11-21 22:38</span><br>
<span>有种tome4的味道，真想试试看肉鸽味的宝可梦</span><br>
<span>比tome4还刺激。</span><br>
<span>想象一下，如果tome4的全职业技能树全开，但是不能手动选技能树，只能靠每攻略一个区域随机开一个技能树……</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1867003[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
