<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>晓女的美版和日版相比有什么不同？</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>晓女的美版和日版相比有什么不同？</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 16:03:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>晓女的美版和日版相比有什么不同？[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1914969-1-1.html</link>
      <description>晓女的美版和日版相比有什么不同？&#13;
这几天重温了一遍汉化版。据说美版比日版多了一些内容，剧情和系统上的，但是汉化版又是基于日版的，请问美版多出来了哪些内容？</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>iamsolowingpixy: </b><br>
<span>晓女的美版和日版相比有什么不同？</span><br>
<span>这几天重温了一遍汉化版。据说美版比日版多了一些内容，剧情和系统上的，但是汉化版又是基于日版的，请问美版多出来了哪些内容？</span><br>
</p><p><b>浅木飞鸟: </b><br>
<span>Normal, Hard and Maniac modes were renamed to Easy, Normal and Hard mode. There were other changes, such as the enemies in the final chapter having their stats increased.</span><br>
<span>The Data Transfer freezes when Easy mode saves from Path of Radiance are loaded (only in early copies of the NA version).</span><br>
<span>In-game permanent saves were added, for Easy and Normal modes.</span><br>
<span>Support for 16:9 widescreen was added.</span><br>
<span>Originally there was extra dialogue in Hard/Maniac mode, but all modes were changed to have the same dialogue (based on the shortened-down Japanese Normal mode dialogue).</span><br>
<span>In the first cutscene, Micaiah speaks something that resembles Latin, as opposed to galldr, when casting her spell.</span><br>
<span>Edward and Leonardo’s starting levels were raised from 1 to 4, and their stats raised accordingly.</span><br>
<span>Tempest Blade’s critical rate was raised from 0 to 5, Tomahawk’s critical rate was raised from 0 to 5 and Nosferatu’s Hit rate was raised from 65 to 85.</span><br>
<span>Wrath now requires 30% HP or less instead of 20% HP or less, and its activation rate was changed from (Skill)% to 100%.</span><br>
<span>Resolve now requires 50% HP or less instead of 20% HP or less, and its activation rate was changed from (Strength)% to 100%.</span><br>
<span>Edward, Leonardo and Nolan received an unique weapon each (Caladbolg, Lughnasadh and Tarvos).</span><br>
<span>Some new base conversations were added, to obtain the above three weapons and also one featuring Nico.</span><br>
<span>Forging points were no longer needed to forge weapons. Points were originally obtained from selling unwanted weapons.</span><br>
<span>Master Crowns were no longer requires for characters to advance from 2nd Tier to 3rd Tier (they can now promote by gaining 100 EXP at Level 21).</span><br>
<span>Some obtainable Master Crowns were removed and replaced with other items, such as Arms Scrolls.</span><br>
<span>The treasure bug was removed. Originally you could repeatedly try and obtain hidden treasures by cycling through the Direct and Cancel commands.</span><br>
<span>Mist can now promote without a Holy Crown.</span><br>
<span>Preview movies were added inbetween Parts.</span><br>
<span>A character illustration gallery was added, featuring many new character illustrations.</span><br>
</p><p><b>zfz4869: </b><br>
<span>日本国外版（北米・オセアニア版およびヨーロッパ版の2種類）には、以下に挙げる日本版とは異なる独自のイベントや仕様が存在する。ここではその中のいくつかを紹介する。</span><br>
<span>第三部と第四部でいくつかの会話と一枚絵が追加され、とくにミカヤの台詞や血の誓約関連に大幅な変更がある。</span><br>
<span>ノイス、エディ、レオナルドに、それぞれ能力補正のある強力な専用の武器であるタルヴォス、カラドボルグ、ルグナサドと入手時の拠点会話が追加されている。</span><br>
<span>特定のクラスの上限値、キャラクターの初期値、武器の性能が上昇している。</span><br>
<span>本体でリセットしても中断セーブが消えない（日本語版を含む最近のシリーズでは消える）。また、従来のFEでは中断セーブが1つしか作れないが、日本国外版では日本版のマニアックモード（表記はハードである）でのみ複数作れるので2人以上同じセーブブロックが使用できる。</span><br>
<span>最上級職アイテム、「マスタークラウン」と「ホーリークラウン」無しでクラスチェンジが可能。</span><br>
<span>「悟りの符号」の入手がかなり規制が入っている。</span><br>
<span>スキル「勇将」の発動判定と効果は説明文こそ同じだが、実際には国内版のHP20%未満で力%の発動率で力・技・速さが1.5倍から、海外版ではHP50%未満で常に技・速さが1.5倍に変更されている。</span><br>
<span>スキル「怒り」の発動判定と効果が、国内版のHP20%未満で技%の発動率で必殺率が+50%から、海外版ではHP30%未満で常に必殺率+50%に変更されている。</span><br>
<span>ギャラリーが存在し、味方全員と一部の脇役や敵対キャラクターの公式イラストを閲覧できる。</span><br>
<span>画面比率を、ノーマル（4:3）とワイド（16:9）から選択できる。</span><br>
<span>「Nintendo DREAM 任天堂ゲーム攻略本 ファイアーエムブレム 暁の女神」を見ないと難解な古代語が、日本国外用に翻訳されている。</span><br>
<span>化身解除を選択して化身を解除した場合、化身ゲージの値は国内版のように0とならず、そのまま保持される。</span><br>
<span>武器の錬成が日本版と違い、作成する前に自軍の武器を売ってポイントを溜める必要がない。</span><br>
<span>第2部以降に次の部に関連した予告編ムービーがある。</span><br>
<span>ヨーロッパ版ではメッセージが英語のみであった前作と異なり、英語・ドイツ語・フランス語・スペイン語・イタリア語の5ヶ国語対応になっている。</span><br>
<span>日本語版ではハード以上の難易度でテキストが詳しくなっているが、海外版では難易度にかかわらず日本語版ノーマルモードと同様のテキストである。</span><br>
</p><p><b>masterzx: </b><br>
<span>大量不同，相当于国际版/加强完整版</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1914969[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
