<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>印度军队到底有多强大</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>印度军队到底有多强大</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 18:13:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>印度军队到底有多强大[50-100]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1854436-1-1.html</link>
      <description>印度军队到底有多强大&#13;
How strong is the Indian Army actually?印度军队到底有多强大? 以下是Quora读者的评论：Karan Sachdev, A proud Indian; A defence Aspirant and an IT professionalI’ll try to answer this by using the example of 2008 Mumbai attacks. The NSG comes from the Indian army and is commanded by the officers of the special forces.我会以2008年孟买袭击事件为例来回答这个问题。印度军队派出了国家安全卫队，由特种部队军官指挥。It looks very simple from outside. The city was attacked by 10 terrorists and situation was out of control for the Mumbai police and ATS. So the NSG was called in.. They killed 8 terrorists (1 killed and 1 arrested by Police/ATS) and freed the people.形势看似简单。这座城市遭到了10名恐怖分子的袭击，孟买警方和ATS已经失去了控制。国家安全卫队被调用。他们歼灭了8名恐怖分子(1名被警察击毙，1名被警察逮捕)，并解放了人民。But below are some of the points to be noted:但以下是一些需要注意的事:1.For 14 hours, the NSG was kept on stand-by. To explain the difficulty level of this simple statement to IT guys like me: Let us suppose you have to give a presentation at 9 AM. You reach the hall and you’re told you have to present 10 mins later.. then again delayed by 15 mins.. then delayed by 10 mins again and so on.. Your turn comes at 11 PM. (9 AM to 11 fuckin’ PM.) You can’t leave because you never know when you’ll be called in to present. (Just imagine how would your presentation go.. Completely messed up..)1. 14个小时以来，国家安全卫队一直处于待命状态。为了向我这样的IT人士解释，我这么说吧：假设你必须在上午9点做演讲。你到达大厅后，他们告诉你要在10分钟演讲。然后延迟了15分钟。接着又推迟了10分钟，以此类推。晚上11点，终于轮到你了。(从早上9点一直等到晚上11点。)你不能离开，因为你永远不知道什么时候要演讲)想象一下你的演讲会做成什么样…你的节奏被完全打乱了. .)2.When they left Delhi, there was one particular person who was leading. Most of the troops didn’t know each other as they keep rotating and changing units.2.当他们离开德里时，有一个特别的人指挥。大多数士兵都不认识对方，因为他们不停地轮换和更换部队。3.Upon reaching Mumbai, they were divided into three groups, so they have a new team leader now.3.到达孟买后，他们被分成三组，他们又有了一个新的领导。4.When they were called in, they didn’t have a map/blue print of any of the locations. It was there with BMC but not available at hand. so they cant plan from where to enter, where do we have rooms, where is the staircase etc etc.4.当他们被召集上阵的时候，他们没有任何地点的地图/蓝图。所以他们无法筹划该从哪里进入，哪里有房间，楼梯在哪里等等。5.Each of the hotel rooms could have A. Terrorists B. Civilians C. Civilians captured by Terrorists. Hence they can’t use grenades. More than 1000 such rooms had to be cleared (one by one) manually.5.任何酒店都可能有A.恐怖分子B.平民C.被恐怖分子俘虏的平民。因此他们不能使用手榴弹。这样的房间超过了1000个，必须(一个一个地)手工清理。 6.Since the Taj is sea facing, there was no building opposite to the hotel to give any cover fire or for the NSG to climb at a certain height and plan an assault etc.6.由于泰姬陵是面向大海的，所以酒店对面没有任何建筑可以提供火力掩护，或者让国家安全卫队爬到一定的高度，策划袭击等。7.Once they clear a floor and move to the next one, they had to leave at least to 2 men on that floor to handle terrorists, in case they come down. (So as they are approaching the top floors, the number of men we have is decreasing).7.他们清理完一层，接着清理下一层时，必须在那层留下至少两个人来对付恐怖分子，以防他们往下跑。(所以当他们接近顶层时，人手越来越少减少)。This is just a brief description of the difficulty level they had to face.这只是对他们所面临的困难程度的简单描述。NSG rescued over 600 civilians from the three locations.. After the NSG took over, there was no civilian casualty.. Not a single civilian casualty.. The only casualties were the two martyrs (Maj Sandeep and Havaldar Gajendra Singh sahab.)国家安全卫队从这三个地点救出了600多名平民。国家安全卫队接管后，没有再次出现平民伤亡。没有平民伤亡。唯一的伤亡是两名烈士(Maj Sandeep和Havaldar Gajendra Singh sahab)。I could give numbers like we have N number of tanks, rifles, artillery guns, latest missiles, Nukes etc etc. but that’s not what makes an army strong..我可以给出一些数字，比如我们有N辆坦克、**、大炮、最新的导弹、核武器等等，但这并不是军队之所以强大的原因。The weapon is important, but the person holding the weapon is more than the weapon itself.武器很重要，但是控制武器的人比武器本身更重要。This is what our armed forces have proven time and again..这就是被多次证实的我们武装部队的强大实力。Whether its building a railway bridge in Mumbai, cleaning lakes in Bengaluru, saving children from bore well somewhere in Haryana.. Unfortunate natural calamities like the Uttarakhand floods, Kerala floods, the earthquake in J&amp;K in 2005, or the counter terrorist operations along the borders in J&amp;K or north east..无论是在孟买建一座铁路桥，还是在班加罗尔清理湖泊，还是在哈里亚纳邦的某个地方拯救井水里的孩子……不幸的自然灾害，比如北阿坎德邦的洪水，喀拉拉邦的洪水，2005年J&amp;K的地震，或者J&amp;K或东北边境的反恐行动。They come, They see.. They conquer and They humbly leave..他们来了，他们看到乐…他们征服了，然后低调地离开了。That’s what makes our Army the greatest of all..这就是我们的军队之所以是最伟大的原因…Jai Hind!印度万岁！
&#13;
Harishankar Pandey, Knows a few things about the Indian Armed Forces“QUANTUM OF SOLACE”THE STORY OF TWO ARMY OFFICERS“量子危机”两个军官的故事http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/9076452b8512c85683251546e916b9f3.jpgColonel Santosh Mahadik, Ambush ExpertColonel Santosh Yashwant Mahadik, the CO of the 41 Rashtriya Rifles, got a tip-off from an officer of the 57 Rashtriya Rifles about a group of terrorists. Colonel Mahadik was a commando himself, originally from an elite Para-SF unit, so he was used to leading and sitting in ambushes for 2-3 days, even as a CO. He enjoyed being in the field.管理41支Rashtriya**的指挥官Santosh Yashwant Mahadik上校从管理57支Rashtriya**的一名军官那里得到了关于一群恐怖分子的密报。Mahadik上校本人就是一名突击队员，最初来自一个精锐的Para-SF部队，所以他即使身为指挥官，也常常领导士兵埋伏2-3天。他喜欢战场上的感觉。The search for the terrorrists was getting fierce and aggressive. Colonel Mahadik was concerned about the safety of the villagers and his men, while patrolling along the nullah.对恐怖分子的搜寻越来越激烈。Mahadik上校在沿峡谷巡逻时，十分担心村民和他的士兵的安全。Just outside the village they spotted something - a bottle of mineral water, and some freshly cooked rice and meat.就在村外，他们发现了一些东西—一瓶矿泉水，一些刚煮熟的米饭和肉。译文来源：三泰虎http://www.santaihu.com/48263.html译者：JoyceliuTwo things were clear and disturbing. The suspects were nearby, that was the good news; and they had likely abandoned their precious food because they had spotted the Army Team, and were certainly in a postion of advantage - that was the bad news. There was no time to readjust.有两件事十分清楚，也令人不安。嫌疑人就在附近，这是个好消息；他们可能因为发现了军队，放弃了他们珍贵的食物，而且肯定处于有利地位—这是个坏消息。没有时间重新调整。Then a burst of fire opened from the unknown hideout of one of the terrorists, and the army team also opened fire in retaliation. Colonel Mahadik was hit as nobody could see where the firing had come from.随后，一名恐怖分子从藏身之处突然开火，这支部队也采取了报复行动。Mahadik上校被击中，因为没有人知道枪声是从哪里发出的。The 3 men with the Colonel were in the open, and were sitting ducks because of being exposed to danger. To save his team, Colonel Mahadik opened fire even though blood was gushing from his wounds. He fired continuously while still being exposed and heavily wounded. He basically ensured that the terrorist did not fire the men behind him.和上校在一起行动的三个人都处在露天场地，由于暴露在危险之中，他们成了攻击目标。为了拯救他的队伍，Mahadik上校开枪了，尽管伤口鲜血四溅。他不断开枪，但仍然没有掩护，受了重伤。他确保了恐怖分子无法向他身后的人开枪。He ran out of ammunition but still kept the terrorists on the defensive mode, and was successful in his attempt; but blood loss was heavy. Colonel Mahadik had to be air lifted with the assistance of Major Praveen.他的弹药用完了，但恐怖分子依然处于防守状态，他的尝试成功了；但失血过多。Mahadik上校不得不在Praveen少校的协助下乘飞机离开。While airlifting, Major Praveen got a call from Col. Mahadik’s wife. All she asked with a tearful quivering voice was “ZINDA RAHENGE YA NAHI RAHENGE ? BAS ITNA BATA DO” (Will he survive or not? Just answer this). This question still haunts Major Praveen.在空运过程中，Praveen少校接到了Mahadik上校妻子的电话。她含泪颤抖着只问了一句：“他能活下来吗？只要回答我这个问题”。这个问题仍然困扰着Praveen少校。Colonel Mahadik was declared brought-in dead at the 92 Base Hospital in Srinagar. Colonel Mahadik was martyred in the line of duty, but till his last moments, he ensured the safety of his men. Salute to the Brave soul and his family.Mahadik上校在斯里纳加尔的92所基地医院被宣布死亡。Mahadik上校因公殉职，但直到他的最后一项任务，他都一直确保他属下士兵的安全。向这个勇敢的灵魂和他的家人致敬。http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/f3717e231e3bbea9e53ab14fb64c9654.jpg
&#13;
 Col. Mahadik with his family - Happy Times. Wish time could stand still at these moments.THE OTHER OFFICERMahadik上校和他的家人-快乐的时光。但愿时间能在这些时刻停止。另一个军官http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/3d727a84838c31e0e20620508171fa7f.jpg
&#13;
 http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/57a584d08a11fdf71c870200eb57619d.jpg
&#13;
 The Officer and the Gentlewoman军官和那位贵妇人She is Lt. Swati Mahadik, wife of the Late Colonel Santosh Mahadik. She was commissioned into the Indian Army as Lieutenant in 2017.她是斯瓦蒂·马哈迪克中尉，已故上校桑托什·马哈迪克的妻子。2017年，她被任命为印度陆军中尉。As she completed her Passing-Out Parade, she broke down into tears both of joy and remembrance. The proud moment of the Passing Out Parade was witnessed by her son Swaraj and daughter Kartikee.当她完成她的送别会操时，她高兴得热泪盈眶，回忆起往事。她的儿子斯瓦拉杰和女儿卡蒂基见证了这一自豪的时刻。Such is the grit and determination of our Armed Forces and their families. She had silently resolved to join the Indian Army at the funeral of her husband in November 2015.这就是我们的武装部队及其家属的勇气和决心。2015年11月，在丈夫的葬礼上，她暗自决定加入印度军队。Swati had already crossed the upper age limit for entering the army, and it was only after the Indian Army and Ministry of Defence specially relaxed the age limit for her that she could initiate her new career goals.斯瓦蒂已经过了参军的年龄上限，在印度军队和国防部特别放宽了对她的年龄限制之后，她才得以开始新的职业目标。After undergoing several rounds of SSB and physical fitness and medical examinations as part of the process, she was selected to join the Officers Training Academy in Chennai.在经历了几轮SSB和身体健康及体检后，她被选中加入金奈的军官培训学院。Her husband’s martyrdom did not become her tragedy, it was not her setback. It became her life fuel. Their children, too, will grow up knowing the true meaning of valour, family and patriotism.她丈夫的殉难没有成为她的悲剧，也没有成为她的挫折。反而成了她生命的燃料。他们的孩子长大后也会明白勇敢、家庭和爱国主义的真正含义。Strength does not come from ammunitions, tanks and weapons. It comes from the will power, determination and mettle of the minds operating these weapons.力量不是来自弹药、坦克和武器。而是来自操作这些武器的人的意志力、决心和勇气。THIS IS ARMY STRONG - INDIAN ARMY STRONG这是一支强大的军队—强大的印度军队Salute to the people in uniform and their families.向军人和他们的家属致敬。A Heartfelt Thank you to the Press Information Bureau of India and Shiv Aroor of India Today and Rahul Singh of the Hindustan Times for the wonderful insight.衷心感谢印度新闻局、《今日印度》的希夫·阿鲁尔和《印度斯坦时报》的拉胡尔·辛格的精彩见解。Jai Hind.印度万岁。
&#13;
Oraf Moin, Proprietor at Hind National Exports (1992-present)Strong enough , really strong, if you looked at the armed forces within an Indic prism but weak or too below potential if you look at us from the lens of a traditional power like British empire, Russian empire, Ottoman empire etc.如果你从印度的角度来看武装力量，那足够强大，非常强大，但如果你从传统强国的角度看待我们，比如大英帝国，俄罗斯帝国，奥斯曼帝国等等，你就会发现我们的实力很弱，或者说太无潜力。The modern Indic nation sees the army as a force designed to knock out any blitzkrieg onto our land as with what happened in 1962. We can make any war costly enough for even multiple aggressors to consider it not worth it.现代印度国家将军队视为一种旨在摧毁我们土地上任何闪电战的力量，就像1962年发生的那样。我们可以让任何战争都付出足够惨重的代价，让侵略者认为这种进攻得不偿失。But then we can't fight offensive wars or occupy new territory and hold it till it's incorporated into our mainland. No, our armed forces can't pull that off.但是我们没有能力展开进攻性的战争或者占领新的领土，让其并入我们的大陆。不，我们的军队做不到。We can't fight a long theater war either but then we don't need to as we're nuclear armed already and are just a step away from intercontinental missile research conclusion. We have a robust space programme to complement this.我们也没有能力展开长期战争，不过我们也没有这个需要，因为我们已经拥有核武器，距离洲际导弹的成功仅有一步之遥。我们有强大的太空计划来补充这一点。We are an excellent defensive force but we never were a warning expansionist nation even during Akbar. We ceased that since Kalinga battle under Asoka.我们是一支优秀的防御力量，但即使在阿克巴时期，我们也不是扩张主义国家。自从阿育王治下的卡林加战役以来，我们就停止了这种行动。
&#13;
Dheeraj K. Shavan, Doctor of veterinary med from SKUAST JammuIndian army is the 2nd largest army in the world.But not in terms of numbers, Indian army has proven its strength time and again ,let me supplement it with few recent happenings in my state of j&amp;k.印度军队是世界第二大军队。但不是在数量上，印度军队已经一次又一次证明了它的实力，让我补充一下我所在的查谟邦最近发生的一些事情。http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/f6c46efc08cd93903ffec50621e044a5.jpg
&#13;
 1.The guy encircled in the above pic is Naved Jutt the most dreaded terrorist and commander of LeT in Kashmir. He is from Multan Pakistan. He has escaped from police custody 10 months back . Few days ago his video surfaced on net in which he was roaming outside his hideout and it was snowing there . Based on this video and inputs from it Indian army and intelligence agencies tracked him and he was killed along with his associates in Budgam today . This shows Indian army’s capability.
&#13;
[*]上图中圈中的人是克什米尔地区最可怕的恐怖分子和LeT的指挥官。他来自巴基斯坦的木尔坦。10个月前，他从警方的拘留中逃脱。几天前，他的视频出现在网上，当时他正在藏身之处外面散步，那里正在下雪。根据这个视频，印度军队和情报机构对他进行了跟踪，他和他的同伙今天在布加姆被杀。这显示了印度军队的能力。
&#13;
moral: Indian army is too powerful to be challenged in this way . These terrorists had tried to show that Indian army is weak and they can openly post pics and videos online without being traced . Indian army proved them wrong .Jai Hind.印度军队太强大了，无法通过这种方式被挑衅。这些恐怖分子试图表明印度军队软弱无能，他们可以公开在网上发布照片和视频，行踪不会被发现。印度军队证明他们大错特错。印度万岁。</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>法皇干政: </b><br>
<span>zz_mps 发表于 2019-8-19 14:39</span><br>
<span>"帕蒂尔介绍说，初步调查显示，共有10名恐怖分子参与了袭击，其中9人在交火中被击毙，1人被活捉。"</span><br>
<span>"2008 ...</span><br>
<span>看来这是三哥的光荣传统了，难怪这次红茶派骆驼也成为英雄了</span><br>
<span>Jai Hind!</span><br>
</p><p><b>金赛性学报告: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 金赛性学报告 于 2019-8-19 16:50 编辑 </span><br>
<span>Then a burst of fire opened from the unknown hideout of one of the terrorists, and the army team also opened fire in retaliation. Colonel Mahadik was hit as nobody could see where the firing had come from. 随后，一名恐怖分子从藏身之处突然开火，这支部队也采取了报复行动。Mahadik上校被击中，因为没有人知道枪声是从哪里发出的。 The 3 men with the Colonel were in the open, and were sitting ducks because of being exposed to danger. To save his team, Colonel Mahadik opened fire even though blood was gushing from his wounds. He fired continuously while still being exposed and heavily wounded. He basically ensured that the terrorist did not fire the men behind him. 和上校在一起行动的三个人都处在露天场地，由于暴露在危险之中，他们成了攻击目标。为了拯救他的队伍，Mahadik上校开枪了，尽管伤口鲜血四溅。他不断开枪，但仍然没有掩护，受了重伤。他确保了恐怖分子无法向他身后的人开枪。 He ran out of ammunition but still kept the terrorists on the defensive mode, and was successful in his attempt; but blood loss was heavy. Colonel Mahadik had to be air lifted with the assistance of Major Praveen. 他的弹药用完了，但恐怖分子依然处于防守状态，他的尝试成功了；但失血过多。Mahadik上校不得不在Praveen少校的协助下乘飞机离开。</span><br>
<span>团长，你在干什么啊团长</span><br>
<span>希望之花</span><br>
</p><p><b>deuce693: </b><br>
<span>来 了</span><br>
<span>废 狗 传 统 艺 能</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 samsung SM-G9008W, Android 6.0.1上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>deuce693: </b><br>
<span>已编辑</span><br>
</p><p><b>boom33: </b><br>
<span>Jai Hind.</span><br>
</p><p><b>爱吃冻鳗的猫: </b><br>
<span>Jai Hind原来是万岁的意思啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>克拉苏: </b><br>
<span>现代印度国家将军队视为一种旨在摧毁我们土地上任何闪电战的力量，就像1962年发生的那样。我们可以让任何战争都付出足够惨重的代价，让侵略者认为这种进攻得不偿失。</span><br>
</p><p><b>永远的海格力斯: </b><br>
<span>活久见 发表于 2019-8-19 14:15</span><br>
<span>7.他们清理完一层，接着清理下一层时，必须在那层留下至少两个人来对付恐怖分子，以防他们往下跑。(所以当 ...</span><br>
<span>可能是在出数学题？</span><br>
</p><p><b>oT3To: </b><br>
<span>シャスタ 发表于 2019-8-19 14:19</span><br>
<span>印度内有恐怖分子,外有巴基斯坦. </span><br>
<span>跟中国的双方投石在边界群殴,就不算威胁了吧......</span><br>
<span>远不如中国，同样的事情PLA连新闻都不算</span><br>
</p><p><b>7217210868: </b><br>
<span>额，怎么说呢，我只能说三哥牛13</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1854436[50-100]</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>印度军队到底有多强大[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1854436-1-1.html</link>
      <description>印度军队到底有多强大&#13;
How strong is the Indian Army actually?印度军队到底有多强大? 以下是Quora读者的评论：Karan Sachdev, A proud Indian; A defence Aspirant and an IT professionalI’ll try to answer this by using the example of 2008 Mumbai attacks. The NSG comes from the Indian army and is commanded by the officers of the special forces.我会以2008年孟买袭击事件为例来回答这个问题。印度军队派出了国家安全卫队，由特种部队军官指挥。It looks very simple from outside. The city was attacked by 10 terrorists and situation was out of control for the Mumbai police and ATS. So the NSG was called in.. They killed 8 terrorists (1 killed and 1 arrested by Police/ATS) and freed the people.形势看似简单。这座城市遭到了10名恐怖分子的袭击，孟买警方和ATS已经失去了控制。国家安全卫队被调用。他们歼灭了8名恐怖分子(1名被警察击毙，1名被警察逮捕)，并解放了人民。But below are some of the points to be noted:但以下是一些需要注意的事:1.For 14 hours, the NSG was kept on stand-by. To explain the difficulty level of this simple statement to IT guys like me: Let us suppose you have to give a presentation at 9 AM. You reach the hall and you’re told you have to present 10 mins later.. then again delayed by 15 mins.. then delayed by 10 mins again and so on.. Your turn comes at 11 PM. (9 AM to 11 fuckin’ PM.) You can’t leave because you never know when you’ll be called in to present. (Just imagine how would your presentation go.. Completely messed up..)1. 14个小时以来，国家安全卫队一直处于待命状态。为了向我这样的IT人士解释，我这么说吧：假设你必须在上午9点做演讲。你到达大厅后，他们告诉你要在10分钟演讲。然后延迟了15分钟。接着又推迟了10分钟，以此类推。晚上11点，终于轮到你了。(从早上9点一直等到晚上11点。)你不能离开，因为你永远不知道什么时候要演讲)想象一下你的演讲会做成什么样…你的节奏被完全打乱了. .)2.When they left Delhi, there was one particular person who was leading. Most of the troops didn’t know each other as they keep rotating and changing units.2.当他们离开德里时，有一个特别的人指挥。大多数士兵都不认识对方，因为他们不停地轮换和更换部队。3.Upon reaching Mumbai, they were divided into three groups, so they have a new team leader now.3.到达孟买后，他们被分成三组，他们又有了一个新的领导。4.When they were called in, they didn’t have a map/blue print of any of the locations. It was there with BMC but not available at hand. so they cant plan from where to enter, where do we have rooms, where is the staircase etc etc.4.当他们被召集上阵的时候，他们没有任何地点的地图/蓝图。所以他们无法筹划该从哪里进入，哪里有房间，楼梯在哪里等等。5.Each of the hotel rooms could have A. Terrorists B. Civilians C. Civilians captured by Terrorists. Hence they can’t use grenades. More than 1000 such rooms had to be cleared (one by one) manually.5.任何酒店都可能有A.恐怖分子B.平民C.被恐怖分子俘虏的平民。因此他们不能使用手榴弹。这样的房间超过了1000个，必须(一个一个地)手工清理。 6.Since the Taj is sea facing, there was no building opposite to the hotel to give any cover fire or for the NSG to climb at a certain height and plan an assault etc.6.由于泰姬陵是面向大海的，所以酒店对面没有任何建筑可以提供火力掩护，或者让国家安全卫队爬到一定的高度，策划袭击等。7.Once they clear a floor and move to the next one, they had to leave at least to 2 men on that floor to handle terrorists, in case they come down. (So as they are approaching the top floors, the number of men we have is decreasing).7.他们清理完一层，接着清理下一层时，必须在那层留下至少两个人来对付恐怖分子，以防他们往下跑。(所以当他们接近顶层时，人手越来越少减少)。This is just a brief description of the difficulty level they had to face.这只是对他们所面临的困难程度的简单描述。NSG rescued over 600 civilians from the three locations.. After the NSG took over, there was no civilian casualty.. Not a single civilian casualty.. The only casualties were the two martyrs (Maj Sandeep and Havaldar Gajendra Singh sahab.)国家安全卫队从这三个地点救出了600多名平民。国家安全卫队接管后，没有再次出现平民伤亡。没有平民伤亡。唯一的伤亡是两名烈士(Maj Sandeep和Havaldar Gajendra Singh sahab)。I could give numbers like we have N number of tanks, rifles, artillery guns, latest missiles, Nukes etc etc. but that’s not what makes an army strong..我可以给出一些数字，比如我们有N辆坦克、**、大炮、最新的导弹、核武器等等，但这并不是军队之所以强大的原因。The weapon is important, but the person holding the weapon is more than the weapon itself.武器很重要，但是控制武器的人比武器本身更重要。This is what our armed forces have proven time and again..这就是被多次证实的我们武装部队的强大实力。Whether its building a railway bridge in Mumbai, cleaning lakes in Bengaluru, saving children from bore well somewhere in Haryana.. Unfortunate natural calamities like the Uttarakhand floods, Kerala floods, the earthquake in J&amp;K in 2005, or the counter terrorist operations along the borders in J&amp;K or north east..无论是在孟买建一座铁路桥，还是在班加罗尔清理湖泊，还是在哈里亚纳邦的某个地方拯救井水里的孩子……不幸的自然灾害，比如北阿坎德邦的洪水，喀拉拉邦的洪水，2005年J&amp;K的地震，或者J&amp;K或东北边境的反恐行动。They come, They see.. They conquer and They humbly leave..他们来了，他们看到乐…他们征服了，然后低调地离开了。That’s what makes our Army the greatest of all..这就是我们的军队之所以是最伟大的原因…Jai Hind!印度万岁！
&#13;
Harishankar Pandey, Knows a few things about the Indian Armed Forces“QUANTUM OF SOLACE”THE STORY OF TWO ARMY OFFICERS“量子危机”两个军官的故事http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/9076452b8512c85683251546e916b9f3.jpgColonel Santosh Mahadik, Ambush ExpertColonel Santosh Yashwant Mahadik, the CO of the 41 Rashtriya Rifles, got a tip-off from an officer of the 57 Rashtriya Rifles about a group of terrorists. Colonel Mahadik was a commando himself, originally from an elite Para-SF unit, so he was used to leading and sitting in ambushes for 2-3 days, even as a CO. He enjoyed being in the field.管理41支Rashtriya**的指挥官Santosh Yashwant Mahadik上校从管理57支Rashtriya**的一名军官那里得到了关于一群恐怖分子的密报。Mahadik上校本人就是一名突击队员，最初来自一个精锐的Para-SF部队，所以他即使身为指挥官，也常常领导士兵埋伏2-3天。他喜欢战场上的感觉。The search for the terrorrists was getting fierce and aggressive. Colonel Mahadik was concerned about the safety of the villagers and his men, while patrolling along the nullah.对恐怖分子的搜寻越来越激烈。Mahadik上校在沿峡谷巡逻时，十分担心村民和他的士兵的安全。Just outside the village they spotted something - a bottle of mineral water, and some freshly cooked rice and meat.就在村外，他们发现了一些东西—一瓶矿泉水，一些刚煮熟的米饭和肉。译文来源：三泰虎http://www.santaihu.com/48263.html译者：JoyceliuTwo things were clear and disturbing. The suspects were nearby, that was the good news; and they had likely abandoned their precious food because they had spotted the Army Team, and were certainly in a postion of advantage - that was the bad news. There was no time to readjust.有两件事十分清楚，也令人不安。嫌疑人就在附近，这是个好消息；他们可能因为发现了军队，放弃了他们珍贵的食物，而且肯定处于有利地位—这是个坏消息。没有时间重新调整。Then a burst of fire opened from the unknown hideout of one of the terrorists, and the army team also opened fire in retaliation. Colonel Mahadik was hit as nobody could see where the firing had come from.随后，一名恐怖分子从藏身之处突然开火，这支部队也采取了报复行动。Mahadik上校被击中，因为没有人知道枪声是从哪里发出的。The 3 men with the Colonel were in the open, and were sitting ducks because of being exposed to danger. To save his team, Colonel Mahadik opened fire even though blood was gushing from his wounds. He fired continuously while still being exposed and heavily wounded. He basically ensured that the terrorist did not fire the men behind him.和上校在一起行动的三个人都处在露天场地，由于暴露在危险之中，他们成了攻击目标。为了拯救他的队伍，Mahadik上校开枪了，尽管伤口鲜血四溅。他不断开枪，但仍然没有掩护，受了重伤。他确保了恐怖分子无法向他身后的人开枪。He ran out of ammunition but still kept the terrorists on the defensive mode, and was successful in his attempt; but blood loss was heavy. Colonel Mahadik had to be air lifted with the assistance of Major Praveen.他的弹药用完了，但恐怖分子依然处于防守状态，他的尝试成功了；但失血过多。Mahadik上校不得不在Praveen少校的协助下乘飞机离开。While airlifting, Major Praveen got a call from Col. Mahadik’s wife. All she asked with a tearful quivering voice was “ZINDA RAHENGE YA NAHI RAHENGE ? BAS ITNA BATA DO” (Will he survive or not? Just answer this). This question still haunts Major Praveen.在空运过程中，Praveen少校接到了Mahadik上校妻子的电话。她含泪颤抖着只问了一句：“他能活下来吗？只要回答我这个问题”。这个问题仍然困扰着Praveen少校。Colonel Mahadik was declared brought-in dead at the 92 Base Hospital in Srinagar. Colonel Mahadik was martyred in the line of duty, but till his last moments, he ensured the safety of his men. Salute to the Brave soul and his family.Mahadik上校在斯里纳加尔的92所基地医院被宣布死亡。Mahadik上校因公殉职，但直到他的最后一项任务，他都一直确保他属下士兵的安全。向这个勇敢的灵魂和他的家人致敬。http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/f3717e231e3bbea9e53ab14fb64c9654.jpg
&#13;
 Col. Mahadik with his family - Happy Times. Wish time could stand still at these moments.THE OTHER OFFICERMahadik上校和他的家人-快乐的时光。但愿时间能在这些时刻停止。另一个军官http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/3d727a84838c31e0e20620508171fa7f.jpg
&#13;
 http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/57a584d08a11fdf71c870200eb57619d.jpg
&#13;
 The Officer and the Gentlewoman军官和那位贵妇人She is Lt. Swati Mahadik, wife of the Late Colonel Santosh Mahadik. She was commissioned into the Indian Army as Lieutenant in 2017.她是斯瓦蒂·马哈迪克中尉，已故上校桑托什·马哈迪克的妻子。2017年，她被任命为印度陆军中尉。As she completed her Passing-Out Parade, she broke down into tears both of joy and remembrance. The proud moment of the Passing Out Parade was witnessed by her son Swaraj and daughter Kartikee.当她完成她的送别会操时，她高兴得热泪盈眶，回忆起往事。她的儿子斯瓦拉杰和女儿卡蒂基见证了这一自豪的时刻。Such is the grit and determination of our Armed Forces and their families. She had silently resolved to join the Indian Army at the funeral of her husband in November 2015.这就是我们的武装部队及其家属的勇气和决心。2015年11月，在丈夫的葬礼上，她暗自决定加入印度军队。Swati had already crossed the upper age limit for entering the army, and it was only after the Indian Army and Ministry of Defence specially relaxed the age limit for her that she could initiate her new career goals.斯瓦蒂已经过了参军的年龄上限，在印度军队和国防部特别放宽了对她的年龄限制之后，她才得以开始新的职业目标。After undergoing several rounds of SSB and physical fitness and medical examinations as part of the process, she was selected to join the Officers Training Academy in Chennai.在经历了几轮SSB和身体健康及体检后，她被选中加入金奈的军官培训学院。Her husband’s martyrdom did not become her tragedy, it was not her setback. It became her life fuel. Their children, too, will grow up knowing the true meaning of valour, family and patriotism.她丈夫的殉难没有成为她的悲剧，也没有成为她的挫折。反而成了她生命的燃料。他们的孩子长大后也会明白勇敢、家庭和爱国主义的真正含义。Strength does not come from ammunitions, tanks and weapons. It comes from the will power, determination and mettle of the minds operating these weapons.力量不是来自弹药、坦克和武器。而是来自操作这些武器的人的意志力、决心和勇气。THIS IS ARMY STRONG - INDIAN ARMY STRONG这是一支强大的军队—强大的印度军队Salute to the people in uniform and their families.向军人和他们的家属致敬。A Heartfelt Thank you to the Press Information Bureau of India and Shiv Aroor of India Today and Rahul Singh of the Hindustan Times for the wonderful insight.衷心感谢印度新闻局、《今日印度》的希夫·阿鲁尔和《印度斯坦时报》的拉胡尔·辛格的精彩见解。Jai Hind.印度万岁。
&#13;
Oraf Moin, Proprietor at Hind National Exports (1992-present)Strong enough , really strong, if you looked at the armed forces within an Indic prism but weak or too below potential if you look at us from the lens of a traditional power like British empire, Russian empire, Ottoman empire etc.如果你从印度的角度来看武装力量，那足够强大，非常强大，但如果你从传统强国的角度看待我们，比如大英帝国，俄罗斯帝国，奥斯曼帝国等等，你就会发现我们的实力很弱，或者说太无潜力。The modern Indic nation sees the army as a force designed to knock out any blitzkrieg onto our land as with what happened in 1962. We can make any war costly enough for even multiple aggressors to consider it not worth it.现代印度国家将军队视为一种旨在摧毁我们土地上任何闪电战的力量，就像1962年发生的那样。我们可以让任何战争都付出足够惨重的代价，让侵略者认为这种进攻得不偿失。But then we can't fight offensive wars or occupy new territory and hold it till it's incorporated into our mainland. No, our armed forces can't pull that off.但是我们没有能力展开进攻性的战争或者占领新的领土，让其并入我们的大陆。不，我们的军队做不到。We can't fight a long theater war either but then we don't need to as we're nuclear armed already and are just a step away from intercontinental missile research conclusion. We have a robust space programme to complement this.我们也没有能力展开长期战争，不过我们也没有这个需要，因为我们已经拥有核武器，距离洲际导弹的成功仅有一步之遥。我们有强大的太空计划来补充这一点。We are an excellent defensive force but we never were a warning expansionist nation even during Akbar. We ceased that since Kalinga battle under Asoka.我们是一支优秀的防御力量，但即使在阿克巴时期，我们也不是扩张主义国家。自从阿育王治下的卡林加战役以来，我们就停止了这种行动。
&#13;
Dheeraj K. Shavan, Doctor of veterinary med from SKUAST JammuIndian army is the 2nd largest army in the world.But not in terms of numbers, Indian army has proven its strength time and again ,let me supplement it with few recent happenings in my state of j&amp;k.印度军队是世界第二大军队。但不是在数量上，印度军队已经一次又一次证明了它的实力，让我补充一下我所在的查谟邦最近发生的一些事情。http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/f6c46efc08cd93903ffec50621e044a5.jpg
&#13;
 1.The guy encircled in the above pic is Naved Jutt the most dreaded terrorist and commander of LeT in Kashmir. He is from Multan Pakistan. He has escaped from police custody 10 months back . Few days ago his video surfaced on net in which he was roaming outside his hideout and it was snowing there . Based on this video and inputs from it Indian army and intelligence agencies tracked him and he was killed along with his associates in Budgam today . This shows Indian army’s capability.
&#13;
[*]上图中圈中的人是克什米尔地区最可怕的恐怖分子和LeT的指挥官。他来自巴基斯坦的木尔坦。10个月前，他从警方的拘留中逃脱。几天前，他的视频出现在网上，当时他正在藏身之处外面散步，那里正在下雪。根据这个视频，印度军队和情报机构对他进行了跟踪，他和他的同伙今天在布加姆被杀。这显示了印度军队的能力。
&#13;
moral: Indian army is too powerful to be challenged in this way . These terrorists had tried to show that Indian army is weak and they can openly post pics and videos online without being traced . Indian army proved them wrong .Jai Hind.印度军队太强大了，无法通过这种方式被挑衅。这些恐怖分子试图表明印度军队软弱无能，他们可以公开在网上发布照片和视频，行踪不会被发现。印度军队证明他们大错特错。印度万岁。</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>狒狗: </b><br>
<span>印度军队到底有多强大</span><br>
<span>How strong is the Indian Army actually?印度军队到底有多强大? 以下是Quora读者的评论：Karan Sachdev, A proud Indian; A defence Aspirant and an IT professionalI’ll try to answer this by using the example of 2008 Mumbai attacks. The NSG comes from the Indian army and is commanded by the officers of the special forces.我会以2008年孟买袭击事件为例来回答这个问题。印度军队派出了国家安全卫队，由特种部队军官指挥。It looks very simple from outside. The city was attacked by 10 terrorists and situation was out of control for the Mumbai police and ATS. So the NSG was called in.. They killed 8 terrorists (1 killed and 1 arrested by Police/ATS) and freed the people.形势看似简单。这座城市遭到了10名恐怖分子的袭击，孟买警方和ATS已经失去了控制。国家安全卫队被调用。他们歼灭了8名恐怖分子(1名被警察击毙，1名被警察逮捕)，并解放了人民。But below are some of the points to be noted:但以下是一些需要注意的事:1.For 14 hours, the NSG was kept on stand-by. To explain the difficulty level of this simple statement to IT guys like me: Let us suppose you have to give a presentation at 9 AM. You reach the hall and you’re told you have to present 10 mins later.. then again delayed by 15 mins.. then delayed by 10 mins again and so on.. Your turn comes at 11 PM. (9 AM to 11 fuckin’ PM.) You can’t leave because you never know when you’ll be called in to present. (Just imagine how would your presentation go.. Completely messed up..)1. 14个小时以来，国家安全卫队一直处于待命状态。为了向我这样的IT人士解释，我这么说吧：假设你必须在上午9点做演讲。你到达大厅后，他们告诉你要在10分钟演讲。然后延迟了15分钟。接着又推迟了10分钟，以此类推。晚上11点，终于轮到你了。(从早上9点一直等到晚上11点。)你不能离开，因为你永远不知道什么时候要演讲)想象一下你的演讲会做成什么样…你的节奏被完全打乱了. .)2.When they left Delhi, there was one particular person who was leading. Most of the troops didn’t know each other as they keep rotating and changing units.2.当他们离开德里时，有一个特别的人指挥。大多数士兵都不认识对方，因为他们不停地轮换和更换部队。3.Upon reaching Mumbai, they were divided into three groups, so they have a new team leader now.3.到达孟买后，他们被分成三组，他们又有了一个新的领导。4.When they were called in, they didn’t have a map/blue print of any of the locations. It was there with BMC but not available at hand. so they cant plan from where to enter, where do we have rooms, where is the staircase etc etc.4.当他们被召集上阵的时候，他们没有任何地点的地图/蓝图。所以他们无法筹划该从哪里进入，哪里有房间，楼梯在哪里等等。5.Each of the hotel rooms could have A. Terrorists B. Civilians C. Civilians captured by Terrorists. Hence they can’t use grenades. More than 1000 such rooms had to be cleared (one by one) manually.5.任何酒店都可能有A.恐怖分子B.平民C.被恐怖分子俘虏的平民。因此他们不能使用手榴弹。这样的房间超过了1000个，必须(一个一个地)手工清理。 6.Since the Taj is sea facing, there was no building opposite to the hotel to give any cover fire or for the NSG to climb at a certain height and plan an assault etc.6.由于泰姬陵是面向大海的，所以酒店对面没有任何建筑可以提供火力掩护，或者让国家安全卫队爬到一定的高度，策划袭击等。7.Once they clear a floor and move to the next one, they had to leave at least to 2 men on that floor to handle terrorists, in case they come down. (So as they are approaching the top floors, the number of men we have is decreasing).7.他们清理完一层，接着清理下一层时，必须在那层留下至少两个人来对付恐怖分子，以防他们往下跑。(所以当他们接近顶层时，人手越来越少减少)。This is just a brief description of the difficulty level they had to face.这只是对他们所面临的困难程度的简单描述。NSG rescued over 600 civilians from the three locations.. After the NSG took over, there was no civilian casualty.. Not a single civilian casualty.. The only casualties were the two martyrs (Maj Sandeep and Havaldar Gajendra Singh sahab.)国家安全卫队从这三个地点救出了600多名平民。国家安全卫队接管后，没有再次出现平民伤亡。没有平民伤亡。唯一的伤亡是两名烈士(Maj Sandeep和Havaldar Gajendra Singh sahab)。I could give numbers like we have N number of tanks, rifles, artillery guns, latest missiles, Nukes etc etc. but that’s not what makes an army strong..我可以给出一些数字，比如我们有N辆坦克、**、大炮、最新的导弹、核武器等等，但这并不是军队之所以强大的原因。The weapon is important, but the person holding the weapon is more than the weapon itself.武器很重要，但是控制武器的人比武器本身更重要。This is what our armed forces have proven time and again..这就是被多次证实的我们武装部队的强大实力。Whether its building a railway bridge in Mumbai, cleaning lakes in Bengaluru, saving children from bore well somewhere in Haryana.. Unfortunate natural calamities like the Uttarakhand floods, Kerala floods, the earthquake in J&K in 2005, or the counter terrorist operations along the borders in J&K or north east..无论是在孟买建一座铁路桥，还是在班加罗尔清理湖泊，还是在哈里亚纳邦的某个地方拯救井水里的孩子……不幸的自然灾害，比如北阿坎德邦的洪水，喀拉拉邦的洪水，2005年J&K的地震，或者J&K或东北边境的反恐行动。They come, They see.. They conquer and They humbly leave..他们来了，他们看到乐…他们征服了，然后低调地离开了。That’s what makes our Army the greatest of all..这就是我们的军队之所以是最伟大的原因…Jai Hind!印度万岁！</span><br>
<span>Harishankar Pandey, Knows a few things about the Indian Armed Forces“QUANTUM OF SOLACE”THE STORY OF TWO ARMY OFFICERS“量子危机”两个军官的故事http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/9076452b8512c85683251546e916b9f3.jpgColonel Santosh Mahadik, Ambush ExpertColonel Santosh Yashwant Mahadik, the CO of the 41 Rashtriya Rifles, got a tip-off from an officer of the 57 Rashtriya Rifles about a group of terrorists. Colonel Mahadik was a commando himself, originally from an elite Para-SF unit, so he was used to leading and sitting in ambushes for 2-3 days, even as a CO. He enjoyed being in the field.管理41支Rashtriya**的指挥官Santosh Yashwant Mahadik上校从管理57支Rashtriya**的一名军官那里得到了关于一群恐怖分子的密报。Mahadik上校本人就是一名突击队员，最初来自一个精锐的Para-SF部队，所以他即使身为指挥官，也常常领导士兵埋伏2-3天。他喜欢战场上的感觉。The search for the terrorrists was getting fierce and aggressive. Colonel Mahadik was concerned about the safety of the villagers and his men, while patrolling along the nullah.对恐怖分子的搜寻越来越激烈。Mahadik上校在沿峡谷巡逻时，十分担心村民和他的士兵的安全。Just outside the village they spotted something - a bottle of mineral water, and some freshly cooked rice and meat.就在村外，他们发现了一些东西—一瓶矿泉水，一些刚煮熟的米饭和肉。译文来源：三泰虎http://www.santaihu.com/48263.html译者：JoyceliuTwo things were clear and disturbing. The suspects were nearby, that was the good news; and they had likely abandoned their precious food because they had spotted the Army Team, and were certainly in a postion of advantage - that was the bad news. There was no time to readjust.有两件事十分清楚，也令人不安。嫌疑人就在附近，这是个好消息；他们可能因为发现了军队，放弃了他们珍贵的食物，而且肯定处于有利地位—这是个坏消息。没有时间重新调整。Then a burst of fire opened from the unknown hideout of one of the terrorists, and the army team also opened fire in retaliation. Colonel Mahadik was hit as nobody could see where the firing had come from.随后，一名恐怖分子从藏身之处突然开火，这支部队也采取了报复行动。Mahadik上校被击中，因为没有人知道枪声是从哪里发出的。The 3 men with the Colonel were in the open, and were sitting ducks because of being exposed to danger. To save his team, Colonel Mahadik opened fire even though blood was gushing from his wounds. He fired continuously while still being exposed and heavily wounded. He basically ensured that the terrorist did not fire the men behind him.和上校在一起行动的三个人都处在露天场地，由于暴露在危险之中，他们成了攻击目标。为了拯救他的队伍，Mahadik上校开枪了，尽管伤口鲜血四溅。他不断开枪，但仍然没有掩护，受了重伤。他确保了恐怖分子无法向他身后的人开枪。He ran out of ammunition but still kept the terrorists on the defensive mode, and was successful in his attempt; but blood loss was heavy. Colonel Mahadik had to be air lifted with the assistance of Major Praveen.他的弹药用完了，但恐怖分子依然处于防守状态，他的尝试成功了；但失血过多。Mahadik上校不得不在Praveen少校的协助下乘飞机离开。While airlifting, Major Praveen got a call from Col. Mahadik’s wife. All she asked with a tearful quivering voice was “ZINDA RAHENGE YA NAHI RAHENGE ? BAS ITNA BATA DO” (Will he survive or not? Just answer this). This question still haunts Major Praveen.在空运过程中，Praveen少校接到了Mahadik上校妻子的电话。她含泪颤抖着只问了一句：“他能活下来吗？只要回答我这个问题”。这个问题仍然困扰着Praveen少校。Colonel Mahadik was declared brought-in dead at the 92 Base Hospital in Srinagar. Colonel Mahadik was martyred in the line of duty, but till his last moments, he ensured the safety of his men. Salute to the Brave soul and his family.Mahadik上校在斯里纳加尔的92所基地医院被宣布死亡。Mahadik上校因公殉职，但直到他的最后一项任务，他都一直确保他属下士兵的安全。向这个勇敢的灵魂和他的家人致敬。http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/f3717e231e3bbea9e53ab14fb64c9654.jpg</span><br>
<span> Col. Mahadik with his family - Happy Times. Wish time could stand still at these moments.THE OTHER OFFICERMahadik上校和他的家人-快乐的时光。但愿时间能在这些时刻停止。另一个军官http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/3d727a84838c31e0e20620508171fa7f.jpg</span><br>
<span> http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/57a584d08a11fdf71c870200eb57619d.jpg</span><br>
<span> The Officer and the Gentlewoman军官和那位贵妇人She is Lt. Swati Mahadik, wife of the Late Colonel Santosh Mahadik. She was commissioned into the Indian Army as Lieutenant in 2017.她是斯瓦蒂·马哈迪克中尉，已故上校桑托什·马哈迪克的妻子。2017年，她被任命为印度陆军中尉。As she completed her Passing-Out Parade, she broke down into tears both of joy and remembrance. The proud moment of the Passing Out Parade was witnessed by her son Swaraj and daughter Kartikee.当她完成她的送别会操时，她高兴得热泪盈眶，回忆起往事。她的儿子斯瓦拉杰和女儿卡蒂基见证了这一自豪的时刻。Such is the grit and determination of our Armed Forces and their families. She had silently resolved to join the Indian Army at the funeral of her husband in November 2015.这就是我们的武装部队及其家属的勇气和决心。2015年11月，在丈夫的葬礼上，她暗自决定加入印度军队。Swati had already crossed the upper age limit for entering the army, and it was only after the Indian Army and Ministry of Defence specially relaxed the age limit for her that she could initiate her new career goals.斯瓦蒂已经过了参军的年龄上限，在印度军队和国防部特别放宽了对她的年龄限制之后，她才得以开始新的职业目标。After undergoing several rounds of SSB and physical fitness and medical examinations as part of the process, she was selected to join the Officers Training Academy in Chennai.在经历了几轮SSB和身体健康及体检后，她被选中加入金奈的军官培训学院。Her husband’s martyrdom did not become her tragedy, it was not her setback. It became her life fuel. Their children, too, will grow up knowing the true meaning of valour, family and patriotism.她丈夫的殉难没有成为她的悲剧，也没有成为她的挫折。反而成了她生命的燃料。他们的孩子长大后也会明白勇敢、家庭和爱国主义的真正含义。Strength does not come from ammunitions, tanks and weapons. It comes from the will power, determination and mettle of the minds operating these weapons.力量不是来自弹药、坦克和武器。而是来自操作这些武器的人的意志力、决心和勇气。THIS IS ARMY STRONG - INDIAN ARMY STRONG这是一支强大的军队—强大的印度军队Salute to the people in uniform and their families.向军人和他们的家属致敬。A Heartfelt Thank you to the Press Information Bureau of India and Shiv Aroor of India Today and Rahul Singh of the Hindustan Times for the wonderful insight.衷心感谢印度新闻局、《今日印度》的希夫·阿鲁尔和《印度斯坦时报》的拉胡尔·辛格的精彩见解。Jai Hind.印度万岁。</span><br>
<span>Oraf Moin, Proprietor at Hind National Exports (1992-present)Strong enough , really strong, if you looked at the armed forces within an Indic prism but weak or too below potential if you look at us from the lens of a traditional power like British empire, Russian empire, Ottoman empire etc.如果你从印度的角度来看武装力量，那足够强大，非常强大，但如果你从传统强国的角度看待我们，比如大英帝国，俄罗斯帝国，奥斯曼帝国等等，你就会发现我们的实力很弱，或者说太无潜力。The modern Indic nation sees the army as a force designed to knock out any blitzkrieg onto our land as with what happened in 1962. We can make any war costly enough for even multiple aggressors to consider it not worth it.现代印度国家将军队视为一种旨在摧毁我们土地上任何闪电战的力量，就像1962年发生的那样。我们可以让任何战争都付出足够惨重的代价，让侵略者认为这种进攻得不偿失。But then we can't fight offensive wars or occupy new territory and hold it till it's incorporated into our mainland. No, our armed forces can't pull that off.但是我们没有能力展开进攻性的战争或者占领新的领土，让其并入我们的大陆。不，我们的军队做不到。We can't fight a long theater war either but then we don't need to as we're nuclear armed already and are just a step away from intercontinental missile research conclusion. We have a robust space programme to complement this.我们也没有能力展开长期战争，不过我们也没有这个需要，因为我们已经拥有核武器，距离洲际导弹的成功仅有一步之遥。我们有强大的太空计划来补充这一点。We are an excellent defensive force but we never were a warning expansionist nation even during Akbar. We ceased that since Kalinga battle under Asoka.我们是一支优秀的防御力量，但即使在阿克巴时期，我们也不是扩张主义国家。自从阿育王治下的卡林加战役以来，我们就停止了这种行动。</span><br>
<span>Dheeraj K. Shavan, Doctor of veterinary med from SKUAST JammuIndian army is the 2nd largest army in the world.But not in terms of numbers, Indian army has proven its strength time and again ,let me supplement it with few recent happenings in my state of j&k.印度军队是世界第二大军队。但不是在数量上，印度军队已经一次又一次证明了它的实力，让我补充一下我所在的查谟邦最近发生的一些事情。http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-08-19/f6c46efc08cd93903ffec50621e044a5.jpg</span><br>
<span> 1.The guy encircled in the above pic is Naved Jutt the most dreaded terrorist and commander of LeT in Kashmir. He is from Multan Pakistan. He has escaped from police custody 10 months back . Few days ago his video surfaced on net in which he was roaming outside his hideout and it was snowing there . Based on this video and inputs from it Indian army and intelligence agencies tracked him and he was killed along with his associates in Budgam today . This shows Indian army’s capability.</span><br>
<span>[*]上图中圈中的人是克什米尔地区最可怕的恐怖分子和LeT的指挥官。他来自巴基斯坦的木尔坦。10个月前，他从警方的拘留中逃脱。几天前，他的视频出现在网上，当时他正在藏身之处外面散步，那里正在下雪。根据这个视频，印度军队和情报机构对他进行了跟踪，他和他的同伙今天在布加姆被杀。这显示了印度军队的能力。</span><br>
<span>moral: Indian army is too powerful to be challenged in this way . These terrorists had tried to show that Indian army is weak and they can openly post pics and videos online without being traced . Indian army proved them wrong .Jai Hind.印度军队太强大了，无法通过这种方式被挑衅。这些恐怖分子试图表明印度军队软弱无能，他们可以公开在网上发布照片和视频，行踪不会被发现。印度军队证明他们大错特错。印度万岁。</span><br>
</p><p><b>十六夜pad长: </b><br>
<span>太长了我看不过来，不过我看到了最后两个单词，我觉得已经很能概括本文的主旨了。</span><br>
<span>Jai Hind.</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 OPPO PCCM00, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>Awensama: </b><br>
<span>别问，问就是Jai Hind</span><br>
</p><p><b>darkgem: </b><br>
<span>学习到了一些无用的知识，JAI HIND!</span><br>
</p><p><b>typeunknown: </b><br>
<span>看了几行，就是说，指挥系统一团乱麻？</span><br>
</p><p><b>猫?魔铃: </b><br>
<span>是是,知道你不再是封建家将制,装备了电话,会看表识字,好厉害啊</span><br>
<span>— from Xiaomi MIX 2, Android 9 of S1 Next Goose v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>blackll7: </b><br>
<span>我觉得搬运粪这种事情，无论是国产粪还是印度产粪丢到泥潭这个垃圾箱里都是违反垃圾处理公约的，请自觉排入下水道</span><br>
</p><p><b>活久见: </b><br>
<span>7.他们清理完一层，接着清理下一层时，必须在那层留下至少两个人来对付恐怖分子，以防他们往下跑。(所以当他们接近顶层时，人手越来越少减少)。</span><br>
<span>这是黑还是在赞。。。写算法也不这么写吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>シャスタ: </b><br>
<span>typeunknown 发表于 2019-8-19 14:14</span><br>
<span>看了几行，就是说，指挥系统一团乱麻？</span><br>
<span>讲的是一团乱麻然后表现出色....</span><br>
<span>这么大的国家,有几个能打的本来也不稀罕.</span><br>
</p><p><b>搞不好是洗衣粉: </b><br>
<span>草，用孟买恐怖袭击吹军队，印度人真的牛逼</span><br>
</p><p><b>敖轩: </b><br>
<span>写得很好，应该真的能忽悠到不太了解印度的人。</span><br>
</p><p><b>yujiacyl: </b><br>
<span>1962，jai hind！</span><br>
</p><p><b>シャスタ: </b><br>
<span>印度内有恐怖分子,外有巴基斯坦. </span><br>
<span>跟中国的双方投石在边界群殴,就不算威胁了吧......</span><br>
<span>内外威胁的大小,军队实际出动的需求比我国还高吧.</span><br>
</p><p><b>victorzl: </b><br>
<span>整支部队一边跳舞一边做布朗运动并且还能完成任务确实很了不起....</span><br>
</p><p><b>viasnow: </b><br>
<span>印度军队有勇敢之人，高尚之人，有专业的反恐精英</span><br>
<span>指挥部嘛，建议慈父式清洗</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 OnePlus ONEPLUS A6010, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>lexi: </b><br>
<span>Jai Hind.</span><br>
<span>Jai Hind.</span><br>
<span>Jai Hind.</span><br>
<span>真相不重要，重要的是Jai Hind. 重要的事情要说三遍。</span><br>
</p><p><b>白夜羽: </b><br>
<span>Jai Hind!就完事了</span><br>
</p><p><b>KA0827: </b><br>
<span>说传统强国的时候，为什么要把奥斯曼拿出来说事</span><br>
</p><p><b>213专用: </b><br>
<span>Jai Hind.</span><br>
</p><p><b>狒狗: </b><br>
<span>lexi 发表于 2019-8-19 14:22</span><br>
<span>Jai Hind.</span><br>
<span>Jai Hind.</span><br>
<span>Jai Hind.</span><br>
<span>jail hind！</span><br>
</p><p><b>爱周日的风: </b><br>
<span>孟买事件其实持续了三天这也能吹，放同样装备人数的恐怖份子要能在上海蹦哒三天简直不可想象</span><br>
</p><p><b>ST2002: </b><br>
<span>搞不好是洗衣粉 发表于 2019-8-19 14:16</span><br>
<span>草，用孟买恐怖袭击吹军队，印度人真的牛逼</span><br>
<span>我觉得是高端黑，类似“我家是茅坑随你进，反正迟早给熏跑”的感觉</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 OnePlus ONEPLUS A6010, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>星野心叶: </b><br>
<span>Jai Hind!</span><br>
</p><p><b>Ritchie.Player: </b><br>
<span>茶好喝先生那么近的例子咋不吹阿？</span><br>
<span>mig21击落F16可是空战史留名的哦</span><br>
</p><p><b>十六夜pad长: </b><br>
<span>爱周日的风 发表于 2019-8-19 14:28</span><br>
<span>孟买事件其实持续了三天这也能吹，放同样装备人数的恐怖份子要能在上海蹦哒三天简直不可想象 ...</span><br>
<span>我本来想掏出毛子来喷一下三哥，结果一查莫斯科大剧院人质事件，毛子也是等了三天</span><br>
<span>当然两件事的难度也许不能相提并论，但这一瞬间我倒是无处下口了</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 OPPO PCCM00, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>Realplayer: </b><br>
<span>这不是自黑？</span><br>
</p><p><b>钢琴男: </b><br>
<span> 天啊 孟买恐怖袭击也能丧事喜办的么…… 我还以为会脸红一下</span><br>
</p><p><b>kuputaer: </b><br>
<span>KA0827 发表于 2019-8-19 14:24</span><br>
<span>说传统强国的时候，为什么要把奥斯曼拿出来说事</span><br>
<span>罗马当然是强国</span><br>
</p><p><b>zz_mps: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 zz_mps 于 2019-8-19 14:41 编辑 </span><br>
<span>"帕蒂尔介绍说，初步调查显示，共有10名恐怖分子参与了袭击，其中9人在交火中被击毙，1人被活捉。"</span><br>
<span>"2008年11月26日21点30分至29日10点长达近60个小时的恐怖袭击造成195人死亡，另有295人受伤，死者主要是印度人，但也包括至少22名外国旅客。"</span><br>
<span>“11月26日21时30分左右，一伙端着冲锋枪、拎着手榴弹的恐怖分子闯入孟买最知名的五星级饭店——**饭店，他们见人就扫射，随处投掷手榴弹。几乎与此同时，奥贝罗伊酒店、犹太人聚居的纳里曼大楼、一个大市场以及交通最繁忙的CST火车站等9个地方也遭到恐怖分子的袭击。”</span><br>
<span>我怀疑这规模的恐怖袭击不只十个人</span><br>
</p><p><b>pureblackcc: </b><br>
<span>这个有个电影的电影看完感觉印度是真的垃圾</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 OnePlus ONEPLUS A3010, Android 8.0.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.0-play</span><br>
</p><p><b>tyx776: </b><br>
<span>我怎么看着觉得是自黑。三人中了伏击，一般来说是应该是赶紧找掩体躲起来吧，原地乱射是干嘛？</span><br>
</p><p><b>触手皇帝: </b><br>
<span>Jai Hind</span><br>
</p><p><b>天网: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 天网 于 2019-8-19 14:49 编辑 </span><br>
<span>十亿印度人真是人人都能吐莲花，快点给他们输出百家号，每个人都注册个账号上去吹牛逼，每天一打开搜索引起全是各种jai hind百家号 , 各种点、各种关联推荐无限jai hind ，让印度互联网上每一个角度充满jai hind，让印度人每天上网的娱乐活动就是沉浸在各种jai hind里，盛况超过两千年前的全民辩经</span><br>
</p><p><b>KA0827: </b><br>
<span>文章里说反恐的那个例子，很大一部分是在批评官僚系统无能乱指挥，赞美勇于牺牲的基层士兵和军官。我觉得这部分的立意还是不错的</span><br>
</p><p><b>flyreder: </b><br>
<span>想知道印度的反恐战跟我们南疆的治安战比成色怎么样？</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>走在路上: </b><br>
<span>十六夜pad长 发表于 2019-8-19 14:33</span><br>
<span>我本来想掏出毛子来喷一下三哥，结果一查莫斯科大剧院人质事件，毛子也是等了三天</span><br>
<span> ...</span><br>
<span>毛子那边首先四十多个恐怖分子，印度只有十来个</span><br>
<span>最重要的是，两边虽然都死了一百多老百姓，但是莫斯科那边大部分都是毛子自己弄死的，孟买是被恐怖分子弄死的，完全不一样好吧</span><br>
<span>当然我建议你可以两边一起黑</span><br>
</p><p><b>wuxan94: </b><br>
<span>flyreder 发表于 2019-8-19 15:11</span><br>
<span>想知道印度的反恐战跟我们南疆的治安战比成色怎么样？</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端 ...</span><br>
<span>西域省已经成为种花灯芯了……</span><br>
<span>三哥敢说他的东北邦么～</span><br>
</p><p><b>03e7: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 03e7 于 2019-8-19 15:46 编辑 </span><br>
<span>总结一下：</span><br>
<span>孟买事件！</span><br>
<span>Jai Hind！</span><br>
<span>一个上校带队搜索恐怖分子，被对面打了伏击英勇牺牲！</span><br>
<span>Jai Hind！</span><br>
<span>一个军人遗孀在丈夫去世后加入了军队！</span><br>
<span>Jai Hind！</span><br>
<span>印度62年赢了！</span><br>
<span>印度从没进攻过其他国家！</span><br>
<span>印军通过一个逃离了监狱10个月的恐怖分子头目发布的视频，锁定了他的所在地并击毙了他！</span><br>
<span>Jai Hind！</span><br>
</p><p><b>soulogic: </b><br>
<span>第一个答案那哥们，为了确认不是高级黑专门找了原帖 https://www.quora.com/How-strong-is-the-Indian-Army-actually/answer/Karan-Sachdev-10</span><br>
<span>签名是： A proud Indian; A defence Aspirant and an IT professional</span><br>
<span>貌似目前在印度空军做运维 JWM in Ordnance Factory. at Ministry of Defence, India and Sachin Hooda, works at Indian Air Force (2003-present)</span><br>
</p><p><b>03e7: </b><br>
<span>国家安全卫队从这三个地点救出了600多名平民。国家安全卫队接管后，没有再次出现平民伤亡。没有平民伤亡。唯一的伤亡是两名烈士</span><br>
<span>没记错的话这时恐怖分子已经处决了手上的所有人质，40分钟后科比再也不能从我手上拿走1分？</span><br>
</p><p><b>popeacg: </b><br>
<span>炊事班警告</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 OnePlus ONEPLUS A5010, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>比琪老师: </b><br>
<span>我们可以放局座</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 vivo NEX S, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.0.4-play</span><br>
</p><p><b>hcmn: </b><br>
<span>他们肯定不会说最近的空袭巴基斯坦是什么下场来着</span><br>
</p><p><b>woxihuan23: </b><br>
<span>嘟嘟嘟！呼嘎咕！</span><br>
</p><p><b>剑鹰: </b><br>
<span>举的例子完全看不出印度军队有啥强大的...感觉是弱鸡啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>血满沙场: </b><br>
<span>看标题就猜到是废狗老师</span><br>
</p><p><b>Spartan-117: </b><br>
<span>zz_mps 发表于 2019-8-19 14:39</span><br>
<span>"帕蒂尔介绍说，初步调查显示，共有10名恐怖分子参与了袭击，其中9人在交火中被击毙，1人被活捉。"</span><br>
<span>"2008 ...</span><br>
<img src="https://pic3.zhimg.com/80/v2-e632458851226f2ccc568f61b46d4e3e_hd.jpg" title="https://pic3.zhimg.com/80/v2-e632458851226f2ccc568f61b46d4e3e_hd.jpg"><br>
<span>毕竟是这样放反恐的。。。</span><br>
</p><p><b>ualiant: </b><br>
<span>hcmn 发表于 2019-8-19 16:03</span><br>
<span>他们肯定不会说最近的空袭巴基斯坦是什么下场来着</span><br>
<span>不是宣布大获全胜了么</span><br>
</p><p><b>kawa11: </b><br>
<span>满篇都是我淦你讲吼，你造我们军队有多努力吗</span><br>
</p><p><b>dark_templar: </b><br>
<span>hcmn 发表于 2019-8-19 16:03</span><br>
<span>他们肯定不会说最近的空袭巴基斯坦是什么下场来着</span><br>
<span>只有印度能击落不存在的F-16！Jai Hind!</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1854436[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
