<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>看一本小说，看到里边介绍的一种搞笑的历史学派</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>看一本小说，看到里边介绍的一种搞笑的历史学派</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 19:33:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>看一本小说，看到里边介绍的一种搞笑的历史学派[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1841744-1-1.html</link>
      <description>看一本小说，看到里边介绍的一种搞笑的历史学派&#13;
如题，这种搞笑历史学派真的存在吗，有大佬了解的话，介绍一下</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>慈悲为怀海大王: </b><br>
<span>看一本小说，看到里边介绍的一种搞笑的历史学派</span><br>
<span>如题，这种搞笑历史学派真的存在吗，有大佬了解的话，介绍一下</span><br>
</p><p><b>Diabolosis: </b><br>
<span>建议使用图床</span><br>
<span>http://sm.ms</span><br>
</p><p><b>mcmurdo: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 mcmurdo 于 2019-6-23 23:55 编辑 </span><br>
<span>The Strauss–Howe generational theory, also known as the Fourth Turning theory or simply the Fourth Turning, which was created by authors William Strauss and Neil Howe, describes a theorized recurring generation cycle in American history.</span><br>
<span>According to the theory, historical events are associated with recurring generational personas (archetypes). Each generational persona unleashes a new era (called a turning) in which a new social, political, and economic climate exists. Turnings tend to last around 20–22 years. They are part of a larger cyclical "saeculum" (a long human life, which usually spans between 80–90 years, although some saecula have lasted longer).</span><br>
<span>The theory states that after every Saeculum, a crisis recurs in American history, which is followed by a recovery (high). During this recovery, institutions and communitarian values are strong. Ultimately, succeeding generational archetypes attack and weaken institutions in the name of autonomy and individualism, which ultimately creates a tumultuous political environment that ripens conditions for another crisis.</span><br>
<span>Strauss and Howe laid the groundwork for their theory in their 1991 book Generations, which discusses the history of the United States as a series of generational biographies going back to 1584. In their 1997 book The Fourth Turning, the authors expanded the theory to focus on a fourfold cycle of generational types and recurring mood eras in American history. They have since expanded on the concept in a variety of publications. It was developed to describe the history of the United States, including the Thirteen Colonies and their British antecedents, and this is where the most detailed research has been done. However, the authors have also examined generational trends elsewhere in the world and described similar cycles in several developed countries.</span><br>
<span>In a 2009 article published in The Chronicle of Higher Education, Eric Hoover called the authors pioneers in a burgeoning industry of consultants, speakers and researchers focused on generations. Academic response to the theory has been mixed—some applauding Strauss and Howe for their "bold and imaginative thesis" and others criticizing the theory. Criticism has focused on the lack of rigorous empirical evidence for their claims, and the authors' view that generational groupings are far more powerful than other social groupings such as economic class, race, sex, religion and political parties.</span><br>
<span>According to The New York Times, many academic historians dismiss the work of Strauss & Howe as "about as scientific as astrology or a Nostradamus text."</span><br>
<span>Strauss-Howe generational theory has been described by some historians and journalists as a "pseudoscience" and "an elaborate historical horoscope that will never withstand scholarly scrutiny."另外说一句，这俩人只有Strauss是哈佛毕业的，俩人后来也都没在哈佛工作</span><br>
</p><p><b>Thermo: </b><br>
<span>我的眼睛</span><br>
</p><p><b>慈悲为怀海大王: </b><br>
<span>再试试</span><br>
</p><p><b>慈悲为怀海大王: </b><br>
<span>blob:https://sm.ms/218e2042-657a-4305-b34f-e65eda478708</span><br>
</p><p><b>mcmurdo: </b><br>
<span>慈悲为怀海大王 发表于 2019-6-24 00:06</span><br>
<span>blob:https://sm.ms/218e2042-657a-4305-b34f-e65eda478708</span><br>
<span>别试了，都给你找出来了……</span><br>
</p><p><b>慈悲为怀海大王: </b><br>
<span>说实话这种历史解读方式跟我们的300年王朝轮回挺像的</span><br>
</p><p><b>小小陌路人: </b><br>
<span>这字，莫不是打了马赛克，就不能发文字吗？</span><br>
</p><p><b>j0n2: </b><br>
<span>贴文字啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>苑生百花: </b><br>
<span>傅高义？</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1841744[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
