<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>【美国】得州发生枪击事件，已造成20人死亡</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>【美国】得州发生枪击事件，已造成20人死亡</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 18:33:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>【美国】得州发生枪击事件，已造成20人死亡[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1851150-1-1.html</link>
      <description>【美国】得州发生枪击事件，已造成20人死亡&#13;
【美国得州发生一起严重枪击案 造成至少19人死亡】#美国得州超市枪击案#当地时间3日，美国得克萨斯州艾尔帕索市一超市发生一起严重枪击案，造成至少19人死亡，40人受伤。目前警方已逮捕3名嫌疑人，另有媒体报道警方只逮捕了一名嫌疑人。有媒体称，枪手是一名年轻的白人男子，作案动机目前仍不清楚。（央视新闻）

https://i.loli.net/2019/08/04/BN3UZrceXTovLhF.jpg

个人感想：行吧，日常又来了，这次怎么没有红脖子拔枪对射了？</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>lDaive: </b><br>
<span>【美国】得州发生枪击事件，已造成20人死亡</span><br>
<span>【美国得州发生一起严重枪击案 造成至少19人死亡】#美国得州超市枪击案#当地时间3日，美国得克萨斯州艾尔帕索市一超市发生一起严重枪击案，造成至少19人死亡，40人受伤。目前警方已逮捕3名嫌疑人，另有媒体报道警方只逮捕了一名嫌疑人。有媒体称，枪手是一名年轻的白人男子，作案动机目前仍不清楚。（央视新闻）</span><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/08/04/BN3UZrceXTovLhF.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/08/04/BN3UZrceXTovLhF.jpg"><br>
<span>个人感想：行吧，日常又来了，这次怎么没有红脖子拔枪对射了？</span><br>
</p><p><b>lhawp: </b><br>
<span>说好的人均配枪呢？</span><br>
</p><p><b>fatimagg01: </b><br>
<span>艾尔帕索 南美城市的名字啊。。。</span><br>
</p><p><b>Benighted: </b><br>
<span>EL PASO, Texas - UPDATE #6 5:30:</span><br>
<span>In a news conference surrounded by city leaders and law enforcement agencies, Governor Greg Abbott confirmed that 20 people have died in the mass shooting near Cielo Vista Mall. </span><br>
<span>Police responded at 10:45 a.m., six minutes after the first 911 call went out. El Paso Police said 26 people are injured. Chief Greg Allen said the scene is a horrific one. </span><br>
<span>Chief Allen said the suspect who is in custody is a 21-year-old white male from Allen, TX. He would not confirm the suspect's name. Police confirmed the suspect used an AK-47 rifle in the attack. </span><br>
<span>The deceased will also remain at the scene until the crime is cleared. </span><br>
<span>The State of Texas will be the lead agency prosecuting the suspect. It is not confirmed if the mass shooting is a hate crime. </span><br>
<span>The FBI said is it a murder investigation and is currently reviewing all the evidence at this time. </span><br>
<span>The suspect was around outside the Walmart where the initial shooting took place. Chief Allen said he surrendered to police. </span><br>
<span>Governor Abbott said the state is doing more than ever before, specifically during the last legislative session, to make sure students are safer than ever before after the mass shooting at Santa Fe High School near Houston. "During that time, as far as I know, we did not evaluate for or plan for a situation like this." Abbott said that during the legislative session, the most agreed upon issue was how to challenge mental health in the state.</span><br>
<span>Chief Allen said if there is additional information that needs to be released, another new conference could be scheduled. </span><br>
<span>The eighth deadliest shooting in the United States. This is the third year in a row that Texas has had a mass shooting. In 2018, 10 people died in the Santa Fe High School shooting. In 2017, 26 people died in the Sutherland Springs shooting. </span><br>
<span>UPDATE #5 4:21 pm </span><br>
<span>Law enforcement official tells the AP at least 15 dead in El Paso attack</span><br>
<span>The Associated Press and ABC News is reporting the suspect is 21-year-old Patrick Crusius</span><br>
<span>UPDATE #4 3:30 pm</span><br>
<span>From El Paso Police El Paso PD confirms 1 person in custody who is a white male in his 20s.</span><br>
<span>There were between 1-3 thousand people at Walmart when the shooting started. Police have transitioned into the criminal investigation. There have been fatalities but no confirmation on numbers of injuries or fatalities. Police believe at this time the shooter acted alone. The mall and Walmart have been cleared of potential shooting suspects. They do not believe there is a continued danger to the public. No motive or reason for why the sooting started given yet.</span><br>
<span>UPDATE #3 Del Sol Medical Center in El Paso confirms 11 patients ranging in age from 35yrs old to 82 yrs old were taken to their hospital. They say two are of the patients are in stable condition and nine are listed in critical condition. University Medical Center confirms 13 patients, 1 dead. No word on their conditions. Ages 2 through senior citizens.</span><br>
<span>These people need your help, by donating blood, you can directly save lives. Blood donation centers Vitalent Blood Services at 424 s Mesa Hills and 133 N Zaragoza. </span><br>
<span>UPDATE #2: Multiple people have been killed in the mass shooting in El Paso, according to police and the mayor's office. (WATCH LIVE COVERAGE BELOW)</span><br>
<span>One suspect was in custody, but authorities did not say exactly how many people were injured.</span><br>
<span>UPDATE #1: A witness told ABC-7 that they were next to the Wal-Mart off of Hawkins, and police started evacuating the area. The witness says there were people that came out of the Wal-Mart covered in blood. The witness walked into the Wal-Mart and says he saw one body on the ground with a serious injury to the head. </span><br>
<span>Police told everyone to evacuate the area or hide behind cars, according to the witness. Police believe multiple shooters are involved. </span><br>
<span>A second witness tells ABC-7 she was in JC Penny at the Cielo Vista mall when the reports of shooting came down. This witness says people were evacuated from Dillard's into JC Penny and then they were all evacuated from the area. </span><br>
<span>Our ABC-7 eyewitness confirms presence of Local & State Police, ICE, FBI, and the Homeland Security, as well as a mass casualty ambulance bus.</span><br>
<span>ORIGINAL REPORT:</span><br>
<span>El Paso police are reporting an active shooter situation near the Walmart on Hawkins and Gateway East and the Cielo Vista Mall; police said there were multiple reports of multiple shooters and they are conducting a large area search.</span><br>
<span>Police said the scene on the city's east side is still active and they are warning all members of the public to stay away from the area of Airway to Hawkins north of Interstate 10.</span><br>
<span>A witness tells ABC-7 people are being escorted out of the mall with their hands in the air.</span><br>
<span>The federal Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco and Firearms had agents en route to the mall area; the ATF asked that people refrain from posting images of first responders to social media.</span><br>
<span>Employees at several nearby restaurants told CNN they see a lot of police, helicopters and people running around outside.</span><br>
<span>"We never thought it would be so close to us this time," Landry's Seafood House restaurant manager Oscar Collazo told CNN. "You see on the news all the time, but you don't think it could happen here until it does."​​​​​​</span><br>
<span>We will continue to update as more information becomes available.</span><br>
</p><p><b>Benighted: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 Benighted 于 2019-8-4 08:53 编辑 </span><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/08/04/xjrV9XldzuZPJnA.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/08/04/xjrV9XldzuZPJnA.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/08/04/fLUj26WCwvarY1q.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/08/04/fLUj26WCwvarY1q.jpg"><br>
</p><p><b>雨井绫: </b><br>
<span>洒洒水啦，大家斗习惯了</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>amachi333: </b><br>
<span>让你们不996，看把人闲的</span><br>
</p><p><b>慈父斯大林: </b><br>
<span>这次怎么没有红脖子拔枪对射了</span><br>
<span>当前人力0，美国每个月可以补充6个红脖子。</span><br>
<span>每月获得：6</span><br>
<span>基础：5</span><br>
<span>MAGA：+20%</span><br>
<span>人力反映了可以在枪击案中拔枪对射的红脖子数量。</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1851150[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
