<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>美国上空惊现神秘天象！</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>美国上空惊现神秘天象！</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 11:04:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>美国上空惊现神秘天象！[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1906212-1-1.html</link>
      <description>美国上空惊现神秘天象！&#13;
https://b23.tv/av80986242

美国人还是赶快习惯，明年好多的不要大惊小怪啦</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>shadowm: </b><br>
<span>美国上空惊现神秘天象！</span><br>
<span>https://b23.tv/av80986242</span><br>
<span>美国人还是赶快习惯，明年好多的不要大惊小怪啦</span><br>
</p><p><b>lrinr: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 lrinr 于 2019-12-29 05:56 编辑 </span><br>
<span>疑似蹭热度，边上推荐那个观察网的长征7号才是原版吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>nominication47: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 nominication47 于 2019-12-29 06:13 编辑 </span><br>
<span>一开始我还以为是假新闻，没想到是真的。关岛和塞班岛的美国居民拍到的。</span><br>
<span>下面是新闻来源</span><br>
<span>https://pncguam.com/ghs-reports- ... danger-to-marianas/</span><br>
<span>Friday night lights may have been debris from Chinese commercial rocket</span><br>
<span>By Pacific News Center      - December 28, 2019</span><br>
<img src="https://wx4.sinaimg.cn/mw690/005PijCAly1gad6gv753dj30zy0p8wn9.jpg" title="https://wx4.sinaimg.cn/mw690/005PijCAly1gad6gv753dj30zy0p8wn9.jpg"><br>
<span>It seems that the light show residents saw Friday night over Guam skies may not have been a meteorite after all, but debris from a Chinese commercial rocket launch falling back to earth.</span><br>
<span>Guam Homeland Security/Office of Civil Defense is citing Chinese media reports about “a heavy-lift Long March 5 rocket” carrying a test satellite payload that blasted off from the Wenchang launch site on the southern island of Hainan at 8.45 p.m. Friday night</span><br>
<span>According to Homeland Security, this commercial space launch occurred at 10:45 ChST and corresponds with an FAA Notice to Airmen that was active from 10:43 p.m. until 2:41 a.m.</span><br>
<span>Tim Cornelison, Air Traffic Manager, Guam Air Route Traffic Control Center, said the following official communique was issued from FAA:</span><br>
<span>“The China National Space Administration has planned a rocket launch. Debris from this launch will fall within an area defined as 1425n/14853e to 1518n/14906e to 1547n/14655e to 1454n/14643e to point of origin. In the interest of safety, all non-participating air traffic are advised to avoid the notamed (notice to airmen) area. If aircraft under ATC jurisdiction should anticipate clearance around the notamed area. Sfc-unl, 27 dec 12:43 2019 until 27 dec 16:41 2019. Created: 24 dec 16:32 2019.”</span><br>
<span>Cornelson said the times referred to in the notice are UTC coordinated universal time and not local time.</span><br>
<span>It is unclear whether notice was given to local authorities as well.</span><br>
<span>But Cornelson said the notice to airmen are distributed worldwide on an aviation network and also publicly available.</span><br>
<span>He added that the basic rule is that all pilots check NOTAMs before they fly and all airlines check NOTAMs prior to releasing, or dispatching flights.</span><br>
<span>Connected?</span><br>
<span>“The atmospheric phenomena that was witnessed in the vicinity of the Marianas occurred around 11:25 p.m. ChST,” GHS stated in a news release without elaborating whether the Chinese rocket launch and the “atmospheric phenomena” were connected.</span><br>
<span>There was no mention of whether the “atmospheric phenomena” that GHS was referring to were the lights seen descending down the sky Friday night, which had earlier been described by a National Weather Service meteorologist as a meteorite that was breaking up.</span><br>
<span>GHS did assure that there is no direct threat to the Marianas from the launch and that more information will be provided as it becomes available.</span><br>
<span>According to a Dec. 27 report on the website SPACEFLIGHT NOW, the third launch of China’s heavy-lift Long March 5 rocket successfully delivered its satellite payload to orbit Friday, clearing the way for the launch of a Chinese Mars rover and lunar sample return mission in 2020.</span><br>
<span>According to the article, the 187-foot-tall (57-meter) rocket is the most powerful in China’s fleet and it lifted off from the Wenchang Satellite Launch Center on Hainan Island in southern China at 1245 GMT (7:45 a.m. EST; 8:45 p.m. Beijing time) Friday.</span><br>
<span>The National Weather Service has also not issued any conclusive statement on whether the lights were a meteorite and acknowledges in its Facebook page that the lights may be debris from an earlier Chinese rocket or booster test.</span><br>
<span>The Friday night lights came amid speculation about a North Korean “Christmas surprise” missile test launch that didn’t materialize.</span><br>
<span>Still, a number of PNC Facebook viewers expressed concern about Guam’s early warning system.</span><br>
<span>One commented: “What if it was the real thing? No alarm system activated. What’s the use of the alarm system test?</span><br>
<span>##</span><br>
<span>整天JB说中国民用航天与军方联系深厚，是巨大威胁。</span><br>
<span>结果真有东西砸到自己军事基地附近的时候，赶紧出来平息事端，告诉国民是“商用火箭”。</span><br>
<span>呵呵，美帝真是好交往呢，不讲道理，只认力量。</span><br>
</p><p><b>lrinr: </b><br>
<span>nominication47 发表于 2019-12-29 05:52</span><br>
<span>一开始我还以为是假新闻，没想到是真的。关岛和塞班岛的美国居民拍到的。</span><br>
<span>下面是新闻来源</span><br>
<span>https://pncguam. ...</span><br>
<span>是真的啊...我看路径离塞班有段距离，竟然这么闪亮。</span><br>
</p><p><b>nanrendu: </b><br>
<span>好大的烟火，好看。</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1906212[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
