<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>雷普斯坦：为什么印度女孩的态度很傲？</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>雷普斯坦：为什么印度女孩的态度很傲？</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 19:58:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>雷普斯坦：为什么印度女孩的态度很傲？[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1837642-1-1.html</link>
      <description>雷普斯坦：为什么印度女孩的态度很傲？&#13;
Why in India girls have so much of attitude?为什么印度女孩态度很傲？http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-06-07/0be93f82288f6eb74091b1134eccde32.jpgQuora读者的评论：AnonymousNot all of them have attitude but situations make you feel so.I'm going to answer this question according to the experience I had.About me: I'm a regular girl in my late teens and curvy (not fat) and interested in sports.I'm not going to be a feminist or a feminazi here, nor am I here to put down any of the gender. So please read it with a neutral mind.Back to the school days…..不是所有的人都是这样的态度，但是有些情况下会让你有这样的感觉。我会根据我的经验来回答这个问题。说说我自己：我是一个普通的十八九岁少女，身材玲珑有致(不胖)，对体育感兴趣。我不想把自己变成女权主义者或极端女权主义者，也不会在这里贬低任何性别。所以请大家以中立的心态来阅读。回到学生时代…Incident 1.Class 12th, badminton court (2 years ago)I love playing badminton and used to give a tough competition to everybody.We were playing a doubles match and my team mate was a boy (let's call him T)So I've standard size breasts. Suddenly out of no where another boy (let's name him K) standing in the same hall said “Hey T, nice T-shirt”. And then they all looked at me. It was clear that the remark was made for me.Just imagine the embarrassment I felt when he made a comment in front of a teacher, 4-5 girls, 7-8 boys. If I would have said anything then they would have clearly shrugged off this topic saying that they were praising T’s T-shirt. (Really? Praising. School uniform? Everyone else was wearing the same T-shirt).K is the same boy who rants about respecting girls on facebook. He has an elder sister and he loves his sister and mother and respect them (or shows it on facebook and instagram). He is the same boy who says how each one of us should respect a person.Now just imagine me ever meeting him in future. I'll always remember his words. I would never want to talk to him, I would not be able to. Then he'll be saying that what a arrogant bitch I'm who is so full of attitude.事件1。12年纪(2年前)，在羽毛球场我喜欢打羽毛球，曾经跟每个人都PK过。我们打双打，我的队友是个男孩(我们叫他T吧)我的胸部大小很正常。突然，另一个男孩(我们叫他K吧)站在大厅里说:“嘿，T，T恤真漂亮。”然后他们都盯着我。很明显，这句话是冲我说的。想象一下，当他当着老师和4-5个女孩，7-8个男孩的面说这话时，我有多尴尬。如果我说点什么，他们肯定会对撇开这个话题，说他们只是说T恤好看。(你们说的是真的吗？那可是校服啊！大家都穿着一样的衣服)。K也正是那个在facebook上痛声疾呼要尊重女孩的男孩。他有一个姐姐，他爱他的姐姐和妈妈，尊重她们(或者有可能只是在facebook和instagram上尊重而已)。他就是那个嘴里说着我们所有人都应该尊重别人的男孩。现在想象一下我将来遇到他会怎样。我会永远记住他的话。我永远不想和他说话，我没办法跟他交流。然后他就会说我是一个多么傲慢的婊子，态度那么拽。
&#13;
Hetal Dhanak, An Indian.Originally answered : why do girls in India have attitude problem ?I'm Indian girlI don't know whether I'm metro girl or normal typical Indian girl but I'll present my views here.1.I used to play with boys when I was a kid. At that time, both boys and girls were equal for me. (Metro girl)2.In primary school, we had boys and girls both in our class and we studied together. We used to talk (metro girl)3.In high school, we had only girls in our class so we never talked to boys. And yes WE WARE NOT ALLOWED TO TALK. Be it any reason( typical Indian girl)4.In 11-12 science. Again we had boys with us but again we were restricted. So we used to talk on study related topics only. (Somewhere between metro and typical Indian girl)5.Now, I'm in college. During initial days, there were problems interacting with boys because I never had talked before. ( attitude problem) and I was given so many advices boys are like this, they'll do this etc etc(I know there's nothing like that) but now I can talk with anyone. There's no problem(metro girl)So, you see the “the typical Indian girl” is having attitude problem(difficulty in interaction) because she has been given “typical”(disbelief and doubts) environment.Today also, if I'm standing with a boy, so many eyes will be staring me and not that boy. Such behaviour makes a normal Indian girl “a typical Indian girl”. (In some areas in India)I hope now you understood why we have attitude problem.译文来源：三泰虎 http://www.santaihu.com/47783.html 译者：Joyceliu最初的回答是：为什么印度女孩的态度都不好？我是个印度女孩。我也不知道我属于城市女孩还是普通女孩，但我想表达一下我的观点。1.我小时候常和男孩子们一起玩。那时，对我来说男孩和女孩都是平等的。(城市女孩)2.小学时，我们班有男孩和女孩，我们一起学习。我们会互相交谈(城市女孩)3.高中时，我们班只有女生，所以我们从来不和男生说话。是的，我们不允许跟男生说话。不管是什么原因(典型的印度女孩)4.在11 - 12年纪。我们又跟男孩在一起上课，但受到了很多限制。所以我们过去只讨论与学习相关的话题。(介于城市和典型印度女孩之间)5.现在，我在上大学。一开始我和男孩子们交流有一些问题，因为我从来没有和他们说过话。(于是我态度就显得有问题了)我得到了很多建议，比如男孩是这样的，他们会这样做，等等，但现在我可以和任何人无障碍交谈了。没有任何问题(城市女孩)所以，你看到“典型的印度女孩”有态度问题(交流困难)，因为她从小接受的就是“典型的”环境。今天，如果我和一个男孩站在一起，那么很多人会盯着我看，而不是那个男孩。这种行为使一个普通的印度女孩成为“一个典型的印度女孩”。(在印度的某些地区)我希望你现在明白为什么我们有态度方面的问题。
&#13;
AnonymousIf you meet an Indian girl born in the states or western country then she will not have an attitude and would be easier to deal with. So it is a culture thing.Here is why:1.Most of them do not have a lot of experience dating. Sure they must have been with a guy or maybe too. But, they haven’t really dated in the sense like western world does.2.They get pestered a lot by guys. Indian guys can be a bit possessive. I am Indian i know. Look at the movies in India. The hero is a loser who doesn’t stop chasing girls around.3.They know that no matter how they behave guys will keep tolerating there behavior. The guys in America and other countries have a lot of options and are not going to tolerate stupid behavior(they do to some extent). But, if the girl wants to keep a guy she has to have something more than looks. She needs a personality.How to fix the problem? I don’t know. But, you can be with an Indian girl who is a joy to be with not just a joy to look at. Also, i feel that once you get to know a person then they will open up and remove the fake attitude facade and be friendly to you如果你遇到一个出生在美国或西方国家的印度女孩，她就不会有态度，也更容易相处。所以这归根结底是文化问题。原因在于：1.她们中的大多数人没有丰富的约会经验。当然，她们肯定跟男的想出过。但是，她们并没有真正像西方世界那样约会过。2.她们经常被男人纠缠。印度男人占有欲可能有点太强了。我是印度人，所以我知道。看看印度的电影。英雄如果不停地追逐女孩子，就是个失败者。3.她们知道，不管她们怎么做，男人都会继续容忍她们的行为。美国和其他国家的男人有很多选择，但不会容忍愚蠢的行为(在某种程度上他们会)。但是，如果女孩想要留住一个男孩，她必须拥有比外表更重要的东西。她需要个性。如何解决这个问题？我不知道。但是，如果一个印度女孩是一个相处起来令人愉快的人，而不仅仅只是个花瓶，那么你可以跟她好好相处。而且，我觉得，一旦你了解一个人，她们就会敞开心扉，抛开虚假的态度，对你展现友好。
&#13;
Ritika Ojha, lived in IndiaIt took me a while to monitor myself regarding this question and here I am to satisfy your query.Yes I have been at times accused of this- guilty as charged. For some I am awesome, while a few pointed what an as***** I was, straight on my face.These views have been presented to me by strangers with whom I have interacted over the past few weeks. In former case, the company was enjoyable and we had a blast. We parted ways clearly commenting to each other how awesome the other person was, irrespective of the gender.Now comes the latter case, where either of the party didn't find something common to connect over. As such soon I lost interest and it became quite obvious through my body language. One date mentioned I was too rigid with my pov , because I didn't agree to his idea of HIS date. Another person thought I was shallow, and so forth. To be honest I have no shame in agreeing what they stated , as they were mostly true and the clear root cause was my own lack of further interest in their company.I have rarely had any such attitude issues with women , but such comments are more common from men, and I barely ever manage to lend an ear to it. At times when I was pointed out about this by the right person, I did realise my mistake and accepted it. The only reason was because he/she meant it in a genuine way.So in short, I mostly reflect back, your own attitude towards me. If you give me an attitude , be prepared to have a taste of your own medicine. For rest of the time, life js good.Disclaimer: this is the view of AN INDIAN LADY. Use of common sense is strongly advised ;)我花了一段时间来思考自己对这个问题的看法，现在我来回答你的疑问。是的，我有时会被指控——被指控态度有问题。有些人认为我很高傲，而有些人则认为我是一个彻头彻尾的混蛋。这些观点是我在过去几周内接触过的陌生人向我提出的。在以前的情况下，大家相处得很愉快，我们玩得很开心。我们分别的时候，不管对方是男是女，我们都清楚地告诉对方对方有多棒。现在是后一种情况，双方都没有找到共同点。所以很快我就失去了兴趣，通过我的肢体语言，我的态度变得非常明显。有一次约会时，因为我不同意对方对约会的看法，对方就说我的观念太死板了。另一个人认为我肤浅，等等。说实话，我同意他们的说法，但并不以为耻，因为大多数情况是真的，而根本原因就是我自己对他们缺乏进一步的兴趣。我对女性很少有这样的态度问题，但在男性中经常听到这种评论，我从来不想听。有时候，当有的人指出这一点时，我确实意识到自己的错误，我就接受。唯一的原因是因为他/她对我是真心实意的。所以简而言之，我会用你对我的态度反过来对付你。如果你对我态度不好，那就准备好自食其果吧。而除此之外，生活是美好的。免责声明：这是一位印度女士的观点。强烈建议读者阅读时要有基本常识。
&#13;
Pramod Kumar, studied at S.P College, Tilak Road, Pune-30.An Indian girl wants her family , relatives and society to believe that she doesn't have any boyfriend, she won't break their trust, she won't let her parents down, she has a fear inside to be called by different insulting names. In short, she prefers butt kissing of elders over love with her future possible life partner.Indian girls are so conservative that they don't even realise that it's just a matter of generation gap. Elders don't give a shit about her life, her desire, her colourful days. They just know to teach her to respect elders and kill her passion. An Indian girl has no idea how much she hurts her lover or boyfriend because of this awful and worthless societal customs. She believes hurting her bf is fine, cause he is a man so a man doesn't feel pain. She is afraid in taking a bold step and goes across boundaries. Many Indian girls are getting physically assaulted by their own parents. They are not physically strong to defend and protect themselves. Indian parents usually are famous for dominance over their children especially over daughters. That'swhy they have no other way but to show attitude to everyone even to strangers. The result is disastrous, they don't believe on anyone. They become a heartless creature with just flesh and blood looks like a “Real Girl”. Indian girls are not real girls. They are manufactured by societal fears as they grow up and become artifical inside and outside.一个印度女孩希望她的家人、亲戚和社会相信她没有男朋友，她不会辜负他们的信任，她不会让她的父母失望，她内心害怕被别人用侮辱性的名字称呼。简而言之，比起和未来可能的生活伴侣相爱，她更喜欢拍长辈的马屁。印度女孩非常保守，她们甚至没有意识到这只是代沟的问题。长辈们根本不关心她的生活，她的欲望，她多姿多彩的日子。他们只知道教她尊重长辈，扼杀她的激情。因为这种可怕的和毫无价值的社会习俗，一个印度女孩不知道她会如何伤害她的爱人或男友。她相信伤害她的男朋友是好的，因为他是一个男人，所以男人不会感到痛苦。她不敢迈出大胆的一步，不敢跨越界限。许多印度女孩被自己的父母殴打。她们没有强壮的身体来保护自己。印度父母通常以控制孩子，尤其是女儿而名声远扬。这就是为什么她们没有别的办法，只能对每个人，甚至是陌生人表现出桀骜的态度。结果是灾难性的，她们不相信任何人。她们变成了只有血肉的无情动物，只为了看起来像个“真正的女孩”。印度女孩不是真正的女孩。她们是由社会的恐惧制造出来的，随着她们的成长，她们的里里外外都不再真实。
&#13;
Abhishek Kumar, Web and Mobile Application DeveloperGirls have a simple formula ( especially for boys ). She will pay heed to you only if you are of some use for her. Now you will think, I am definitely of some use to some girl :) . Well, it works like this. She already has many (guys/boys) friends for entertaining her, so she don’t need you for entertainment, she already has several boyfriends ( and all are unaware of each other :) ), so, again she don’t need you for dating. she already has a brother and also some boys who pretend to be brother, so again she don’t need one more brother.In India, it doesn’t matter if a girl is beautiful or not. It’s not difficult for her to find guys to play some role in her life. But for boys, its just the opposite. If you are handsome, girls will definitely get attracted towards you but in some way or the other you will not fit her criteria and then you will be again no use for her.女孩有一个简单的公式(尤其是对男孩)。只有当你对她有用时，她才会注意你。现在你会想，我肯定对某些女孩有用。事实是这样的：她已经有很多(男孩)朋友陪她了，所以她不需要你，她已经有好几个男朋友了(而且互相都不认识)，所以，她也不需要你跟她约会。她已经有了一个哥哥，还有一些愿意假扮她哥哥的男孩，所以她也不需要再多一个哥哥了。在印度，女孩漂亮与否并不重要。对她来说，找到能在她生活中扮演某种角色的男人并不难。但对男孩来说，正好相反。如果你很帅，女孩肯定会被你吸引，但在某种程度上，如果你不符合她的标准，你对她毫无用处。
&#13;
Amar Bhatia, Php developer at HAV Solutions (2009-present)Buddy, I’ll tell you one thing for sure, Indian Girls are bullshit due to shitty bollywood movies, they think i will make this guy my dog and off course they can because all are the same but if you have enough money to blow, they themselves will come to you, off course not directly. let me explain.Dialogue of every women in the fucking world: I don’t want money, I want your Respect.Now, the real game starts if you don’t fulfil her demands you don’t respect her.so long story short you have money, then you can have any girl you desire even if she has a hell lot of attitude she will fuck with you.And any girl/women who thinks i don’t respect women a kind note for them, I Respect prostitutes instead of virgins because they are worst then prostitute.伙计，我要告诉你一件事，可以肯定的是，印度女孩变成这种德行正式由于糟糕的宝莱坞电影，她们认为我得把这个家伙变成我的宠物狗，但是如果你有足够的钱，她们自然会贴上来，当然不会那么直接啦。让我解释一下。世界上所有女人都这么说：我不要钱，我要你的尊重。现在，真正的游戏开始了，如果你不满足她的要求，你就不尊重她。长话短说，只要你有钱，你就可以拥有任何你想要的女孩，即使她态度很恶劣，她也会和你上床。对那些觉得我不尊重女人的女孩/女人，我尊重妓女而不是处女，因为她们比妓女更坏。
&#13;
AnonymousWe don't have attitude. Its just that we don't like to talk with our opposite gender counterparts who are too much interested in us, and can't stop interfering in our lives. Just back off, don't talk to us or talk only when there is any work. Otherwise may be that's just me, not every indian girl, but i don't like to talk even to my own father. And it's not because of attitude, it's because of hate that i have for mens. Look at the history, look at our society, look at our surroundings, where you males haven’t interfere in our (girls) business. And if you want to blame anyone for you poor condition, then blame poor sex ratio of our nation, and for this sex ratio blame our older generations who don't like girls even now. In childhood i used to have several males friend but with time they got adult and start proving that “men will be men”我们态度没问题啊。只是我们不喜欢和对我们太感兴趣的异**谈，他们不停地干涉我们的生活。请你们退后，不要和我们说话，或者只有必需的时候再跟我们说话。可能只有我是特例，不是每个印度女孩都像我一样，但我甚至都不喜欢和我自己的父亲说话。不是因为态度，而是因为我讨厌男人。看看我们的历史，看看我们所处的社会，看看我们所处的环境，你们男性一直干涉我们(女孩)的事情。如果你想为你的贫穷境遇责怪任何人，那就责怪我们国家的可怜的性别比例，这个性别比就归咎于我们的老一辈，他们到现在都还不喜欢女孩。小时候，我有几个男性朋友，但随着时间的推移，他们长大了，开始证明“男人注定要变成男人”。
&#13;
Abin Abraham, studies Bachelor of Science in Physics &amp; Electrical and Electronics Engineering at Indian Institute of Coz girls in India are given too much Importance and priority in India so they know they can do anything and no one is gonna stop them , coz simply they are girls, girls also get so much proposals and compliments from men which further boosts their ego . All Indian women are same greedy stupid and egoistic and want men to come and propose her even have sex with them , if a girl doesn't like the way the man had sex or gave her enjoyment , she will file a false rape case against that man and destroy the man's life . All Indian Girls are bitches no matter how much you love them, care them they are simply gonna ignore it and look for men mostly richer than the previous to propose and have sex with them just like a slut.因为在印度，女孩被给予了太多的重视和优先权，所以她们知道自己可以做任何事情，没有人会阻止她们，因为她们只是女孩，女孩会从男人那里得到很多建议和赞美，这进一步提升了她们的自尊。所有的印度妇女都一样的贪婪、愚蠢、以自我为中心。不管你有多爱她们，关心她们，她们只会忽视这一切，寻找更富有的男人。
&#13;
Nakul Singh, studied at Sri Venkateswara College, Delhi UniversityThey don't not all but it seems the following reasons are1 sex ratio is low in India , girls are looked down upon by society and parents. She has to kill her passion and sexuality that's why they are rude.2 societal construction if girl is open sexually or not virgin she is labelled slut or impure3 India is home for lot of sex crimes like rape, trafficking etc5 lot of guys in India don't know how to woo girl they learn from Bollywood movies and society. In USA there are dating coaches and PUA which is not present in India6 Girl will show attitude when you give them unwanted attention or if you try to attract woman out of your league.并不是所有的女孩都这样，但原因似乎有以下几点：印度的性别比例很低，女孩被社会和父母轻视。她必须扼杀自己的激情和性欲，这就是她们很粗鲁的原因。如果女孩在性方面很开放，或者已经不是处女，她就会被贴上荡妇或者不洁的标签。印度是许多性犯罪的发源地，比如强奸、人口贩卖等印度很多男人不知道如何向女孩求爱，他们从宝莱坞电影和社会中学到了很多。在美国有约会教练，可是印度没有。如果你给她们不必要的关注，或者你试图把她们从你的圈子里吸引过来，她们就会表现出冷傲的态度。
&#13;
AnonymousIndian girls will pay heed only to a hot and sexy guy. If not, then they will show attitude.印度女孩眼里只有性感帅哥。如果不是帅哥，她们就会表现出冷傲的态度。
&#13;
Vasudeva Reddy, An Observer( I guess the question was asked by a guy)What do you mean by attitude?And, from when attitude has become a wrong thing to have?Dude, don't you have any attitude? If not, go get some. It's your representation. Attitude is what you are. If you have a certain definition of attitude and someone else is not fitting in that framework, it's not their problem, it is yours.Statistically speaking, if you think every girl out there is having attitude, the problem must be with you, not with them.So buddy, what attitude problems do you have?(我想这个问题肯定是男人问的)你说的态度是什么意思呢？那么，从什么时候起，有态度变成一种错了？老兄，你自己就没有态度吗？如果没有，你也表现表现呗。态度决定了你是谁。如果你对态度有一个明确的定义，而其他人不符合这个定义，那不是他们的问题，而是你的问题。从统计学上讲，如果你认为每个女孩都有这种态度，那么问题一定出在你身上，而不是她们身上。老兄，你有什么态度方面的问题呢？
&#13;
Geetika Mishra, worked at R Systems International, Noida (2009-2012)This question made me Laugh. you are asking an Indian girl about this, what shall I do, shall I support, or defend. Funny.Well, your observation is totally based on small sample size, and mostly as you mentioned is related to the feedback you got online.Here I will go with the comment made by Ms. Anonymous, it is a cultural difference. If you happen to meet Indian girls face to face, they are as normal as Indian guys.We Indians have some resistance towards strangers, and that grows more when someone tries to contact you online without any specific purpose. I might not be the best person to explain the reason behind this, but this is how we are.这个问题让我发笑。你对一个印度女孩提出这个问题，我该做什么，我应该支持，还是辩护呢。有趣。嗯，你的观察完全是基于小样本量，正如你所提到的，大部分与你在网上得到的反馈有关。在此，我赞同无名氏女士的评论，这是一种文化差异。如果你遇到印度女孩，你会发现她们和印度男人一样正常。我们印度人对陌生人有一些抵触情绪，当有人试图在没有任何特定目的的情况下在网上联系你时，这种情绪会变得更加强烈。我可能不是解释这背后原因的最佳人选，但这就是我们。
&#13;
Ashu Tailor, Preparing for Ras OfficerIn india it doesn't matter that girl is successful or not,,,, beautiful or not but they all have onething common that is attiude but they can't understand too much ego killl your self...i think ravana was more successful powerful than any indian girl we can call him a legend he has a great knowledge of veda upnishad and also he is herculean but ghamand to uska bhi toota to yeh ladkiya kya hai jo bina qualities kai ego dikhati hai在印度，女孩成功与否、美丽与否并不重要，但她们都有一个共同点，那就是装模作样，但她们并不自知，她们太过自负了。我认为拉瓦娜比任何一个印度女孩都更成功，更强大，我们可以称他为一个传奇，他对《吠陀·厄普尼沙德》有很深的了解，而且他是一个非常伟大的人。
&#13;
Gsbsbs VbnmmkBecause Pro s tuition business is born in India and all Indian women are of that pros genome.. That's why they have attitude因为娼妓业诞生于印度，所有的印度女性都是这方面的专家。这就是为什么她们总是目中无人的原因。
&#13;
Fahad Anwar, Office Assistant (2015-present)One has one’s own attitude,attitude has nothing to do with gender or culture or in what space of ground one is living in.One can change attitude but can’t kill it,only statue is there available without it.There is nothing wrong in it,one can be humble &amp; lovely isn’t this an attitude?.Such +ve attitude,such pure understanding makes one’s life joyfull. Keep it,polish it &amp; shine.每个人都有自己的态度，与性别、文化或生活的地区无关。一个人可以改变态度，但不能扼杀它，只有雕像没有态度。态度本身没有错，一个人可以谦虚可爱，这难道就不是一种态度吗?这样的态度，这样纯洁的理解，使人的生活充满快乐。
&#13;
Gagan Singgirls in India are not mature as in developed nations . They dress up like developed nations but their thoughts are rotten. They feel every men a foolish. They misuses laws. They always think they are above laws &amp; flying in sky. It will take centuries to mature them.印度的女孩不像发达国家的女孩那样成熟。她们打扮得像发达国家，但她们的思想还是陈腐的。她们觉得每个人都是傻瓜。她们滥用法律。她们总是认为自己凌驾于法律之上，高高在上。她们还需要几个世纪的时间才能成熟起来。</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>废狗: </b><br>
<span>雷普斯坦：为什么印度女孩的态度很傲？</span><br>
<span>Why in India girls have so much of attitude?为什么印度女孩态度很傲？http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-06-07/0be93f82288f6eb74091b1134eccde32.jpgQuora读者的评论：AnonymousNot all of them have attitude but situations make you feel so.I'm going to answer this question according to the experience I had.About me: I'm a regular girl in my late teens and curvy (not fat) and interested in sports.I'm not going to be a feminist or a feminazi here, nor am I here to put down any of the gender. So please read it with a neutral mind.Back to the school days…..不是所有的人都是这样的态度，但是有些情况下会让你有这样的感觉。我会根据我的经验来回答这个问题。说说我自己：我是一个普通的十八九岁少女，身材玲珑有致(不胖)，对体育感兴趣。我不想把自己变成女权主义者或极端女权主义者，也不会在这里贬低任何性别。所以请大家以中立的心态来阅读。回到学生时代…Incident 1.Class 12th, badminton court (2 years ago)I love playing badminton and used to give a tough competition to everybody.We were playing a doubles match and my team mate was a boy (let's call him T)So I've standard size breasts. Suddenly out of no where another boy (let's name him K) standing in the same hall said “Hey T, nice T-shirt”. And then they all looked at me. It was clear that the remark was made for me.Just imagine the embarrassment I felt when he made a comment in front of a teacher, 4-5 girls, 7-8 boys. If I would have said anything then they would have clearly shrugged off this topic saying that they were praising T’s T-shirt. (Really? Praising. School uniform? Everyone else was wearing the same T-shirt).K is the same boy who rants about respecting girls on facebook. He has an elder sister and he loves his sister and mother and respect them (or shows it on facebook and instagram). He is the same boy who says how each one of us should respect a person.Now just imagine me ever meeting him in future. I'll always remember his words. I would never want to talk to him, I would not be able to. Then he'll be saying that what a arrogant bitch I'm who is so full of attitude.事件1。12年纪(2年前)，在羽毛球场我喜欢打羽毛球，曾经跟每个人都PK过。我们打双打，我的队友是个男孩(我们叫他T吧)我的胸部大小很正常。突然，另一个男孩(我们叫他K吧)站在大厅里说:“嘿，T，T恤真漂亮。”然后他们都盯着我。很明显，这句话是冲我说的。想象一下，当他当着老师和4-5个女孩，7-8个男孩的面说这话时，我有多尴尬。如果我说点什么，他们肯定会对撇开这个话题，说他们只是说T恤好看。(你们说的是真的吗？那可是校服啊！大家都穿着一样的衣服)。K也正是那个在facebook上痛声疾呼要尊重女孩的男孩。他有一个姐姐，他爱他的姐姐和妈妈，尊重她们(或者有可能只是在facebook和instagram上尊重而已)。他就是那个嘴里说着我们所有人都应该尊重别人的男孩。现在想象一下我将来遇到他会怎样。我会永远记住他的话。我永远不想和他说话，我没办法跟他交流。然后他就会说我是一个多么傲慢的婊子，态度那么拽。</span><br>
<span>Hetal Dhanak, An Indian.Originally answered : why do girls in India have attitude problem ?I'm Indian girlI don't know whether I'm metro girl or normal typical Indian girl but I'll present my views here.1.I used to play with boys when I was a kid. At that time, both boys and girls were equal for me. (Metro girl)2.In primary school, we had boys and girls both in our class and we studied together. We used to talk (metro girl)3.In high school, we had only girls in our class so we never talked to boys. And yes WE WARE NOT ALLOWED TO TALK. Be it any reason( typical Indian girl)4.In 11-12 science. Again we had boys with us but again we were restricted. So we used to talk on study related topics only. (Somewhere between metro and typical Indian girl)5.Now, I'm in college. During initial days, there were problems interacting with boys because I never had talked before. ( attitude problem) and I was given so many advices boys are like this, they'll do this etc etc(I know there's nothing like that) but now I can talk with anyone. There's no problem(metro girl)So, you see the “the typical Indian girl” is having attitude problem(difficulty in interaction) because she has been given “typical”(disbelief and doubts) environment.Today also, if I'm standing with a boy, so many eyes will be staring me and not that boy. Such behaviour makes a normal Indian girl “a typical Indian girl”. (In some areas in India)I hope now you understood why we have attitude problem.译文来源：三泰虎 http://www.santaihu.com/47783.html 译者：Joyceliu最初的回答是：为什么印度女孩的态度都不好？我是个印度女孩。我也不知道我属于城市女孩还是普通女孩，但我想表达一下我的观点。1.我小时候常和男孩子们一起玩。那时，对我来说男孩和女孩都是平等的。(城市女孩)2.小学时，我们班有男孩和女孩，我们一起学习。我们会互相交谈(城市女孩)3.高中时，我们班只有女生，所以我们从来不和男生说话。是的，我们不允许跟男生说话。不管是什么原因(典型的印度女孩)4.在11 - 12年纪。我们又跟男孩在一起上课，但受到了很多限制。所以我们过去只讨论与学习相关的话题。(介于城市和典型印度女孩之间)5.现在，我在上大学。一开始我和男孩子们交流有一些问题，因为我从来没有和他们说过话。(于是我态度就显得有问题了)我得到了很多建议，比如男孩是这样的，他们会这样做，等等，但现在我可以和任何人无障碍交谈了。没有任何问题(城市女孩)所以，你看到“典型的印度女孩”有态度问题(交流困难)，因为她从小接受的就是“典型的”环境。今天，如果我和一个男孩站在一起，那么很多人会盯着我看，而不是那个男孩。这种行为使一个普通的印度女孩成为“一个典型的印度女孩”。(在印度的某些地区)我希望你现在明白为什么我们有态度方面的问题。</span><br>
<span>AnonymousIf you meet an Indian girl born in the states or western country then she will not have an attitude and would be easier to deal with. So it is a culture thing.Here is why:1.Most of them do not have a lot of experience dating. Sure they must have been with a guy or maybe too. But, they haven’t really dated in the sense like western world does.2.They get pestered a lot by guys. Indian guys can be a bit possessive. I am Indian i know. Look at the movies in India. The hero is a loser who doesn’t stop chasing girls around.3.They know that no matter how they behave guys will keep tolerating there behavior. The guys in America and other countries have a lot of options and are not going to tolerate stupid behavior(they do to some extent). But, if the girl wants to keep a guy she has to have something more than looks. She needs a personality.How to fix the problem? I don’t know. But, you can be with an Indian girl who is a joy to be with not just a joy to look at. Also, i feel that once you get to know a person then they will open up and remove the fake attitude facade and be friendly to you如果你遇到一个出生在美国或西方国家的印度女孩，她就不会有态度，也更容易相处。所以这归根结底是文化问题。原因在于：1.她们中的大多数人没有丰富的约会经验。当然，她们肯定跟男的想出过。但是，她们并没有真正像西方世界那样约会过。2.她们经常被男人纠缠。印度男人占有欲可能有点太强了。我是印度人，所以我知道。看看印度的电影。英雄如果不停地追逐女孩子，就是个失败者。3.她们知道，不管她们怎么做，男人都会继续容忍她们的行为。美国和其他国家的男人有很多选择，但不会容忍愚蠢的行为(在某种程度上他们会)。但是，如果女孩想要留住一个男孩，她必须拥有比外表更重要的东西。她需要个性。如何解决这个问题？我不知道。但是，如果一个印度女孩是一个相处起来令人愉快的人，而不仅仅只是个花瓶，那么你可以跟她好好相处。而且，我觉得，一旦你了解一个人，她们就会敞开心扉，抛开虚假的态度，对你展现友好。</span><br>
<span>Ritika Ojha, lived in IndiaIt took me a while to monitor myself regarding this question and here I am to satisfy your query.Yes I have been at times accused of this- guilty as charged. For some I am awesome, while a few pointed what an as***** I was, straight on my face.These views have been presented to me by strangers with whom I have interacted over the past few weeks. In former case, the company was enjoyable and we had a blast. We parted ways clearly commenting to each other how awesome the other person was, irrespective of the gender.Now comes the latter case, where either of the party didn't find something common to connect over. As such soon I lost interest and it became quite obvious through my body language. One date mentioned I was too rigid with my pov , because I didn't agree to his idea of HIS date. Another person thought I was shallow, and so forth. To be honest I have no shame in agreeing what they stated , as they were mostly true and the clear root cause was my own lack of further interest in their company.I have rarely had any such attitude issues with women , but such comments are more common from men, and I barely ever manage to lend an ear to it. At times when I was pointed out about this by the right person, I did realise my mistake and accepted it. The only reason was because he/she meant it in a genuine way.So in short, I mostly reflect back, your own attitude towards me. If you give me an attitude , be prepared to have a taste of your own medicine. For rest of the time, life js good.Disclaimer: this is the view of AN INDIAN LADY. Use of common sense is strongly advised ;)我花了一段时间来思考自己对这个问题的看法，现在我来回答你的疑问。是的，我有时会被指控——被指控态度有问题。有些人认为我很高傲，而有些人则认为我是一个彻头彻尾的混蛋。这些观点是我在过去几周内接触过的陌生人向我提出的。在以前的情况下，大家相处得很愉快，我们玩得很开心。我们分别的时候，不管对方是男是女，我们都清楚地告诉对方对方有多棒。现在是后一种情况，双方都没有找到共同点。所以很快我就失去了兴趣，通过我的肢体语言，我的态度变得非常明显。有一次约会时，因为我不同意对方对约会的看法，对方就说我的观念太死板了。另一个人认为我肤浅，等等。说实话，我同意他们的说法，但并不以为耻，因为大多数情况是真的，而根本原因就是我自己对他们缺乏进一步的兴趣。我对女性很少有这样的态度问题，但在男性中经常听到这种评论，我从来不想听。有时候，当有的人指出这一点时，我确实意识到自己的错误，我就接受。唯一的原因是因为他/她对我是真心实意的。所以简而言之，我会用你对我的态度反过来对付你。如果你对我态度不好，那就准备好自食其果吧。而除此之外，生活是美好的。免责声明：这是一位印度女士的观点。强烈建议读者阅读时要有基本常识。</span><br>
<span>Pramod Kumar, studied at S.P College, Tilak Road, Pune-30.An Indian girl wants her family , relatives and society to believe that she doesn't have any boyfriend, she won't break their trust, she won't let her parents down, she has a fear inside to be called by different insulting names. In short, she prefers butt kissing of elders over love with her future possible life partner.Indian girls are so conservative that they don't even realise that it's just a matter of generation gap. Elders don't give a shit about her life, her desire, her colourful days. They just know to teach her to respect elders and kill her passion. An Indian girl has no idea how much she hurts her lover or boyfriend because of this awful and worthless societal customs. She believes hurting her bf is fine, cause he is a man so a man doesn't feel pain. She is afraid in taking a bold step and goes across boundaries. Many Indian girls are getting physically assaulted by their own parents. They are not physically strong to defend and protect themselves. Indian parents usually are famous for dominance over their children especially over daughters. That'swhy they have no other way but to show attitude to everyone even to strangers. The result is disastrous, they don't believe on anyone. They become a heartless creature with just flesh and blood looks like a “Real Girl”. Indian girls are not real girls. They are manufactured by societal fears as they grow up and become artifical inside and outside.一个印度女孩希望她的家人、亲戚和社会相信她没有男朋友，她不会辜负他们的信任，她不会让她的父母失望，她内心害怕被别人用侮辱性的名字称呼。简而言之，比起和未来可能的生活伴侣相爱，她更喜欢拍长辈的马屁。印度女孩非常保守，她们甚至没有意识到这只是代沟的问题。长辈们根本不关心她的生活，她的欲望，她多姿多彩的日子。他们只知道教她尊重长辈，扼杀她的激情。因为这种可怕的和毫无价值的社会习俗，一个印度女孩不知道她会如何伤害她的爱人或男友。她相信伤害她的男朋友是好的，因为他是一个男人，所以男人不会感到痛苦。她不敢迈出大胆的一步，不敢跨越界限。许多印度女孩被自己的父母殴打。她们没有强壮的身体来保护自己。印度父母通常以控制孩子，尤其是女儿而名声远扬。这就是为什么她们没有别的办法，只能对每个人，甚至是陌生人表现出桀骜的态度。结果是灾难性的，她们不相信任何人。她们变成了只有血肉的无情动物，只为了看起来像个“真正的女孩”。印度女孩不是真正的女孩。她们是由社会的恐惧制造出来的，随着她们的成长，她们的里里外外都不再真实。</span><br>
<span>Abhishek Kumar, Web and Mobile Application DeveloperGirls have a simple formula ( especially for boys ). She will pay heed to you only if you are of some use for her. Now you will think, I am definitely of some use to some girl :) . Well, it works like this. She already has many (guys/boys) friends for entertaining her, so she don’t need you for entertainment, she already has several boyfriends ( and all are unaware of each other :) ), so, again she don’t need you for dating. she already has a brother and also some boys who pretend to be brother, so again she don’t need one more brother.In India, it doesn’t matter if a girl is beautiful or not. It’s not difficult for her to find guys to play some role in her life. But for boys, its just the opposite. If you are handsome, girls will definitely get attracted towards you but in some way or the other you will not fit her criteria and then you will be again no use for her.女孩有一个简单的公式(尤其是对男孩)。只有当你对她有用时，她才会注意你。现在你会想，我肯定对某些女孩有用。事实是这样的：她已经有很多(男孩)朋友陪她了，所以她不需要你，她已经有好几个男朋友了(而且互相都不认识)，所以，她也不需要你跟她约会。她已经有了一个哥哥，还有一些愿意假扮她哥哥的男孩，所以她也不需要再多一个哥哥了。在印度，女孩漂亮与否并不重要。对她来说，找到能在她生活中扮演某种角色的男人并不难。但对男孩来说，正好相反。如果你很帅，女孩肯定会被你吸引，但在某种程度上，如果你不符合她的标准，你对她毫无用处。</span><br>
<span>Amar Bhatia, Php developer at HAV Solutions (2009-present)Buddy, I’ll tell you one thing for sure, Indian Girls are bullshit due to shitty bollywood movies, they think i will make this guy my dog and off course they can because all are the same but if you have enough money to blow, they themselves will come to you, off course not directly. let me explain.Dialogue of every women in the fucking world: I don’t want money, I want your Respect.Now, the real game starts if you don’t fulfil her demands you don’t respect her.so long story short you have money, then you can have any girl you desire even if she has a hell lot of attitude she will fuck with you.And any girl/women who thinks i don’t respect women a kind note for them, I Respect prostitutes instead of virgins because they are worst then prostitute.伙计，我要告诉你一件事，可以肯定的是，印度女孩变成这种德行正式由于糟糕的宝莱坞电影，她们认为我得把这个家伙变成我的宠物狗，但是如果你有足够的钱，她们自然会贴上来，当然不会那么直接啦。让我解释一下。世界上所有女人都这么说：我不要钱，我要你的尊重。现在，真正的游戏开始了，如果你不满足她的要求，你就不尊重她。长话短说，只要你有钱，你就可以拥有任何你想要的女孩，即使她态度很恶劣，她也会和你上床。对那些觉得我不尊重女人的女孩/女人，我尊重妓女而不是处女，因为她们比妓女更坏。</span><br>
<span>AnonymousWe don't have attitude. Its just that we don't like to talk with our opposite gender counterparts who are too much interested in us, and can't stop interfering in our lives. Just back off, don't talk to us or talk only when there is any work. Otherwise may be that's just me, not every indian girl, but i don't like to talk even to my own father. And it's not because of attitude, it's because of hate that i have for mens. Look at the history, look at our society, look at our surroundings, where you males haven’t interfere in our (girls) business. And if you want to blame anyone for you poor condition, then blame poor sex ratio of our nation, and for this sex ratio blame our older generations who don't like girls even now. In childhood i used to have several males friend but with time they got adult and start proving that “men will be men”我们态度没问题啊。只是我们不喜欢和对我们太感兴趣的异**谈，他们不停地干涉我们的生活。请你们退后，不要和我们说话，或者只有必需的时候再跟我们说话。可能只有我是特例，不是每个印度女孩都像我一样，但我甚至都不喜欢和我自己的父亲说话。不是因为态度，而是因为我讨厌男人。看看我们的历史，看看我们所处的社会，看看我们所处的环境，你们男性一直干涉我们(女孩)的事情。如果你想为你的贫穷境遇责怪任何人，那就责怪我们国家的可怜的性别比例，这个性别比就归咎于我们的老一辈，他们到现在都还不喜欢女孩。小时候，我有几个男性朋友，但随着时间的推移，他们长大了，开始证明“男人注定要变成男人”。</span><br>
<span>Abin Abraham, studies Bachelor of Science in Physics & Electrical and Electronics Engineering at Indian Institute of Coz girls in India are given too much Importance and priority in India so they know they can do anything and no one is gonna stop them , coz simply they are girls, girls also get so much proposals and compliments from men which further boosts their ego . All Indian women are same greedy stupid and egoistic and want men to come and propose her even have sex with them , if a girl doesn't like the way the man had sex or gave her enjoyment , she will file a false rape case against that man and destroy the man's life . All Indian Girls are bitches no matter how much you love them, care them they are simply gonna ignore it and look for men mostly richer than the previous to propose and have sex with them just like a slut.因为在印度，女孩被给予了太多的重视和优先权，所以她们知道自己可以做任何事情，没有人会阻止她们，因为她们只是女孩，女孩会从男人那里得到很多建议和赞美，这进一步提升了她们的自尊。所有的印度妇女都一样的贪婪、愚蠢、以自我为中心。不管你有多爱她们，关心她们，她们只会忽视这一切，寻找更富有的男人。</span><br>
<span>Nakul Singh, studied at Sri Venkateswara College, Delhi UniversityThey don't not all but it seems the following reasons are1 sex ratio is low in India , girls are looked down upon by society and parents. She has to kill her passion and sexuality that's why they are rude.2 societal construction if girl is open sexually or not virgin she is labelled slut or impure3 India is home for lot of sex crimes like rape, trafficking etc5 lot of guys in India don't know how to woo girl they learn from Bollywood movies and society. In USA there are dating coaches and PUA which is not present in India6 Girl will show attitude when you give them unwanted attention or if you try to attract woman out of your league.并不是所有的女孩都这样，但原因似乎有以下几点：印度的性别比例很低，女孩被社会和父母轻视。她必须扼杀自己的激情和性欲，这就是她们很粗鲁的原因。如果女孩在性方面很开放，或者已经不是处女，她就会被贴上荡妇或者不洁的标签。印度是许多性犯罪的发源地，比如强奸、人口贩卖等印度很多男人不知道如何向女孩求爱，他们从宝莱坞电影和社会中学到了很多。在美国有约会教练，可是印度没有。如果你给她们不必要的关注，或者你试图把她们从你的圈子里吸引过来，她们就会表现出冷傲的态度。</span><br>
<span>AnonymousIndian girls will pay heed only to a hot and sexy guy. If not, then they will show attitude.印度女孩眼里只有性感帅哥。如果不是帅哥，她们就会表现出冷傲的态度。</span><br>
<span>Vasudeva Reddy, An Observer( I guess the question was asked by a guy)What do you mean by attitude?And, from when attitude has become a wrong thing to have?Dude, don't you have any attitude? If not, go get some. It's your representation. Attitude is what you are. If you have a certain definition of attitude and someone else is not fitting in that framework, it's not their problem, it is yours.Statistically speaking, if you think every girl out there is having attitude, the problem must be with you, not with them.So buddy, what attitude problems do you have?(我想这个问题肯定是男人问的)你说的态度是什么意思呢？那么，从什么时候起，有态度变成一种错了？老兄，你自己就没有态度吗？如果没有，你也表现表现呗。态度决定了你是谁。如果你对态度有一个明确的定义，而其他人不符合这个定义，那不是他们的问题，而是你的问题。从统计学上讲，如果你认为每个女孩都有这种态度，那么问题一定出在你身上，而不是她们身上。老兄，你有什么态度方面的问题呢？</span><br>
<span>Geetika Mishra, worked at R Systems International, Noida (2009-2012)This question made me Laugh. you are asking an Indian girl about this, what shall I do, shall I support, or defend. Funny.Well, your observation is totally based on small sample size, and mostly as you mentioned is related to the feedback you got online.Here I will go with the comment made by Ms. Anonymous, it is a cultural difference. If you happen to meet Indian girls face to face, they are as normal as Indian guys.We Indians have some resistance towards strangers, and that grows more when someone tries to contact you online without any specific purpose. I might not be the best person to explain the reason behind this, but this is how we are.这个问题让我发笑。你对一个印度女孩提出这个问题，我该做什么，我应该支持，还是辩护呢。有趣。嗯，你的观察完全是基于小样本量，正如你所提到的，大部分与你在网上得到的反馈有关。在此，我赞同无名氏女士的评论，这是一种文化差异。如果你遇到印度女孩，你会发现她们和印度男人一样正常。我们印度人对陌生人有一些抵触情绪，当有人试图在没有任何特定目的的情况下在网上联系你时，这种情绪会变得更加强烈。我可能不是解释这背后原因的最佳人选，但这就是我们。</span><br>
<span>Ashu Tailor, Preparing for Ras OfficerIn india it doesn't matter that girl is successful or not,,,, beautiful or not but they all have onething common that is attiude but they can't understand too much ego killl your self...i think ravana was more successful powerful than any indian girl we can call him a legend he has a great knowledge of veda upnishad and also he is herculean but ghamand to uska bhi toota to yeh ladkiya kya hai jo bina qualities kai ego dikhati hai在印度，女孩成功与否、美丽与否并不重要，但她们都有一个共同点，那就是装模作样，但她们并不自知，她们太过自负了。我认为拉瓦娜比任何一个印度女孩都更成功，更强大，我们可以称他为一个传奇，他对《吠陀·厄普尼沙德》有很深的了解，而且他是一个非常伟大的人。</span><br>
<span>Gsbsbs VbnmmkBecause Pro s tuition business is born in India and all Indian women are of that pros genome.. That's why they have attitude因为娼妓业诞生于印度，所有的印度女性都是这方面的专家。这就是为什么她们总是目中无人的原因。</span><br>
<span>Fahad Anwar, Office Assistant (2015-present)One has one’s own attitude,attitude has nothing to do with gender or culture or in what space of ground one is living in.One can change attitude but can’t kill it,only statue is there available without it.There is nothing wrong in it,one can be humble & lovely isn’t this an attitude?.Such +ve attitude,such pure understanding makes one’s life joyfull. Keep it,polish it & shine.每个人都有自己的态度，与性别、文化或生活的地区无关。一个人可以改变态度，但不能扼杀它，只有雕像没有态度。态度本身没有错，一个人可以谦虚可爱，这难道就不是一种态度吗?这样的态度，这样纯洁的理解，使人的生活充满快乐。</span><br>
<span>Gagan Singgirls in India are not mature as in developed nations . They dress up like developed nations but their thoughts are rotten. They feel every men a foolish. They misuses laws. They always think they are above laws & flying in sky. It will take centuries to mature them.印度的女孩不像发达国家的女孩那样成熟。她们打扮得像发达国家，但她们的思想还是陈腐的。她们觉得每个人都是傻瓜。她们滥用法律。她们总是认为自己凌驾于法律之上，高高在上。她们还需要几个世纪的时间才能成熟起来。</span><br>
</p><p><b>佐塚間桐: </b><br>
<span>这妹子印度的？好漂亮啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>Lozs: </b><br>
<span>太长不看，妹子好看</span><br>
<span>不知道说什么，就JAI hind吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>listener: </b><br>
<span>印度何洁？</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>sunmedia: </b><br>
<span>说那么复杂干什么,无非就是种姓制度的延伸.印度女性习惯性的把不符合自己当前利益的男性看做贱民处理.</span><br>
<span>其他国家的女性也不说就一定尊重男性,但是至少不会对一般情况下[不包括死缠烂打]失败的追求者表达反感.</span><br>
</p><p><b>考茨基: </b><br>
<span>这妹纸一看就非常婆罗门</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>罗克萨斯: </b><br>
<span>印度咖喱味的美少女是不是很多？</span><br>
</p><p><b>qiniuwang001: </b><br>
<span>这个妹子前段时间有套图，真的是惊为天人。</span><br>
</p><p><b>momoooo: </b><br>
<span>我碰到的印度女生都挺好的，看我没带饭吃会给我分享他们的东西，还有帮我介绍工作的。大概这是我对印度人唯一好的印象了</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MIX 2, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>会玩熊孩子: </b><br>
<span>qiniuwang001 发表于 2019-6-7 15:47</span><br>
<span>这个妹子前段时间有套图，真的是惊为天人。</span><br>
<span>所以地址或者关键词呢</span><br>
</p><p><b>废狗: </b><br>
<span>qiniuwang001 发表于 2019-6-7 15:47</span><br>
<span>这个妹子前段时间有套图，真的是惊为天人。</span><br>
<span>套图</span><br>
</p><p><b>曾颀: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 曾颀 于 2019-6-7 15:55 编辑 </span><br>
<span>今年三月，印度的传统节日胡里节上，一位印度摄影师发觉了一双让人非常惊艳的眼睛。面对着这位拥有着橄榄绿色眼睛的印度女孩Riya Sanyal，他果断的选择记录下这瞬间。</span><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa17691151322973.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa17691151322973.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa1769aa29d44041.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa1769aa29d44041.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa176a5276f52700.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa176a5276f52700.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa176b8b8f075891.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa176b8b8f075891.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa176c3c04e17518.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa176c3c04e17518.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa1797d4abc27497.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa1797d4abc27497.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa17987d04712570.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa17987d04712570.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa179928f1d92257.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa179928f1d92257.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa1799c62bc17763.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa1799c62bc17763.jpg"><br>
</p><p><b>qiniuwang001: </b><br>
<span>会玩熊孩子 发表于 2019-6-7 15:51</span><br>
<span>所以地址或者关键词呢</span><br>
<span>我在微博上看的，当时没保存下来。</span><br>
</p><p><b>暴跳如雷: </b><br>
<span>为什么印度的美女那么多……前段时间在b站沉迷看女神希里黛玉跳舞……太美了！</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>萨基: </b><br>
<span>好看，搜了下叫Riya Sanyal</span><br>
</p><p><b>令和猛男: </b><br>
<span>恨不能远征印度，救菠萝门美女于水深火热之中</span><br>
</p><p><b>qiniuwang001: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 qiniuwang001 于 2019-6-7 15:58 编辑 </span><br>
<span>安努舒卡·莎玛当时迷了好久，到处找她的电影，在我的审美里，印度美女远超欧美。</span><br>
</p><p><b>废狗: </b><br>
<span>令和猛男 发表于 2019-6-7 15:55</span><br>
<span>恨不能远征印度，救菠萝门美女于水深火热之中</span><br>
<span>且去远征</span><br>
</p><p><b>tianyagk: </b><br>
<span>求妹子信息和套图 </span><br>
</p><p><b>天才我心: </b><br>
<span>太好看了叭</span><br>
</p><p><b>Sherry: </b><br>
<span>怎么看都是摆拍啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>realoctopus: </b><br>
<span>不用看了，只有那几张照片好看，其实就是一普通胖妞</span><br>
</p><p><b>CR2: </b><br>
<span>真棒</span><br>
</p><p><b>66367749: </b><br>
<span>曾颀 发表于 2019-6-7 15:52</span><br>
<span>今年三月，印度的传统节日胡里节上，一位印度摄影师发觉了一双让人非常惊艳的眼睛。面对着这位拥有着橄榄绿 ...</span><br>
<span>面对着这位拥有着橄榄绿色眼睛的印度女孩Riya Sanyal</span><br>
</p><p><b>東方凌: </b><br>
<span>kora! 歪楼了啊喂！</span><br>
</p><p><b>曾颀: </b><br>
<span>生活照:</span><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa254a8fa3087466.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa254a8fa3087466.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa25451f57d16979.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa25451f57d16979.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa2545c83b189323.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa2545c83b189323.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa25404911e86064.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/06/07/5cfa25404911e86064.jpg"><br>
</p><p><b>stannislas: </b><br>
<span>哇 这个妹子好漂亮，东西方风格混合</span><br>
</p><p><b>angluss: </b><br>
<span>阿三不都是黑不溜秋的吗，这个三妹挺白</span><br>
</p><p><b>秦心heart。: </b><br>
<span>歪楼一点也不奇怪，自从我点进这个贴看到那个图，接下来的文字索然无味。</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>小月亮李再含: </b><br>
<span>五官感觉不像印度人</span><br>
</p><p><b>LoliType: </b><br>
<span>前几楼嘲讽印度女人的是不看标题最前面那几个字吗，这种鬼话也说得出来，不愧仇女论坛。</span><br>
</p><p><b>F·U·罗格纳: </b><br>
<span>世界上所有女人都这么说：我不要钱，我要你的尊重。</span><br>
<span>现在，真正的游戏开始了，如果你不满足她的要求，你就不尊重她。</span><br>
<span>这个印度男孩悟了</span><br>
</p><p><b>傅剑寒: </b><br>
<span>废狗 发表于 2019-6-7 15:57</span><br>
<span>且去远征</span><br>
<span>打进新德里 一人一个美女婆罗门</span><br>
</p><p><b>dalarmar: </b><br>
<span>曾颀 发表于 2019-6-7 15:52</span><br>
<span>今年三月，印度的传统节日胡里节上，一位印度摄影师发觉了一双让人非常惊艳的眼睛。面对着这位拥有着橄榄绿 ...</span><br>
<span>真好看啊太好看了</span><br>
</p><p><b>ardin: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 ardin 于 2019-6-7 17:40 编辑 </span><br>
<span>这个吧，要几步走。</span><br>
<span>先切掉印度东北几邦，解放黄种人。然后以此为基地，顺河而上打进新德里。最终目标：解放婆罗门美女。</span><br>
<span>ps. 雷普斯坦？Ripstan? 这名字怎么读起来这么怪。脑中突然回响起 Nirvana乐队的科特·柯本的歌：Rape Me</span><br>
</p><p><b>无敌大法师: </b><br>
<span>曾颀 发表于 2019-6-7 16:50</span><br>
<span>生活照:</span><br>
<span>没感觉了</span><br>
</p><p><b>埃罗芒阿: </b><br>
<span>这肤色，在印度是婆罗门吗？</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HUAWEI PCT-AL10, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>Okumur: </b><br>
<span>LoliType 发表于 2019-6-7 17:08</span><br>
<span>前几楼嘲讽印度女人的是不看标题最前面那几个字吗，这种鬼话也说得出来，不愧仇女论坛。 ...</span><br>
<span>光看你id还以为玩女论坛，更过分了</span><br>
</p><p><b>__爱撕衣: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 __爱撕衣 于 2019-6-7 19:31 编辑 </span><br>
<span>编辑</span><br>
</p><p><b>exgloris: </b><br>
<span>妹子其实一般，但是第一张照片也拍得太好看了吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>__爱撕衣: </b><br>
<span>ardin 发表于 2019-6-7 17:35</span><br>
<span>这个吧，要几步走。</span><br>
<span>先切掉印度东北几邦，解放黄种人。然后以此为基地，顺河而上打进新德里。最终目标：解 ...</span><br>
<span>rape-stan，指印度</span><br>
</p><p><b>vanmercury: </b><br>
<span>印度的漂亮女人是真漂亮，而且是东西方公认的那种漂亮</span><br>
</p><p><b>触手酱133: </b><br>
<span>特爱看印度电影美女看得飞起，必须能傲啊太好看了</span><br>
</p><p><b>hoilc: </b><br>
<span>曾颀 发表于 2019-6-7 15:52</span><br>
<span>今年三月，印度的传统节日胡里节上，一位印度摄影师发觉了一双让人非常惊艳的眼睛。面对着这位拥有着橄榄绿 ...</span><br>
<span>好看诶</span><br>
</p><p><b>best: </b><br>
<span>比斋藤飞鸟差五条街的水平</span><br>
</p><p><b>isaih: </b><br>
<span>看到第一张图已经完全忘记帖子讲啥了</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HUAWEI ALP-AL00, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1837642[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
