<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>《博德之门》百多年后，明斯克VS鸦阁魔域领主斯托德</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>《博德之门》百多年后，明斯克VS鸦阁魔域领主斯托德</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 16:23:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>《博德之门》百多年后，明斯克VS鸦阁魔域领主斯托德[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1765565-1-1.html</link>
      <description>《博德之门》百多年后，明斯克VS鸦阁魔域领主斯托德&#13;
 本帖最后由 xjtxp 于 2018-9-22 08:45 编辑 

在1479DR，年过百岁高龄的正史版渣内姆死亡，巴尔最终复活
&#13;
在时间线为1480DR的官方漫画，明斯克与布布被某女性月精灵狂法妹子从石像状态解封——这个系列的官方漫画除了最后1期外都已汉化
&#13;
然后在大概两年前出版的第二个系列里，发生下面的剧情
&#13;
虽然我们博德之门百年后的明斯克，等级从5版他的卡上看只有6级，但是我们此时的明斯克智商比博德时期大幅度提高——有人吐槽后面三项属性都是驾驶员布布的，而且自带永久被动破邪斩——见宿敌
&#13;
以这样的配置，对上鸦阁魔域领主斯托德·凡·泽尔维奇，自然……明斯克只有被吊打的份了
&#13;
顺便，4版里杀死年过百岁的正史渣内姆的维耶康变成的那杀戮者属性——如果渣内姆赢，这就是渣内姆变身的杀戮者属性——的日文版官方图 - -
&#13;
所以这其实根本就是俩百岁老爷爷街头斗殴
&#13;
不过也别因为这个，而把正史渣想的太弱。
&#13;
官方对这模组设定解释是巴尔死亡太久，所以这个杀戮者很弱鸡
&#13;
而官方认定是正史的官方小说里，正史渣其实变身是掠夺者（就是游戏里打梅阿姨前，巴尔空间最后一场试炼的BOSS怪，升级版的杀戮者）。但在前两本写太烂了，游戏编剧接手补锅的第三本结局里也说了：
&#13;
"You understand that if you reject this destiny you will lose the essence of those you have absorbed within you. You will cease to be an avatar, and you will become a normal human male, with all the vulnerabilities and weaknesses of other men."
&#13;
"I understand." With a rueful smile, Abdel added, "I'm looking forward to it. I was not meant to be a god, or even an avatar. It is not who I am."
&#13;
"Then I shall free you from this burden."
&#13;
Deep within his body Abdel felt the faintest pull. It lasted but a moment, and was completely painless. He peered into his soul and discovered only the tiniest ember of Bhaal's spirit within himself. This minuscule portion of immortal essence was his to keep. It had been a part of him at his birth and it would be a part of him when he died. But it was simply that. A part of him. A small, virtually insignificant piece of a much greater puzzle.
&#13;
他放弃封神后巴尔的相关力量已经基本没了
&#13;
小说那个博德时期正史渣的表现是：
&#13;
正常情况不变身也有对抗五裔里部分大概20级以上同胞的战力，虽然跟巴和尚这30级武僧动手是被一边倒的吊锤，打不过变身掠夺者后仍然被巴和尚这30级武僧给吊锤。
&#13;
不过这其实也不算丢人，我觉得起码比某个作大死作得鳌老板都感动，在他永不超生前亲自给他婊彰，封他为愚蠢与狂妄之神的卡尔苏斯（为此有了卡傻子的黑称）在2版正史模组的黑历史——当年卡尔苏斯不会许愿术打不了Tarrasque，然后……这家伙花钱雇了几个14级以下的冒险者，帮他打了T兽弄到施法材料——比，被30级武僧吊锤好像也不算丢人。
&#13;
至于最后打小说版梅阿姨（梅阿姨30法/30牧，最终战是开始进化封神蜕变时，被官方表示实力大概相当于半神，超过表面级别的水平）的渣内姆，用王八拳乱拳砸翻对方时大概暂时相当于一个真正的巴尔化身亲临，这个状态玩家其实就算用SK与KK修改也达不到。
&#13;
不过小说渣的战力，是严重依赖巴尔血统的力量，即使不变身战力也明显是得到巴尔血缘加成。小说结局里巴尔的相关力量已经基本没了后，本来就实力大减，再加上物理系战士过了百岁……那水平其实也不算意外</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>xjtxp: </b><br>
<span>《博德之门》百多年后，明斯克VS鸦阁魔域领主斯托德</span><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 xjtxp 于 2018-9-22 08:45 编辑 </span><br>
<span>在1479DR，年过百岁高龄的正史版渣内姆死亡，巴尔最终复活</span><br>
<span>在时间线为1480DR的官方漫画，明斯克与布布被某女性月精灵狂法妹子从石像状态解封——这个系列的官方漫画除了最后1期外都已汉化</span><br>
<span>然后在大概两年前出版的第二个系列里，发生下面的剧情</span><br>
<span>虽然我们博德之门百年后的明斯克，等级从5版他的卡上看只有6级，但是我们此时的明斯克智商比博德时期大幅度提高——有人吐槽后面三项属性都是驾驶员布布的，而且自带永久被动破邪斩——见宿敌</span><br>
<span>以这样的配置，对上鸦阁魔域领主斯托德·凡·泽尔维奇，自然……明斯克只有被吊打的份了</span><br>
<span>顺便，4版里杀死年过百岁的正史渣内姆的维耶康变成的那杀戮者属性——如果渣内姆赢，这就是渣内姆变身的杀戮者属性——的日文版官方图 - -</span><br>
<span>所以这其实根本就是俩百岁老爷爷街头斗殴</span><br>
<span>不过也别因为这个，而把正史渣想的太弱。</span><br>
<span>官方对这模组设定解释是巴尔死亡太久，所以这个杀戮者很弱鸡</span><br>
<span>而官方认定是正史的官方小说里，正史渣其实变身是掠夺者（就是游戏里打梅阿姨前，巴尔空间最后一场试炼的BOSS怪，升级版的杀戮者）。但在前两本写太烂了，游戏编剧接手补锅的第三本结局里也说了：</span><br>
<span>"You understand that if you reject this destiny you will lose the essence of those you have absorbed within you. You will cease to be an avatar, and you will become a normal human male, with all the vulnerabilities and weaknesses of other men."</span><br>
<span>"I understand." With a rueful smile, Abdel added, "I'm looking forward to it. I was not meant to be a god, or even an avatar. It is not who I am."</span><br>
<span>"Then I shall free you from this burden."</span><br>
<span>Deep within his body Abdel felt the faintest pull. It lasted but a moment, and was completely painless. He peered into his soul and discovered only the tiniest ember of Bhaal's spirit within himself. This minuscule portion of immortal essence was his to keep. It had been a part of him at his birth and it would be a part of him when he died. But it was simply that. A part of him. A small, virtually insignificant piece of a much greater puzzle.</span><br>
<span>他放弃封神后巴尔的相关力量已经基本没了</span><br>
<span>小说那个博德时期正史渣的表现是：</span><br>
<span>正常情况不变身也有对抗五裔里部分大概20级以上同胞的战力，虽然跟巴和尚这30级武僧动手是被一边倒的吊锤，打不过变身掠夺者后仍然被巴和尚这30级武僧给吊锤。</span><br>
<span>不过这其实也不算丢人，我觉得起码比某个作大死作得鳌老板都感动，在他永不超生前亲自给他婊彰，封他为愚蠢与狂妄之神的卡尔苏斯（为此有了卡傻子的黑称）在2版正史模组的黑历史——当年卡尔苏斯不会许愿术打不了Tarrasque，然后……这家伙花钱雇了几个14级以下的冒险者，帮他打了T兽弄到施法材料——比，被30级武僧吊锤好像也不算丢人。</span><br>
<span>至于最后打小说版梅阿姨（梅阿姨30法/30牧，最终战是开始进化封神蜕变时，被官方表示实力大概相当于半神，超过表面级别的水平）的渣内姆，用王八拳乱拳砸翻对方时大概暂时相当于一个真正的巴尔化身亲临，这个状态玩家其实就算用SK与KK修改也达不到。</span><br>
<span>不过小说渣的战力，是严重依赖巴尔血统的力量，即使不变身战力也明显是得到巴尔血缘加成。小说结局里巴尔的相关力量已经基本没了后，本来就实力大减，再加上物理系战士过了百岁……那水平其实也不算意外</span><br>
</p><p><b>lxpzzj: </b><br>
<span>诶？不是说游戏一代默认队伍是小明戴娜黑JJ和卡立德么，为什么打了一圈下来只有六级啊</span><br>
<span>顺便借地求问一下，没看过小说，正史是怎么解释的查内姆离开博德之门的原因啊？</span><br>
</p><p><b>厨具战士: </b><br>
<span>DND看看设定就好，历史流变啥的还不如魔兽呢。</span><br>
</p><p><b>shyso: </b><br>
<span>lxpzzj 发表于 2018-9-23 01:22</span><br>
<span>诶？不是说游戏一代默认队伍是小明戴娜黑JJ和卡立德么，为什么打了一圈下来只有六级啊</span><br>
<span>顺便借地求问 ...</span><br>
<span>一代上限不也就7级</span><br>
</p><p><b>shyso: </b><br>
<span>话说散塔林会现在是什么状态，以前超喜欢曼松（主要是被立绘毒害），几个克隆在新版本的战役设定中还有出现过吗</span><br>
<span>感觉是不是外域和神级高端反派太多，凡人反派组织都没什么笔墨了</span><br>
</p><p><b>xjtxp: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 xjtxp 于 2018-9-23 06:25 编辑 </span><br>
<span>lxpzzj 发表于 2018-9-23 01:22</span><br>
<span>诶？不是说游戏一代默认队伍是小明戴娜黑JJ和卡立德么，为什么打了一圈下来只有六级啊</span><br>
<span>顺便借地求问 ...</span><br>
<span>你不打MOD看看博德1你能到几级 - - ？</span><br>
<span>在被卫生纸认为是正史的小说中，明斯克跟小说渣一起行动的剧情只有第二部，他跟小说渣一起被关强尼的地牢里，然后俩人一起跑路。然后就没他的剧情……</span><br>
<span>当然小说尤其前两本魔改的太重，比如为了把小说渣跟贾希拉凑CP而在第一本就整死卡立德，而且小说把这锅由强尼换成了老沙——后果就是后来玩强尼队友那MOD时，收强尼入队时贾希拉的不满反应，总让我联想到小说第三本主角复活老沙时的贾希拉 - - 。由于小说前两本太烂，卫生纸在第三本不得不找博德游戏编剧去补锅，但因为前两本已经把剧情线砍烂了+这编剧虽然擅长大纲但细节文笔并不好，于是第三本小说虽然有些不错亮点，但总体还是烂书范畴。</span><br>
<span>至于离开博德之门？延续小说的正史路线后来他是博德之门大公啊，最后也是死在博德之门的。</span><br>
<span>如果你是指离开烛堡，跟游戏不同，开篇葛立安还活着时他就已经跑出去当了雇佣兵了。</span><br>
<span>哦，按照小说剧情其实有一点：</span><br>
<span> 官方漫画里明斯克把解封他石像的月精灵狂法术士妹子当成涅拉，而从小说看正史渣内姆是不认识涅拉的——当然小说时也根本没创作涅拉这增强版角色，所以……正史大概是在不通过渣内姆的情况下，涅拉跟明斯克布布他们组的队</span><br>
</p><p><b>xjtxp: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 xjtxp 于 2018-9-23 06:24 编辑 </span><br>
<span>厨具战士 发表于 2018-9-23 01:40</span><br>
<span>DND看看设定就好，历史流变啥的还不如魔兽呢。</span><br>
<span>我主要是喜欢这漫画系列，被明斯克当成涅拉的月精灵狂法术士妹子、明斯克、布布等这帮人太可爱了</span><br>
<span>虽然第二个系列画风不怎么好，但第一个跟第三个系列画风都很薄，上面是第三个系列结局里怒扑霜巨人首领的布布终极形态</span><br>
<span>话说按照小说剧情的话，漫画其实有一点：</span><br>
<span> 官方漫画里明斯克把解封他石像的月精灵狂法术士妹子当成涅拉，而从小说看正史渣内姆是不认识涅拉的——当然小说时也根本没创作涅拉这增强版角色，所以……正史大概是在不通过渣内姆的情况下，涅拉跟明斯克布布他们组的队</span><br>
</p><p><b>volanta: </b><br>
<span>驾驶员布布可还行</span><br>
</p><p><b>lxpzzj: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 lxpzzj 于 2018-9-23 09:15 编辑 </span><br>
<span>xjtxp 发表于 2018-9-23 06:12</span><br>
<span>你不打MOD看看博德1你能到几级 - - ？</span><br>
<span>唔……我直接玩的大世界没玩过原版，对不起</span><br>
<span>我第二个问题是想问查内姆是为什么被关进强尼的地牢里啊……这个有题么，不会真的是龙矛围攻的剧情吧这个漫画也很有意思诶，戴娜黑是不是在小说漫画里根本没这个人啊？还是戴娜黑死了之后明斯克找上了涅拉？就跟游戏里找艾黎一样</span><br>
</p><p><b>qweqweqwe2: </b><br>
<span>我玩了N遍博德之门，最后选的都是封神。原因是这些遍主角的智力属性都在6以上，所以不可能去选傻子才选的放弃封神选项。</span><br>
</p><p><b>Hidewhite: </b><br>
<span>小说走的是贾希拉线，好人妻</span><br>
</p><p><b>lostneverland: </b><br>
<span>话说封神结局都是和攻略的妹子分别，不理解为啥，当了神就不能泡妹子了吗？</span><br>
</p><p><b>Hidewhite: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 Hidewhite 于 2018-9-23 12:44 编辑 </span><br>
<span>lostneverland 发表于 2018-9-23 12:20</span><br>
<span>话说封神结局都是和攻略的妹子分别，不理解为啥，当了神就不能泡妹子了吗？ ...</span><br>
<span>费伦的神没法停留在物质界的吧，下来耗费高加高风险。而且成神以后半规则化了，人格这个东西保存程度成疑。</span><br>
<span>奇怪的是神界原罪2成神我红龙王子也和洛思分手了，照理说这个是有肉身的神不应该啊。不知道其他角色成神关系怎样</span><br>
</p><p><b>xjtxp: </b><br>
<span>lostneverland 发表于 2018-9-23 12:20</span><br>
<span>话说封神结局都是和攻略的妹子分别，不理解为啥，当了神就不能泡妹子了吗？ ...</span><br>
<span>跟妹子分别属于游戏搞的房规</span><br>
<span>小说是当时第三本游戏编剧接手前两本烂摊子后，大发便当，爱蒙贾希拉老沙被他发了个连串便当，结果小说主角亲朋死绝。</span><br>
<span>最后鳌老板手下曦天使问他是否封神时，他问吸甜食自己封神能否复活爱蒙贾希拉葛立安，吸甜食表示不行“Even a god must accept certain events as things that cannot be undone.”，然后小说渣就放弃封神了。</span><br>
<span>不过介于当年无论正史小说还是非正史游戏，AO直属的这曦天使都说过巴尔无法复活，结果巴尔还是复活了来看（即使是鳌老板的秘书，也毕竟还是秘书）……我怀疑小说渣真选择封神的话，没准跟这仨信仰的神交涉下，把他们从自己信仰神祗的死后国度里带到自己身边也不是完全不可能 - -</span><br>
</p><p><b>xjtxp: </b><br>
<span>qweqweqwe2 发表于 2018-9-23 11:13</span><br>
<span>我玩了N遍博德之门，最后选的都是封神。原因是这些遍主角的智力属性都在6以上，所以不可能去选傻子才选的放 ...</span><br>
<span>我的主角是傻子真抱歉https://static.saraba1st.com/image/smiley/face2017/226.png</span><br>
</p><p><b>xjtxp: </b><br>
<span>Hidewhite 发表于 2018-9-23 12:12</span><br>
<span>小说走的是贾希拉线，好人妻</span><br>
<img src="http://img.saraba1st.com/forum/201707/07/121751h6pod1dkk1pjjjj3.png" title="http://img.saraba1st.com/forum/201707/07/121751h6pod1dkk1pjjjj3.png"><br>
<img src="http://img.saraba1st.com/forum/201707/07/121752qzz669czhuemcp6c.png" title="http://img.saraba1st.com/forum/201707/07/121752qzz669czhuemcp6c.png"><br>
<img src="http://img.saraba1st.com/forum/201707/07/121752d69n9644p6ru59p5.png" title="http://img.saraba1st.com/forum/201707/07/121752d69n9644p6ru59p5.png"><br>
<img src="http://img.saraba1st.com/forum/201707/07/121753rxxx4b1dzgaxajyz.png" title="http://img.saraba1st.com/forum/201707/07/121753rxxx4b1dzgaxajyz.png"><br>
<img src="http://img.saraba1st.com/forum/201707/07/121754x1c6n101od3no1wm.png" title="http://img.saraba1st.com/forum/201707/07/121754x1c6n101od3no1wm.png"><br>
<span>小说版贾希拉……起码前两本我很不喜欢，完全没游戏里那种强气年上御姐阿姨的感觉，虽然对她外表描写我挺满意</span><br>
<span>哦，小说版渣内姆跟巴荻有一腿，上面是巴荻跟小说渣的床戏——其实巴荻是小说版里我最喜欢的女角色</span><br>
</p><p><b>xjtxp: </b><br>
<span>既然要做博德3了，自己挖下这贴，小明还是可以在3代继续当队友的</span><br>
</p><p><b>七七见: </b><br>
<span>芭狄 骚 想干</span><br>
</p><p><b>sosgame67: </b><br>
<span>巴荻在原作不打mod完全没法ons吧..</span><br>
</p><p><b>灰色的狐狸: </b><br>
<span>刚好3就在百年之后。。hmm</span><br>
</p><p><b>SuThoth: </b><br>
<span>那么爱黎应该还活着吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>不可避免: </b><br>
<span>小说太烂，我不承认。</span><br>
</p><p><b>novem: </b><br>
<span>查内姆竟然狗带了，我不能接受，说好的封神呢</span><br>
</p><p><b>xjtxp: </b><br>
<span>SuThoth 发表于 2019-6-7 11:13</span><br>
<span>那么爱黎应该还活着吧</span><br>
<span>"Abdel took Bhaal's taint from me," Imoen said, still vainly flailing away at the impenetrable gloom. Her words were punctuated by the swish of her blade as it sliced only air.</span><br>
<span>"We have plans for that one," the voice assured her.</span><br>
<span>It sounded as if the assassin was right in her ear. Imoen swore she could feel the hot breath of her killer tickling her skin. But when she thrust her elbow back there was nothing to connect with.</span><br>
<span>"You may kill me, but Abdel will avenge me. He'll kill you ... all of you. You have no idea how strong he is." Imoen warned.</span><br>
<span>"Yes, my pretty young girl, we do. The news of your death will break his warrior spirit."</span><br>
<span>Imoen felt the blade plunge into her back, skewering vital organs as the assassin struck with uncanny, lethal accuracy. Her screams of agony were nothing but a silent rush of air and a faint gurgle of blood as Sendai mercifully slit her throat.</span><br>
<span>Chapter Seventeen</span><br>
<span>Abdel's entire existence had become a world of pain. Fire rained down on him from the sky. It erupted from the ground to consume him. It arced in jets from the fingers of his tormentor to sear and melt his flesh.</span><br>
<span>Above the roaring blaze he could hear Abazigal's laughter as the scaly skinned mage fed the conflagration devouring Abdel's body and soul.</span><br>
<span>Then suddenly the fire stopped, winking out of existence. Abdel, his eyes shut tight against the heat, peeked from beneath his blistered lids. Abazigal's body lay beside him on the hard rock of the plateau. The wizard's reptilian head lay several feet away. Standing over them both was Sarevok, the blades on his forearms dripping with the green blood of the mage.</span><br>
<span>Abdel tried to speak, though he didn't know what he would say. His scorched throat could only manage a feeble cracking cough.</span><br>
<span>Hampered by his heavy plate armor, Sarevok crouched down with difficulty beside Abdel. "The dragons are returning," he said simply. "Already I see their mighty forms on the horizon. They will rend us limb from limb if we do not escape."</span><br>
<span>Unable to reply, Abdel could only shake his head. He could hear the shrieking screams of the enraged dragons reverberating across the mountain plateau, growing steadily louder as the wyrms drew ever closer. But he was too badly injured to even stand, let alone attempt the treacherous descent. Sarevok seemed to understand.</span><br>
<span>"You can escape into Bhaal's realm," the armored warrior explained. "You have done it before, when you killed Illasera and Yaga Shura. You are weaker now, and it will be more difficult. You must allow yourself to be drawn there by the essence of Bhaal as it flees Abazigal's dead body. It will lead you to the plane of our father. There your body will be restored, and the dragons cannot follow you."</span><br>
<span>Too weak to argue, Abdel closed his eyes and tried to do as Sarevok had instructed. He could feel it, a faint tug on his innermost being like a zephyr of wind on a still summer day. Abdel focused on the sensation, and the zephyr became a breeze. The breeze became a gale, the gale a hurricane. Abdel felt his soul snatched up by the roaring spirit wind and opened his eyes in surprise.</span><br>
<span>For a brief second he was still lying on the ground, the decapitated remains of Abazigal beside him. Sarevok stood several yards away, his body braced to meet the onslaught of the dragons alighting all around them. A pair of taloned feet struck the ground next to Abdel's head. He could smell the terrible scent of the wyrm's fury as it investigated the corpse of its master.</span><br>
<span>As one, the assembled dragons screamed, but Abdel never heard the sound. The material world had already begun to dissolve.</span><br>
<span>Abdel found himself prostrate on cool, brown dirt. His body was still covered in burns, but he could feel it healing. Within seconds he felt strong enough to stand.</span><br>
<span>He was back in the Abyssal realm of Bhaal. The great empty plains still stretched before him, but somehow they looked less barren. The earth was a dark, fertile brown, and in the sky were wisps of what might have been rain clouds beginning to form. Before him stood the familiar free-standing doors, but now they numbered only three.</span><br>
<span>The big sellsword cared little for the magical or mystical, but even he could plainly see what was happening to this world. With the death of the Bhaalspawn, the Lord of Murder's essence was returning to the Abyssal plane from which it had first been born. The dead world was slowly being resurrected—though what hideous forms of life might sprout up in the accursed realm was anyone's guess.</span><br>
<span>He heard the sound of someone walking behind him and spun to face his unknown companion. Abdel didn't know who or what to expect. Had Sarevok followed him? Perhaps it was the spirit of the recently slain Abazigal, whose spirit had led Abdel here. Maybe it was the other star-covered being, waiting to taunt him with more maddening prophecies or eager to offer more shrouded, secretive, useless advice. Whatever awaited him, Abdel was ready for anything. Except what he saw.</span><br>
<span>"Jaheira!"</span><br>
<span>The half-elf smile at him. "I prayed to Mielikki you would come before it was too late," she whispered.</span><br>
<span>Abdel pulled her close, clutching her to his chest, relentlessly pressing himself into her body as if he hoped they would become one and he might never lose her again.</span><br>
<span>"I thought you were dead," he said, tears of relief streaming down his face.</span><br>
<span>The druid clung to him as fiercely as he clung to her, but when she spoke her voice was filled with grief. "I am dead, Abdel. That is why I am here."</span><br>
<span>Reluctantly Abdel loosened his grip so that he could look into his lover's eyes and see if she was joking. What he saw was a longing so deep it made his heart want to rend itself in two.</span><br>
<span>"You . .. are you a ghost?"</span><br>
<span>She brushed her long, delicate fingers across his brow, smoothing out the wrinkles of confusion on Abdel's forehead. Her touch was warm and soothing. "This is but my spirit, my love. My body is no more, though in this world my spirit is as real as my physical self was on the material plane."</span><br>
<span>"No!" Abdel declared, his voice rising in angry denial as he pulled Jaheira's taut, muscular form tight against his own. "No, this cannot be!"</span><br>
<span>The half-elf nestled her head against Abdel's powerful chest. The subtle scent of his lover's hair filled the sell-sword's lungs.</span><br>
<span>"It is true, my love," she whispered. "We must accept it and make the most of my time here. I begged Mielikki to grant me this time, but I cannot stay for long. My link to you keeps me here, but soon my soul must become one with the whole of nature."</span><br>
<span>Abdel pushed her away, refusing to give up. "No, it doesn't have to be like this! I brought Sarevok back to life. I can do the same for you!"</span><br>
<span>Jaheira gently shook her head. "No, Abdel. That cannot be. I am not a child of Bhaal, I do not possess the same essence you and Sarevok share. You cannot give me a piece of your soul to make me live again."</span><br>
<span>"Why not?" Abdel demanded. "It might work. It's worth a try." He turned and marched toward the nearest door, determined to return to the material plane and reenact the ritual that had reincarnated Sarevok.</span><br>
<span>"I beg you, Abdel, stop this madness." The soft pleas of Jaheira caused the big sellsword to freeze in midstride. Part of Abdel knew what she was about to say.</span><br>
<span>"Even if you can perform the ritual to restore me, what will that accomplish? You have seen Sarevok. He is not truly alive anymore. He is a thing, cold and passionless, without emotion. Is that what you would wish for me?"</span><br>
<span>Abdel dropped his head and turned back to face his lover, desperate tears burning his eyes. "Maybe Sarevok was like that to begin with. Maybe you will be as you always were."</span><br>
<span>With a wan smile, Jaheira walked slowly over to him. "No, my love. This is not nature's way. My time on that world has passed, and my time on this one grows short. Share this time with me, Abdel. Do not waste it with frantic plans and foolish wishes that cannot be fulfilled. Let us just enjoy the little time we have left."</span><br>
<span>She reached out, and her touch caused Abdel's skin to tingle. His blood boiled with desire, and he reached out with trembling hands to peel away the simple tunic Jaheira wore, exposing his lover's breasts before pulling her close. Jaheira's fingers slid beneath the scraps of his charred shirt still hanging from his shoulders and traced a sensuous path down Abdel's powerful back, caressing his muscles before tearing away the tattered remains of his breeches.</span><br>
<span>Abdel took her there, in the soft brown earth of Bhaal's realm. Their love making was savage and primal, fuelled by urgent desire and the fierce longing brought on by the knowledge of their imminent separation. Above them lightning crackled, and thunder rolled as the skies burst, dousing them with the shock of chill rains that couldn't quell their desperate passion.</span><br>
<span>When they were finished, they lay side by side in the cool mud, letting the downpour wash their bodies clean.</span><br>
<span>Jaheira snuggled up against Abdel, pressing herself into the crook of his arm and drawing on her lover's heat to ease the shivering of her naked form. Physically spent, exhausted by their furious copulation, Abdel held his half-elf lover and pretended they would be together forever.</span><br>
<span>The rains ceased, and their soaking bodies slowly dried beneath the empty night sky of the Abyssal plane. How many hours they spent together taking comfort in the simple closeness of each other, Abdel could not say. An eternity would have seemed but an instant to him, no length of time would ever be enough to justify the unfairness of having to ever let his lover go.</span><br>
<span>It was Jaheira who finally broke their embrace. "I can stay no longer," she apologized as she tried to get up. "I must leave."</span><br>
<span>Clutching her firmly but gently by the wrist, Abdel kept her from standing. "How can this be?" he asked, staring up into her violet eyes as she crouched overtop of him. "How can I go on without you?"</span><br>
<span>The half-elf bent to kiss him deep on the lips, then softly pulled herself away.</span><br>
<span>"You will find a way, Abdel. You must. Do not let my death poison you against the world," the half-elf warned. "If you let hate and regret consume your mind, the foul essence of Bhaal will swallow your soul."</span><br>
<span>"I don't want to be alone," he whispered.</span><br>
<span>"You won't always be alone," she assured him. "There will be others. Other friends. Other lovers."</span><br>
<span>The big sellsword shook his head. "No. Not like you. Never like you."</span><br>
<span>The half-elf smiled again, though her eyes were sad. "I loved you Abdel, as I loved no other man. But I also loved my husband Khalid as I loved no other man. Someday I hope you will find another to share your love, as I have, but that will not diminish what we have shared."</span><br>
<span>With a despondent sigh, Abdel rose to stand beside her. "You are my strength and my wisdom, Jaheira. Without you, I am lost. I cannot face the world alone. Without you I am nothing."</span><br>
<span>"You are Abdel Adrian: hero of Baldur's Gate, savior of the Tree of Life, son of Bhaal, ward of Gorion, lover of Jaheira," the half-elf replied simply. "You are who you are, Abdel, and nothing will change that. The way before you will be difficult, the tunnel of your future is long and dark. But if you remember who and what you are, I am confident you will emerge in the light on the other side."</span><br>
<span>"Will I ever see you again?" Abdel asked, frightened at what the answer might be.</span><br>
<span>Jaheira planted a kiss on his chest. Her lips were cold, bringing goose bumps to Abdel's exposed skin. "Such questions not even the gods can answer, my love."</span><br>
<span>Her voice sounded distant, as if she was speaking to him across a great chasm.</span><br>
<span>"No!" Abdel cried out reaching to grab hold of his lover. "No, not yet! Don't go yet!"</span><br>
<span>His hands passed through Jaheira as if she was nothing but mist.</span><br>
<span>"No!" he screamed as the half-elf began to fade away before his eyes, vanishing like a column of smoke dissipating on the breeze. Her body was dissolving, whisked away by some force Abdel could neither see nor stop nor comprehend.</span><br>
<span>Just before all trace of her features vanished, Jaheira spoke the last words Abdel would ever hear from her lips.</span><br>
<span>"I love you, Abdel Adrian. Forever."</span><br>
<span>Abdel clutched one last time at the vanishing wisp of wind, then collapsed to his knees. Jaheira was gone, and he was alone in his father's realm, sobbing uncontrollably and clawing at the damp, dark earth in grief and anger.</span><br>
<span>………</span><br>
<span>*   *   *   *   *</span><br>
<span>He felt empty and numb. Abdel's grief slipped into the ground and loam beneath his fists. It poured out of him in tears and wails of anguish, and now there was nothing left inside. His spirit was hollow, his naked body an empty shell.</span><br>
<span>Abdel filled the void with the only thing he had left— thoughts of vengeance. He no longer cared about the fate of his Bhaalspawn kin. It no longer mattered to him if Bhaal returned and ravaged the land, or if the Lord of Murder stayed dead forever. Jaheira's death had liberated him, freed him from the confusion and moral turmoil that came with being at the center of such epic events. Abdel's life had become very, very simple. He would kill the Five for what they had done to Jaheira. Beyond that nothing mattered.</span><br>
<span>He couldn't avenge her death here, wallowing in the dirt of Bhaal's realm. Abdel Adrian rose to his feet and stepped through the nearest of the three remaining doors.</span><br>
<span>He found himself alone on the plateau just outside the entrance to Abazigal's lair. By the position of the sun, Abdel guessed he had been gone for several hours, though an entire night had passed in the Abyssal plane. All around him were the signs of a great battle. Abdel stood in the aftermath of Sarevok's confrontation with Abazigal's hoard.</span><br>
<span>Along with Abazigal's decapitated form, half a dozen great dragon carcasses were strewn about the blood-soaked battlefield. Their corpses were scarred and disfigured by deep, ragged gashes from the blades forged onto Sarevok's arms and legs, or horribly gouged and gored by the terrible spikes jutting from the dark warrior's knees and elbows.</span><br>
<span>Sarevok himself was gone. Scattered around the dragons' remains were bits and pieces of his armor, rent asunder by mighty talons, or charred and blackened by the fire and acid spewed forth from the jaws of Sarevok's enemies. At Abdel's feet lay the armored warrior's visored helm, cloven nearly in two. There was no sign of Sarevok's body.</span><br>
<span>Abdel wasn't surprised. The victorious dragons would have devoured the flesh of their defeated foe—if there was even anything to devour. After his encounter with Jaheira's departing soul, Abdel couldn't help but wonder if Sarevok had been anything more than a suit of armor animated by a disembodied spirit. Whatever Sarevok might have been, man or ghost, the evidence of his grisly end was indisputable.</span><br>
<span>The many fallen corpses of the serpent horde attested to the legendary battle Sarevok must have fought before he succumbed to their overwhelming numbers. Had Abdel's emotions not been purged from his heart by Jaheira's death, he might have shed a tear for Sarevok's noble sacrifice. His half brother had saved his life, slaying Abazigal and then standing alone against the dragons while Abdel had retreated into the safety of Bhaal's nether world.</span><br>
<span>But Abdel had no more use for legendary heroics. In the bloody aftermath smeared across the plateau, Sarevok was still dead, and the dragons, bereft of their master, were gone.</span><br>
<span>Yet Abdel lived. He shivered as a cold blast of wind swept across the plateau, and he realized he was naked, his clothes reduced to ashes by Abazigal's fiery magic. He scoured the battlefield, searching for anything to cover his exposed body. In the end, he was forced to strip the bloodstained robe from Abazigal's headless corpse.</span><br>
<span>The loose-fitting garment barely came down to his knees, and his arms extended well past the cuffs of the sleeves. The hooded cowl was better than wandering around fully exposed. Armed only with the heavy broadsword he had salvaged from the carnage of Sarevok's final stand, Abdel began the long descent back to the mountain's base.</span><br>
<span>*   *   *   *   *</span><br>
<span>如果你是指卫生纸认定为正史的小说时间线的话</span><br>
<span>卫生纸在小说1、2部被写烂+剧情线崩溃后，拉出救场的巴尔王座编剧（也是后来质量效应1、2代的总编剧），在第三本小说里搞的便当大派送</span><br>
<span>用以上连续的剧情发了老妹爱蒙、贾阿姨、老哥三份便当</span><br>
<span>其实这段便当派送我觉得不错，但很多玩家（尤其老妹粉）非常愤怒</span><br>
<span>虽然我觉得博德3这方面不一定依照DND正史了</span><br>
</p><p><b>xjtxp: </b><br>
<span>sosgame67 发表于 2019-6-7 07:50</span><br>
<span>巴荻在原作不打mod完全没法ons吧..</span><br>
<span>没法</span><br>
<span>而且小说不止一夜情，有感情的</span><br>
</p><p><b>sosgame67: </b><br>
<span>xjtxp 发表于 2019-6-7 14:55</span><br>
<span>没法</span><br>
<span>而且小说不止一夜情，有感情的</span><br>
<span>真照小说剧情来总觉得各种ooc，bg3大概率只会把前作人物一笔带过，我现在只能希望几个出场老人物别写崩了</span><br>
</p><p><b>xjtxp: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 xjtxp 于 2019-6-7 15:35 编辑 </span><br>
<span>sosgame67 发表于 2019-6-7 15:11</span><br>
<span>真照小说剧情来总觉得各种ooc，bg3大概率只会把前作人物一笔带过，我现在只能希望几个出场老人物别写崩了 ...</span><br>
<span>其实把各家游戏房规都算上……背叛者的面具最邪恶路线主角，按结局似乎跟灵吸怪有些合作，不按正史……博德3把他也算上当反派NPC怎样？</span><br>
<span>虽然这房规结局是米尔寇没法复活（面具哪个结局米尔寇都不能复活），而DND正史是米尔寇跟巴尔一样复活了</span><br>
</p><p><b>sosgame67: </b><br>
<span>xjtxp 发表于 2019-6-7 15:31</span><br>
<span>其实把各家游戏房规都算上……背叛者的面具最邪恶路线主角，按结局似乎跟灵吸怪有些合作，不按正史……博 ...</span><br>
<span>按正史整个bg还有nwn都是白搭..不过拉瑞的剧情我也没做太高指望，系统好玩别太喂屎就行了</span><br>
</p><p><b>感冒的喷火龙: </b><br>
<span>枯了，查都挂了，小明居然还活着。要是有的话必须带着了，小明大概是整个博德流程中最欢乐的队友了</span><br>
<span>还记得当年想进禁魔监狱，小明可以直接被当成神经病送进去，笑死我了</span><br>
</p><p><b>PureIllusion: </b><br>
<span>费伦的故事实在越看越不喜欢，我去看看受好评的艾伯伦</span><br>
</p><p><b>误中副車: </b><br>
<span>说起来三代里崔老三还会客串吗？毕竟岁数也不大</span><br>
</p><p><b>AlienFromEarth: </b><br>
<span>xjtxp 发表于 2019-6-7 15:31</span><br>
<span>其实把各家游戏房规都算上……背叛者的面具最邪恶路线主角，按结局似乎跟灵吸怪有些合作，不按正史……博 ...</span><br>
<span>最邪恶结局是当神孽了，逼格是真的高</span><br>
<span>然而肯定不算正史，要不是博得之门历史意义那群人连这都不会算，而且就算算了也拼命黑拼命踩，还在需要的时候拿出来用当吸钱工具，比如这漫画……</span><br>
<span>当初无冬2原版牧师妹子提到无名氏的时候多让人高兴啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>哈曼的YY: </b><br>
<span>AlienFromEarth 发表于 2019-6-23 11:47</span><br>
<span>最邪恶结局是当神孽了，逼格是真的高</span><br>
<span>然而肯定不算正史，要不是博得之门历史意义那群人连这都不会算，而 ...</span><br>
<span>无名氏的故事算正史不</span><br>
</p><p><b>iqbsh38: </b><br>
<span>看3代日志 查内姆跟另一个巴儿砸决战紫禁之巅 谁赢都一样 反正赢了就巴尔上身成为新的杀戮之神把原先的小瘦子一脚蹬了 之前的人格也就神形俱灭了 可怜的工具人宿命....</span><br>
<span>预告解说貌似要搞3神归一 CG里的章鱼头只是为了酷炫做进来 实际上故事里不一定会按CG那样发展</span><br>
</p><p><b>AlienFromEarth: </b><br>
<span>哈曼的YY 发表于 2019-7-25 17:23</span><br>
<span>无名氏的故事算正史不</span><br>
<span>迄今为止只有无冬之夜2原版里吉斯人牧师队友提到过</span><br>
<span>而无冬之夜自己都是黑历史……</span><br>
</p><p><b>干嘛呢: </b><br>
<span>lxpzzj 发表于 2018-09-23 01:22:26</span><br>
<span>诶？不是说游戏一代默认队伍是小明戴娜黑JJ和卡立德么，为什么打了一圈下来只有六级啊</span><br>
<span>顺便借地求问一下， ...游戏里不是被精灵法师抓到安姆的嘛？</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>xjtxp: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 xjtxp 于 2019-7-26 21:43 编辑 </span><br>
<span>iqbsh38 发表于 2019-7-25 17:35</span><br>
<span>看3代日志 查内姆跟另一个巴儿砸决战紫禁之巅 谁赢都一样 反正赢了就巴尔上身成为新的杀戮之神把原先的小瘦 ...</span><br>
<span>别侮辱紫禁之巅啦</span><br>
<span>你再仔细看下1楼那杀戮者资料 - - </span><br>
<span>他们那纯属俩百岁老大爷斗殴。4级渣内姆，无论谁赢变成的杀戮者就这情况</span><br>
<img src="https://img.saraba1st.com/forum/201809/22/080135ed2lbwwnv2bn2vkb.png" title="https://img.saraba1st.com/forum/201809/22/080135ed2lbwwnv2bn2vkb.png"><br>
<span>1楼贴了，官方图日文版</span><br>
<span>当然就小说来讲，这倒可以解释。</span><br>
<span>1楼已经说了，《博德之门》官方小说到了第三本由游戏编剧负责的《巴尔王座》里，渣内姆的实力是：</span><br>
<span>除了最后对梅阿姨之战的开挂状态外</span><br>
<span>物理战士系，正常不变身也可以对抗部分二三十级的五裔同胞，但是……对上巴和尚这个三十级武僧是被一边倒的吊打，打不过变身掠夺者后仍然被巴和尚这30级武僧给吊锤。大概常态就是二十多级战士的水平吧，小说本来AO手下那曦天使选择阻止梅阿姨封神的人选是巴和尚，但结果巴和尚把巴尔污染隔绝的太好，揍翻了小说渣后巴和尚发现自己进不了巴尔空间……然后巴和尚自杀，靠自己体内的神性把小说渣送进了巴尔空间，然后就是最终战。</span><br>
<span>最后打小说版梅阿姨（梅阿姨本身30法/30牧，最终战是开始进化封神蜕变时，被官方表示实力大概相当于半神，超过表面级别的水平）的渣内姆，用王八拳乱拳砸翻对方时大概暂时相当于一个真正的巴尔化身亲临，这个状态玩家其实就算用SK与KK修改也达不到。</span><br>
<span>不过小说渣的战力，是严重依赖巴尔血统的力量，即使不变身战力也明显是得到巴尔血缘加成。小说结局里巴尔的相关力量已经基本没了后，本来就实力大减，再加上物理系战士过了百岁……那水平其实也不算意外</span><br>
<span>其实这最终战我还挺喜欢，起码反映出了几乎相当于半神，是人神之别</span><br>
<span>The realm of Bhaal vanished, and Abdel found himself in the void once again. But this void was already occupied. Melissan hovered in the emptiness, her body encased in a pillar of glowing power. The ends of the shining column stretched to infinity in every direction, but its width was barely enough for a single person.</span><br>
<span>At least, Abdel assumed it was Melissan in the light. The tall, attractive woman he remembered from previous meetings was gone. In her place floated a hairless, smooth skinned being who was neither male nor female. Melissan had become both ageless and sexless. She had shed all previous identities, and was in the process of being reborn, remade, and rebuilt as an immortal.</span><br>
<span>The new Melissan noticed Abdel hovering in the void beside her. When she spoke Abdel was not surprised to discover her voice had already begun to adopt the infinite depth of an immortal.</span><br>
<span>"So the Avatar of Bhaal has triumphed over Balthazar. I am impressed." Despite her words, Abdel knew she was mocking him.</span><br>
<span>"Have you come to stop me, Abdel? Come to strip me of my destiny?"</span><br>
<span>Abdel said nothing, but simply nodded. Melissan drifted free from the column of power, gasping slightly for air as if she had been taking a long drink.</span><br>
<span>"If you want Bhaal's power, all you have to do is come and get it," she taunted.</span><br>
<span>Angry, vengeful thoughts propelled Abdel through the void as he flew at her throat. His outstretched hands clasped themselves around the entity's neck and squeezed. Melissan disintegrated into sparkling dust, then reformed a few feet away.</span><br>
<span>"Your ignorance is amusing," she chuckled. "You cannot kill me here, Abdel. This is Bhaal's world, and I am now a part of it. Not just a part of it, Abdel. I am this world! This world is me! I have become one with the immortal essence!"</span><br>
<span>Abdel recalled how his encounter with Sarevok in the Abyss had been similarly ineffective. He realized it might truly be impossible to kill Melissan in this world, but somehow, he vowed, he would make her pay for Jaheira's and Imoen's deaths.</span><br>
<span>He hurtled toward her again, but Melissan simply raised a smooth hand and repelled his assault with a flick of her wrist. Abdel felt himself spiraling toward the glowing column in the center of the empty universe.</span><br>
<span>Melissan watched with interest as the big sellsword was sucked into the pillar. Abdel felt the euphoria of infinite power washing over him. He felt the endless possibilities of immortality, the unlimited potential of being a god. He was drowning in the essence of Bhaal.</span><br>
<span>His euphoria turned to panic. Abdel could feel himself dissolving. He was becoming incorporeal, his form washing away in the river of energy raging through him. His physical manifestation was being wiped away, buried beneath the all-consuming identity of the immortal. Like Melissan he was becoming one with the sum of Bhaal's essence. Unlike Melissan, Abdel was not prepared for it.</span><br>
<span>"Good," Melissan cooed, "give yourself over to Bhaal's power. Mingle your essence with that of your father and your siblings that I may devour you all."</span><br>
<span>Abdel tried to break free of the glowing pillar. It was like swimming from the center of a whirlpool. The currents drawing him back to the center were too strong to resist.</span><br>
<span>"Do not struggle, Abdel," Melissan advised. "This is what must be. From Bhaal's common seed all the Children were born, and to a single pool you must all return. You are all one and the same. Bhaalspawn, offspring of the Lord of Murder. It is what you are. It is what defines you."</span><br>
<span>"No," Abdel said weakly, his very will to resist vanishing beneath the onslaught, his identity and sense of self eroding. His memories were vanishing despite his efforts to hang on to them, spilling through his clenched fists like grains of sand.</span><br>
<span>Imoen, Gorion. The names meant nothing to him now, and then even the names were gone, swept away by the irresistible currents of the collective infinite identity surrounding him. Everything he had been was being stripped away, until only the essence of his father remained. Even his own name was lost now. All he had left was the face of a woman, her slightly pointed ears and violet eyes hinting at the elf side of her parentage.</span><br>
<span>Jaheira. He clung to her memory, refusing to lose the last spark of his individuality. He drew strength from her name. Jaheira. He managed to conjure up recollections of not just her face but her voice. Jaheira. Abdel could feel substance returning to his body. He could hear his lover's laugh, he could feel her warm touch. Jaheira.</span><br>
<span>"Your submission to the collective essence is inevitable," Melissan declared. "You are a Bhaalspawn."</span><br>
<span>Jaheira. He could remember her clearly now, the half-elf druid who had stood by him during his darkest times. The lover who had even resisted the call of death to spend one last night by his side. He remembered everything about her: the feel of her soft touch, the smell of her long hair, the sound of her laugh.</span><br>
<span>And he remembered what she had told him. Remember who you are. At last he understood. They were all wrong—</span><br>
<span>Gorion, Sarevok, Melissan, the Five, Balthazar. Even Jaheira had been wrong, though it was her words and love that had saved him and led him to true understanding.</span><br>
<span>"No!" Abdel's voice resonated with renewed strength. "I am not just some speck floating in this infinite whole! I am not just a Bhaalspawn!</span><br>
<span>"I am Abdel Adrian! Hero of Baldur's Gate! Savior of the Tree of Life! Son of Bhaal, ward of Gorion, lover of Jaheira!"</span><br>
<span>Abdel finally understood.</span><br>
<span>He stopped trying to deny the part of him that was his father's legacy. The taint of Bhaal was within him, it was a part of who he was. Gorion and Jaheira had tried to suppress that part of him, and to please them Abdel had tried to separate himself from it. Balthazar had succeeded in accomplishing what Abdel could not. He had cut himself completely off from his immortal taint, caging it so completely that he was not able to call upon it when he needed it. That was not the answer. By denying that part of his soul, Abdel left a hole in his own identity.</span><br>
<span>But Sarevok, the Five and even Melissan had gone too far in acknowledging the essence of the Lord of Murder within the Bhaalspawn. They had fed and nurtured the small bit of evil within them, until it became consuming and they lost themselves to their father's fury. That was not the answer either.</span><br>
<span>He was a Child of Bhaal. It was a part of him. But only a part, nothing more. It did not define him—he would not let it define him. He was who he was, nothing more, nothing less. He was Abdel Adrian.</span><br>
<span>"I am Abdel Adrian." he declared once more, affirming his individuality against the force drawing him in toward a single, collective existence.</span><br>
<span>The current sucking him down toward the center of the pillar was suddenly gone, and Abdel was able to float back out into the void to confront Melissan again.</span><br>
<span>Surprised, she watched him emerge from the glowing column of divinity. Abdel casually swung his fist at Melissan's face. As before, her form simply dissolved and reformed, completely unharmed by his punch.</span><br>
<span>"Your fortitude and persistence surprise me, Bhaalspawn," she admitted. "But no matter. I have no need of your essence to complete my ascension. And once I am a god I will crush you without a second thought."</span><br>
<span>"You are no god," Abdel said simply. "You are Melissan, nothing more."</span><br>
<span>He reached out again and swung his fist through his foe's insubstantial form. But this time he felt a hint of resistance as he made contact. From the expression on her face as her spirit reformed, he knew Melissan felt it too.</span><br>
<span>"You are Melissan, Bhaal's Anointed," he insisted, "False protector of the Bhaalspawn. Betrayer of the Five. Manipulator. Liar. Deceiver. But you, Melissan, are no god. You are an invader in this realm. You are not a part of this world. You do not belong!"</span><br>
<span>Abdel's fist caught Melissan beneath a suddenly solid chin, and he felt the jaw bone crack beneath the force of his blow. Her hairless head snapped back, and her mouth twisted into an O of shock and pain.</span><br>
<span>Long before he had met Melissan or even Jaheira, long before he had any hint of his immortal heritage, Abdel had been a brawler. A blade for hire. A mercenary and a sellsword. He settled his disputes with fists and weapons, and all his problems could be solved with simple brute force.</span><br>
<span>With the knowledge of who and what he truly was, Abdel's life had become much more complicated. The responsibilities and challenges facing the son of a god were convoluted and complex, and required more than mere fisticuffs to solve. But now, on the cusp of immortality, facing the greatest challenge of his life, Abdel had returned to his simple roots.</span><br>
<span>"I am Abdel Adrian," he declared, slamming his heavy hands into Melissan again and again, "and you are no god."</span><br>
<span>He pummeled the suddenly all too physically real spirit of Melissan with his bare hands, pounding her body into submission as it feebly tried to ward off his fists. He beat the woman who had betrayed and manipulated him since Saradush until she was nothing but a bloody, bruised pulp of physical, mortal existence. Then he grabbed the thing that would be a god by its shoulders and hurled it into the glowing, pulsating pillar.</span><br>
<span>The column flared momentarily as Melissan's screaming form was consumed by the light. The essence of Bhaal that she had already managed to steal became one with the greater whole. The insignificant physical shell that remained—the part of Melissan that was still Melissan—was instantly and totally obliterated by the divine power.</span><br>
<span>Abdel waited for an eternity to be sure his enemy was truly gone. Once he was confident Melissan's existence had been completely annihilated, he willed himself back through the door between the void of Bhaal's true essence and the realm of the Abyss Bhaal had chosen to make his own.</span><br>
<span>另外，跟百岁渣内姆决战那个就是游戏里的维耶康……从此我巴尔王座里一向亲手宰了他</span><br>
</p><p><b>iqbsh38: </b><br>
<span>xjtxp 发表于 2019-7-26 21:41</span><br>
<span>别侮辱紫禁之巅啦</span><br>
<span>和尚果然是最开挂的后期职业</span><br>
</p><p><b>xjtxp: </b><br>
<span>AlienFromEarth 发表于 2019-7-25 20:51</span><br>
<span>迄今为止只有无冬之夜2原版里吉斯人牧师队友提到过</span><br>
<span>而无冬之夜自己都是黑历史…… ...</span><br>
<span>其实博德游戏里也提过，去渥金商场的冒险者集市，可以买到达肯的剑跟维勒的头盔，装备介绍里写着他俩协助无名者时被摧毁。</span><br>
</p><p><b>xjtxp: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 xjtxp 于 2019-8-2 18:25 编辑 </span><br>
<span>误中副車 发表于 2019-6-23 11:28</span><br>
<span>说起来三代里崔老三还会客串吗？毕竟岁数也不大</span><br>
<span>我觉得应该会</span><br>
<span>话说在无冬网游里，玩家遇到他以及明斯克的相关互动里，明斯克会警告让关海法离布布远点233</span><br>
<span>无冬网游里的明斯克跟布布，也是博德2百年之后了</span><br>
</p><p><b>xjtxp: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 xjtxp 于 2019-8-2 18:25 编辑 </span><br>
<span>感冒的喷火龙 发表于 2019-6-13 18:07</span><br>
<span>枯了，查都挂了，小明居然还活着。要是有的话必须带着了，小明大概是整个博德流程中最欢乐的队友了</span><br>
<span>还记得 ...</span><br>
<span>https://img.saraba1st.com/forum/201908/02/182143lm5varz89k9oag8o.png </span><br>
<span>无冬网游里出场的明斯克跟布布，也是博德2百年之后了</span><br>
<span>在玩家遇到明斯克以及崔斯特的相关互动里，明斯克会警告让关海法离布布远点233</span><br>
</p><p><b>AlienFromEarth: </b><br>
<span>xjtxp 发表于 2019-8-2 18:19</span><br>
<span>其实博德游戏里也提过，去渥金商场的冒险者集市，可以买到达肯的剑跟维勒的头盔，装备介绍里写着他俩协助 ...</span><br>
<span>达肯的剑不是银剑么！</span><br>
<span>拿那玩意得被追杀的吧！</span><br>
</p><p><b>xjtxp: </b><br>
<span>AlienFromEarth 发表于 2019-8-2 20:12</span><br>
<span>达肯的剑不是银剑么！</span><br>
<span>拿那玩意得被追杀的吧！</span><br>
<span>提到的三件武器</span><br>
<span>哦，禁魔监狱里爱芙瑞尔其实也有间接</span><br>
<span>虽然，这些都没法证明是DND正史</span><br>
</p><p><b>AlienFromEarth: </b><br>
<span>xjtxp 发表于 2019-8-3 09:18</span><br>
<span>提到的三件武器</span><br>
<span>连博德之门都要阴暗的黑设定，能指望版权方什么呢</span><br>
</p><p><b>朴念仁3: </b><br>
<span>为啥会有日文？</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1765565[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
