<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>美国IT公司起诉美国政府拒绝向印度专业人士发放H-1B签证</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>美国IT公司起诉美国政府拒绝向印度专业人士发放H-1B签证</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 20:28:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>美国IT公司起诉美国政府拒绝向印度专业人士发放H-1B签证[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1832641-1-1.html</link>
      <description>美国IT公司起诉美国政府拒绝向印度专业人士发放H-1B签证&#13;
US IT company sues government for denying H-1B visa to Indian professional美国IT公司起诉美国政府拒绝向印度专业人士发放H-1B签证NEW DELHI: A Silicon Valley-based IT company has filed a lawsuit against the US government for denying the most sought-after H-1B visa to a highly qualified Indian professional, terming the renunciation "arbitrary" and a "clear abuse of discretion".新德里: 总部位于硅谷的一家IT公司对美国政府提起诉讼，称美国政府拒绝向一名高素质的印度专业人士发放最抢手的H-1B签证，称这是“武断的”，而且“明显滥用自由裁量权”。 http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-05-19/e3173c064ac2d62115e7c9fe126e07f6.jpg印度科技媒体gadgetsnow读者的评论：Arjan SinghLocation - 21 hours agoThe real reason for denial is that he is a Gulti (Telugu guy). The US has had enough of noisy Andhra people who never assimilate with the local population but instead hang around with their groups talking loudly in Telugu. They are harmless but they love to show off their wealth which leads to them being shot by jealous locals.拒签的真正原因在于申请者是一个泰卢固人。美国已经受够了聒噪的安得拉邦人，他们从未融入当地居民的生活。他们对社会无害，但喜欢炫耀自己的财富，这导致他们被当地人嫉妒，然后被开枪打死。
&#13;
Sam Santra1 day agoHis H1B should have been denied for having such a long name. Praharsh Chandra Sai Venkata Anisetty.应该是因为名字太长而被拒签，看这名字Praharsh Chandra Sai Venkata Anisetty。
&#13;
Avon OH - 22 hours agoUSCIS is right Business Analysis does not qualify as advanced profession locals can do the job - don’t require outside candidate - sorry美国移民局做得对，商业分析师不符合高级人才，当地人可以做的工作-不需要外国人来做-
&#13;
T PatLocation - 21 hours ago -FollowObviously right decision as like many andhra fekus this guy seems one more.显然是正确的决定，就像很多安得拉邦人一样，这家伙看着就像是一个骗子。
&#13;
VictorK12 hours ago -FollowI can give 100 American citizens who are business analysts and unrmployed.我可以找到100名美国公民，他们都是商业分析师，而且都没有工作。
&#13;
PK Nag10 hours ago -FollowIt is saddening to see people here are happy about the rejection of visa for this guy! You guys have problem with people who want to succed有些人对这个家伙被拒签感到高兴，真是可悲! 你们对想要获得成功的人有意见。
&#13;
A Googler12 hours ago -FollowBusiness analyst did not qualify as a specialized profession. Moreover this can be done by many Americans. MAGA. These gultis come so much fraud and bring bad name to Indians. Look at the student visa scandals. Majority of the 100s who got deported are gultis. We need to get rid of the gultis in this great country. MAGA. Go Trump!!!!商业分析师不算专业人才。许多美国人能胜任这个工作。泰卢固人很多都是骗子，败坏了印度人的名声。看看学生签证丑闻吧，100多名被驱逐出境的人中，大多数是泰卢固人。我们需要把泰卢固人都赶走。让美国再次伟大! ! ! !
&#13;
chanakyaMumbai - 16 hours ago -FollowBusiness analyst is not a specialized skillset. Many americans are qualified for this job. Visa dept was right in rejecting his visa商业分析师并不算专业人才。许多美国人都能胜任这项工作，签证部门拒签是对的
&#13;
zak46Location - 17 hours ago -FollowThe only skill H1B needs to have these days is to agree to work for super low wages.现在H1B签证持有者唯一需要的技能就是能接受超低的工资。
&#13;
Nimi Shah18 hours ago -FollowHe shoukd be first kicked and put behind bars for couple of yearand if still he isinterested he should be dumped in syria.telugu Virus in US are the sole reason why USCIS deny visa to others.让他坐几年牢，如果他还想申请，就把他扔到叙利亚。泰卢固人是造成美国移民局拒绝其他国家签证的唯一原因。
&#13;
Dilip Kumar19 hours ago -FollowTrump kept on pursuing his goal of America First... now he is successful ... this has hurt several counries, yet realignment is must....特朗普继续追求他“美国第一”的目标。现在他成功了，不过伤到了几个国家，必须重新调整政策……
&#13;
OracularmanUSA - 19 hours agoThe headline should read “Indian or Chinese owned US IT company sues US government for denying H-1B visa to Indian professional“...LOL标题应该是“印度或中国人开的美国IT公司起诉美国政府拒绝向印度专业人士发放H-1B签证”……哈哈
&#13;
arakimusJapan - 21 hours agoWhy you Indians are obsessed with America, here jobs are not for you, go back to your country. Do you give foreigners job in India no you dont, you only rape women为什么你们印度人如此迷恋美国，美国的工作不适合你们，回你们自己的国家去吧。在印度，你们给外国人提供工作机会吗?你们没有，你们只会强奸妇女。
&#13;
Pbch ChowdhuriIndia - 22 hours ago -FollowThe war for cheap intellectual labour from India has now begun in the US between the government and the IT cimoanies.在美国，政府和IT公司之间的劳动力争夺战已经打响。
&#13;
GatothkachIndia - 4 hours ago -FollowThey don''t want Indians or Chinese in their country anymore period他们再也不想让印度人或中国人留在他们国家了
&#13;
RakeshCalifornia - 14 hours agoThis company wants cheap labor. Locals can do this job but will ask higher salary. Also it is possible the company is owned by a Gulti and he wants to hire a Gulti. Why would he want to spend thousands of dollars on hiring a foreigner?这家公司需要的是廉价劳动力。当地人可以胜任这项工作，但会要求更高的薪水。也有可能这家公司是泰卢固人开的，他想雇佣一个泰卢固人。不然他为什么要花几千美元雇佣一个外国人呢?
&#13;
guru balanow at Boston MA USA - 17 hours ago -Followthat is why we call it is US -united states, power of individual rights are very spirit of We Poeple!美国就是美国，个人全利是人民的精神支柱!
&#13;
zak46Location - 17 hours ago -FollowH1B is only granted for skills that are not available in the US. Business Systems Analyst skills are not uncommon locally hence the denial.H1B只签发给美国缺乏的人才。商业分析师在当地并不少见，因此他被拒签了。
&#13;
CA Amol20 hours ago -FollowKeep it up继续申请，坚持下去
&#13;
San dy1 day ago -FollowIt seems US IT companies are hatching conspiracy theories against The United States.. US government must be watchful in this regard.看来美国IT公司正在酝酿针对美国的阴谋论。美国政府必须保持警惕。
&#13;
AROP1 day ago -FollowUS government knows what is good for US, they are keeping national interest on top unlike us.美国政府知道怎么做对美国有好处，他们把国家利益放在首位，不像我们印度政府。
&#13;
Dan Shibara3 hours ago -FollowUS should ban this useless H1B visa nonsense completely. It does not benefit US one bit, it takes our local American jobs away, and it bring in pathetic, useless, people from a 3rd world country like India, whom do not assimilate with US culture at all and stay in their own ghettos, wearing funky 70''s style shirts, and heavy oil in their hair, smell really bad, and speak with a very annoying accent, Tung, Tung, Tata tata, Tung, Tung.. Ewwe..... Disgusting.美国应该完全取消这种毫无用处的H1B签证。对美国没一点好处, 反而抢走了当地人的就业机会, 还招来来自**国家（比如印度）的废材。他们和美国文化格格不入。还是留在自己的贫民窟吧,穿着时髦的70年代风格的衬衫, 头发抹一层厚厚的油,身体散发体味,说话口音又重，太恶心了。
&#13;
Paadi Pantalu4 hours ago -FollowOh boy, so much hate on Telugu guys, unbelievable. Fellow Telugus, watch your manners and earn respect man. This kind of negative fame from your fellow Indians is not good.天啊，太讨厌泰卢固人了。泰卢固兄弟，请注意你的言行举止，赢得尊重。败坏印度同胞的名声是不好的。
&#13;
hellUSA - 8 hours agoWhat''s hell? Americans sue US for Indians? Indians should know: in US anybody can sue anybody anytime.怎么回事?美国人为印度人起诉美国政府?印度人应该知道:在美国，任何人可以随时起诉任何人。
&#13;
Mahi13 hours ago -FollowAmericans should be boycotted抵制美国人
&#13;
Rafael Federer13 hours ago -FollowOk ok what''s the big deal.这有什么大不了的。
&#13;
Bharat Sharma16 hours ago -FollowTHIS is how a company should support its employees..公司就该这么维护自己的员工。
&#13;
Straight talking man17 hours ago -FollowI did not know the qualifications and experience requirement of this job. Reading this news, it could be two things; one could be he is over qualified or the people evaluating these applications are high school graduates with a community college degree, which means that these immigration stuffs are not qualified for evaluating technology specific jobs.我不知道这份工作的岗位要求。有两种可能;一种可能是他资历过高，另一种是评估这些申请的人是持社区大学学位的高中毕业生，这意味着这些移民官不具备评估特定技术岗位的资格。
&#13;
NavalUSA - 17 hours ago -FollowBusiness Analyst is very common job role in US IT Industry I don''t think BA role is highly specialized or unique which local Americans can''t do? This role does not need masters qualification either. This case will not stand in court.商业分析师在美国IT行业是很普通的岗位，当地美国人不能干吗?这个岗位也不需要硕士学位。这个案子在法庭上站不住脚。
&#13;
Jaddu India - 18 hours agoUSCIS is a rowdy organization with racist illiterates美国移民局是一个有种族主义歧视的组织
&#13;
Mumbai - 19 hours agoThere is no transparency in approving H!B Visa. How there can be bias approach? If US is not interested in Indian IT professionals,should clearly declare the policyH1B签证的审批一点不透明，怎么能带有歧视?如果美国对印度的IT人才不感兴趣，那应该明确宣布政策。
&#13;
Nitesh Kaushik23 hours ago -FollowThis is not the first case of denial without any reason but surely it would not be the last. But if this case gets the positive response, this can create a good precedence for future.这不是美国第一次毫无理由的拒签，肯定也不会是最后一次。如果这个案子得到了积极的响应，可以为将来开创一个先例。
&#13;
BenchSH - 1 day agohow many hours H1B worked daily and not paid overtime ?H1B签证持有者每天工作多少小时？没有加班费?</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>废狗: </b><br>
<span>美国IT公司起诉美国政府拒绝向印度专业人士发放H-1B签证</span><br>
<span>US IT company sues government for denying H-1B visa to Indian professional美国IT公司起诉美国政府拒绝向印度专业人士发放H-1B签证NEW DELHI: A Silicon Valley-based IT company has filed a lawsuit against the US government for denying the most sought-after H-1B visa to a highly qualified Indian professional, terming the renunciation "arbitrary" and a "clear abuse of discretion".新德里: 总部位于硅谷的一家IT公司对美国政府提起诉讼，称美国政府拒绝向一名高素质的印度专业人士发放最抢手的H-1B签证，称这是“武断的”，而且“明显滥用自由裁量权”。 http://i.santaihu.com/india/2019-05-19/e3173c064ac2d62115e7c9fe126e07f6.jpg印度科技媒体gadgetsnow读者的评论：Arjan SinghLocation - 21 hours agoThe real reason for denial is that he is a Gulti (Telugu guy). The US has had enough of noisy Andhra people who never assimilate with the local population but instead hang around with their groups talking loudly in Telugu. They are harmless but they love to show off their wealth which leads to them being shot by jealous locals.拒签的真正原因在于申请者是一个泰卢固人。美国已经受够了聒噪的安得拉邦人，他们从未融入当地居民的生活。他们对社会无害，但喜欢炫耀自己的财富，这导致他们被当地人嫉妒，然后被开枪打死。</span><br>
<span>Sam Santra1 day agoHis H1B should have been denied for having such a long name. Praharsh Chandra Sai Venkata Anisetty.应该是因为名字太长而被拒签，看这名字Praharsh Chandra Sai Venkata Anisetty。</span><br>
<span>Avon OH - 22 hours agoUSCIS is right Business Analysis does not qualify as advanced profession locals can do the job - don’t require outside candidate - sorry美国移民局做得对，商业分析师不符合高级人才，当地人可以做的工作-不需要外国人来做-</span><br>
<span>T PatLocation - 21 hours ago -FollowObviously right decision as like many andhra fekus this guy seems one more.显然是正确的决定，就像很多安得拉邦人一样，这家伙看着就像是一个骗子。</span><br>
<span>VictorK12 hours ago -FollowI can give 100 American citizens who are business analysts and unrmployed.我可以找到100名美国公民，他们都是商业分析师，而且都没有工作。</span><br>
<span>PK Nag10 hours ago -FollowIt is saddening to see people here are happy about the rejection of visa for this guy! You guys have problem with people who want to succed有些人对这个家伙被拒签感到高兴，真是可悲! 你们对想要获得成功的人有意见。</span><br>
<span>A Googler12 hours ago -FollowBusiness analyst did not qualify as a specialized profession. Moreover this can be done by many Americans. MAGA. These gultis come so much fraud and bring bad name to Indians. Look at the student visa scandals. Majority of the 100s who got deported are gultis. We need to get rid of the gultis in this great country. MAGA. Go Trump!!!!商业分析师不算专业人才。许多美国人能胜任这个工作。泰卢固人很多都是骗子，败坏了印度人的名声。看看学生签证丑闻吧，100多名被驱逐出境的人中，大多数是泰卢固人。我们需要把泰卢固人都赶走。让美国再次伟大! ! ! !</span><br>
<span>chanakyaMumbai - 16 hours ago -FollowBusiness analyst is not a specialized skillset. Many americans are qualified for this job. Visa dept was right in rejecting his visa商业分析师并不算专业人才。许多美国人都能胜任这项工作，签证部门拒签是对的</span><br>
<span>zak46Location - 17 hours ago -FollowThe only skill H1B needs to have these days is to agree to work for super low wages.现在H1B签证持有者唯一需要的技能就是能接受超低的工资。</span><br>
<span>Nimi Shah18 hours ago -FollowHe shoukd be first kicked and put behind bars for couple of yearand if still he isinterested he should be dumped in syria.telugu Virus in US are the sole reason why USCIS deny visa to others.让他坐几年牢，如果他还想申请，就把他扔到叙利亚。泰卢固人是造成美国移民局拒绝其他国家签证的唯一原因。</span><br>
<span>Dilip Kumar19 hours ago -FollowTrump kept on pursuing his goal of America First... now he is successful ... this has hurt several counries, yet realignment is must....特朗普继续追求他“美国第一”的目标。现在他成功了，不过伤到了几个国家，必须重新调整政策……</span><br>
<span>OracularmanUSA - 19 hours agoThe headline should read “Indian or Chinese owned US IT company sues US government for denying H-1B visa to Indian professional“...LOL标题应该是“印度或中国人开的美国IT公司起诉美国政府拒绝向印度专业人士发放H-1B签证”……哈哈</span><br>
<span>arakimusJapan - 21 hours agoWhy you Indians are obsessed with America, here jobs are not for you, go back to your country. Do you give foreigners job in India no you dont, you only rape women为什么你们印度人如此迷恋美国，美国的工作不适合你们，回你们自己的国家去吧。在印度，你们给外国人提供工作机会吗?你们没有，你们只会强奸妇女。</span><br>
<span>Pbch ChowdhuriIndia - 22 hours ago -FollowThe war for cheap intellectual labour from India has now begun in the US between the government and the IT cimoanies.在美国，政府和IT公司之间的劳动力争夺战已经打响。</span><br>
<span>GatothkachIndia - 4 hours ago -FollowThey don''t want Indians or Chinese in their country anymore period他们再也不想让印度人或中国人留在他们国家了</span><br>
<span>RakeshCalifornia - 14 hours agoThis company wants cheap labor. Locals can do this job but will ask higher salary. Also it is possible the company is owned by a Gulti and he wants to hire a Gulti. Why would he want to spend thousands of dollars on hiring a foreigner?这家公司需要的是廉价劳动力。当地人可以胜任这项工作，但会要求更高的薪水。也有可能这家公司是泰卢固人开的，他想雇佣一个泰卢固人。不然他为什么要花几千美元雇佣一个外国人呢?</span><br>
<span>guru balanow at Boston MA USA - 17 hours ago -Followthat is why we call it is US -united states, power of individual rights are very spirit of We Poeple!美国就是美国，个人全利是人民的精神支柱!</span><br>
<span>zak46Location - 17 hours ago -FollowH1B is only granted for skills that are not available in the US. Business Systems Analyst skills are not uncommon locally hence the denial.H1B只签发给美国缺乏的人才。商业分析师在当地并不少见，因此他被拒签了。</span><br>
<span>CA Amol20 hours ago -FollowKeep it up继续申请，坚持下去</span><br>
<span>San dy1 day ago -FollowIt seems US IT companies are hatching conspiracy theories against The United States.. US government must be watchful in this regard.看来美国IT公司正在酝酿针对美国的阴谋论。美国政府必须保持警惕。</span><br>
<span>AROP1 day ago -FollowUS government knows what is good for US, they are keeping national interest on top unlike us.美国政府知道怎么做对美国有好处，他们把国家利益放在首位，不像我们印度政府。</span><br>
<span>Dan Shibara3 hours ago -FollowUS should ban this useless H1B visa nonsense completely. It does not benefit US one bit, it takes our local American jobs away, and it bring in pathetic, useless, people from a 3rd world country like India, whom do not assimilate with US culture at all and stay in their own ghettos, wearing funky 70''s style shirts, and heavy oil in their hair, smell really bad, and speak with a very annoying accent, Tung, Tung, Tata tata, Tung, Tung.. Ewwe..... Disgusting.美国应该完全取消这种毫无用处的H1B签证。对美国没一点好处, 反而抢走了当地人的就业机会, 还招来来自**国家（比如印度）的废材。他们和美国文化格格不入。还是留在自己的贫民窟吧,穿着时髦的70年代风格的衬衫, 头发抹一层厚厚的油,身体散发体味,说话口音又重，太恶心了。</span><br>
<span>Paadi Pantalu4 hours ago -FollowOh boy, so much hate on Telugu guys, unbelievable. Fellow Telugus, watch your manners and earn respect man. This kind of negative fame from your fellow Indians is not good.天啊，太讨厌泰卢固人了。泰卢固兄弟，请注意你的言行举止，赢得尊重。败坏印度同胞的名声是不好的。</span><br>
<span>hellUSA - 8 hours agoWhat''s hell? Americans sue US for Indians? Indians should know: in US anybody can sue anybody anytime.怎么回事?美国人为印度人起诉美国政府?印度人应该知道:在美国，任何人可以随时起诉任何人。</span><br>
<span>Mahi13 hours ago -FollowAmericans should be boycotted抵制美国人</span><br>
<span>Rafael Federer13 hours ago -FollowOk ok what''s the big deal.这有什么大不了的。</span><br>
<span>Bharat Sharma16 hours ago -FollowTHIS is how a company should support its employees..公司就该这么维护自己的员工。</span><br>
<span>Straight talking man17 hours ago -FollowI did not know the qualifications and experience requirement of this job. Reading this news, it could be two things; one could be he is over qualified or the people evaluating these applications are high school graduates with a community college degree, which means that these immigration stuffs are not qualified for evaluating technology specific jobs.我不知道这份工作的岗位要求。有两种可能;一种可能是他资历过高，另一种是评估这些申请的人是持社区大学学位的高中毕业生，这意味着这些移民官不具备评估特定技术岗位的资格。</span><br>
<span>NavalUSA - 17 hours ago -FollowBusiness Analyst is very common job role in US IT Industry I don''t think BA role is highly specialized or unique which local Americans can''t do? This role does not need masters qualification either. This case will not stand in court.商业分析师在美国IT行业是很普通的岗位，当地美国人不能干吗?这个岗位也不需要硕士学位。这个案子在法庭上站不住脚。</span><br>
<span>Jaddu India - 18 hours agoUSCIS is a rowdy organization with racist illiterates美国移民局是一个有种族主义歧视的组织</span><br>
<span>Mumbai - 19 hours agoThere is no transparency in approving H!B Visa. How there can be bias approach? If US is not interested in Indian IT professionals,should clearly declare the policyH1B签证的审批一点不透明，怎么能带有歧视?如果美国对印度的IT人才不感兴趣，那应该明确宣布政策。</span><br>
<span>Nitesh Kaushik23 hours ago -FollowThis is not the first case of denial without any reason but surely it would not be the last. But if this case gets the positive response, this can create a good precedence for future.这不是美国第一次毫无理由的拒签，肯定也不会是最后一次。如果这个案子得到了积极的响应，可以为将来开创一个先例。</span><br>
<span>BenchSH - 1 day agohow many hours H1B worked daily and not paid overtime ?H1B签证持有者每天工作多少小时？没有加班费?</span><br>
</p><p><b>fang帅: </b><br>
<span>Jai Hind！！</span><br>
<span>印度人才回流，印度一定会好</span><br>
</p><p><b>大哀之君: </b><br>
<span>上来就地狱骑士也太真实了吧</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>普雷尔公: </b><br>
<span>泰卢固是哪里，印度的福建么</span><br>
</p><p><b>废狗: </b><br>
<span>普雷尔公 发表于 2019-5-19 12:07</span><br>
<span>泰卢固是哪里，印度的福建么</span><br>
<span>对啊</span><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/19/5ce0d799ed95e50267.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/19/5ce0d799ed95e50267.jpg"><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1832641[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
