<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>“尽全力避免”这句话是个什么意思呢</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>“尽全力避免”这句话是个什么意思呢</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 18:09:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>“尽全力避免”这句话是个什么意思呢[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1855057-1-1.html</link>
      <description>“尽全力避免”这句话是个什么意思呢&#13;
 本帖最后由 松鼠和葱花 于 2019-8-21 23:44 编辑 

Valve 对“Steam 中国”有关疑问作出了回应：将确保 Steam 国际版保持原有现状，尽全力避免 Steam 国际版在中国无法使用的情况。 

https://i.loli.net/2019/08/21/YbpIhjfSwVraEAi.jpg

https://m.weibo.cn/5750886435/4407851742913536</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>松鼠和葱花: </b><br>
<span>“尽全力避免”这句话是个什么意思呢</span><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 松鼠和葱花 于 2019-8-21 23:44 编辑 </span><br>
<span>Valve 对“Steam 中国”有关疑问作出了回应：将确保 Steam 国际版保持原有现状，尽全力避免 Steam 国际版在中国无法使用的情况。 </span><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/08/21/YbpIhjfSwVraEAi.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/08/21/YbpIhjfSwVraEAi.jpg"><br>
<span>https://m.weibo.cn/5750886435/4407851742913536</span><br>
</p><p><b>雪菜碧池: </b><br>
<span>就是无法避免</span><br>
</p><p><b>Rorgen: </b><br>
<span>G胖尽力了，这球没法打</span><br>
</p><p><b>医生狼多: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 医生狼多 于 2019-8-22 15:15 编辑 </span><br>
<span>这种事肯定不能摆在明面上说的，只有到时知道</span><br>
<span>你们难道希望他跳出来说:你们放心一切照常，我们是不会听从管理的?</span><br>
<span>分分钟被定点爆破</span><br>
</p><p><b>鱿鲤: </b><br>
<span>翻译加私货而已，原文就是说以保持steam国际版现状为目标。</span><br>
</p><p><b>哈罗: </b><br>
<span>就是如果不幸发生了悲剧，我们已经尽力了的意思</span><br>
</p><p><b>卿卿雅儿: </b><br>
<span>你们贩卖焦虑大半年了，还能再卖多久？</span><br>
</p><p><b>acejoe: </b><br>
<span>实在不行就GOG，波兰蠢驴牛逼，就对了</span><br>
</p><p><b>战术核辣条: </b><br>
<span>翻译加私货了吧，人家说的是steam国际版不会变，后来追问的时候说总有东西是预料不到的</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 OnePlus ONEPLUS A6000, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>neonhex: </b><br>
<span>意思是你中文不行英文也不行</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi Mi Note 3, Android 8.1.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>juelian92: </b><br>
<span>就是字面意思啊</span><br>
<span>他们要保全，但是万一遇到不可抗力.....</span><br>
</p><p><b>juelian92: </b><br>
<span>不过说实话，我相信V社肯定会尽力</span><br>
<span>但是他们在国内的影响力非常小，主要靠完美，但是完美也产生不了决定性的影响。</span><br>
<span>在能够做决定的那些人下决定之前一切都是未知的。</span><br>
</p><p><b>处男鉴黄师: </b><br>
<span>to be contined ×</span><br>
<span>（完）         ⚪</span><br>
</p><p><b>ybfelix: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 ybfelix 于 2019-8-22 03:05 编辑 </span><br>
<span>请阅读原英文，人家意思就是计划全球版Steam一切不变，舞照跳马照跑，一球两制</span><br>
<span>至于最后一句追问“有什么外部因素可能导致全球版Steam在中国用不了吗”，这只能说do you guys not have 在中国住过吗？谁敢出来拍胸脯一个外国网络服务在中国绝对不会被墙，你吗？</span><br>
</p><p><b>Estella: </b><br>
<span>说转战gog的，steam要是凉了gog被wall也是迟早的事</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 8, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>luoyianwu: </b><br>
<span>搞不好原文是中文，是英文版加了私货</span><br>
</p><p><b>overmindoyj: </b><br>
<span>就是任天的意思</span><br>
</p><p><b>freedomtsubasa: </b><br>
<span>就是任天的意思</span><br>
</p><p><b>ギナ: </b><br>
<span>Estella 发表于 2019-08-22 08:19:18</span><br>
<span>说转战gog的，steam要是凉了gog被wall也是迟早的事</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 8, Android 9上的v2.1.2 ...gog你只管付款就行了，然后下载请去三大妈</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>valand: </b><br>
<span>话都说到这份上了，随缘呗</span><br>
</p><p><b>Solid/Liquid: </b><br>
<span> ギナ replied on 2019-8-22 10:42 引用:Estella 发表于 2019-08-22 08:19:18 说转战gog的，steam要是凉了gog被wall也是迟早的事—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 8, Android 9上的  v2.1.2 ...gog你只管付款就行了，然后下载请去三大妈  -- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 Android客户端 </span><br>
<span>真实</span><br>
<span>那我预购的2077也可以放心了</span><br>
<span>发自我的iPhone via Saralin 2.1.7</span><br>
</p><p><b>Johnie01: </b><br>
<span>最简单的免责声明啊 稍微有点业务交往常识的应该都听得明白吧</span><br>
<span>就跟方便面的一切以实物为准差不多</span><br>
</p><p><b>遥仰苍穹: </b><br>
<span>尽力保持原样，如果遇到了不可抗力，v社也没办法？</span><br>
</p><p><b>samyami: </b><br>
<span>蒸汽人是不是我国游戏玩家群体里最有被迫害妄想，最喜欢给自己加戏的群体？</span><br>
</p><p><b>kula01: </b><br>
<span>我就说一句，就算一开始能用，也会有人举报的。</span><br>
</p><p><b>2659646573: </b><br>
<span>卿卿雅儿 发表于 2019-8-21 23:55</span><br>
<span>你们贩卖焦虑大半年了，还能再卖多久？</span><br>
<span>大半年也太少了，说蒸汽要被封的起码都几年了吧，一出现网络波动就说要被封了，要被封了，搞得我都有点逆反心理，想着什么时候全都封了算了</span><br>
</p><p><b>Pz079: </b><br>
<span>samyami 发表于 2019-8-22 14:11</span><br>
<span>蒸汽人是不是我国游戏玩家群体里最有被迫害妄想，最喜欢给自己加戏的群体？ ...</span><br>
<span>对不起，没有你们三十年主机老玩家走私偷渡焊板改线苟延残喘的高贵感</span><br>
</p><p><b>fenrir: </b><br>
<span>kula01 发表于 2019-8-22 14:13</span><br>
<span>我就说一句，就算一开始能用，也会有人举报的。</span><br>
<span>那不叫人，是狗，虽然这世上多的就是狗，不足为怪。</span><br>
</p><p><b>LMartius: </b><br>
<span>samyami 发表于 2019-8-22 14:11</span><br>
<span>蒸汽人是不是我国游戏玩家群体里最有被迫害妄想，最喜欢给自己加戏的群体？ ...</span><br>
<span>我国玩家被政策和资本迫害这么多年看到风吹草动有点焦虑感不正常吗？</span><br>
<span>还是说要逆来顺受才不算得被害妄想？</span><br>
</p><p><b>Limpidity: </b><br>
<span>这还不好理解吗 就是明说了现有情况不变</span><br>
<span>只不过把话提前说谨慎一点 真要是万一未来出了点啥事政策变了 那我们也没办法</span><br>
</p><p><b>暗影之诗: </b><br>
<span>我觉得平稳落地的方法，基本上也就是闷声发大财的方法，其他平台哪个不是套壳做国服给外服打掩护？</span><br>
<span>如果什么都任由一帮子媒体和荷尔蒙过剩的小年轻杂杂呼呼，再来几个举报党定点打击，想不爆炸都难。</span><br>
</p><p><b>leafS: </b><br>
<span>就国内这变来变去的政策，哪个敢出来打包票的，最正常不过的公关声明而已，难道还对着干吗？</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 6, Android 8.1.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.0-play</span><br>
</p><p><b>samyami: </b><br>
<span>LMartius 发表于 2019-8-22 15:10</span><br>
<span>我国玩家被政策和资本迫害这么多年看到风吹草动有点焦虑感不正常吗？</span><br>
<span>还是说要逆来顺受才不算得被 ...</span><br>
<span>我不知道截图里哪个词可以被翻译成“尽全力避免”的，连V社传递的正面消息都要硬加私货制造恐慌，不是被迫害妄想和喜欢加戏是什么</span><br>
</p><p><b>eshin: </b><br>
<span>“搞砸了别怪我们”</span><br>
</p><p><b>Samvery: </b><br>
<span>拿某个不可说的巴子游戏举例，上头下命令下架那个游戏，恁就下架。上头不说，恁也不管，大家照玩。</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi Mi Note 2, Android 8.0.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>makece: </b><br>
<span>为了保证国际版能在国内出现愿意做出任何让步</span><br>
</p><p><b>pgain2004: </b><br>
<span>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2019-08-21-valve-talks-steam-china-curation-exclusivity</span><br>
<span>Eurogamer: So, Steam is available as it stands in China - yesterday I was able to buy, download and play a game without a VPN - so what's behind this? Was it an internal decision?</span><br>
<span>Powers: So, Steam China's just gonna be a much better experience for Chinese customers. Local servers, all localised content, so it's different in that it's just a service targeted at the Chinese gamers, as opposed to right now, where Chinese gamers are coming to Steam but it's you know, it's outside of China that they're accessing.</span><br>
<span>Eurogamer: So was it a decision on Valve's part to start Steam China?</span><br>
<span>Powers: I'm not sure I know the genesis of exactly how the conversation started. We've worked with Perfect World for a long time. They've published Dota and CS:GO in partnership with Valve. I think in some sense we've been working with them, for a long time, in terms of what Steam would look like in China, but I don't know the genesis.</span><br>
<span>Eurogamer: I guess what I'm dancing around is: there are regulations in China about what's appropriate for a Chinese audience. So was that a driving force behind a Steam China that was a little bit more curated, in that sense?</span><br>
<span>Powers: Yeah. We want Chinese customers to have really high-quality access to Steam games, and that means getting a set of games approved through the appropriate channels, and a service that is local. The servers that are right there, they can have fast download times, features make their quality of life better obviously.</span><br>
<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2019/articles/2019-08-21-13-57/three_kingdoms.jpg/EG11/resize/690x-1/quality/75/format/jpg" title="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2019/articles/2019-08-21-13-57/three_kingdoms.jpg/EG11/resize/690x-1/quality/75/format/jpg"><br>
<span>Chinese gamers can currently access the international version of Steam, which has boosted the popularity of games such as Total War: Three Kingdoms.</span><br>
<span>Eurogamer: Will there be some kind of community or forum or discussion area, as I know that's one part you can't access right now in China?</span><br>
<span>Powers: Yeah, I think that our long-term goal would be to have those features for the audience. We're hopeful.</span><br>
<span>Eurogamer: And on that topic of "curation", I know that's obviously come up in the past with Steam in the rest of the world, and that's not something you seem to be to keen on. Your attitude has been essentially anything that's legal goes, so have you had a shift in attitude? Or is it that you feel China requires a different attitude to that?</span><br>
<span>Powers: I mean obviously it's a different market, where, there's just a process that games have to go through. The way we operate Steam worldwide, where it's really developers coming to us, they sign up, they ship their game, you just can't have that same operation here. And so we're working with the processes in place and we'll get as many games on the platform as we can, but there's just a limit, and by definition kind of has to be a little more curated.</span><br>
<span>Eurogamer: Do you think there are some lessons you can learn from that approach that you could maybe apply in a Western environment?</span><br>
<span>Powers: I don't know about lessons. I think it'll be interesting to see just how a market reacts to a more curated storefront. I mean we know a lot of that, I've been at Steam a long time and I remember when Steam was very curated for a number of reasons as well, that we worked really hard to kind of eliminate over the years some of those barriers, but, yeah I think we'll just be interested in how consumers react to it, and if we do learn something that tells us we should be more open to that kind of storefront, then we'll take that data and consider it, for sure.</span><br>
<span>Eurogamer: And there's an expectation as well that companies will sort of "self-regulate" in a way. I think Tencent is an example where it implemented time limits for younger players off its own back, before government regulation came in. Will you consider self-regulating certain things as well?</span><br>
<span>Powers: There's just policies and laws in place that we have to follow, so yeah, we'll adhere to all of those.</span><br>
<span>Eurogamer: So it's more a reactive sense of "whatever the local laws are that's what we'll do"?</span><br>
<span>Powers: Yeah.</span><br>
<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2019/articles/2019-08-21-14-01/steam_forums.jpg/EG11/resize/690x-1/quality/75/format/jpg" title="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2019/articles/2019-08-21-14-01/steam_forums.jpg/EG11/resize/690x-1/quality/75/format/jpg"><br>
<span>Valve hopes to have forums and discussions available in Steam China.</span><br>
<span>Eurogamer: Jumping back to the topic of forums again - if I wanted to find something unsavoury on the Steam forums in the rest of the world, it wouldn't take me long. Obviously, China being China, that's not going to be able to fly out here. Have you thought about how you're going to manage that yet? If you're going to have forums there'll have to be some kind of moderation?</span><br>
<span>Powers: I think we have a little bit, but nothing that's in place that we could talk about at this point.</span><br>
<span>Eurogamer: Okay. You've talked about how there's going to be a different, curated version of the store - do you have an idea of how that's going to look, even visually?</span><br>
<span>Powers: We do, we didn't bring any of that here. And, you know, in due time and hopefully pretty soon we'll have more information about launch timing and what it's going to look like - but internally we have a bunch of designs for what that experience is going to look like, and it's great. We're all very excited about where it's headed. It really is good. The benefit of having a smaller group of games is you could really feature them in ways that it's hard to do on rest-of-world Steam. So, we're excited to tell you guys more about that stuff. It's just, I can't talk about it.</span><br>
<span>Eurogamer: Alright. So changing subjects - a part of the negative sentiment towards one of your rivals, the Epic Games store, is based on a quite broadly anti-Chinese sentiment, with it being at least part-owned by Tencent, with things like it supposedly being a "security risk" coming up a lot, justified or not. Are you concerned at all that there might be a similar attitude for Steam, now that you're sort of rubber-stamping Steam in China and working more closely with the respective people here?</span><br>
<span>Powers: I really don't want to have a comment on other services, it's not really appropriate for me to talk about. We are expecting excitement from Chinese customers. Dota and CS:GO have been received very well here, and we went through a similar process to get those games through in a Chinese market. So, a lot of this is not new to us. It's a different animal - it's a bunch of third-party games and it's not all stuff that is ours but, we're really expecting the reception to be quite positive. And as you said earlier we have a lot of Chinese customers that are customers of Steam now, and we're trying as hard as we can to make it as good an experience as possible, with payment methods and download speeds and all that, and localised content. So we're just going to keep relying on that, and creating the best service we can for this customer base, and I think that'll be received well. I'm not going to get dragged into any other issues.</span><br>
<img src="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2019/articles/2019-08-21-13-54/Steam.jpg/EG11/resize/690x-1/quality/75/format/jpg" title="https://d2skuhm0vrry40.cloudfront.net/2019/articles/2019-08-21-13-54/Steam.jpg/EG11/resize/690x-1/quality/75/format/jpg"><br>
<span>Steam China is separate from the international version of Steam.      </span><br>
<span>Eurogamer: Are you going to have any games that are exclusive to Steam China here?</span><br>
<span>Powers: No, no. Our approach has always been pretty non-exclusive. We think games are best when they're available in as many places as possible, and our approach with Steam China will be just the same. If you ship a game on Steam China we're happy for you to ship it anywhere else; we would encourage you to ship it in other places.</span><br>
<span>Eurogamer: And you mentioned as well obviously there are a large amount of players here who enjoy gaming on Steam as it stands. Let's say I'm a Chinese citizen and I want to play, I don't know, FTL, and I've played a hundred hours in FTL and I don't want to lose all my saves and everything like that - what happens when Steam China comes in? Will my saves move over? Will I lose my library? Will I keep my library?</span><br>
<span>Powers: Our goal is to make sure your library remains, your data, your saves remain, you're not losing anything.</span><br>
<span>Eurogamer: What if I own a game on Steam as-is, that isn't on Steam China at launch?</span><br>
<span>Powers: Nothing'll change about Steam global.</span><br>
<span>Eurogamer: So Steam global will still be available in China?</span><br>
<span>Powers: Nothing'll change about Steam global.</span><br>
<span>Eurogamer: Okay, could something external prevent Steam global from being available in China?</span><br>
<span>Powers: I mean, anything, yeah. There's always externalities you can't control. But the direction we're headed is that Steam global remains as it is today.</span><br>
<span>Valve / Perfect World paid for flights and travel to and from the event.</span><br>
</p><p><b>pgain2004: </b><br>
<span>自翻：</span><br>
<span>EGR：在Steam上买下玩都不用翻，那现在这是干嘛？</span><br>
<span>鲍尔斯：蒸汽中国版用中国服务器，提供本地化内容，面向中国玩家。目前中国玩家实际上在访问国外内容。</span><br>
<span>EGR：阀门自己决定搞中国版的吗？</span><br>
<span>鲍尔斯：我们和完美长期合作，研究Steam应以何面貌立于中国。但我个人不太清楚起端。</span><br>
<span>EGR：不绕了，中国有内容限制，这是否推动了中国版诞生？</span><br>
<span>鲍尔斯：嗯。通过恰当审核且本地储存的内容能显著提升用户的访问质量。</span><br>
<span>EGR：会有社区吗？现在的还是404呢。</span><br>
<span>鲍尔斯：积极展望，长远目标。</span><br>
<span>EGR：以前在其它国家遇到类似事情你们都是“合法就得过”的态度，这次咋变卦了呢？还是说你们认为中国得特殊对待？</span><br>
<span>鲍尔斯：明显不同——在别处都是开发者自己上门注册发布，这里不行啊，我们也只能尽可能让更多作品能上咯，即使那意味着一点限制。</span><br>
<span>EGR：从这学到的某些教训能用在西方环境吗？</span><br>
<span>鲍尔斯：什么教训啊真难听。Steam自己以前也受筛啊，费时费力才越过了一些障碍。但不妨看看市场受众对这种受筛内容的反应，如果数据说应该更放开对待这茬，我们也得实事求是。</span><br>
<span>EGR：企业还可能搞点“自律自查自纠自阉”，例如企鹅就会在官法介入前给年轻用户定游玩时限。你们会考虑吗？</span><br>
<span>鲍尔斯：有法依，吾必依。</span><br>
<span>EGR：就是“让我们咋样就咋样”？</span><br>
<span>鲍尔斯：欸。</span><br>
<span>EGR：说回论坛——我在其它地区上Steam社区找点粗鄙之语不难，在中国就看不到了。你们想过怎么处理这事吗？如果开中国版社区，会有审核之类的吗？</span><br>
<span>鲍尔斯：想过一点，暂时无可奉告。</span><br>
<span>EGR：行吧。前面说中国版将是独特受筛的，你们对它会变成怎样甚至长成怎样有啥想法么？</span><br>
<span>鲍尔斯：有，但不能细说。只能说内部有很多不错的设计稿，希望能尽快公布日期和卖相。作品池小反而更方便我们搞一些新东西。形势一片大好，不是小好，大家都很想分享，但我暂时只能三缄其口。</span><br>
<span>EGR：好，换话题，针对你们对手EGS的一些负面反响是基于反那啥情结的，诸如企鹅部分控股是安全风险之类的。现在Steam深入中国市场且与相关成员更紧密合作，你们有想过这可能触发类似意见吗？</span><br>
<span>鲍尔斯：不想谈，不宜谈。在中国备受喜爱的DotA和CSGO当初就通过类似方式进来，很多事并不陌生，我们预期玩家这次也会夹道欢迎。就像你之前说的，华夏Steam用户甚多，而我们正从下载、支付、本地化等方面全力提供优质体验，那就秉前功，给他们最好的，自会得到良好回馈。其余杂事并不会让我偏离这点。</span><br>
<span>EGR：会有中国版独占作品吗？</span><br>
<span>鲍尔斯：否。我们一直坚持不独占，游戏就是越容易玩到越好，于Steam中国版亦然。我们乐见并鼓励在Steam中国版发行的作品也在任何其它平台发行。</span><br>
<span>EGR：你也提过不少玩家显然喜欢在Steam玩游戏。就当我是中国公民，想玩，呃FTL吧，可不希望丢掉Steam上几百小时的云存档什么的，那开中国版后呢？存档会转移么？游戏库是留是丢？</span><br>
<span>鲍尔斯：我们的目标是确保你的游戏库、数据和存档不变，啥都不会丢。</span><br>
<span>EGR：库里未在Steam中国发行的作品呢？</span><br>
<span>鲍尔斯：全球版一切不变。</span><br>
<span>EGR：全球版还能在中国上？</span><br>
<span>鲍尔斯：不变。</span><br>
<span>EGR：好吧，有什么可能的外部干扰导致在中国用不了全球版么？</span><br>
<span>鲍尔斯：啥都有可能，总有不可控因素。而我们要做的就是确保全球版一如今夕。</span><br>
<span>阀门/完美世界支付了旅费。</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1855057[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
