<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>【旧】《纽约客》：那场即将摧毁美国西北部的超级大地震</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>【旧】《纽约客》：那场即将摧毁美国西北部的超级大地震</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 19:14:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>【旧】《纽约客》：那场即将摧毁美国西北部的超级大地震[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1844703-1-1.html</link>
      <description>【旧】《纽约客》：那场即将摧毁美国西北部的超级大地震&#13;
“美国西北部太平洋海岸大断层 恐引发9级大地震海啸可越洋袭日本”，这个可用不到30个字概括的新闻，《纽约客》记者Kathryn Schulz将它写成了一篇特稿《The Really Big One》（超级大地震），并在今年（2016年）首次为《纽约客》摘得普利策特稿奖。
&#13;
与我们惯常所理解的“非虚构或者讲故事型”的特稿不同，这是一篇解释性报道，阐释了一个自日本2011年“3•11”大地震以来围绕在美国西北海岸人民心头的“大噩梦”： 位于美国近海50英里(80.47千米)处的卡斯卡迪亚断层(Cascadia Fault)线有一天可能会裂开，引发地震和海啸。这个断层发生里氏8级以上的大规模地震的平均时间间隔是240年，300多年前该地发生最后一次“超级地震”。灾难似乎迫在眉睫，却又具体时限不明，人类显得无助又脆弱。
&#13;
这个涉及了地质、科学、环境、历史等多个领域的问题，女记者Kathryn Schulz用她令人印象深刻的时空视野交织成篇，展现了她对文字非凡的驾驭能力。普利策评奖委员会说，文章是对卡斯卡迪亚断层带雅致又科学的叙述，是环境报道与写作的杰作。
&#13;
值得一提的是，普利策直到2014年才对杂志开放。2015年，以品味以及写作著称的《纽约客》就入围了特稿奖；最终在普利策100周年之际，夺得特稿奖和批评奖，开创了杂志拿到普利策的先河。
&#13;
传媒狐（微信号：media-fox）独家编译了这篇约1万字的特稿，随同公号的新栏目“长悦读”一并推出。
&#13;
文｜Kathryn Schulz 编译｜Meow
&#13;
2011年的地震与海啸袭击日本东北时，克里斯•戈尔德芬格（Chris Goldfinger）正在200英里（约321千米）外的柏市（Kashiwa）参加地震学国际会议。地面刚开始晃动，房间里的每个人都笑了。地震在日本很平常——已经是一个礼拜里的第三次——而且无论怎样讲，与会者参加的正是跟地震有关的会议。接着，每个人都看了看时间。
&#13;
地震学家清楚，地震持续的时间可以用来预示它的里氏级数。1989年夺去了63人性命造成60亿美元损失的加利福尼亚洛马•普雷塔（Loma Prieta）地震持续了15秒，里氏震级6.9级。时长30秒左右的地震通常在7.5级左右；时长1分钟的地震规模更大，但仍处于7级；震动长达2分钟，震级就会进入8级；持续3分钟，标度会在8的范围内继续提升。到达4分钟，地震就可达里氏9级。
&#13;
戈尔德芬格看向他的手表时，时间是下午2点45分。会议正进入当日的尾声。他在头脑里盘算起了寿司。讲台上的人有些犹豫，不知是否该继续发言。震感不算强，但超过了60秒标记线，持续时间比这周的其他几次都要久。晃动感在增强。会议室里用的是小型带底轮的塑料椅子。身材高大结实的戈尔德芬格琢磨着，我才不要钻下身避难呢。1分30秒后，会议室里的每个人都站起身，跑向门口。
&#13;
时值三月。空气中尚有寒意，骤然间有雪飘来，落到地面又不见了踪迹。同样不见了的是往常的地面，如今变得折断、凸起，开裂。戈尔德芬格打了个比方，就像是驾着没有缓冲装置的汽车驶过岩石路面，而车子和岩石路又恰好处于大海的包围中。震动已经持续了超过2分钟。树上还挂着上个秋天的枯叶，发出一阵沙沙的奇怪声响。他与同事刚刚路过的大楼顶部的旗杆正以40度的幅度晃动。建筑本身使用了防震技术，大楼主体建在可移动的承重体上，而非直接建在地基上。戈尔德芬格探出身子。底座正倾斜成一个角度，以前后约一英尺的幅度摆动着，在院子里磕出了一道沟。他认为应该没什么大问题，收回了身子。他的手表指针已经划过了3分钟，还在不断滴答往前。
&#13;
妈的，戈尔德芬格想，虽然还不至于惊慌失措，却足够使他诧异。几十年来，地震学家都相信日本不可能发生超过8.4级的地震。然而2005年时，在日本北淡町（Hokudan）举行的一次会议中，一位名叫池田安隆（Yasutaka Ikeda）的日本地震学家辩称，日本很可能将要发生达9.0级的地震——并造成灾难性后果，而日本举世闻名的地震海啸预防措施——包括防波堤的高度，都是基于错误的科学设计的。他的演讲收到了一阵彬彬有礼的掌声，很快就被人忘记了。如今，在震动持续4分钟后，戈尔德芬格意识到，我们生活的行星本身证明了那位日本“卡珊德拉”（希腊神话人物，有预言能力）的预言是正确的。
&#13;
有一阵子，场面是相当激动人心的：这几乎是一场实时地震科学的革命。然而很快，兴奋的心情就烟消云散了。戈尔德芬格和每一位站在北淡町空地上的地震学家都知道，接下来将会发生什么。他们中的一人拿出了手机，检索起NHK电视台的视频，那是晃动一开始时，由飞行至海面上空的直升机拍摄的。戈尔德芬格在室外站了30分钟后，他在两英寸的屏幕上看到了席卷而过的海啸波。
&#13;
最终，超过1万8千人在这场9.0级的东日本大地震以及随后引发的海啸中死亡，重创了日本东北省份，导致福岛核电站停工，并造成约2200亿美元损失。那周早前的几次晃动，被证实是日本历史上有记录以来破坏力最大的地震的前震。但对戈尔德芬格而言，作为美国俄勒冈州立大学的古地震专家，世界上鲜有人问津的断层线（fault line）研究权威，这场地震本身只是前震：是另一场地震的“前奏”。
&#13;
http://img.mp.itc.cn/upload/20160421/9d4e6cbc78e746dd98146b54946a0e12_th.jpg
&#13;
壹
&#13;
大部分美国人听过圣安德烈亚斯（San Andreas）断层线的名字，它几乎与加利福尼亚州等长，还经年不休地流传着马上就要“大爆发”的传言。不管圣安德烈亚斯以前发生过什么，传言本身很有误导性。每条断层线都有它的能量上限，由它的长度、宽度，以及能够波及的距离而定。就圣安德烈亚斯——这条世界上研究最多最彻底的断层线——而言，它的最高上限约为8.2级——的确算得上是大地震，但由于里氏震级是由地震波最大振幅的常用对数演算而来的，这仅是2011年东日本地震强度的6%。
&#13;
然而，在圣安德烈亚斯北部还有一条断层线，卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带（Cascadia subduction zone），它沿太平洋西北地区分布，长约700英里（约1126千米）。从加利福尼亚州的门多西诺角（Cape Mendocino）附近出发，一路经过俄勒冈州、华盛顿州，另一端位于加拿大南部的温哥华岛（Vancouver Island）。“卡斯卡迪亚”的名字，一部分来源于卡斯卡迪山脉（Cascade Range）,它是贯穿同样路径且有数英里蔓延至内陆的火山山脉；“俯冲带”是指两个板块相遇，一个板块插入另一个相对被动的板块之下的部分。地壳板块是由地幔（mantle）与地壳（crust）组成的巨大平面，经过岁月漫长的漂移，重新塑造着地球表面与海洋。大多数时间，它们的移动十分缓慢、无灾无害，也不易察觉。
&#13;
伸出你的双手，手掌向下，中指指尖相对。你的右手代表的是北美地壳板块，在它之上，就是我们生活的整片大陆，分布着从纽约的世界贸易中心一号到西雅图的太空针。你的左手代表的是胡安德富卡（Juan de Fuca）海洋板块，面积约9万平方英里（约23万平方千米）。它们相遇的地方，就是卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带。现在，将你的左手在下方滑过你的右手。这就是胡安德富卡所做的运动：缓慢的，持续的，往北美地壳的下方移动着。当你尝试这么做，你的右手会滑过左手的胳膊，就像要捋起袖子那样。而北美地壳却不是这样前进的：它会卡住，锲入另一板块的表面。
&#13;
现在停止移动你的双手，将你的右手指关节曲起。在胡安德富卡板块下方，被卡住的北美地壳就是这样向上凸起的，在它的东边方向受到挤压，以每年相对3至4毫米及30至40毫米的速度发生着。这样的过程可以经历相当长时间。大陆是在不停生长的，它还很年轻，上面的岩石还具有弹性（岩石就像我们人类一样，年代越久就越僵硬）。但这不可能是无期限的。它会碰到阻挡物——所谓的“稳定地块”（craton），位于大陆中心地带年代久远的巨大僵硬陆地——或早或晚，北美地壳会变得像一只弹簧那样。出现那样的状况，只有卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带南部作出让步——比方说，抬起你的前两只手指——导致的结果是发生8.0级至8.6级地震。那可是场大地震。而如果是整个俯冲带“妥协”（compromised），地震学家称之为整体断裂（full-margin rupture），造成的地震将达8.7级至9.2级。
&#13;
毫无疑问，那是超级大地震。
&#13;
将你的右手向外翻开，使些力气，你的手掌可以倒转平摊下来。第二次大地震在此时发生时，大陆的西北边缘，从加利福尼亚到加拿大，从大陆架到卡斯卡迪，会下沉6英尺（约1.8米），以及向西弹出30至100英尺（9.1米到30。48米）——在仅仅几分钟内，释放出几个世纪积聚的隆起与被挤压的巨大能量。有些移动会发生在海底，改变巨量海水的位置（留意当你翻转手掌时手指的反应）。海水会向上形成巨大的高山般的立面，在顷刻之间又轰然崩塌。其中的一面会涌向西部，往日本的方向；另一面会涌向东部，这道长达700英里的水墙将会抵达西北部海岸。平均来讲，就在地震发生的15分钟之后。当地面的震动平息，海啸退去，原先的地表会变得面目全非。肯尼思•墨菲（Kenneth Murphy）是美国联邦紧急事务管理署（FEMA）X区块的负责人，监督的区域包括俄勒冈州、华盛顿州、爱达荷州和阿拉斯加。墨菲表示:“我们认为，5号洲际公路以西将会被一举摧毁。”
&#13;
在美国西北部，受影响的范围将超过4000平方英里（约1万平方千米），包括西雅图、塔科马港（华盛顿西部城市）、波特兰、尤金（俄勒冈西部城市）、塞勒姆（俄勒冈首府），奥林匹亚（华盛顿首府），波及700万居民。当整体断裂发生，那些地区会遭遇北美大陆历史上最严峻的自然灾害。约有3000人死于1906年的旧金山大地震；近2000人死于卡特琳娜飓风；近300人死于桑迪飓风。FEMA估计，将会有1万3千人死于卡斯卡迪亚地震及海啸，另有2万7千人受伤。他们估计，大约需要为100万重新安置的人提供临时住所，以及为另外220万人提供饮用水和食物。“这一次我真的希望是科学出错了，人类在之后的一千年都不要经历这些。”墨菲说。
&#13;
事实上，相关的科学研究相当活跃，幕后主导的科学家就是克里斯•戈尔德芬格。感谢他与他的同事的努力工作，我们目前得知卡斯卡迪亚地震在接下来50年爆发的机率大约是三分之一；而发生超级大地震的机率大约是十分之一。即使这些数字仍不足以全面反映它潜在的危险——或者更准确来讲，整个北美西北地区在“大敌当前”时竟是如此大意。整个故事中最令人忧虑的地方在于：30年前，从没有人知道卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带曾发生过大地震；45年前，甚至没有人知道这里发生过地震。
&#13;
贰
&#13;
1804年5月，梅里韦瑟•刘易斯（Meriwether Lewis）和威廉•克拉克（William Clark）与他们的探险队从圣路易斯出发，进行美国历史上首次官方国情考察。18个月后，他们到达太平洋，在俄勒冈州如今靠近阿斯托利亚（Astoria）的地方驻扎下来。那时，美利坚合众国刚成立29年，加拿大甚至还未宣布建国。这片大陆广袤的土地对白人探险者来说几乎一无所知。主导这次探险的托马斯•杰斐逊（Thomas Jefferson）甚至认为他们可能会遇见猛犸象。印第安人已经在西北地区生活了数十个世纪，但他们没有书面语言，早前来到这里的欧洲人也没有交给他们关于地震的记录。新来的人仅凭表面的样子决定来如何使用土地。就表面价值而言，这里算是相当富饶：广袤、廉价、气温宜人、高产，无论从哪个方面看，都挑不出毛病。
&#13;
近一个半世纪的时光流逝而过，没有人留意到长久以来宁静安详的美国西北部有任何躁动的迹象。要再过50年后，科学家才逐渐解读出这里的地震历史。地理学——就像很多地理学家会告诉你的那样，绝不是什么富有魅力的学科，研究隐没于地下的尘土之中，而靓丽的荣光属于人类及宇宙——从遗传学，到神经系统科学，到物理学。但或早或晚，每个学科都有它的奠基之日。而对发现卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带来说，就是我们这个时代最伟大的地理发现。
&#13;
最早的线索来自地理学。世界上最严重的地震几乎都发生在环太平洋火山带（Ring of Fire）。这条火山带活动频繁，地质极不稳定，从新西兰往上经过印度尼西亚和日本，穿过海洋抵达阿拉斯加，再向下延伸至美国西部海岸及智利。日本，2011年，9.0级地震；印度尼西亚，2004年，9.1级地震；阿拉斯加，1964年，9.2级地震；智利1960年，9.5级地震——就算还不及1960年代提出板块运动学说，地理学家就注意到了其中的规律。最终，环太平洋火山带被证实就是由俯冲带形成的环状区域。几乎这个地区所有地震的成因都是大陆板块在运动中受到了海洋板块的阻挡——就像北美板块受到来自胡安德富卡的阻挡——在瞬间释放出能量；几乎所有火山爆发的成因都是海洋板块滑入大陆板块之下，积聚到一定温度后，压力达到极致，熔化了上方的岩石。
&#13;
美国西北部正好位于环太平洋火山带。它的海岸处，海洋板块正滑入大陆板块下方。在内陆，卡斯卡迪火山山脉下方，胡安德富卡板块的温度正不断上升，熔化了它上方的一切。换一种说法就是，卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带正如戈尔德芬格指出的那样：“完美印证了所有地质结构运动上的假设”。然而，没有任何历史记录下这里曾爆发过大地震——或者说，曾发生过地震。相反，其他俯冲带不时就爆发大地震，小地震更是不胜枚举: 5.0级地震，4.0级地震，震感就如同困扰为什么邻居要在半夜挪沙发。在日本待上一周，你就会对此习以为常。而你可能在美国西北地区的好几个城市生活了一辈子——有过几次，事实上如果你足够“幸运”的话——都没感受到过大地的震动。1970年代，地理学家面临的问题是，究竟卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带是否打破过它那吊诡的沉默？
&#13;
1980年代晚期，美国地质调查局的布莱恩•艾特沃特（Brian Atwater）和一位名叫戴维•亚玛古奇（David Yamaguchi）的研究生找到了上述问题的答案，以及卡斯卡迪拼图的另一主要线索。他们的发现主要在一个被称为幽灵森林的地方。华盛顿州海岸一线，科波利斯河（Copalis River）两岸生长的一片美西红侧柏（western red cedars）。2014年夏天，当我与艾特沃特和亚玛古奇一道漫步其中，很快就明白了它得名的原因。整片红侧柏分布在河流北部宽广的一片低矮的沼泽地里。树木早已死去，但枝干依旧摧枯拉朽地立在那里。树叶早就落光，枝丫折断，树皮也不见踪迹，只剩下光秃秃的树干隐没在一片银灰之中，就好像它们在身体里给自己盖下了坟墓。
&#13;
导致幽灵森林里红侧柏死亡的是海水浸泡。长久以来，人们都以为四周的海平面不断上升，淹没了它们的树根，于是在漫长的消耗中一棵一棵死去。然而1987年时，艾特沃特在土层中找到了地面突然沉降的证据，并且在华盛顿海岸一线都有相似发现，于是他怀疑，在过去时——由于地面突然下降，树木是在顷刻间死去的。为了得到证实，他找到了研究树木年轮的专家亚玛古奇。亚玛古奇提取了红侧柏的样本，得出了它们是同时死亡的结论：每一棵树的最后一道年轮都中止在1699年的夏天。由于树木不会在冬季生长，他与艾特沃特认为，在1699年8月至1700年5月间的某个时候，这里发生的地震使土地突然下沉，并最终导致了树木的死亡。这个时间假设把美国西北部的书面历史整整提早了一百年——公正说来，幽灵森林这种侦探故事可以就此打住了。
&#13;
但事情并没有完。如果你从幽灵森林出发，正对南方行进5000英里(约8046千米)，将会抵达的是日本东北沿岸。2011年的地震清楚地证明了那里是海啸高危区。而日本自公元599年起就有对海啸的相关记录。在此后的1400年中，有一件古怪的事不时引起过关注。元禄时代（Genroku era）第12年的第12个月的第8天，长达600英里（约956千米）的海浪侵袭了海岸，夷平了房屋，漫过了护城河。日本人知道，海啸是由地震导致的，而在元禄时代，没有人感受到大地震动。海浪的来袭没有任何可察觉的迹象，当科学家开始研究此现象时，将它称作“孤立子体海啸事件”（orphan tsunami）
&#13;
终于，在1996年的《自然》（Nature）杂志上，地震学家佐竹建治（Kenji Satake）和他的三位同事借鉴了艾特沃特和亚玛古奇的研究，为那个“孤立子体”找到了它的“母体”——也为卡斯卡迪亚的故事填补上了细节详实的空白。大约是1700年1月26日晚上9点时分，一场里氏9.0级地震袭击了美国西北部，导致了土地沉降，淹死了沿岸的森林，在大海中掀起了达整片大陆一半长度的巨型海浪；而另一半海浪用了10个小时才横渡过大洋，大约在1700年1月27日抵达日本：按照当地的历法，正是元禄时代第12年的第12个月的第8天。
&#13;
当科学家们重建出1700年的那场地震，以前被忽视的一些记录突然成为了作证的线索。1964年，不列颠哥伦比亚Huu-ay-aht First Nation部落的首领路易斯•努克米斯（Louis Nookmis）讲过一个故事，一直流传了子孙七代。故事是关于生活在温哥华岛上帕赤纳湾（Pachena Bay）人们的集体死亡。“我想是因为那天晚上大地的剧烈震动，”努克米斯回忆。根据另外一个部落的历史，“他们突然沉到了海底，全都淹死了，没有人生还。”大约100年前，Makah部落的首领比利•鲍尔奇（Billy Balch）回忆了一个相似的故事。听说在他出生前，所有海水都从华盛顿州的尼亚湾（Neah Bay）退去，又突然倒灌回来，淹没了整个地区。幸存者发现独木舟挂到了树上。2005年的研究中，彼时华盛顿大学的地震学家露丝•鲁德温（Ruth Ludwin）和9位同事一起，收集和分析了印第安人的地震与海水泛滥记录。有些记录包含了足够的信息来估计地震发生的时间范围。大体上而言，这个时间的中间值域位于1701年。
&#13;
对欧裔美国人来讲，这些故事并不能成为假设的充分证据，直到假设本身得到印证。然而对1700年卡斯卡迪亚地震的还原依旧是一片稀有的自然拼图，完美地勾勒了地壳移动说暂时无法解释的部分。这真是令人惊叹的科学；对科学来讲，这简直是令人惊叹的发现。然而对数百万生活在美国西北部的人们来说，这无疑是个噩耗，正如戈尔德芬格所说：“在80年代晚期和90年代早期，人们已经感觉到了沮丧。”
&#13;
戈尔德芬格是在他位于俄勒冈州立大学的实验室里对我说这番话的。那是一栋低矮的组合式预制房，穿过英语文学系后，很容易误认为到了维修部门。实验室里有步入式冷冻柜。进入冷冻柜，从地面延伸至天花板的架子上摆满了贴有各种标签的试管，直径4英寸（约10厘米），长5英尺（约1.5米）。每支试管里都摆着一块海底的岩芯样本。每个样本都包含了过去1万年间铭刻在海底的历史。俯冲带地震爆发时，土壤如激流般从陆地的坡面一泻而下，在海底形成永久沉积物。通过考量每个样本的数量与体积，比较它们在卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带的连续分布，戈尔德芬格与他的同事一起测定了整块地区已经断裂的面积，发生的频率，以及激烈程度。
&#13;
得益于那项工作，我们如今知道美国西北部在过去的1万年里经历了41次地震。如果你用1万除以41，会得出243，那就是卡斯卡迪亚爆发的重复周期：每次地震爆发间歇的平均时间又会不断削减。这样的时间跨度显现了它的危险性，即因为它爆发的周期很长——漫长到让我们疏忽地在最糟糕的断层线上建立起了整个文明——而同时它又不足够漫长——自1700年那次地震以来，我们如今正进入243年重复周期的第315年（注：报道发表于2015年）。
&#13;
可说起来，如果要在这些数字里挑刺并非什么难事。重复周期取的是平均数，而平均数本身是很“狡猾”的：10是1和11的平均数，也是11和2的平均数。然而，这却不足以回避我们所面临问题的严峻性。2011年发生在日本的灾难亦是矛盾导致的结果：日本拥有最先进的地震科学预报，而预报基于的却是错误的当地可承受损害的预判。美国西北部也会面临相似的现实——不过蕴藏的矛盾更是千丝万缕。“就科学而言，这是很有意思的（研究），”戈尔德芬格说，“我很享受它。然而在我们所知与所应付诸行动之间的鸿沟却日益扩大。我已经在世界上地震预防最完备的国家经历了一次大地震，而如果那是在波特兰”——戈尔德芬格在讲完这句话前摇了摇头，“这么说吧，我还是不要在那里的好。”
&#13;
叁
&#13;
卡斯卡迪亚大地震爆发的第一个信号将会是出现压缩波，从断层带向外散发而出。压缩波是传播速度很快的高频波，犬类以及一些其他动物能够听到，但对人类而言只是一些微不足道的颤动。它们不会造成什么伤害，不过对预报来讲却十分有效。由于它们的传播速度快，地震传感器往往能够在早于其他地震波30至90秒之间探测到它。这些时间已经足够启动地震报警系统，比如日本全境目前都在使用这种方法。它会自动激活各种救生模式：中止铁路运行，关闭发电厂，启动电梯及消防闸门，通报医院停止手术，触发警报，而使公众能所有防备。美国西北部是没有地震报警系统的。当卡斯卡迪亚地震爆发时，将会传来一片刺耳的狗吠声，在表面波到达前，人们会发出不知所以然的“究竟是怎么回事”的疑惑。表面波的传播速度较慢，是低频波，会让整个地表上下或是左右翻转：直到这种晃动出现，才会引来人们的严阵以待。
&#13;
震动发生不久，卡斯卡迪亚以西甚至更广大地区的电网就会中断。如果地震发生在夜晚，接下来的劫难都将在一片漆黑中一一降临。理论上地震时那些待在家里的人是最安全的；在私人住宅加装避震设施常常花不了多少钱，执行起来也最容易，但生活在美国西北部的人们常年被安逸的环境麻痹了风险意识，几乎对此漠不关心。然而这种冷漠很快就会被击破，以及房间里所有的玻璃制品。房间里的所有东西，只要不是固定住的，都会随地板倾斜，或是直接摔下：书架、台灯、电脑、餐具间里装着各种调料的瓶瓶罐罐。冰箱会跑出厨房，自动拔掉电源，整个翻转了身。电热水壶掉下了台子，压坏了室内输气管道。地基不稳的房子开始滑动——或者，它们会依照惯性原地不动，直到地基与下边的地面一道，朝西边震动。地面起伏不定，房屋即将崩塌。
&#13;
整片地区的大型设施也不会幸免于难。直到1974年，俄勒冈州才有了第一部抗震指引；直到1994年，美国西北部的少数几个地方才制定了应对9.0级地震的规定。大量建筑都是在那之前修建的。俄勒冈州地矿局（DOGAMI）负责人伊恩•马丁（Ian Madin）估计，州内75%的设施无法应对卡斯卡迪亚大地震。FEMA的估算是，整个地区的100万栋建筑——其中超过3000栋是学校——将轰然崩塌或是在地震中毫无抵抗力。行将崩塌的还包括一半的公路桥梁；三分之二的铁路与机场；三分之一的消防局；一半的警察局，三分之二的医院，以及波特兰两条河流上17座桥梁中的15座，均无法幸存。
&#13;
灾难往往发端于诸多细小的问题，从而导致致命的后果：因为少了一颗钉子，而输了一场战争；因为15个各自独立又不紧要的小错误，而使喷气式客机失事。俯冲带地震因循的却是相反的规律：一个巨大的问题引发出成千上万问题。卡斯卡迪亚地震会引起整个地区的土地滑坡——西雅图的应急管理办公室预计，本市受到影响的范围将达3万平方英里（约7万平方千米）。它还会导致液化（liquefaction）现象。看起来坚固的土地像是液体那样“流动”起来，摧毁上方的一切建造。西雅图有15%的面积是可液化土地，包括17座日托中心，以及34500人的房屋。俄勒冈的能源基础设施枢纽面临的是同样的困境。从波特兰方向延伸来的6英里长的管道中输送的是州内90%的液态能源，提供着从变电站到天然气终端的每日所需。于此同时，摇晃、滑坡，震动会接着触发火灾、洪水、管道故障、堤坝决口，以及有害物质泄漏。以上任何一种二次灾害都毫无疑问会造成损失、破坏与死伤。
&#13;
犬吠过4至6分钟后，震动会慢慢平息。在接下来的几分钟，整个地区会继续自身崩坏到四分五裂。这时，海浪就赶到了。真正的破坏才要刚刚启幕。
&#13;
在所有的自然灾害中，在海啸中生还的机率是最低的。唯一活命的方法是当海啸来临时，你不要出现在现场：避开海啸高危区，或者尽快跑去高处。对生活在卡斯卡迪亚洪灾区（inundation zone）的7万1千名居民而言，两次灾难发生之间逃生的窗口期十分短暂。直到知道地震来了，人们才会明白发生了什么——“震动-预警系统”，俄勒冈西塞德（Seaside）的城市规划师凯文•库普勒斯（Kevin Cupples）开玩笑说——雪上加霜的是，由于地震破坏了道路，人们只能依靠自己的双腿逃生。取决于所处地点的不同，你所拥有的时间在10分钟到30分钟之间不等。这意味着你没有时间找手电筒，没有时间在毁于一旦的屋子里茫然犹豫，不能寻找家人，或者是当个“好人”。“海啸来时，你所能做的只有拔腿就跑，”俄勒冈地震安全政策顾问委员会（OSSPAC）主席杰•威尔森（Jay Wilson）说，“你只能保护自己，不要回头，不要回去救任何人。你拔腿就跑，为了保住自己的性命。”
&#13;
在海啸中救人的最好时机是在它发生之前，但西北海岸的人们尚未严肃对待这件事。没有人要求旅店和公司公布逃生路线，或者为雇员提供逃生训练。在俄勒冈，自1995年起不再允许在洪灾区修建医院、学校、消防局和警察局，但已经建好的设施不会受到影响，开发商想要修建旅店、能源设施、养老院也不是没有可能，他们只需要与DOGAMI商议逃生计划即可。“你来到办公室，坐下，”伊恩•马丁说道：“我说，‘那简直蠢透了’，但你说，‘好吧，看来我们已经讨论完了。’”
&#13;
过分宽松的安全政策使洪灾区内的人们无法幸免灾害。俄勒冈海岸22%的人口是65岁以上的老人，州内29%的人口是残疾人，这些数字在其他有些海边城市只会更为可观。“我们没法救他们，”凯文•库普勒斯说，“我不会讲些什么糖衣炮弹的话，比如‘啊，好吧，我们会照看老人的。’不，我们不会。”同样，也不会有人想着要救游客。在洪灾区内的华盛顿国家公园每天接待的游客平均数是1万7千人。马丁预计，夏日周末，5万至10万人会来到俄勒冈的海滩度假。“他们中的大多数人根本不知道要如何逃生，”他说，“而海滩恰恰是最难逃生的地点。”
&#13;
那些没能靠自身逃出洪灾区的人，很快会迎来更大的威胁。一个成年人会被时速6.7英里（约10公里），深至脚踝的海浪击倒。当海浪逼近时，速度会达到原来的两倍，高度会随海岸线的轮廓改变，由20英尺至超过100英尺不等（约6米到30米）。这根本不是日本艺术家葛饰北斋（Katsushika Hokusai）的浮世绘，海浪从海平面跃起，从高处回落。现实是，会像整个大洋被高高抬起，瞬间淹没陆地。迎面击来的也绝不只有海水——在美国西北部的沿海城镇，那将会是5层楼高的巨浪，席卷着卡车、门框、捕鱼船，电线杆，以及目力所及一切。
&#13;
当海啸退去，查看受灾状况时，你需要的是国际空间站的协助。灾害将从加利福尼亚蔓延至加拿大。地震对卡斯卡迪亚西部造成的浩劫，可波及加利福尼亚的萨克拉门托和印第安纳州东北部的韦恩堡（Fort Wayne）这样的重灾区，亦可及至纽约。FEMA预计，搜救将在10万平方英里（约26万平方千米）的范围内进行，受灾海岸线将长达453英里（约729千米）。就伤亡人数而言：正如我之前引述的数据——2万7千人受伤，近1万3千人死亡——基于的是官方预设的一种状况：假使地震发生在2月6日的上午9点41分。而如果地震爆发在夏季，海滩上挤满了度假的人，以上遇难人数可能只是实际的一个小数点。
&#13;
玻璃酒杯、古董花瓶、髋关节骨头、心脏：会在瞬间破碎的，修复却往往缓慢，如果还可以被修复的话。OSSPAC预计，5号洲际公路通道上，由地震造成的电力中断需要1个月至3个月才能恢复；需要1个月至1年才能恢复供应饮用水和启动下水道；需要6个月至1年开通高速公路；需要18个月来重建医院。在沿海地区，需要的时间更加漫长。任何选择或者别无选择滞留灾区的人们，要在没有电的情况下生活3至6个月；在没有饮用水和下水道的情况下生活1至3年；在没有医院的情况下生活3年甚至更久。而且这些预计数据不适用于洪灾区，之后的数年那里都不再适合人类居住。
&#13;
所有这些，究竟会造成多少损失？FEMA的救灾与重建计划中纳入了各项数字，唯独不包括损失金额。但无论最终的数字是多少——就像之前的其他灾难一样，美国的纳税人会负担起其中75%的份额——美国西北部的经济都会全面崩溃。由于基础设施受到重创，公司要么倒闭要么就不得不搬迁。当地居民也会逃也般的搬走。OSSPAC预计会有大规模人口迁移以及长期的人口下滑。地震发生时，克里斯•戈尔德芬格本人可不想在那里。但无论出于何种考量，灾害过后前往那里或者留下的想法都实在糟糕透了。
&#13;
肆
&#13;
表面看来，地震展现在我们面前的似乎是空间问题：我们生活在断层线上，住在砖块盖起的大楼里，中意靠近海边的度假屋，而实则隐患重重。但问题的另一面是，它也在我们面前抛出了时间问题。地球已经有45亿年历史，但我们却是年轻的物种，相较而言，每个人不过就是这么一辈子，人类生命之短暂，造成了一种时空感上的狭隘——相比自身而言，我们对缓慢的行星运转是如此无知，或者说，无知无觉。
&#13;
这个问题是双向的。我们长久以来都对卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带一无所知，是因为我们无法窥见久远的过去。而如今它对我们所造成的威胁，是因为我们无法预见长远的将来。这不是资讯匮乏的问题。如今我们已经心知肚明在卡斯卡迪亚断层线上，在某一天会发生什么。这也不是想象力匮乏的问题；如果你觉得问题出在这，可以看看今年（注：2015年）夏天上映的由布拉德•佩顿（Brad Peyton）主演的《末日崩塌》（San Andreas）——地震是如何摧毁几乎整个西海岸的。不仅如此，整个世界都笼罩在各种末日阴影之中：病毒、机器人、资源短缺、僵尸、外星人、瘟疫。电影画面证实了我们其实长于编写未来的脚本，包括写书悲剧。然而世界末日的景象透露的不过是一种逃生主义，而非道德唤醒。我们从未想过要实际做些什么——而对严峻将来的预见理应要让我们设法阻止它的出现。
&#13;
诚然，问题不单局限于地震。卡斯卡迪亚面临的状况——似乎触手可及的灾难，也是对这个世代生态报复的寓言。它所揭示的问题，正是我们当下所要正视的。一个社会应当如何应对毁灭性灾难即将到来的危机，尽管它迫在眉睫，却具体时限不明？而当其建立的全部文明与设施在自然灾害面前将不堪一击，它又应当如何纠正自身的所作所为？
&#13;
在美国西北部，我见的最后一个人是西塞德的学校负责人道格•多尔蒂（Doug Dougherty）。西塞德的大部分学校都在海啸洪灾区。多尔蒂负责的4间学校——学生总人数达1600名，只有一间是相对安全的，其他几间都建在海平面以上5至15英尺（约1.5米到4.5米）的位置。一旦发生海啸，他们将会被没入45英尺（约13.7米）深的海底。
&#13;
多尔蒂在2009年时告诉我，他发现在洪灾区以外有一些正在出售的土地，打算要盖从幼儿园到12年级的校园。4年后，为了支付1亿2千800万美元账单，该地区发行了债券。多尔蒂试图向俄勒冈州的国会代表寻求帮助却一无所获。俄勒冈州在抗震升级上花费不菲，但各种措施均不适用于洪灾区内的建筑。目前，多尔蒂能做的就是让他的学生了解逃生路线。
&#13;
然而，这并非对所有学生都有用。在吉尔哈特（Gearhart）社区的一间小学，学生将逃无可逃。“他们不可能从那间学校逃走，”多尔蒂说，“他们无处可去。”学校的一边是大海，另一边是宽阔的沼泽地。海啸来时，吉尔哈特唯一可去的地方是学校后面的小山坡。山顶高出海平面45英尺——低于整体断裂时的海浪高度。目前，通往山坡的路上有标识写道：“临时海啸集合地点”。我向多尔蒂问起州内的长远计划。“没有长远计划。”他说。
&#13;
多尔蒂的办公室位于洪灾区的深处，距离海滩有数个街区远。每一天，在他看不见的地方，海浪卷起，消散，化作泡沫，冲上海滩。80英里（约128千米）外，大海1万英尺（3048米）深处，地质时钟的指针缓慢但一刻不停地滑动。而地震学家都举起了他们的手表，在地质时间赶上人类的时间之前，他们还剩多少时间，他们还有什么可做。</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>両儀織: </b><br>
<span>【旧】《纽约客》：那场即将摧毁美国西北部的超级大地震</span><br>
<span>“美国西北部太平洋海岸大断层 恐引发9级大地震海啸可越洋袭日本”，这个可用不到30个字概括的新闻，《纽约客》记者Kathryn Schulz将它写成了一篇特稿《The Really Big One》（超级大地震），并在今年（2016年）首次为《纽约客》摘得普利策特稿奖。</span><br>
<span>与我们惯常所理解的“非虚构或者讲故事型”的特稿不同，这是一篇解释性报道，阐释了一个自日本2011年“3•11”大地震以来围绕在美国西北海岸人民心头的“大噩梦”： 位于美国近海50英里(80.47千米)处的卡斯卡迪亚断层(Cascadia Fault)线有一天可能会裂开，引发地震和海啸。这个断层发生里氏8级以上的大规模地震的平均时间间隔是240年，300多年前该地发生最后一次“超级地震”。灾难似乎迫在眉睫，却又具体时限不明，人类显得无助又脆弱。</span><br>
<span>这个涉及了地质、科学、环境、历史等多个领域的问题，女记者Kathryn Schulz用她令人印象深刻的时空视野交织成篇，展现了她对文字非凡的驾驭能力。普利策评奖委员会说，文章是对卡斯卡迪亚断层带雅致又科学的叙述，是环境报道与写作的杰作。</span><br>
<span>值得一提的是，普利策直到2014年才对杂志开放。2015年，以品味以及写作著称的《纽约客》就入围了特稿奖；最终在普利策100周年之际，夺得特稿奖和批评奖，开创了杂志拿到普利策的先河。</span><br>
<span>传媒狐（微信号：media-fox）独家编译了这篇约1万字的特稿，随同公号的新栏目“长悦读”一并推出。</span><br>
<span>文｜Kathryn Schulz 编译｜Meow</span><br>
<span>2011年的地震与海啸袭击日本东北时，克里斯•戈尔德芬格（Chris Goldfinger）正在200英里（约321千米）外的柏市（Kashiwa）参加地震学国际会议。地面刚开始晃动，房间里的每个人都笑了。地震在日本很平常——已经是一个礼拜里的第三次——而且无论怎样讲，与会者参加的正是跟地震有关的会议。接着，每个人都看了看时间。</span><br>
<span>地震学家清楚，地震持续的时间可以用来预示它的里氏级数。1989年夺去了63人性命造成60亿美元损失的加利福尼亚洛马•普雷塔（Loma Prieta）地震持续了15秒，里氏震级6.9级。时长30秒左右的地震通常在7.5级左右；时长1分钟的地震规模更大，但仍处于7级；震动长达2分钟，震级就会进入8级；持续3分钟，标度会在8的范围内继续提升。到达4分钟，地震就可达里氏9级。</span><br>
<span>戈尔德芬格看向他的手表时，时间是下午2点45分。会议正进入当日的尾声。他在头脑里盘算起了寿司。讲台上的人有些犹豫，不知是否该继续发言。震感不算强，但超过了60秒标记线，持续时间比这周的其他几次都要久。晃动感在增强。会议室里用的是小型带底轮的塑料椅子。身材高大结实的戈尔德芬格琢磨着，我才不要钻下身避难呢。1分30秒后，会议室里的每个人都站起身，跑向门口。</span><br>
<span>时值三月。空气中尚有寒意，骤然间有雪飘来，落到地面又不见了踪迹。同样不见了的是往常的地面，如今变得折断、凸起，开裂。戈尔德芬格打了个比方，就像是驾着没有缓冲装置的汽车驶过岩石路面，而车子和岩石路又恰好处于大海的包围中。震动已经持续了超过2分钟。树上还挂着上个秋天的枯叶，发出一阵沙沙的奇怪声响。他与同事刚刚路过的大楼顶部的旗杆正以40度的幅度晃动。建筑本身使用了防震技术，大楼主体建在可移动的承重体上，而非直接建在地基上。戈尔德芬格探出身子。底座正倾斜成一个角度，以前后约一英尺的幅度摆动着，在院子里磕出了一道沟。他认为应该没什么大问题，收回了身子。他的手表指针已经划过了3分钟，还在不断滴答往前。</span><br>
<span>妈的，戈尔德芬格想，虽然还不至于惊慌失措，却足够使他诧异。几十年来，地震学家都相信日本不可能发生超过8.4级的地震。然而2005年时，在日本北淡町（Hokudan）举行的一次会议中，一位名叫池田安隆（Yasutaka Ikeda）的日本地震学家辩称，日本很可能将要发生达9.0级的地震——并造成灾难性后果，而日本举世闻名的地震海啸预防措施——包括防波堤的高度，都是基于错误的科学设计的。他的演讲收到了一阵彬彬有礼的掌声，很快就被人忘记了。如今，在震动持续4分钟后，戈尔德芬格意识到，我们生活的行星本身证明了那位日本“卡珊德拉”（希腊神话人物，有预言能力）的预言是正确的。</span><br>
<span>有一阵子，场面是相当激动人心的：这几乎是一场实时地震科学的革命。然而很快，兴奋的心情就烟消云散了。戈尔德芬格和每一位站在北淡町空地上的地震学家都知道，接下来将会发生什么。他们中的一人拿出了手机，检索起NHK电视台的视频，那是晃动一开始时，由飞行至海面上空的直升机拍摄的。戈尔德芬格在室外站了30分钟后，他在两英寸的屏幕上看到了席卷而过的海啸波。</span><br>
<span>最终，超过1万8千人在这场9.0级的东日本大地震以及随后引发的海啸中死亡，重创了日本东北省份，导致福岛核电站停工，并造成约2200亿美元损失。那周早前的几次晃动，被证实是日本历史上有记录以来破坏力最大的地震的前震。但对戈尔德芬格而言，作为美国俄勒冈州立大学的古地震专家，世界上鲜有人问津的断层线（fault line）研究权威，这场地震本身只是前震：是另一场地震的“前奏”。</span><br>
<img src="http://img.mp.itc.cn/upload/20160421/9d4e6cbc78e746dd98146b54946a0e12_th.jpg" title="http://img.mp.itc.cn/upload/20160421/9d4e6cbc78e746dd98146b54946a0e12_th.jpg"><br>
<span>壹</span><br>
<span>大部分美国人听过圣安德烈亚斯（San Andreas）断层线的名字，它几乎与加利福尼亚州等长，还经年不休地流传着马上就要“大爆发”的传言。不管圣安德烈亚斯以前发生过什么，传言本身很有误导性。每条断层线都有它的能量上限，由它的长度、宽度，以及能够波及的距离而定。就圣安德烈亚斯——这条世界上研究最多最彻底的断层线——而言，它的最高上限约为8.2级——的确算得上是大地震，但由于里氏震级是由地震波最大振幅的常用对数演算而来的，这仅是2011年东日本地震强度的6%。</span><br>
<span>然而，在圣安德烈亚斯北部还有一条断层线，卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带（Cascadia subduction zone），它沿太平洋西北地区分布，长约700英里（约1126千米）。从加利福尼亚州的门多西诺角（Cape Mendocino）附近出发，一路经过俄勒冈州、华盛顿州，另一端位于加拿大南部的温哥华岛（Vancouver Island）。“卡斯卡迪亚”的名字，一部分来源于卡斯卡迪山脉（Cascade Range）,它是贯穿同样路径且有数英里蔓延至内陆的火山山脉；“俯冲带”是指两个板块相遇，一个板块插入另一个相对被动的板块之下的部分。地壳板块是由地幔（mantle）与地壳（crust）组成的巨大平面，经过岁月漫长的漂移，重新塑造着地球表面与海洋。大多数时间，它们的移动十分缓慢、无灾无害，也不易察觉。</span><br>
<span>伸出你的双手，手掌向下，中指指尖相对。你的右手代表的是北美地壳板块，在它之上，就是我们生活的整片大陆，分布着从纽约的世界贸易中心一号到西雅图的太空针。你的左手代表的是胡安德富卡（Juan de Fuca）海洋板块，面积约9万平方英里（约23万平方千米）。它们相遇的地方，就是卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带。现在，将你的左手在下方滑过你的右手。这就是胡安德富卡所做的运动：缓慢的，持续的，往北美地壳的下方移动着。当你尝试这么做，你的右手会滑过左手的胳膊，就像要捋起袖子那样。而北美地壳却不是这样前进的：它会卡住，锲入另一板块的表面。</span><br>
<span>现在停止移动你的双手，将你的右手指关节曲起。在胡安德富卡板块下方，被卡住的北美地壳就是这样向上凸起的，在它的东边方向受到挤压，以每年相对3至4毫米及30至40毫米的速度发生着。这样的过程可以经历相当长时间。大陆是在不停生长的，它还很年轻，上面的岩石还具有弹性（岩石就像我们人类一样，年代越久就越僵硬）。但这不可能是无期限的。它会碰到阻挡物——所谓的“稳定地块”（craton），位于大陆中心地带年代久远的巨大僵硬陆地——或早或晚，北美地壳会变得像一只弹簧那样。出现那样的状况，只有卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带南部作出让步——比方说，抬起你的前两只手指——导致的结果是发生8.0级至8.6级地震。那可是场大地震。而如果是整个俯冲带“妥协”（compromised），地震学家称之为整体断裂（full-margin rupture），造成的地震将达8.7级至9.2级。</span><br>
<span>毫无疑问，那是超级大地震。</span><br>
<span>将你的右手向外翻开，使些力气，你的手掌可以倒转平摊下来。第二次大地震在此时发生时，大陆的西北边缘，从加利福尼亚到加拿大，从大陆架到卡斯卡迪，会下沉6英尺（约1.8米），以及向西弹出30至100英尺（9.1米到30。48米）——在仅仅几分钟内，释放出几个世纪积聚的隆起与被挤压的巨大能量。有些移动会发生在海底，改变巨量海水的位置（留意当你翻转手掌时手指的反应）。海水会向上形成巨大的高山般的立面，在顷刻之间又轰然崩塌。其中的一面会涌向西部，往日本的方向；另一面会涌向东部，这道长达700英里的水墙将会抵达西北部海岸。平均来讲，就在地震发生的15分钟之后。当地面的震动平息，海啸退去，原先的地表会变得面目全非。肯尼思•墨菲（Kenneth Murphy）是美国联邦紧急事务管理署（FEMA）X区块的负责人，监督的区域包括俄勒冈州、华盛顿州、爱达荷州和阿拉斯加。墨菲表示:“我们认为，5号洲际公路以西将会被一举摧毁。”</span><br>
<span>在美国西北部，受影响的范围将超过4000平方英里（约1万平方千米），包括西雅图、塔科马港（华盛顿西部城市）、波特兰、尤金（俄勒冈西部城市）、塞勒姆（俄勒冈首府），奥林匹亚（华盛顿首府），波及700万居民。当整体断裂发生，那些地区会遭遇北美大陆历史上最严峻的自然灾害。约有3000人死于1906年的旧金山大地震；近2000人死于卡特琳娜飓风；近300人死于桑迪飓风。FEMA估计，将会有1万3千人死于卡斯卡迪亚地震及海啸，另有2万7千人受伤。他们估计，大约需要为100万重新安置的人提供临时住所，以及为另外220万人提供饮用水和食物。“这一次我真的希望是科学出错了，人类在之后的一千年都不要经历这些。”墨菲说。</span><br>
<span>事实上，相关的科学研究相当活跃，幕后主导的科学家就是克里斯•戈尔德芬格。感谢他与他的同事的努力工作，我们目前得知卡斯卡迪亚地震在接下来50年爆发的机率大约是三分之一；而发生超级大地震的机率大约是十分之一。即使这些数字仍不足以全面反映它潜在的危险——或者更准确来讲，整个北美西北地区在“大敌当前”时竟是如此大意。整个故事中最令人忧虑的地方在于：30年前，从没有人知道卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带曾发生过大地震；45年前，甚至没有人知道这里发生过地震。</span><br>
<span>贰</span><br>
<span>1804年5月，梅里韦瑟•刘易斯（Meriwether Lewis）和威廉•克拉克（William Clark）与他们的探险队从圣路易斯出发，进行美国历史上首次官方国情考察。18个月后，他们到达太平洋，在俄勒冈州如今靠近阿斯托利亚（Astoria）的地方驻扎下来。那时，美利坚合众国刚成立29年，加拿大甚至还未宣布建国。这片大陆广袤的土地对白人探险者来说几乎一无所知。主导这次探险的托马斯•杰斐逊（Thomas Jefferson）甚至认为他们可能会遇见猛犸象。印第安人已经在西北地区生活了数十个世纪，但他们没有书面语言，早前来到这里的欧洲人也没有交给他们关于地震的记录。新来的人仅凭表面的样子决定来如何使用土地。就表面价值而言，这里算是相当富饶：广袤、廉价、气温宜人、高产，无论从哪个方面看，都挑不出毛病。</span><br>
<span>近一个半世纪的时光流逝而过，没有人留意到长久以来宁静安详的美国西北部有任何躁动的迹象。要再过50年后，科学家才逐渐解读出这里的地震历史。地理学——就像很多地理学家会告诉你的那样，绝不是什么富有魅力的学科，研究隐没于地下的尘土之中，而靓丽的荣光属于人类及宇宙——从遗传学，到神经系统科学，到物理学。但或早或晚，每个学科都有它的奠基之日。而对发现卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带来说，就是我们这个时代最伟大的地理发现。</span><br>
<span>最早的线索来自地理学。世界上最严重的地震几乎都发生在环太平洋火山带（Ring of Fire）。这条火山带活动频繁，地质极不稳定，从新西兰往上经过印度尼西亚和日本，穿过海洋抵达阿拉斯加，再向下延伸至美国西部海岸及智利。日本，2011年，9.0级地震；印度尼西亚，2004年，9.1级地震；阿拉斯加，1964年，9.2级地震；智利1960年，9.5级地震——就算还不及1960年代提出板块运动学说，地理学家就注意到了其中的规律。最终，环太平洋火山带被证实就是由俯冲带形成的环状区域。几乎这个地区所有地震的成因都是大陆板块在运动中受到了海洋板块的阻挡——就像北美板块受到来自胡安德富卡的阻挡——在瞬间释放出能量；几乎所有火山爆发的成因都是海洋板块滑入大陆板块之下，积聚到一定温度后，压力达到极致，熔化了上方的岩石。</span><br>
<span>美国西北部正好位于环太平洋火山带。它的海岸处，海洋板块正滑入大陆板块下方。在内陆，卡斯卡迪火山山脉下方，胡安德富卡板块的温度正不断上升，熔化了它上方的一切。换一种说法就是，卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带正如戈尔德芬格指出的那样：“完美印证了所有地质结构运动上的假设”。然而，没有任何历史记录下这里曾爆发过大地震——或者说，曾发生过地震。相反，其他俯冲带不时就爆发大地震，小地震更是不胜枚举: 5.0级地震，4.0级地震，震感就如同困扰为什么邻居要在半夜挪沙发。在日本待上一周，你就会对此习以为常。而你可能在美国西北地区的好几个城市生活了一辈子——有过几次，事实上如果你足够“幸运”的话——都没感受到过大地的震动。1970年代，地理学家面临的问题是，究竟卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带是否打破过它那吊诡的沉默？</span><br>
<span>1980年代晚期，美国地质调查局的布莱恩•艾特沃特（Brian Atwater）和一位名叫戴维•亚玛古奇（David Yamaguchi）的研究生找到了上述问题的答案，以及卡斯卡迪拼图的另一主要线索。他们的发现主要在一个被称为幽灵森林的地方。华盛顿州海岸一线，科波利斯河（Copalis River）两岸生长的一片美西红侧柏（western red cedars）。2014年夏天，当我与艾特沃特和亚玛古奇一道漫步其中，很快就明白了它得名的原因。整片红侧柏分布在河流北部宽广的一片低矮的沼泽地里。树木早已死去，但枝干依旧摧枯拉朽地立在那里。树叶早就落光，枝丫折断，树皮也不见踪迹，只剩下光秃秃的树干隐没在一片银灰之中，就好像它们在身体里给自己盖下了坟墓。</span><br>
<span>导致幽灵森林里红侧柏死亡的是海水浸泡。长久以来，人们都以为四周的海平面不断上升，淹没了它们的树根，于是在漫长的消耗中一棵一棵死去。然而1987年时，艾特沃特在土层中找到了地面突然沉降的证据，并且在华盛顿海岸一线都有相似发现，于是他怀疑，在过去时——由于地面突然下降，树木是在顷刻间死去的。为了得到证实，他找到了研究树木年轮的专家亚玛古奇。亚玛古奇提取了红侧柏的样本，得出了它们是同时死亡的结论：每一棵树的最后一道年轮都中止在1699年的夏天。由于树木不会在冬季生长，他与艾特沃特认为，在1699年8月至1700年5月间的某个时候，这里发生的地震使土地突然下沉，并最终导致了树木的死亡。这个时间假设把美国西北部的书面历史整整提早了一百年——公正说来，幽灵森林这种侦探故事可以就此打住了。</span><br>
<span>但事情并没有完。如果你从幽灵森林出发，正对南方行进5000英里(约8046千米)，将会抵达的是日本东北沿岸。2011年的地震清楚地证明了那里是海啸高危区。而日本自公元599年起就有对海啸的相关记录。在此后的1400年中，有一件古怪的事不时引起过关注。元禄时代（Genroku era）第12年的第12个月的第8天，长达600英里（约956千米）的海浪侵袭了海岸，夷平了房屋，漫过了护城河。日本人知道，海啸是由地震导致的，而在元禄时代，没有人感受到大地震动。海浪的来袭没有任何可察觉的迹象，当科学家开始研究此现象时，将它称作“孤立子体海啸事件”（orphan tsunami）</span><br>
<span>终于，在1996年的《自然》（Nature）杂志上，地震学家佐竹建治（Kenji Satake）和他的三位同事借鉴了艾特沃特和亚玛古奇的研究，为那个“孤立子体”找到了它的“母体”——也为卡斯卡迪亚的故事填补上了细节详实的空白。大约是1700年1月26日晚上9点时分，一场里氏9.0级地震袭击了美国西北部，导致了土地沉降，淹死了沿岸的森林，在大海中掀起了达整片大陆一半长度的巨型海浪；而另一半海浪用了10个小时才横渡过大洋，大约在1700年1月27日抵达日本：按照当地的历法，正是元禄时代第12年的第12个月的第8天。</span><br>
<span>当科学家们重建出1700年的那场地震，以前被忽视的一些记录突然成为了作证的线索。1964年，不列颠哥伦比亚Huu-ay-aht First Nation部落的首领路易斯•努克米斯（Louis Nookmis）讲过一个故事，一直流传了子孙七代。故事是关于生活在温哥华岛上帕赤纳湾（Pachena Bay）人们的集体死亡。“我想是因为那天晚上大地的剧烈震动，”努克米斯回忆。根据另外一个部落的历史，“他们突然沉到了海底，全都淹死了，没有人生还。”大约100年前，Makah部落的首领比利•鲍尔奇（Billy Balch）回忆了一个相似的故事。听说在他出生前，所有海水都从华盛顿州的尼亚湾（Neah Bay）退去，又突然倒灌回来，淹没了整个地区。幸存者发现独木舟挂到了树上。2005年的研究中，彼时华盛顿大学的地震学家露丝•鲁德温（Ruth Ludwin）和9位同事一起，收集和分析了印第安人的地震与海水泛滥记录。有些记录包含了足够的信息来估计地震发生的时间范围。大体上而言，这个时间的中间值域位于1701年。</span><br>
<span>对欧裔美国人来讲，这些故事并不能成为假设的充分证据，直到假设本身得到印证。然而对1700年卡斯卡迪亚地震的还原依旧是一片稀有的自然拼图，完美地勾勒了地壳移动说暂时无法解释的部分。这真是令人惊叹的科学；对科学来讲，这简直是令人惊叹的发现。然而对数百万生活在美国西北部的人们来说，这无疑是个噩耗，正如戈尔德芬格所说：“在80年代晚期和90年代早期，人们已经感觉到了沮丧。”</span><br>
<span>戈尔德芬格是在他位于俄勒冈州立大学的实验室里对我说这番话的。那是一栋低矮的组合式预制房，穿过英语文学系后，很容易误认为到了维修部门。实验室里有步入式冷冻柜。进入冷冻柜，从地面延伸至天花板的架子上摆满了贴有各种标签的试管，直径4英寸（约10厘米），长5英尺（约1.5米）。每支试管里都摆着一块海底的岩芯样本。每个样本都包含了过去1万年间铭刻在海底的历史。俯冲带地震爆发时，土壤如激流般从陆地的坡面一泻而下，在海底形成永久沉积物。通过考量每个样本的数量与体积，比较它们在卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带的连续分布，戈尔德芬格与他的同事一起测定了整块地区已经断裂的面积，发生的频率，以及激烈程度。</span><br>
<span>得益于那项工作，我们如今知道美国西北部在过去的1万年里经历了41次地震。如果你用1万除以41，会得出243，那就是卡斯卡迪亚爆发的重复周期：每次地震爆发间歇的平均时间又会不断削减。这样的时间跨度显现了它的危险性，即因为它爆发的周期很长——漫长到让我们疏忽地在最糟糕的断层线上建立起了整个文明——而同时它又不足够漫长——自1700年那次地震以来，我们如今正进入243年重复周期的第315年（注：报道发表于2015年）。</span><br>
<span>可说起来，如果要在这些数字里挑刺并非什么难事。重复周期取的是平均数，而平均数本身是很“狡猾”的：10是1和11的平均数，也是11和2的平均数。然而，这却不足以回避我们所面临问题的严峻性。2011年发生在日本的灾难亦是矛盾导致的结果：日本拥有最先进的地震科学预报，而预报基于的却是错误的当地可承受损害的预判。美国西北部也会面临相似的现实——不过蕴藏的矛盾更是千丝万缕。“就科学而言，这是很有意思的（研究），”戈尔德芬格说，“我很享受它。然而在我们所知与所应付诸行动之间的鸿沟却日益扩大。我已经在世界上地震预防最完备的国家经历了一次大地震，而如果那是在波特兰”——戈尔德芬格在讲完这句话前摇了摇头，“这么说吧，我还是不要在那里的好。”</span><br>
<span>叁</span><br>
<span>卡斯卡迪亚大地震爆发的第一个信号将会是出现压缩波，从断层带向外散发而出。压缩波是传播速度很快的高频波，犬类以及一些其他动物能够听到，但对人类而言只是一些微不足道的颤动。它们不会造成什么伤害，不过对预报来讲却十分有效。由于它们的传播速度快，地震传感器往往能够在早于其他地震波30至90秒之间探测到它。这些时间已经足够启动地震报警系统，比如日本全境目前都在使用这种方法。它会自动激活各种救生模式：中止铁路运行，关闭发电厂，启动电梯及消防闸门，通报医院停止手术，触发警报，而使公众能所有防备。美国西北部是没有地震报警系统的。当卡斯卡迪亚地震爆发时，将会传来一片刺耳的狗吠声，在表面波到达前，人们会发出不知所以然的“究竟是怎么回事”的疑惑。表面波的传播速度较慢，是低频波，会让整个地表上下或是左右翻转：直到这种晃动出现，才会引来人们的严阵以待。</span><br>
<span>震动发生不久，卡斯卡迪亚以西甚至更广大地区的电网就会中断。如果地震发生在夜晚，接下来的劫难都将在一片漆黑中一一降临。理论上地震时那些待在家里的人是最安全的；在私人住宅加装避震设施常常花不了多少钱，执行起来也最容易，但生活在美国西北部的人们常年被安逸的环境麻痹了风险意识，几乎对此漠不关心。然而这种冷漠很快就会被击破，以及房间里所有的玻璃制品。房间里的所有东西，只要不是固定住的，都会随地板倾斜，或是直接摔下：书架、台灯、电脑、餐具间里装着各种调料的瓶瓶罐罐。冰箱会跑出厨房，自动拔掉电源，整个翻转了身。电热水壶掉下了台子，压坏了室内输气管道。地基不稳的房子开始滑动——或者，它们会依照惯性原地不动，直到地基与下边的地面一道，朝西边震动。地面起伏不定，房屋即将崩塌。</span><br>
<span>整片地区的大型设施也不会幸免于难。直到1974年，俄勒冈州才有了第一部抗震指引；直到1994年，美国西北部的少数几个地方才制定了应对9.0级地震的规定。大量建筑都是在那之前修建的。俄勒冈州地矿局（DOGAMI）负责人伊恩•马丁（Ian Madin）估计，州内75%的设施无法应对卡斯卡迪亚大地震。FEMA的估算是，整个地区的100万栋建筑——其中超过3000栋是学校——将轰然崩塌或是在地震中毫无抵抗力。行将崩塌的还包括一半的公路桥梁；三分之二的铁路与机场；三分之一的消防局；一半的警察局，三分之二的医院，以及波特兰两条河流上17座桥梁中的15座，均无法幸存。</span><br>
<span>灾难往往发端于诸多细小的问题，从而导致致命的后果：因为少了一颗钉子，而输了一场战争；因为15个各自独立又不紧要的小错误，而使喷气式客机失事。俯冲带地震因循的却是相反的规律：一个巨大的问题引发出成千上万问题。卡斯卡迪亚地震会引起整个地区的土地滑坡——西雅图的应急管理办公室预计，本市受到影响的范围将达3万平方英里（约7万平方千米）。它还会导致液化（liquefaction）现象。看起来坚固的土地像是液体那样“流动”起来，摧毁上方的一切建造。西雅图有15%的面积是可液化土地，包括17座日托中心，以及34500人的房屋。俄勒冈的能源基础设施枢纽面临的是同样的困境。从波特兰方向延伸来的6英里长的管道中输送的是州内90%的液态能源，提供着从变电站到天然气终端的每日所需。于此同时，摇晃、滑坡，震动会接着触发火灾、洪水、管道故障、堤坝决口，以及有害物质泄漏。以上任何一种二次灾害都毫无疑问会造成损失、破坏与死伤。</span><br>
<span>犬吠过4至6分钟后，震动会慢慢平息。在接下来的几分钟，整个地区会继续自身崩坏到四分五裂。这时，海浪就赶到了。真正的破坏才要刚刚启幕。</span><br>
<span>在所有的自然灾害中，在海啸中生还的机率是最低的。唯一活命的方法是当海啸来临时，你不要出现在现场：避开海啸高危区，或者尽快跑去高处。对生活在卡斯卡迪亚洪灾区（inundation zone）的7万1千名居民而言，两次灾难发生之间逃生的窗口期十分短暂。直到知道地震来了，人们才会明白发生了什么——“震动-预警系统”，俄勒冈西塞德（Seaside）的城市规划师凯文•库普勒斯（Kevin Cupples）开玩笑说——雪上加霜的是，由于地震破坏了道路，人们只能依靠自己的双腿逃生。取决于所处地点的不同，你所拥有的时间在10分钟到30分钟之间不等。这意味着你没有时间找手电筒，没有时间在毁于一旦的屋子里茫然犹豫，不能寻找家人，或者是当个“好人”。“海啸来时，你所能做的只有拔腿就跑，”俄勒冈地震安全政策顾问委员会（OSSPAC）主席杰•威尔森（Jay Wilson）说，“你只能保护自己，不要回头，不要回去救任何人。你拔腿就跑，为了保住自己的性命。”</span><br>
<span>在海啸中救人的最好时机是在它发生之前，但西北海岸的人们尚未严肃对待这件事。没有人要求旅店和公司公布逃生路线，或者为雇员提供逃生训练。在俄勒冈，自1995年起不再允许在洪灾区修建医院、学校、消防局和警察局，但已经建好的设施不会受到影响，开发商想要修建旅店、能源设施、养老院也不是没有可能，他们只需要与DOGAMI商议逃生计划即可。“你来到办公室，坐下，”伊恩•马丁说道：“我说，‘那简直蠢透了’，但你说，‘好吧，看来我们已经讨论完了。’”</span><br>
<span>过分宽松的安全政策使洪灾区内的人们无法幸免灾害。俄勒冈海岸22%的人口是65岁以上的老人，州内29%的人口是残疾人，这些数字在其他有些海边城市只会更为可观。“我们没法救他们，”凯文•库普勒斯说，“我不会讲些什么糖衣炮弹的话，比如‘啊，好吧，我们会照看老人的。’不，我们不会。”同样，也不会有人想着要救游客。在洪灾区内的华盛顿国家公园每天接待的游客平均数是1万7千人。马丁预计，夏日周末，5万至10万人会来到俄勒冈的海滩度假。“他们中的大多数人根本不知道要如何逃生，”他说，“而海滩恰恰是最难逃生的地点。”</span><br>
<span>那些没能靠自身逃出洪灾区的人，很快会迎来更大的威胁。一个成年人会被时速6.7英里（约10公里），深至脚踝的海浪击倒。当海浪逼近时，速度会达到原来的两倍，高度会随海岸线的轮廓改变，由20英尺至超过100英尺不等（约6米到30米）。这根本不是日本艺术家葛饰北斋（Katsushika Hokusai）的浮世绘，海浪从海平面跃起，从高处回落。现实是，会像整个大洋被高高抬起，瞬间淹没陆地。迎面击来的也绝不只有海水——在美国西北部的沿海城镇，那将会是5层楼高的巨浪，席卷着卡车、门框、捕鱼船，电线杆，以及目力所及一切。</span><br>
<span>当海啸退去，查看受灾状况时，你需要的是国际空间站的协助。灾害将从加利福尼亚蔓延至加拿大。地震对卡斯卡迪亚西部造成的浩劫，可波及加利福尼亚的萨克拉门托和印第安纳州东北部的韦恩堡（Fort Wayne）这样的重灾区，亦可及至纽约。FEMA预计，搜救将在10万平方英里（约26万平方千米）的范围内进行，受灾海岸线将长达453英里（约729千米）。就伤亡人数而言：正如我之前引述的数据——2万7千人受伤，近1万3千人死亡——基于的是官方预设的一种状况：假使地震发生在2月6日的上午9点41分。而如果地震爆发在夏季，海滩上挤满了度假的人，以上遇难人数可能只是实际的一个小数点。</span><br>
<span>玻璃酒杯、古董花瓶、髋关节骨头、心脏：会在瞬间破碎的，修复却往往缓慢，如果还可以被修复的话。OSSPAC预计，5号洲际公路通道上，由地震造成的电力中断需要1个月至3个月才能恢复；需要1个月至1年才能恢复供应饮用水和启动下水道；需要6个月至1年开通高速公路；需要18个月来重建医院。在沿海地区，需要的时间更加漫长。任何选择或者别无选择滞留灾区的人们，要在没有电的情况下生活3至6个月；在没有饮用水和下水道的情况下生活1至3年；在没有医院的情况下生活3年甚至更久。而且这些预计数据不适用于洪灾区，之后的数年那里都不再适合人类居住。</span><br>
<span>所有这些，究竟会造成多少损失？FEMA的救灾与重建计划中纳入了各项数字，唯独不包括损失金额。但无论最终的数字是多少——就像之前的其他灾难一样，美国的纳税人会负担起其中75%的份额——美国西北部的经济都会全面崩溃。由于基础设施受到重创，公司要么倒闭要么就不得不搬迁。当地居民也会逃也般的搬走。OSSPAC预计会有大规模人口迁移以及长期的人口下滑。地震发生时，克里斯•戈尔德芬格本人可不想在那里。但无论出于何种考量，灾害过后前往那里或者留下的想法都实在糟糕透了。</span><br>
<span>肆</span><br>
<span>表面看来，地震展现在我们面前的似乎是空间问题：我们生活在断层线上，住在砖块盖起的大楼里，中意靠近海边的度假屋，而实则隐患重重。但问题的另一面是，它也在我们面前抛出了时间问题。地球已经有45亿年历史，但我们却是年轻的物种，相较而言，每个人不过就是这么一辈子，人类生命之短暂，造成了一种时空感上的狭隘——相比自身而言，我们对缓慢的行星运转是如此无知，或者说，无知无觉。</span><br>
<span>这个问题是双向的。我们长久以来都对卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带一无所知，是因为我们无法窥见久远的过去。而如今它对我们所造成的威胁，是因为我们无法预见长远的将来。这不是资讯匮乏的问题。如今我们已经心知肚明在卡斯卡迪亚断层线上，在某一天会发生什么。这也不是想象力匮乏的问题；如果你觉得问题出在这，可以看看今年（注：2015年）夏天上映的由布拉德•佩顿（Brad Peyton）主演的《末日崩塌》（San Andreas）——地震是如何摧毁几乎整个西海岸的。不仅如此，整个世界都笼罩在各种末日阴影之中：病毒、机器人、资源短缺、僵尸、外星人、瘟疫。电影画面证实了我们其实长于编写未来的脚本，包括写书悲剧。然而世界末日的景象透露的不过是一种逃生主义，而非道德唤醒。我们从未想过要实际做些什么——而对严峻将来的预见理应要让我们设法阻止它的出现。</span><br>
<span>诚然，问题不单局限于地震。卡斯卡迪亚面临的状况——似乎触手可及的灾难，也是对这个世代生态报复的寓言。它所揭示的问题，正是我们当下所要正视的。一个社会应当如何应对毁灭性灾难即将到来的危机，尽管它迫在眉睫，却具体时限不明？而当其建立的全部文明与设施在自然灾害面前将不堪一击，它又应当如何纠正自身的所作所为？</span><br>
<span>在美国西北部，我见的最后一个人是西塞德的学校负责人道格•多尔蒂（Doug Dougherty）。西塞德的大部分学校都在海啸洪灾区。多尔蒂负责的4间学校——学生总人数达1600名，只有一间是相对安全的，其他几间都建在海平面以上5至15英尺（约1.5米到4.5米）的位置。一旦发生海啸，他们将会被没入45英尺（约13.7米）深的海底。</span><br>
<span>多尔蒂在2009年时告诉我，他发现在洪灾区以外有一些正在出售的土地，打算要盖从幼儿园到12年级的校园。4年后，为了支付1亿2千800万美元账单，该地区发行了债券。多尔蒂试图向俄勒冈州的国会代表寻求帮助却一无所获。俄勒冈州在抗震升级上花费不菲，但各种措施均不适用于洪灾区内的建筑。目前，多尔蒂能做的就是让他的学生了解逃生路线。</span><br>
<span>然而，这并非对所有学生都有用。在吉尔哈特（Gearhart）社区的一间小学，学生将逃无可逃。“他们不可能从那间学校逃走，”多尔蒂说，“他们无处可去。”学校的一边是大海，另一边是宽阔的沼泽地。海啸来时，吉尔哈特唯一可去的地方是学校后面的小山坡。山顶高出海平面45英尺——低于整体断裂时的海浪高度。目前，通往山坡的路上有标识写道：“临时海啸集合地点”。我向多尔蒂问起州内的长远计划。“没有长远计划。”他说。</span><br>
<span>多尔蒂的办公室位于洪灾区的深处，距离海滩有数个街区远。每一天，在他看不见的地方，海浪卷起，消散，化作泡沫，冲上海滩。80英里（约128千米）外，大海1万英尺（3048米）深处，地质时钟的指针缓慢但一刻不停地滑动。而地震学家都举起了他们的手表，在地质时间赶上人类的时间之前，他们还剩多少时间，他们还有什么可做。</span><br>
</p><p><b>风景很好: </b><br>
<span>圣安德烈亚斯让我想起了GTA</span><br>
</p><p><b>自業自得: </b><br>
<span>“10是1和11的平均数，也是11和2的平均数。”老外真的是数学不好</span><br>
</p><p><b>両儀織: </b><br>
<span>自業自得 发表于 2019-7-6 14:26</span><br>
<span>“10是1和11的平均数，也是11和2的平均数。”老外真的是数学不好</span><br>
<span>这是搜狐翻译时候誊抄的错误，原文是Recurrence intervals are averages, and averages are tricky: ten is the average of nine and eleven, but also of eighteen and two. </span><br>
<span>另外文中还有个翻译问题是david yamaguchi名字，明显yamaguchi是日姓山口，译者直接音译虽然不是不可以，但一般还是用汉字比较好。</span><br>
</p><p><b>80天拯救沃夫朗: </b><br>
<span>本以为是讲今天的地震，结果往下一看：今年（2016年）</span><br>
</p><p><b>両儀織: </b><br>
<span>附英文原文，有兴趣的可以看一下，文笔流畅优雅，纽约客的文章只要不是涉及白左意识形态的，文字功底上还是没得说。</span><br>
<span>The Really Big One</span><br>
<span>An earthquake will destroy a sizable portion of the coastal Northwest. The question is when.</span><br>
<span>By Kathryn SchulzJuly 13, 2015</span><br>
<span>When the 2011 earthquake and tsunami struck Tohoku, Japan, Chris Goldfinger was two hundred miles away, in the city of Kashiwa, at an international meeting on seismology. As the shaking started, everyone in the room began to laugh. Earthquakes are common in Japan—that one was the third of the week—and the participants were, after all, at a seismology conference. Then everyone in the room checked the time.</span><br>
<span>Seismologists know that how long an earthquake lasts is a decent proxy for its magnitude. The 1989 earthquake in Loma Prieta, California, which killed sixty-three people and caused six billion dollars’ worth of damage, lasted about fifteen seconds and had a magnitude of 6.9. A thirty-second earthquake generally has a magnitude in the mid-sevens. A minute-long quake is in the high sevens, a two-minute quake has entered the eights, and a three-minute quake is in the high eights. By four minutes, an earthquake has hit magnitude 9.0.</span><br>
<span>When Goldfinger looked at his watch, it was quarter to three. The conference was wrapping up for the day. He was thinking about sushi. The speaker at the lectern was wondering if he should carry on with his talk. The earthquake was not particularly strong. Then it ticked past the sixty-second mark, making it longer than the others that week. The shaking intensified. The seats in the conference room were small plastic desks with wheels. Goldfinger, who is tall and solidly built, thought, No way am I crouching under one of those for cover. At a minute and a half, everyone in the room got up and went outside.</span><br>
<span>It was March. There was a chill in the air, and snow flurries, but no snow on the ground. Nor, from the feel of it, was there ground on the ground. The earth snapped and popped and rippled. It was, Goldfinger thought, like driving through rocky terrain in a vehicle with no shocks, if both the vehicle and the terrain were also on a raft in high seas. The quake passed the two-minute mark. The trees, still hung with the previous autumn’s dead leaves, were making a strange rattling sound. The flagpole atop the building he and his colleagues had just vacated was whipping through an arc of forty degrees. The building itself was base-isolated, a seismic-safety technology in which the body of a structure rests on movable bearings rather than directly on its foundation. Goldfinger lurched over to take a look. The base was lurching, too, back and forth a foot at a time, digging a trench in the yard. He thought better of it, and lurched away. His watch swept past the three-minute mark and kept going.</span><br>
<span>Oh, shit, Goldfinger thought, although not in dread, at first: in amazement. For decades, seismologists had believed that Japan could not experience an earthquake stronger than magnitude 8.4. In 2005, however, at a conference in Hokudan, a Japanese geologist named Yasutaka Ikeda had argued that the nation should expect a magnitude 9.0 in the near future—with catastrophic consequences, because Japan’s famous earthquake-and-tsunami preparedness, including the height of its sea walls, was based on incorrect science. The presentation was met with polite applause and thereafter largely ignored. Now, Goldfinger realized as the shaking hit the four-minute mark, the planet was proving the Japanese Cassandra right.</span><br>
<span>For a moment, that was pretty cool: a real-time revolution in earthquake science. Almost immediately, though, it became extremely uncool, because Goldfinger and every other seismologist standing outside in Kashiwa knew what was coming. One of them pulled out a cell phone and started streaming videos from the Japanese broadcasting station NHK, shot by helicopters that had flown out to sea soon after the shaking started. Thirty minutes after Goldfinger first stepped outside, he watched the tsunami roll in, in real time, on a two-inch screen.</span><br>
<span>In the end, the magnitude-9.0 Tohoku earthquake and subsequent tsunami killed more than eighteen thousand people, devastated northeast Japan, triggered the meltdown at the Fukushima power plant, and cost an estimated two hundred and twenty billion dollars. The shaking earlier in the week turned out to be the foreshocks of the largest earthquake in the nation’s recorded history. But for Chris Goldfinger, a paleoseismologist at Oregon State University and one of the world’s leading experts on a little-known fault line, the main quake was itself a kind of foreshock: a preview of another earthquake still to come.</span><br>
<span>Most people in the United States know just one fault line by name: the San Andreas, which runs nearly the length of California and is perpetually rumored to be on the verge of unleashing “the big one.” That rumor is misleading, no matter what the San Andreas ever does. Every fault line has an upper limit to its potency, determined by its length and width, and by how far it can slip. For the San Andreas, one of the most extensively studied and best understood fault lines in the world, that upper limit is roughly an 8.2—a powerful earthquake, but, because the Richter scale is logarithmic, only six per cent as strong as the 2011 event in Japan.</span><br>
<span>Just north of the San Andreas, however, lies another fault line. Known as the Cascadia subduction zone, it runs for seven hundred miles off the coast of the Pacific Northwest, beginning near Cape Mendocino, California, continuing along Oregon and Washington, and terminating around Vancouver Island, Canada. The “Cascadia” part of its name comes from the Cascade Range, a chain of volcanic mountains that follow the same course a hundred or so miles inland. The “subduction zone” part refers to a region of the planet where one tectonic plate is sliding underneath (subducting) another. Tectonic plates are those slabs of mantle and crust that, in their epochs-long drift, rearrange the earth’s continents and oceans. Most of the time, their movement is slow, harmless, and all but undetectable. Occasionally, at the borders where they meet, it is not.</span><br>
<span>Take your hands and hold them palms down, middle fingertips touching. Your right hand represents the North American tectonic plate, which bears on its back, among other things, our entire continent, from One World Trade Center to the Space Needle, in Seattle. Your left hand represents an oceanic plate called Juan de Fuca, ninety thousand square miles in size. The place where they meet is the Cascadia subduction zone. Now slide your left hand under your right one. That is what the Juan de Fuca plate is doing: slipping steadily beneath North America. When you try it, your right hand will slide up your left arm, as if you were pushing up your sleeve. That is what North America is not doing. It is stuck, wedged tight against the surface of the other plate.</span><br>
<span>Without moving your hands, curl your right knuckles up, so that they point toward the ceiling. Under pressure from Juan de Fuca, the stuck edge of North America is bulging upward and compressing eastward, at the rate of, respectively, three to four millimetres and thirty to forty millimetres a year. It can do so for quite some time, because, as continent stuff goes, it is young, made of rock that is still relatively elastic. (Rocks, like us, get stiffer as they age.) But it cannot do so indefinitely. There is a backstop—the craton, that ancient unbudgeable mass at the center of the continent—and, sooner or later, North America will rebound like a spring. If, on that occasion, only the southern part of the Cascadia subduction zone gives way—your first two fingers, say—the magnitude of the resulting quake will be somewhere between 8.0 and 8.6. That’s the big one. If the entire zone gives way at once, an event that seismologists call a full-margin rupture, the magnitude will be somewhere between 8.7 and 9.2. That’s the very big one.</span><br>
<span>Flick your right fingers outward, forcefully, so that your hand flattens back down again. When the next very big earthquake hits, the northwest edge of the continent, from California to Canada and the continental shelf to the Cascades, will drop by as much as six feet and rebound thirty to a hundred feet to the west—losing, within minutes, all the elevation and compression it has gained over centuries. Some of that shift will take place beneath the ocean, displacing a colossal quantity of seawater. (Watch what your fingertips do when you flatten your hand.) The water will surge upward into a huge hill, then promptly collapse. One side will rush west, toward Japan. The other side will rush east, in a seven-hundred-mile liquid wall that will reach the Northwest coast, on average, fifteen minutes after the earthquake begins. By the time the shaking has ceased and the tsunami has receded, the region will be unrecognizable. Kenneth Murphy, who directs fema’s Region X, the division responsible for Oregon, Washington, Idaho, and Alaska, says, “Our operating assumption is that everything west of Interstate 5 will be toast.”</span><br>
<span>In the Pacific Northwest, the area of impact will cover* some hundred and forty thousand square miles, including Seattle, Tacoma, Portland, Eugene, Salem (the capital city of Oregon), Olympia (the capital of Washington), and some seven million people. When the next full-margin rupture happens, that region will suffer the worst natural disaster in the history of North America. Roughly three thousand people died in San Francisco’s 1906 earthquake. Almost two thousand died in Hurricane Katrina. Almost three hundred died in Hurricane Sandy. fema projects that nearly thirteen thousand people will die in the Cascadia earthquake and tsunami. Another twenty-seven thousand will be injured, and the agency expects that it will need to provide shelter for a million displaced people, and food and water for another two and a half million. “This is one time that I’m hoping all the science is wrong, and it won’t happen for another thousand years,” Murphy says.</span><br>
<span>In fact, the science is robust, and one of the chief scientists behind it is Chris Goldfinger. Thanks to work done by him and his colleagues, we now know that the odds of the big Cascadia earthquake happening in the next fifty years are roughly one in three. The odds of the very big one are roughly one in ten. Even those numbers do not fully reflect the danger—or, more to the point, how unprepared the Pacific Northwest is to face it. The truly worrisome figures in this story are these: Thirty years ago, no one knew that the Cascadia subduction zone had ever produced a major earthquake. Forty-five years ago, no one even knew it existed.</span><br>
<span>In May of 1804, Meriwether Lewis and William Clark, together with their Corps of Discovery, set off from St. Louis on America’s first official cross-country expedition. Eighteen months later, they reached the Pacific Ocean and made camp near the present-day town of Astoria, Oregon. The United States was, at the time, twenty-nine years old. Canada was not yet a country. The continent’s far expanses were so unknown to its white explorers that Thomas Jefferson, who commissioned the journey, thought that the men would come across woolly mammoths. Native Americans had lived in the Northwest for millennia, but they had no written language, and the many things to which the arriving Europeans subjected them did not include seismological inquiries. The newcomers took the land they encountered at face value, and at face value it was a find: vast, cheap, temperate, fertile, and, to all appearances, remarkably benign.</span><br>
<span>A century and a half elapsed before anyone had any inkling that the Pacific Northwest was not a quiet place but a place in a long period of quiet. It took another fifty years to uncover and interpret the region’s seismic history. Geology, as even geologists will tell you, is not normally the sexiest of disciplines; it hunkers down with earthly stuff while the glory accrues to the human and the cosmic—to genetics, neuroscience, physics. But, sooner or later, every field has its field day, and the discovery of the Cascadia subduction zone stands as one of the greatest scientific detective stories of our time.</span><br>
<span>The first clue came from geography. Almost all of the world’s most powerful earthquakes occur in the Ring of Fire, the volcanically and seismically volatile swath of the Pacific that runs from New Zealand up through Indonesia and Japan, across the ocean to Alaska, and down the west coast of the Americas to Chile. Japan, 2011, magnitude 9.0; Indonesia, 2004, magnitude 9.1; Alaska, 1964, magnitude 9.2; Chile, 1960, magnitude 9.5—not until the late nineteen-sixties, with the rise of the theory of plate tectonics, could geologists explain this pattern. The Ring of Fire, it turns out, is really a ring of subduction zones. Nearly all the earthquakes in the region are caused by continental plates getting stuck on oceanic plates—as North America is stuck on Juan de Fuca—and then getting abruptly unstuck. And nearly all the volcanoes are caused by the oceanic plates sliding deep beneath the continental ones, eventually reaching temperatures and pressures so extreme that they melt the rock above them.</span><br>
<span>The Pacific Northwest sits squarely within the Ring of Fire. Off its coast, an oceanic plate is slipping beneath a continental one. Inland, the Cascade volcanoes mark the line where, far below, the Juan de Fuca plate is heating up and melting everything above it. In other words, the Cascadia subduction zone has, as Goldfinger put it, “all the right anatomical parts.” Yet not once in recorded history has it caused a major earthquake—or, for that matter, any quake to speak of. By contrast, other subduction zones produce major earthquakes occasionally and minor ones all the time: magnitude 5.0, magnitude 4.0, magnitude why are the neighbors moving their sofa at midnight. You can scarcely spend a week in Japan without feeling this sort of earthquake. You can spend a lifetime in many parts of the Northwest—several, in fact, if you had them to spend—and not feel so much as a quiver. The question facing geologists in the nineteen-seventies was whether the Cascadia subduction zone had ever broken its eerie silence.</span><br>
<span>In the late nineteen-eighties, Brian Atwater, a geologist with the United States Geological Survey, and a graduate student named David Yamaguchi found the answer, and another major clue in the Cascadia puzzle. Their discovery is best illustrated in a place called the ghost forest, a grove of western red cedars on the banks of the Copalis River, near the Washington coast. When I paddled out to it last summer, with Atwater and Yamaguchi, it was easy to see how it got its name. The cedars are spread out across a low salt marsh on a wide northern bend in the river, long dead but still standing. Leafless, branchless, barkless, they are reduced to their trunks and worn to a smooth silver-gray, as if they had always carried their own tombstones inside them.</span><br>
<span>What killed the trees in the ghost forest was saltwater. It had long been assumed that they died slowly, as the sea level around them gradually rose and submerged their roots. But, by 1987, Atwater, who had found in soil layers evidence of sudden land subsidence along the Washington coast, suspected that that was backward—that the trees had died quickly when the ground beneath them plummeted. To find out, he teamed up with Yamaguchi, a specialist in dendrochronology, the study of growth-ring patterns in trees. Yamaguchi took samples of the cedars and found that they had died simultaneously: in tree after tree, the final rings dated to the summer of 1699. Since trees do not grow in the winter, he and Atwater concluded that sometime between August of 1699 and May of 1700 an earthquake had caused the land to drop and killed the cedars. That time frame predated by more than a hundred years the written history of the Pacific Northwest—and so, by rights, the detective story should have ended there.</span><br>
<span>But it did not. If you travel five thousand miles due west from the ghost forest, you reach the northeast coast of Japan. As the events of 2011 made clear, that coast is vulnerable to tsunamis, and the Japanese have kept track of them since at least 599 A.D. In that fourteen-hundred-year history, one incident has long stood out for its strangeness. On the eighth day of the twelfth month of the twelfth year of the Genroku era, a six-hundred-mile-long wave struck the coast, levelling homes, breaching a castle moat, and causing an accident at sea. The Japanese understood that tsunamis were the result of earthquakes, yet no one felt the ground shake before the Genroku event. The wave had no discernible origin. When scientists began studying it, they called it an orphan tsunami.</span><br>
<span>Finally, in a 1996 article in Nature, a seismologist named Kenji Satake and three colleagues, drawing on the work of Atwater and Yamaguchi, matched that orphan to its parent—and thereby filled in the blanks in the Cascadia story with uncanny specificity. At approximately nine o’ clock at night on January 26, 1700, a magnitude-9.0 earthquake struck the Pacific Northwest, causing sudden land subsidence, drowning coastal forests, and, out in the ocean, lifting up a wave half the length of a continent. It took roughly fifteen minutes for the Eastern half of that wave to strike the Northwest coast. It took ten hours for the other half to cross the ocean. It reached Japan on January 27, 1700: by the local calendar, the eighth day of the twelfth month of the twelfth year of Genroku.</span><br>
<span>Once scientists had reconstructed the 1700 earthquake, certain previously overlooked accounts also came to seem like clues. In 1964, Chief Louis Nookmis, of the Huu-ay-aht First Nation, in British Columbia, told a story, passed down through seven generations, about the eradication of Vancouver Island’s Pachena Bay people. “I think it was at nighttime that the land shook,” Nookmis recalled. According to another tribal history, “They sank at once, were all drowned; not one survived.” A hundred years earlier, Billy Balch, a leader of the Makah tribe, recounted a similar story. Before his own time, he said, all the water had receded from Washington State’s Neah Bay, then suddenly poured back in, inundating the entire region. Those who survived later found canoes hanging from the trees. In a 2005 study, Ruth Ludwin, then a seismologist at the University of Washington, together with nine colleagues, collected and analyzed Native American reports of earthquakes and saltwater floods. Some of those reports contained enough information to estimate a date range for the events they described. On average, the midpoint of that range was 1701.</span><br>
<span>It does not speak well of European-Americans that such stories counted as evidence for a proposition only after that proposition had been proved. Still, the reconstruction of the Cascadia earthquake of 1700 is one of those rare natural puzzles whose pieces fit together as tectonic plates do not: perfectly. It is wonderful science. It was wonderful for science. And it was terrible news for the millions of inhabitants of the Pacific Northwest. As Goldfinger put it, “In the late eighties and early nineties, the paradigm shifted to ‘uh-oh.’ ”</span><br>
<span>Goldfinger told me this in his lab at Oregon State, a low prefab building that a passing English major might reasonably mistake for the maintenance department. Inside the lab is a walk-in freezer. Inside the freezer are floor-to-ceiling racks filled with cryptically labelled tubes, four inches in diameter and five feet long. Each tube contains a core sample of the seafloor. Each sample contains the history, written in seafloorese, of the past ten thousand years. During subduction-zone earthquakes, torrents of land rush off the continental slope, leaving a permanent deposit on the bottom of the ocean. By counting the number and the size of deposits in each sample, then comparing their extent and consistency along the length of the Cascadia subduction zone, Goldfinger and his colleagues were able to determine how much of the zone has ruptured, how often, and how drastically.</span><br>
<span>Thanks to that work, we now know that the Pacific Northwest has experienced forty-one subduction-zone earthquakes in the past ten thousand years. If you divide ten thousand by forty-one, you get two hundred and forty-three, which is Cascadia’s recurrence interval: the average amount of time that elapses between earthquakes. That timespan is dangerous both because it is too long—long enough for us to unwittingly build an entire civilization on top of our continent’s worst fault line—and because it is not long enough. Counting from the earthquake of 1700, we are now three hundred and fifteen years into a two-hundred-and-forty-three-year cycle.</span><br>
<span>It is possible to quibble with that number. Recurrence intervals are averages, and averages are tricky: ten is the average of nine and eleven, but also of eighteen and two. It is not possible, however, to dispute the scale of the problem. The devastation in Japan in 2011 was the result of a discrepancy between what the best science predicted and what the region was prepared to withstand. The same will hold true in the Pacific Northwest—but here the discrepancy is enormous. “The science part is fun,” Goldfinger says. “And I love doing it. But the gap between what we know and what we should do about it is getting bigger and bigger, and the action really needs to turn to responding. Otherwise, we’re going to be hammered. I’ve been through one of these massive earthquakes in the most seismically prepared nation on earth. If that was Portland”—Goldfinger finished the sentence with a shake of his head before he finished it with words. “Let’s just say I would rather not be here.”</span><br>
<span>The first sign that the Cascadia earthquake has begun will be a compressional wave, radiating outward from the fault line. Compressional waves are fast-moving, high-frequency waves, audible to dogs and certain other animals but experienced by humans only as a sudden jolt. They are not very harmful, but they are potentially very useful, since they travel fast enough to be detected by sensors thirty to ninety seconds ahead of other seismic waves. That is enough time for earthquake early-warning systems, such as those in use throughout Japan, to automatically perform a variety of lifesaving functions: shutting down railways and power plants, opening elevators and firehouse doors, alerting hospitals to halt surgeries, and triggering alarms so that the general public can take cover. The Pacific Northwest has no early-warning system. When the Cascadia earthquake begins, there will be, instead, a cacophony of barking dogs and a long, suspended, what-was-that moment before the surface waves arrive. Surface waves are slower, lower-frequency waves that move the ground both up and down and side to side: the shaking, starting in earnest.</span><br>
<span>Soon after that shaking begins, the electrical grid will fail, likely everywhere west of the Cascades and possibly well beyond. If it happens at night, the ensuing catastrophe will unfold in darkness. In theory, those who are at home when it hits should be safest; it is easy and relatively inexpensive to seismically safeguard a private dwelling. But, lulled into nonchalance by their seemingly benign environment, most people in the Pacific Northwest have not done so. That nonchalance will shatter instantly. So will everything made of glass. Anything indoors and unsecured will lurch across the floor or come crashing down: bookshelves, lamps, computers, cannisters of flour in the pantry. Refrigerators will walk out of kitchens, unplugging themselves and toppling over. Water heaters will fall and smash interior gas lines. Houses that are not bolted to their foundations will slide off—or, rather, they will stay put, obeying inertia, while the foundations, together with the rest of the Northwest, jolt westward. Unmoored on the undulating ground, the homes will begin to collapse.</span><br>
<span>Across the region, other, larger structures will also start to fail. Until 1974, the state of Oregon had no seismic code, and few places in the Pacific Northwest had one appropriate to a magnitude-9.0 earthquake until 1994. The vast majority of buildings in the region were constructed before then. Ian Madin, who directs the Oregon Department of Geology and Mineral Industries (dogami), estimates that seventy-five per cent of all structures in the state are not designed to withstand a major Cascadia quake. fema calculates that, across the region, something on the order of a million buildings—more than three thousand of them schools—will collapse or be compromised in the earthquake. So will half of all highway bridges, fifteen of the seventeen bridges spanning Portland’s two rivers, and two-thirds of railways and airports; also, one-third of all fire stations, half of all police stations, and two-thirds of all hospitals.</span><br>
<span>Certain disasters stem from many small problems conspiring to cause one very large problem. For want of a nail, the war was lost; for fifteen independently insignificant errors, the jetliner was lost. Subduction-zone earthquakes operate on the opposite principle: one enormous problem causes many other enormous problems. The shaking from the Cascadia quake will set off landslides throughout the region—up to thirty thousand of them in Seattle alone, the city’s emergency-management office estimates. It will also induce a process called liquefaction, whereby seemingly solid ground starts behaving like a liquid, to the detriment of anything on top of it. Fifteen per cent of Seattle is built on liquefiable land, including seventeen day-care centers and the homes of some thirty-four thousand five hundred people. So is Oregon’s critical energy-infrastructure hub, a six-mile stretch of Portland through which flows ninety per cent of the state’s liquid fuel and which houses everything from electrical substations to natural-gas terminals. Together, the sloshing, sliding, and shaking will trigger fires, flooding, pipe failures, dam breaches, and hazardous-material spills. Any one of these second-order disasters could swamp the original earthquake in terms of cost, damage, or casualties—and one of them definitely will. Four to six minutes after the dogs start barking, the shaking will subside. For another few minutes, the region, upended, will continue to fall apart on its own. Then the wave will arrive, and the real destruction will begin.</span><br>
<span>Among natural disasters, tsunamis may be the closest to being completely unsurvivable. The only likely way to outlive one is not to be there when it happens: to steer clear of the vulnerable area in the first place, or get yourself to high ground as fast as possible. For the seventy-one thousand people who live in Cascadia’s inundation zone, that will mean evacuating in the narrow window after one disaster ends and before another begins. They will be notified to do so only by the earthquake itself—“a vibrate-alert system,” Kevin Cupples, the city planner for the town of Seaside, Oregon, jokes—and they are urged to leave on foot, since the earthquake will render roads impassable. Depending on location, they will have between ten and thirty minutes to get out. That time line does not allow for finding a flashlight, tending to an earthquake injury, hesitating amid the ruins of a home, searching for loved ones, or being a Good Samaritan. “When that tsunami is coming, you run,” Jay Wilson, the chair of the Oregon Seismic Safety Policy Advisory Commission (osspac), says. “You protect yourself, you don’t turn around, you don’t go back to save anybody. You run for your life.”</span><br>
<span>The time to save people from a tsunami is before it happens, but the region has not yet taken serious steps toward doing so. Hotels and businesses are not required to post evacuation routes or to provide employees with evacuation training. In Oregon, it has been illegal since 1995 to build hospitals, schools, firehouses, and police stations in the inundation zone, but those which are already in it can stay, and any other new construction is permissible: energy facilities, hotels, retirement homes. In those cases, builders are required only to consult with dogami about evacuation plans. “So you come in and sit down,” Ian Madin says. “And I say, ‘That’s a stupid idea.’ And you say, ‘Thanks. Now we’ve consulted.’ ”</span><br>
<span>These lax safety policies guarantee that many people inside the inundation zone will not get out. Twenty-two per cent of Oregon’s coastal population is sixty-five or older. Twenty-nine per cent of the state’s population is disabled, and that figure rises in many coastal counties. “We can’t save them,” Kevin Cupples says. “I’m not going to sugarcoat it and say, ‘Oh, yeah, we’ll go around and check on the elderly.’ No. We won’t.” Nor will anyone save the tourists. Washington State Park properties within the inundation zone see an average of seventeen thousand and twenty-nine guests a day. Madin estimates that up to a hundred and fifty thousand people visit Oregon’s beaches on summer weekends. “Most of them won’t have a clue as to how to evacuate,” he says. “And the beaches are the hardest place to evacuate from.”</span><br>
<span>Those who cannot get out of the inundation zone under their own power will quickly be overtaken by a greater one. A grown man is knocked over by ankle-deep water moving at 6.7 miles an hour. The tsunami will be moving more than twice that fast when it arrives. Its height will vary with the contours of the coast, from twenty feet to more than a hundred feet. It will not look like a Hokusai-style wave, rising up from the surface of the sea and breaking from above. It will look like the whole ocean, elevated, overtaking land. Nor will it be made only of water—not once it reaches the shore. It will be a five-story deluge of pickup trucks and doorframes and cinder blocks and fishing boats and utility poles and everything else that once constituted the coastal towns of the Pacific Northwest.</span><br>
<span>To see the full scale of the devastation when that tsunami recedes, you would need to be in the international space station. The inundation zone will be scoured of structures from California to Canada. The earthquake will have wrought its worst havoc west of the Cascades but caused damage as far away as Sacramento, California—as distant from the worst-hit areas as Fort Wayne, Indiana, is from New York. fema expects to coördinate search-and-rescue operations across a hundred thousand square miles and in the waters off four hundred and fifty-three miles of coastline. As for casualties: the figures I cited earlier—twenty-seven thousand injured, almost thirteen thousand dead—are based on the agency’s official planning scenario, which has the earthquake striking at 9:41 a.m. on February 6th. If, instead, it strikes in the summer, when the beaches are full, those numbers could be off by a horrifying margin.</span><br>
<span>Wineglasses, antique vases, Humpty Dumpty, hip bones, hearts: what breaks quickly generally mends slowly, if at all. osspac estimates that in the I-5 corridor it will take between one and three months after the earthquake to restore electricity, a month to a year to restore drinking water and sewer service, six months to a year to restore major highways, and eighteen months to restore health-care facilities. On the coast, those numbers go up. Whoever chooses or has no choice but to stay there will spend three to six months without electricity, one to three years without drinking water and sewage systems, and three or more years without hospitals. Those estimates do not apply to the tsunami-inundation zone, which will remain all but uninhabitable for years.</span><br>
<span>How much all this will cost is anyone’s guess; fema puts every number on its relief-and-recovery plan except a price. But whatever the ultimate figure—and even though U.S. taxpayers will cover seventy-five to a hundred per cent of the damage, as happens in declared disasters—the economy of the Pacific Northwest will collapse. Crippled by a lack of basic services, businesses will fail or move away. Many residents will flee as well. osspac predicts a mass-displacement event and a long-term population downturn. Chris Goldfinger didn’t want to be there when it happened. But, by many metrics, it will be as bad or worse to be there afterward.</span><br>
<span>On the face of it, earthquakes seem to present us with problems of space: the way we live along fault lines, in brick buildings, in homes made valuable by their proximity to the sea. But, covertly, they also present us with problems of time. The earth is 4.5 billion years old, but we are a young species, relatively speaking, with an average individual allotment of three score years and ten. The brevity of our lives breeds a kind of temporal parochialism—an ignorance of or an indifference to those planetary gears which turn more slowly than our own.</span><br>
<span>This problem is bidirectional. The Cascadia subduction zone remained hidden from us for so long because we could not see deep enough into the past. It poses a danger to us today because we have not thought deeply enough about the future. That is no longer a problem of information; we now understand very well what the Cascadia fault line will someday do. Nor is it a problem of imagination. If you are so inclined, you can watch an earthquake destroy much of the West Coast this summer in Brad Peyton’s “San Andreas,” while, in neighboring theatres, the world threatens to succumb to Armageddon by other means: viruses, robots, resource scarcity, zombies, aliens, plague. As those movies attest, we excel at imagining future scenarios, including awful ones. But such apocalyptic visions are a form of escapism, not a moral summons, and still less a plan of action. Where we stumble is in conjuring up grim futures in a way that helps to avert them.</span><br>
<span>That problem is not specific to earthquakes, of course. The Cascadia situation, a calamity in its own right, is also a parable for this age of ecological reckoning, and the questions it raises are ones that we all now face. How should a society respond to a looming crisis of uncertain timing but of catastrophic proportions? How can it begin to right itself when its entire infrastructure and culture developed in a way that leaves it profoundly vulnerable to natural disaster?</span><br>
<span>The last person I met with in the Pacific Northwest was Doug Dougherty, the superintendent of schools for Seaside, which lies almost entirely within the tsunami-inundation zone. Of the four schools that Dougherty oversees, with a total student population of sixteen hundred, one is relatively safe. The others sit five to fifteen feet above sea level. When the tsunami comes, they will be as much as forty-five feet below it.</span><br>
<span>In 2009, Dougherty told me, he found some land for sale outside the inundation zone, and proposed building a new K-12 campus there. Four years later, to foot the hundred-and-twenty-eight-million-dollar bill, the district put up a bond measure. The tax increase for residents amounted to two dollars and sixteen cents per thousand dollars of property value. The measure failed by sixty-two per cent. Dougherty tried seeking help from Oregon’s congressional delegation but came up empty. The state makes money available for seismic upgrades, but buildings within the inundation zone cannot apply. At present, all Dougherty can do is make sure that his students know how to evacuate.</span><br>
<span>Some of them, however, will not be able to do so. At an elementary school in the community of Gearhart, the children will be trapped. “They can’t make it out from that school,” Dougherty said. “They have no place to go.” On one side lies the ocean; on the other, a wide, roadless bog. When the tsunami comes, the only place to go in Gearhart is a small ridge just behind the school. At its tallest, it is forty-five feet high—lower than the expected wave in a full-margin earthquake. For now, the route to the ridge is marked by signs that say “Temporary Tsunami Assembly Area.” I asked Dougherty about the state’s long-range plan. “There is no long-range plan,” he said.</span><br>
<span>Dougherty’s office is deep inside the inundation zone, a few blocks from the beach. All day long, just out of sight, the ocean rises up and collapses, spilling foamy overlapping ovals onto the shore. Eighty miles farther out, ten thousand feet below the surface of the sea, the hand of a geological clock is somewhere in its slow sweep. All across the region, seismologists are looking at their watches, wondering how long we have, and what we will do, before geological time catches up to our own. ♦</span><br>
</p><p><b>xqer1107: </b><br>
<span>8月本来计划带家里长辈去美国玩，现在在犹豫还去不去</span><br>
</p><p><b>西之莉芙路: </b><br>
<span>顺便问下，黄石公园那个“超级炸弹”是偏向网络段子一些还是有科学依据的超级天灾啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>両儀織: </b><br>
<span>80天拯救沃夫朗 发表于 2019-7-6 14:42</span><br>
<span>本以为是讲今天的地震，结果往下一看：今年（2016年）</span><br>
<span>大部分美国人听过圣安德烈亚斯（San Andreas）断层线的名字，它几乎与加利福尼亚州等长，还经年不休地流传着马上就要“大爆发”的传言。不管圣安德烈亚斯以前发生过什么，传言本身很有误导性。每条断层线都有它的能量上限，由它的长度、宽度，以及能够波及的距离而定。就圣安德烈亚斯——这条世界上研究最多最彻底的断层线——而言，它的最高上限约为8.2级——的确算得上是大地震，但由于里氏震级是由地震波最大振幅的常用对数演算而来的，这仅是2011年东日本地震强度的6%。</span><br>
<span>卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带正如戈尔德芬格指出的那样：“完美印证了所有地质结构运动上的假设”。然而，没有任何历史记录下这里曾爆发过大地震——或者说，曾发生过地震。相反，其他俯冲带不时就爆发大地震，小地震更是不胜枚举: 5.0级地震，4.0级地震，震感就如同困扰为什么邻居要在半夜挪沙发。在日本待上一周，你就会对此习以为常。而你可能在美国西北地区的好几个城市生活了一辈子——有过几次，事实上如果你足够“幸运”的话——都没感受到过大地的震动。1970年代，地理学家面临的问题是，究竟卡斯卡迪亚俯冲带是否打破过它那吊诡的沉默？</span><br>
<span>==============================</span><br>
<span>这文章说的就是加州圣安德烈斯断层被关注的多，但其实还不会造成大灾难，cascadia这样安安静静的才令人不安</span><br>
</p><p><b>UnknownRei: </b><br>
<span>关东大地震加速了日本向军国主义坠落的速度，望美西海岸诸位断层继承前辈的意志，为盖娅进一步消灭裸猿恶性寄生菌的治疗疗程作出不可磨灭的贡献。</span><br>
</p><p><b>火烧云: </b><br>
<span>如果你用1万除以41，会得出243，那就是卡斯卡迪亚爆发的重复周期</span><br>
<span>我觉得去找希腊政府和小日本比较好一些</span><br>
<span>在对付243年为周期的事情上他们有丰富经验</span><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/07/06/5d20454edd3b889093.png" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/07/06/5d20454edd3b889093.png"><br>
</p><p><b>Iridescence_C: </b><br>
<span>西之莉芙路 发表于 2019-7-6 14:45</span><br>
<span>顺便问下，黄石公园那个“超级炸弹”是偏向网络段子一些还是有科学依据的超级天灾啊 ...</span><br>
<span>真事。不过时间尺度太大了，你我有生之年基本是没可能看到的。</span><br>
<span>小规模一点的可能会大一些，比如东北的长白山。</span><br>
</p><p><b>Gal3ahad: </b><br>
<span>这么说来，日本其实是我们一道天然的防波堤.....</span><br>
<span>人类真是渺小啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>Neozero: </b><br>
<span>地震对卡斯卡迪亚西部造成的浩劫，可波及加利福尼亚的萨克拉门托和印第安纳州东北部的韦恩堡（Fort Wayne）这样的重灾区，亦可及至纽约。</span><br>
<span>The earthquake will have wrought its worst havoc west of the Cascades but caused damage as far away as Sacramento, California—as distant from the worst-hit areas as Fort Wayne, Indiana, is from New York.</span><br>
<span>这什么傻逼翻译明明是说萨克拉门托到破坏最严重的地区和印第安纳州到纽约一样远，真能搞到纽约怕不是黄石公园炸了</span><br>
<span>— from Google Pixel 3, Android 10 of S1 Next Goose v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>ronac: </b><br>
<span>那电影是布拉德佩顿导演的，主演是巨石强森</span><br>
</p><p><b>両儀織: </b><br>
<span>Neozero 发表于 2019-7-6 15:51</span><br>
<span>地震对卡斯卡迪亚西部造成的浩劫，可波及加利福尼亚的萨克拉门托和印第安纳州东北部的韦恩堡（Fort Wayne） ...</span><br>
<span>搜狐的翻译没办法。。。主要是这种综合涉及到历史地理和自然科学文章对译者的综合素质要求比较高，其他地方还过得去就算了。。。</span><br>
</p><p><b>popeacg: </b><br>
<span>央视网消息：继4日发生6.4级地震后，美国加利福尼亚州南部地区当地时间5日晚又发生了7.1级强震。目前，部分受地震影响地区已宣布进入紧急状态。</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 OnePlus ONEPLUS A5010, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>xiongsuper: </b><br>
<span>最近还是别去美国玩了</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>9号单开道岔: </b><br>
<span>西之莉芙路 发表于 2019-7-6 14:45</span><br>
<span>顺便问下，黄石公园那个“超级炸弹”是偏向网络段子一些还是有科学依据的超级天灾啊 ...</span><br>
<span>人类登上了月球，飞出了太阳系，能看见几十亿年前的光，但是人类对地球内部一无所知，拼死拼活才钻了一万米深，连地球的皮都没破，地面以下的东西全靠猜</span><br>
<span>人类知道黄石公园下面有大断裂带，有多大、什么时候爆发、爆发后果有多大，只能靠猜</span><br>
</p><p><b>xinfengj: </b><br>
<span>popeacg 发表于 2019-7-7 12:44</span><br>
<span>央视网消息：继4日发生6.4级地震后，美国加利福尼亚州南部地区当地时间5日晚又发生了7.1级强震。目前，部分 ...</span><br>
<span>不要怕，今天广播里说了，美国发生更大地震的可能性只有百分之三</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 9, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>battleship64: </b><br>
<span>西之莉芙路 发表于 2019-7-6 14:45</span><br>
<span>顺便问下，黄石公园那个“超级炸弹”是偏向网络段子一些还是有科学依据的超级天灾啊 ...</span><br>
<span>去黄石旅游按照国家公园的人的说法是，黄石下面的岩浆不是一个整体所以并没有说的那么可怕。。。。</span><br>
<span>好像是一个个小的岩浆群，不是一个大锅这样子</span><br>
</p><p><b>askl80: </b><br>
<span>风景很好 发表于 2019-7-6 14:17</span><br>
<span>圣安德烈亚斯让我想起了GTA</span><br>
<span>是的，gta：sa的大海里面也有这么一条断裂带。游戏彩蛋之一</span><br>
</p><p><b>askl80: </b><br>
<span>西之莉芙路 发表于 2019-7-6 14:45</span><br>
<span>顺便问下，黄石公园那个“超级炸弹”是偏向网络段子一些还是有科学依据的超级天灾啊 ...</span><br>
<span>最新的研究成果说是地幔柱导致的，也就是地壳下层的地幔层发生上下方向的垂直运动，然后冲破地壳，发生的大爆发。在黄石，南非，和西伯利亚都有这些遗迹，就是那些宝石矿</span><br>
</p><p><b>Alexmacau8: </b><br>
<span>Talk is cheap...能降房价嘛？</span><br>
</p><p><b>工口兔: </b><br>
<span>xinfengj 发表于 2019-7-8 00:15</span><br>
<span>不要怕，今天广播里说了，美国发生更大地震的可能性只有百分之三</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 9, Android 9上的 ...</span><br>
<span>这比FGO抽到5星的概率高了</span><br>
<span>不过加州那儿和卡斯卡迪亚不是一个断层，并没有关联</span><br>
</p><p><b>myarance: </b><br>
<span>battleship64 发表于 2019-7-8 00:24</span><br>
<span>去黄石旅游按照国家公园的人的说法是，黄石下面的岩浆不是一个整体所以并没有说的那么可怕。。。。</span><br>
<span>好像 ...</span><br>
<span>想想也知道不可能是那种65万年一次的毁天灭地那种，不然恐龙哪里还轮得到小行星来灭绝，不过北美大概率是扑街了</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1844703[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
