<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>今天也只传达给你的忍者真实</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>今天也只传达给你的忍者真实</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 11:24:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>今天也只传达给你的忍者真实[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1944012-1-1.html</link>
      <description>今天也只传达给你的忍者真实&#13;
 本帖最后由 kos_mos 于 2020-6-25 22:13 编辑 

全部为忍殺公式每个工作日中午所发，英语全部公式自带，至NASA那都是自带的中文，后面的中文是自己加的。
&#13;
https://assets.st-note.com/production/uploads/images/13717684/rectangle_large_type_2_607ec25ee7506ebd942567ebc2ab410f.png
&#13;
#ninja_fact / ニンジャファクト・キャンペイグン
&#13;
Title：
&#13;
　ニンジャファクト・キャンペイグン
&#13;
　Ninja Fact Campaign
&#13;
　忍者事实运动
&#13;
　निंजा तथ्य अभियान
&#13;
期間：
&#13;
　2019.07.09 - ongoing
&#13;
ニンジャはいます。
&#13;
Ninja is real.
&#13;
忍者是真的
&#13;
निंजा असली है।
&#13;
ニンジャはカラテで戦います。
&#13;
Ninja fights with the karate.
&#13;
忍者擅长空手道
&#13;
निंजा कराटे से लड़ता है।
&#13;
ニンジャはスシが大好き。
&#13;
Ninja likes sushi, which is a perfect food.
&#13;
忍者喜欢寿司
&#13;
निंजा को सुशी पसंद है।
&#13;
ニンジャは死ぬと爆発四散します。
&#13;
When ninja dies, it explodes.
&#13;
当忍者死亡时，它会爆炸
&#13;
जब निंजा मर जाता है, तो यह विस्फोट हो जाता है।
&#13;
ニンジャは半神的存在です。
&#13;
Ninjas are half-godly entities.
&#13;
忍者是半神半人
&#13;
निनजास डेमिगोड हैं।
&#13;
ニンジャはボトルの蓋の開け方ではなく、切断面の無慈悲さで競います。
&#13;
Ninjas compete in the mercilessness of the cutting surface, not how to open the cap of the bottle.
&#13;
忍者在切割瓶首的无情中竞争，而不是如何打开瓶盖
&#13;
ニンジャの大部分は、ほ乳類です。
&#13;
The majority of ninjas are mammals.
&#13;
大多数忍者都是哺乳动物
&#13;
बहुसंख्यक निनजा स्तनधारी हैं।
&#13;
ある日突然、ニンジャになります。
&#13;
One day suddenly, you become a ninja.
&#13;
突然有一天，你可能成为忍者
&#13;
एक दिन अचानक, आप एक निंजा बन सकते हैं।
&#13;
ニンジャはいたるところに潜んでいます。
&#13;
Ninjas are hiding everywhere.
&#13;
忍者到处都是藏身之地
&#13;
निन्जा हर जगह छिपे हैं
&#13;
ニンジャ同士が出会うと、アイサツします。
&#13;
When the ninjas meet, they bow and introduce themselves.
&#13;
当忍者相遇时，他们自我介绍
&#13;
जब नन्हें मिलते हैं, तो वे झुककर अपना परिचय देते हैं।
&#13;
その後で、殺します。
&#13;
Then kill.
&#13;
然后杀了
&#13;
फिर मार देते हैं।
&#13;
ニンジャの手のひらから、稲妻が発射されました。
&#13;
Lightning bolt was fired from the palm of ninja.
&#13;
忍者从手掌上射出闪电
&#13;
निंजा की हथेली से बिजली के बोल्ट को निकाल दिया गया था।
&#13;
そして人々を殺しました。
&#13;
Then killed people.
&#13;
然后杀了人
&#13;
फिर लोगों को मार डाला।
&#13;
ニンジャの使うマジックパワーは、ジツと呼ばれます。
&#13;
The magic power that ninjas use is called Jitsu.
&#13;
忍者使用的神奇力量称为术
&#13;
निन्जा के उपयोग की जादुई शक्ति को Jitsu कहा जाता है।
&#13;
ニンジャが触れるだけで、あなたは燃え上がります。
&#13;
Ninja touches, you get ignited.
&#13;
忍者接触，你被点燃了
&#13;
निंजा छूता है, आप प्रज्वलित हो जाते हैं।
&#13;
ソドムの都は、ニンジャのジツによって焼き落とされました。
&#13;
The city of Sodom was burned down by ninja's Jitsu.
&#13;
所多玛城被忍者的术烧毁了
&#13;
निंजा के जादू से सदोम शहर जल गया।
&#13;
ニンジャのジツで、女子高生が原子分解されました。
&#13;
A high school girl was atomically disintegrated by ninja's Jitsu.
&#13;
一名高中女生被忍者魔法分解为原子级
&#13;
एक हाई स्कूल की लड़की निंजा के जादू से बुरी तरह से बिखर गई थी।
&#13;
ニンジャは紀元前から存在しています。
&#13;
Ninjas have existed since BC.
&#13;
忍者自公元前就已存在
&#13;
बीकस के बाद से निनजा का अस्तित्व है।
&#13;
ニンジャのスリケンが月面で発見され、アポロ11号が密かに持ち帰りました。
&#13;
Ninja's suriken was discovered on the moon, and Apollo 11 secretly brought it back to Earth.
&#13;
在月球上发现了忍者手里剑，阿波罗11号将它带回了地球
&#13;
NASAやペンタゴンも、ニンジャの脅威を知っています。
&#13;
NASA and the Pentagon also know the threat of Ninja.
&#13;
美国宇航局和五角大楼也知道忍者的威胁
&#13;
नासा और पेंटागन भी निंजा के खतरे को जानते हैं।
&#13;
ゴモラの都についてはよくわかっていません。
&#13;
It is not sure about the city of Gomorrah.
&#13;
关于哥莫拉之都并不清楚
&#13;
ニンジャは会社から給料を得ます。
&#13;
Ninja gets a salary from the dark mega-corp.
&#13;
忍者从会社获得工资
&#13;
ニンジャは他社の機密情報を盗み出します。
&#13;
Ninja steals confidential information from other mega-corps.
&#13;
忍者从他社盗走机密情报
&#13;
ニンジャは未公開株券を奪って逃走しました。
&#13;
Ninja ran away with an unlisted stock certificate.
&#13;
忍者夺走了未公开股票后逃走
&#13;
他の会社のニンジャと出会うと、アイサツします。
&#13;
When a ninja meets another mega-corp’s ninja, they bow and introduce themselves.
&#13;
和他社的忍者相遇，自我介绍
&#13;
その後で、殺します。
&#13;
Then kill.
&#13;
然后杀了
&#13;
ニンジャはいません。
&#13;
Ninja does not exist.
&#13;
忍者不存在
&#13;
ニンジャは吸血鬼やドラゴンと同じ空想上の生き物です。
&#13;
Ninjas are the same fantasy creatures as vampires and dragons.
&#13;
忍者和吸血鬼和龙一样是空想上的生物
&#13;
ニンジャの格好をしてヌンチャクを振り回していると、警察に逮捕されます。
&#13;
If you dress like a ninja and wield Nunchaku, you will be arrested by the police.
&#13;
以忍者的穿着挥舞双节棍，会被警察逮捕
&#13;
人々は本能的にニンジャを恐れているからです。
&#13;
Because people are instinctively afraid of ninja.
&#13;
人本能地恐惧着忍者
&#13;
琥珀に閉じ込められたスリケンが発見されました。
&#13;
An ancient suriken found preserved in amber.
&#13;
封着手里剑的琥珀被发现
&#13;
その犬はニンジャです。
&#13;
The dog is ninja.
&#13;
这只犬也是忍者
&#13;
ニンジャとニンジャの犬はテレパシーで会話します。
&#13;
Ninja and the ninja dog talk by telepathy.
&#13;
忍者和忍者的犬能以心灵感应对话
&#13;
この蛸もニンジャです。
&#13;
This octopus is also a ninja.
&#13;
这只章鱼也是忍者
&#13;
ニンジャとニンジャの蛸はテレパシーで会話します。
&#13;
Ninja and the ninja octopus talk by telepathy.
&#13;
忍者和忍者的章鱼能以心灵感应对话
&#13;
ニンジャは天井裏に隠れていました。
&#13;
The ninja was hiding behind the ceiling.
&#13;
忍者藏在天花板里侧
&#13;
ニンジャは冷蔵庫の中に隠れていました。
&#13;
Ninja was hiding in the refrigerator.
&#13;
忍者藏在冰箱中
&#13;
ニンジャはタクシー運転手に偽装していました。
&#13;
Ninja was disguised as a taxi driver.
&#13;
忍者伪装成taxi驾驶员
&#13;
ニンジャは女子高の教師になりすましていました。
&#13;
Ninja was impersonating a girl’s high school teacher.
&#13;
忍者成为女子高中的教师
&#13;
官房長官もニンジャでした。
&#13;
The chief secretary was also a ninja.
&#13;
官方长官也是忍者
&#13;
ニンジャは他人の影の中に潜みます。
&#13;
Ninja hides in shadows of others.
&#13;
忍者潜入在他人的影中
&#13;
ニンジャの投げたクナイが影に刺さると、あなたは金縛りになります。
&#13;
Ninja throws a kunai dart into your shadow, you get paralyzed.
&#13;
忍者投掷的苦无刺到影子，你会被金缚
&#13;
ニンジャのジツでタワーマンションが影の触手に覆われ、通勤困難になりました。
&#13;
The tower mansion was covered with shadow tentacles by ninja’s jitsu, making commuting difficult.
&#13;
忍者的术的影之触手覆盖了塔公寓，造成通勤困难
&#13;
ハデス神もニンジャ。
&#13;
Hades is also a ninja.
&#13;
哈迪斯神也是忍者
&#13;
ニンジャはとても素早い生き物です。
&#13;
Ninja is a very quick creature.
&#13;
忍者是极为快速的生物
&#13;
ニンジャの脚力はあなたの3倍以上あります。
&#13;
Ninja's leg strength is more than three times yours.
&#13;
忍者的脚力是你的3倍以上
&#13;
全力疾走するニンジャは色付きの風に見えます。
&#13;
A ninja sprinting at full speed looks like a colored wind.
&#13;
全力疾走的忍者看上去就是带色的风
&#13;
ニンジャはハイウェイを走る車と並走できます。
&#13;
Ninja can run side by side with cars on the highway.
&#13;
忍者和高速公路的车并跑
&#13;
一定速度以下になると爆発する装置がニンジャに取り付けられました。
&#13;
A device has been attached to the ninja that explodes when it is below a certain speed.
&#13;
跑步慢于一定速度以下就会爆炸的装置被装在忍者身上
&#13;
ニンジャは歴史の影に潜んでいます。
&#13;
Ninjas lurk in the shadows of history.
&#13;
忍者潜伏在历史的影中
&#13;
関ヶ原の戦いでは両軍に多数のニンジャが参加しました。
&#13;
Many ninjas participated in both sides during the Battle of Sekibahara.
&#13;
关原之战两军多数的忍者参加
&#13;
テキサス独立戦争にもニンジャが関与しています。
&#13;
Ninjas are also involved in the Texas Revolutionary War.
&#13;
德克萨斯独立战争也和忍者有关
&#13;
明智光秀はニンジャ。
&#13;
Akechi Mitsuhide is a ninja.
&#13;
明智光秀是忍者
&#13;
織田信長もニンジャ。
&#13;
Oda Nobunaga is also a ninja.
&#13;
织田信长也是忍者
&#13;
グローバル企業の多くはニンジャを抱えています。
&#13;
Many global mega-corps have ninjas.
&#13;
国际企业拥有多数的忍者
&#13;
CEOもニンジャでした。
&#13;
The CEO is also a ninja.
&#13;
CEO也是忍者
&#13;
ニンジャは寿司屋から給料を得ます。
&#13;
Ninja gets a salary from a sushi bar.
&#13;
忍者从寿司屋获得工资
&#13;
ニンジャはスシを握ります。
&#13;
Ninja makes sushi.
&#13;
忍者握寿司
&#13;
負傷したニンジャは、スシを食べて栄養を補給しました。
&#13;
Injured ninja ate sushi to regain vigor.
&#13;
负伤的忍者，能通过吃寿司补给到营养
&#13;
トロに含まれているDHAが、ニンジャの神経細胞を癒します。
&#13;
DHA contained in Toro heals ninja's neurons.
&#13;
鲔脂所含的DHA，能治愈忍者的神经细胞
&#13;
ニンジャは側転で銃弾をよけます。
&#13;
Ninjas can avoid bullets by cartwheeling.
&#13;
忍者用侧翻躲过子弹
&#13;
世界はニンジャによって操られています。
&#13;
The world is manipulated by ninjas.
&#13;
世界被忍者所操控
&#13;
議会、報道機関、治安維持機構、軍産複合体、宗教法人、空手家の組合などは全てニンジャに支配されています。
&#13;
Parliament, media, security organization, military-industrial complex, religious corporation, Karateka union, etc. are all manipulated by ninjas.
&#13;
议会、报导机关、治安维持机构、军产复合体、宗教法人、空手家的组合灯全被忍者所支配
&#13;
月面にもニンジャ基地が隠されています。
&#13;
There is also a ninja base on the moon.
&#13;
月面也隐藏着忍者基地
&#13;
ニンジャは短距離テレポートを行います。
&#13;
Ninja uses short jumps.
&#13;
忍者能用短距离瞬间移动
&#13;
ニンジャは長距離テレポート用のポータルを開きますが、高い確率で転送者の消滅事故が起こります。
&#13;
Ninjas open a portal for long-distance teleports, but there is a high probability that transferers will disappear.
&#13;
忍者虽然能打开长距离跳跃用的传送门，但是高机率发生传送者的消灭事故
&#13;
ニンジャは天気を操れます。
&#13;
Ninja can control the weather.
&#13;
忍者操控天气
&#13;
ニンジャは死ぬ前にハイクを詠みます。
&#13;
Ninja recites a haiku before death.
&#13;
忍者死前会咏颂俳句
&#13;
ニンジャと金閣寺には深い関係性があります。
&#13;
Ninjas and Kinkaku Temple have a causal connection.
&#13;
忍者和金阁寺有很深的关联性
&#13;
ニンジャの掌から出た神秘的な泡で警備員が溶かされました。
&#13;
The guards were melted by a mysterious bubble from the palm of the ninja.
&#13;
从忍者的掌发出的神秘的泡将警备员溶解了
&#13;
ニンジャのジツのせいでが寒波にみまわれ、通勤困難になりました。
&#13;
The city was hit by a cold wave because of Ninja’s Jitsu, making commuting difficult.
&#13;
因为忍者的术的关系造成了寒波，造成通勤困难
&#13;
ニンジャのジツにより、蟹が強くなりました。
&#13;
The crab became stronger due to the Jitsu of the ninja.
&#13;
忍者的术使蟹变强
&#13;
ニンジャが地面に設置するマキビシは非人道兵器で、かつて大勢の無関係の被害者を生みました。
&#13;
Makibishi, the object which was installed on the ground by ninja was an inhumane weapon and it created many unrelated victims.
&#13;
忍者在地面设置的撒菱是非人道兵器，造成了大量无关系的被害者
&#13;
それは古事記にも書かれています。
&#13;
It is also written in the Kojiki, Records of Ancient Matters.
&#13;
这在古事记也记载了
&#13;
ニンジャはモーターサイクルの上に立って戦います。
&#13;
Ninja stands on the motorcycle and fights.
&#13;
忍者在机动单车上站立战斗
&#13;
ニンジャは大凧に乗って空を飛びます。
&#13;
Ninja flies in the sky with a big kite.
&#13;
忍者用大风筝在空中飞行
&#13;
ニンジャの運転するタクシーがビルに激突しました。
&#13;
A taxi driven by ninja crashed into a building.
&#13;
忍者驾驶的taxi和大楼激突
&#13;
中にいたニンジャは無事でした。
&#13;
The ninja who was inside was safe.
&#13;
里面的忍者没有事
&#13;
ニンジャは都知事の座を狙っています。
&#13;
Ninja is aiming for Governor of the City.
&#13;
忍者瞄准着都知事的座位
&#13;
ニンジャはインターネットを禁止します。
&#13;
Ninja bans the internet.
&#13;
忍者禁止互联网
&#13;
そのニンジャ投手は暗殺野球のプロフェッショナルでした。
&#13;
The ninja pitcher was an assassin baseball professional.
&#13;
这忍者的投手是暗杀棒球的专家
&#13;
ニンジャとニンジャの犬は復讐のために共に戦います。
&#13;
Ninja and the ninja dog fight together for revenge.
&#13;
忍者和忍者的犬一同为复仇战斗
&#13;
ニンジャの身長は20メートル近くあります。
&#13;
The ninja is about 20 meters tall.
&#13;
忍者的身高有今20米
&#13;
殺すためです。
&#13;
To kill.
&#13;
为了杀
&#13;
巨大なニンジャを実際に見ると、あなたは急性ニンジャリアリティショックを起こして発狂します。
&#13;
When you actually see a gargantuan ninja, you will go mad with an Acute Ninja Reality Shock.
&#13;
实际见到巨大的忍者，你会急性NRS（忍者真实性冲击）而发狂
&#13;
ニンジャはチーターに匹敵する速度で匍匐前進しました。
&#13;
The ninja crawled along at a high speed comparable to cheetahs.
&#13;
忍者以和猎豹匹敌的速度匍匐前进
&#13;
ニンジャはカラテチョップにより真っ二つに切断されました。
&#13;
One ninja was cut into two by karate chop.
&#13;
忍者被空手手刀从正中一分为二切断
&#13;
ニンジャは様々な乗り物を乗りこなします。
&#13;
Ninja rides various vehicles.
&#13;
忍者乘在各种各样的载具上
&#13;
ニンジャは高速飛行するVTOLの上に立っています。
&#13;
Ninja stands on top of VTOL flying fast.
&#13;
忍者站立在高速飞行的VTOL上
&#13;
ニンジャは反重力バイクに乗って戦います。
&#13;
Ninja fights on an anti-grav bike.
&#13;
忍者乘着反重力摩托战斗
&#13;
ニンジャがミサイルに乗って高速接近していますので注意してください。
&#13;
WARNING!! A ninja is approaching fast, riding on a missile.
&#13;
WARNING！！忍者乘着导弹高速接近请注意
&#13;
ニンジャは発車直前のスペースシャトルに飛びついて乗りました。
&#13;
Ninja jumped on the space shuttle just before departure.
&#13;
忍者跳到发车直前的宇宙穿梭机
&#13;
ニンジャは宇宙服を着ていたので無事でした。
&#13;
The ninja was safe because wearing a space suit.
&#13;
忍者穿着宇宙服所以没事
&#13;
ニンジャは株式市場を背後から操作します。
&#13;
Ninja controls the stock market from behind.
&#13;
忍者在股票市场的背后进行操作
&#13;
ニンジャは隠し持っていた銃で敵をヘッドショットしました。
&#13;
Ninja made a headshot with a hidden gun.
&#13;
忍者用隐藏的铳将敌人headshoot
&#13;
ニンジャが触れるだけで、あなたは氷漬けになります。
&#13;
Ninja touches, you get iced.
&#13;
忍者只是触碰你，你就会冰冻
&#13;
ニンジャが触れるだけで、あなたは原子分解します。
&#13;
Ninja touches, you get disintegrated.
&#13;
忍者只是触碰你，你就会原子分解
&#13;
アケチ・ニンジャが勝利し、オダ・ニンジャの肉体の一部を奪いました。
&#13;
Akechi Ninja won and took a part of Oda Ninja's body.
&#13;
明智·忍者胜利，夺走了织田·忍者肉体的一部分
&#13;
これが明智光秀が四本腕のニンジャである理由です。
&#13;
This is why Akechi Mitsuhide is the ninja with four arms.
&#13;
这是明智光秀有四支手臂的理由
&#13;
ニンジャはSNSがあまり好きではありません。
&#13;
Ninja doesn't like SNS.
&#13;
忍者不喜欢SNS
&#13;
織田信長のニンジャソウルは明智光秀から逃れ、キンカク・テンプルへと昇りました。
&#13;
Oda's ninja soul escaped from Akechi' hand and ascended to the Golden Cube.
&#13;
织田信长的忍者灵魂从明智光秀手中逃走，升到金阁·temple
&#13;
ニンジャは情報戦を得意としています。
&#13;
Ninja is good at information warfare.
&#13;
忍者擅长情报战
&#13;
ニンジャは周囲に存在するインターネットを知覚できます。
&#13;
Ninja can perceive the Internet around.
&#13;
忍者能感应到周围存在的互联网
&#13;
インターネットを使う人間は惰弱だからです。
&#13;
Because people who use the Internet are weak and pathetic.
&#13;
使用互联网的人类是惰弱的
&#13;
ニンジャは強大なるドラゴンの背にまたがって空に舞い上がります。
&#13;
Ninja flies into the sky on the back of a mighty dragon.
&#13;
忍者在强大的龙的背上飞舞在空中
&#13;
誰にもニンジャを止めることできない。
&#13;
No one can stop ninja.
&#13;
谁都无法阻止忍者
&#13;
伝説のカタナは古代エジプトのピラミッドの中に封印されていました。
&#13;
The legendary katana was sealed in the ancient Egyptian pyramid.
&#13;
传说的刀封印在古代埃及的金字塔中
&#13;
聖なるヌンチャクは京都の地下遺跡に封印されていました。
&#13;
The holy nunchaku was sealed in the ancient ruin in Kyoto.
&#13;
圣双节棍封印在京都的地下遗迹中
&#13;
聖なるヌンチャクはニンジャの三神器のひとつで、三神器が揃うと世界が滅びます。
&#13;
The sacred nunchaku is one of the ninja's three sacred treasures. When all three sacred treasures are complete, the world will be destroyed.
&#13;
圣双节棍是忍者的三神器之一，集齐三神器世界就会毁灭
&#13;
ニンジャが光に弱いというのはただの迷信です。
&#13;
Ninja's sensitivity to light is just superstition.
&#13;
忍者怕光只是迷信
&#13;
ニンジャの吸血鬼は日光が弱点です。
&#13;
Ninja vampires are weak in sunlight.
&#13;
忍者的吸血鬼的弱点是日光
&#13;
ドラキュラのモデルとして有名なブラド・ツェペシュはニンジャです。
&#13;
Brad Tzepesh, famous as a model of Dracula, is a ninja.
&#13;
德古拉的原型有名的弗拉德·采佩什是忍者
&#13;
徳川家康はニンジャではありません。
&#13;
Tokugawa Ieyasu is not a ninja.
&#13;
德川家康不是忍者
&#13;
松尾芭蕉はニンジャではありませんが、彼の俳句はニンジャに滅びをもたらしました。
&#13;
Matsuo Basho is not a ninja, but his haiku brought havoc to many ninjas.
&#13;
松尾芭蕉不是忍者，他的俳句将忍者毁灭了
&#13;
柳生ウォンジもニンジャではありませんが、彼は江戸時代に蘇った明智光秀を再び封印しました。
&#13;
Yagyu Wonji is not a ninja, but he sent Akechi back to nether.
&#13;
柳生王爾也不是忍者，他在江户时代将复苏的明智光秀再度封印
&#13;
ニンジャは荒野で磔になります。
&#13;
Ninja is crucified in the wilderness
&#13;
忍者被磔在荒野
&#13;
ニンジャは磔にした敵の前でスシを食べて拷問しました。
&#13;
Ninja eats sushi and tortures in front of the crucified enemy.
&#13;
忍者被磔他的敌人在其面前吃寿司来拷问
&#13;
ニンジャの力を信じない場合、ホールから出て行ってください。
&#13;
If you don't believe in the power of ninja, leave the hall.
&#13;
不相信忍者的力量的场合，请从大厅出去
&#13;
ニンジャはSNSに偽のレビュー情報を投稿します。
&#13;
Ninja posts fake reviews on SNS.
&#13;
忍者在SNS投稿虚伪的评价情报
&#13;
ニンジャが電車内で戦ったせいで、通勤困難になりました。
&#13;
The ninjas fought on the train, making commuting difficult.
&#13;
忍者在电车内战斗，导致通勤困难
&#13;
ニンジャはワームホールから反物質の武器を生み出します。
&#13;
Ninja creates antimatter weapons from wormholes.
&#13;
忍者从虫洞中生成反物质的武器
&#13;
ニンジャの幽霊に触れられるとカラテを吸い取られます。
&#13;
If you are touched by a ninja ghost, your karate will be drained.
&#13;
忍者的幽灵通过触碰来吸取空手
&#13;
ニンジャの幽霊は地面から数センチ浮いています。
&#13;
Ninja ghosts are floating a few centimeters above the ground.
&#13;
忍者的幽灵浮在地面上数厘米
&#13;
ニンジャの幽霊なので、銃弾はその体を破壊することなく通過してしまいます。
&#13;
Because they are ninja ghosts, bullets do not work.
&#13;
忍者因为是幽灵，子弹无法破坏其身体只会穿过
&#13;
ニンジャのスリケンとドラゴンの炎がすべてを破壊します。
&#13;
Ninja's star and Dragon's flame shall destroy everything.
&#13;
忍者的手里剑和龙的炎将一切破坏
&#13;
ニンジャのジツのせいで、ショッピングモールにゾンビが溢れました。
&#13;
The shopping mall was flooded with zombies because of the Ninja’s Jitsu.
&#13;
因为忍者的术的关系，购物商场四溢着丧尸
&#13;
ニンジャがボタンを押すと床が開き、失敗したビジネスマンが縦穴へ落下しました。
&#13;
When Ninja pressed the button, the floor opened and the failed businessman fell into a pit.
&#13;
忍者按下按钮地板打开，失败的businessman从纵穴落下
&#13;
ピンク色のイルカですが、ニンジャです。
&#13;
It is a pink dolphin, but it is a ninja.
&#13;
粉色的海豚也是忍者
&#13;
その恐竜はニンジャです。
&#13;
The dinosaur is a ninja.
&#13;
这恐龙也是忍者
&#13;
さるかに合戦の猿と蟹はニンジャのメタファーです。
&#13;
Monkey and crabs in the Monkey Crab War are ninja metaphors.
&#13;
猿蟹合战是猿和蟹的忍者的隐喻
&#13;
着地と同時にタイミングよく前転したので、ニンジャは無事でした。
&#13;
Ninja was safe because it made a timely forward roll.
&#13;
着地的同时时机把握好前翻的话，忍者就没事
&#13;
「ニンジャスレイヤー™」はサイバーパンク・ニンジャアクション小説です。
&#13;
NINJA SLAYER™ is a cyberpunk ninja action novel.
&#13;
忍者杀手™是赛博朋克忍者动作小说
&#13;
「ニンジャスレイヤー™」の読者はニンジャヘッズと呼ばれます。
&#13;
The readers of NINJA SLAYER™ are called Ninja Headz.
&#13;
忍者杀手™的读者被称为Ninja Headz
&#13;
AIの試算によると、日本国内におけるニンジャヘッズの人数は５億人です。
&#13;
According to the AI, the estimated number of Ninja Headz in Japan is 500 million.
&#13;
AI试算下，日本国内的Ninja Headz有5亿人
&#13;
江戸時代が終わるまでにニンジャはほぼ絶滅しました。
&#13;
By the end of the Edo period, ninjas were almost extinct.
&#13;
直到江户时代结束忍者几乎绝灭
&#13;
ニンジャは武田信玄の埋蔵金伝説とも深い関係があります。
&#13;
Ninja also has a deep connection with Takeda Shingen's buried gold legend.
&#13;
忍者和武田信玄的埋藏金有很深的关系
&#13;
ニンジャは一億円の入ったスポーツバッグを竹やぶに埋めました。
&#13;
Ninja buried a sports bag containing 100 million yen in bamboo bush.
&#13;
忍者将放着一亿円的运动包埋在竹林里
&#13;
ニンジャは他社のデータセンター要塞に対して強行偵察を行い、旧世紀のIPアドレスを盗み出します。
&#13;
Ninja conducts a forced reconnaissance against other mega-corps’ Data Center Fortresses and steals old century
&#13;
IP addresses.
&#13;
忍者从他社的数据中心要塞进行强行侦查，盗走旧世纪的IP地址
&#13;
ニンジャは数千年生きられます。
&#13;
Ninjas can live for thousands of years.
&#13;
忍者能活数千年
&#13;
ニンジャの数はドージョーで増える傾向があります。
&#13;
Ninjas tend to increase their numbers by training in the dojo.
&#13;
忍者的数量取决于道场的增加
&#13;
ニンジャは絶滅の危機に瀕し、ドージョーの数は激減しました。
&#13;
Ninjas were in danger of extinction, and the number of their dojos decreased sharply.
&#13;
忍者濒临绝灭的危机时，道场的数量激减
&#13;
ニンジャはSNSが大好き。
&#13;
Ninja likes SNS.
&#13;
忍者喜欢SNS
&#13;
ニンジャはSNSにカラテの動画をアップします。
&#13;
Ninja uploads the video of karate on SNS.
&#13;
忍者在SNS上传空手视频
&#13;
ニンジャのドージョーの位置がSNSにより露見しました。
&#13;
The location of the ninja dojo was revealed because of SNS.
&#13;
忍者的道场位置会被SNS显露
&#13;
エジプトのピラミッドの棺にはニンジャが眠っています。
&#13;
Ninja is sleeping in the Egyptian pyramid casket.
&#13;
埃及的金字塔的棺材中沉眠着忍者
&#13;
ニンジャは鐘乳石に偽装していました。
&#13;
Ninja was disguised as a stalagmite.
&#13;
忍者伪装成钟乳石
&#13;
ニンジャのタイピング速度は素晴らしく早い。
&#13;
Ninja typing speed is amazingly fast.
&#13;
忍者的输入速度很快
&#13;
ニンジャはUNIXとケーブル直結してタイピング速度を加速させます。
&#13;
Ninja is wired to UNIX to boost the typing speed.
&#13;
忍者用缆线和UNIX直连能加速输入速度
&#13;
ニンジャが触れるだけで、あなたは人間爆弾になります。
&#13;
Ninja touches, you become a human bomb.
&#13;
忍者只是接触你，你就会变成人类爆弹
&#13;
商談に逆らった会社には、ニンジャが送り込まれます。
&#13;
Ninjas are sent to companies that have refused the business negotiations.
&#13;
对于违逆商谈的会社，会送去忍者
&#13;
ニンジャスレイヤーはクリスマスイブの夜に誕生しました。
&#13;
Ninja Slayer was born on the night of Christmas Eve.
&#13;
忍者杀手在圣诞夜诞生
&#13;
ニンジャスレイヤーはニンジャを殺すニンジャです。
&#13;
Ninja Slayer is a ninja that kills ninjas.
&#13;
忍者杀手是杀死忍者的忍者</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>kos_mos: </b><br>
<span>今天也只传达给你的忍者真实</span><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 kos_mos 于 2020-6-25 22:13 编辑 </span><br>
<span>全部为忍殺公式每个工作日中午所发，英语全部公式自带，至NASA那都是自带的中文，后面的中文是自己加的。</span><br>
<img src="https://assets.st-note.com/production/uploads/images/13717684/rectangle_large_type_2_607ec25ee7506ebd942567ebc2ab410f.png" title="https://assets.st-note.com/production/uploads/images/13717684/rectangle_large_type_2_607ec25ee7506ebd942567ebc2ab410f.png"><br>
<span>#ninja_fact / ニンジャファクト・キャンペイグン</span><br>
<span>Title：</span><br>
<span>　ニンジャファクト・キャンペイグン</span><br>
<span>　Ninja Fact Campaign</span><br>
<span>　忍者事实运动</span><br>
<span>　निंजा तथ्य अभियान</span><br>
<span>期間：</span><br>
<span>　2019.07.09 - ongoing</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはいます。</span><br>
<span>Ninja is real.</span><br>
<span>忍者是真的</span><br>
<span>निंजा असली है।</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはカラテで戦います。</span><br>
<span>Ninja fights with the karate.</span><br>
<span>忍者擅长空手道</span><br>
<span>निंजा कराटे से लड़ता है।</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはスシが大好き。</span><br>
<span>Ninja likes sushi, which is a perfect food.</span><br>
<span>忍者喜欢寿司</span><br>
<span>निंजा को सुशी पसंद है।</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは死ぬと爆発四散します。</span><br>
<span>When ninja dies, it explodes.</span><br>
<span>当忍者死亡时，它会爆炸</span><br>
<span>जब निंजा मर जाता है, तो यह विस्फोट हो जाता है।</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは半神的存在です。</span><br>
<span>Ninjas are half-godly entities.</span><br>
<span>忍者是半神半人</span><br>
<span>निनजास डेमिगोड हैं।</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはボトルの蓋の開け方ではなく、切断面の無慈悲さで競います。</span><br>
<span>Ninjas compete in the mercilessness of the cutting surface, not how to open the cap of the bottle.</span><br>
<span>忍者在切割瓶首的无情中竞争，而不是如何打开瓶盖</span><br>
<span>ニンジャの大部分は、ほ乳類です。</span><br>
<span>The majority of ninjas are mammals.</span><br>
<span>大多数忍者都是哺乳动物</span><br>
<span>बहुसंख्यक निनजा स्तनधारी हैं।</span><br>
<span>ある日突然、ニンジャになります。</span><br>
<span>One day suddenly, you become a ninja.</span><br>
<span>突然有一天，你可能成为忍者</span><br>
<span>एक दिन अचानक, आप एक निंजा बन सकते हैं।</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはいたるところに潜んでいます。</span><br>
<span>Ninjas are hiding everywhere.</span><br>
<span>忍者到处都是藏身之地</span><br>
<span>निन्जा हर जगह छिपे हैं</span><br>
<span>ニンジャ同士が出会うと、アイサツします。</span><br>
<span>When the ninjas meet, they bow and introduce themselves.</span><br>
<span>当忍者相遇时，他们自我介绍</span><br>
<span>जब नन्हें मिलते हैं, तो वे झुककर अपना परिचय देते हैं।</span><br>
<span>その後で、殺します。</span><br>
<span>Then kill.</span><br>
<span>然后杀了</span><br>
<span>फिर मार देते हैं।</span><br>
<span>ニンジャの手のひらから、稲妻が発射されました。</span><br>
<span>Lightning bolt was fired from the palm of ninja.</span><br>
<span>忍者从手掌上射出闪电</span><br>
<span>निंजा की हथेली से बिजली के बोल्ट को निकाल दिया गया था।</span><br>
<span>そして人々を殺しました。</span><br>
<span>Then killed people.</span><br>
<span>然后杀了人</span><br>
<span>फिर लोगों को मार डाला।</span><br>
<span>ニンジャの使うマジックパワーは、ジツと呼ばれます。</span><br>
<span>The magic power that ninjas use is called Jitsu.</span><br>
<span>忍者使用的神奇力量称为术</span><br>
<span>निन्जा के उपयोग की जादुई शक्ति को Jitsu कहा जाता है।</span><br>
<span>ニンジャが触れるだけで、あなたは燃え上がります。</span><br>
<span>Ninja touches, you get ignited.</span><br>
<span>忍者接触，你被点燃了</span><br>
<span>निंजा छूता है, आप प्रज्वलित हो जाते हैं।</span><br>
<span>ソドムの都は、ニンジャのジツによって焼き落とされました。</span><br>
<span>The city of Sodom was burned down by ninja's Jitsu.</span><br>
<span>所多玛城被忍者的术烧毁了</span><br>
<span>निंजा के जादू से सदोम शहर जल गया।</span><br>
<span>ニンジャのジツで、女子高生が原子分解されました。</span><br>
<span>A high school girl was atomically disintegrated by ninja's Jitsu.</span><br>
<span>一名高中女生被忍者魔法分解为原子级</span><br>
<span>एक हाई स्कूल की लड़की निंजा के जादू से बुरी तरह से बिखर गई थी।</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは紀元前から存在しています。</span><br>
<span>Ninjas have existed since BC.</span><br>
<span>忍者自公元前就已存在</span><br>
<span>बीकस के बाद से निनजा का अस्तित्व है।</span><br>
<span>ニンジャのスリケンが月面で発見され、アポロ11号が密かに持ち帰りました。</span><br>
<span>Ninja's suriken was discovered on the moon, and Apollo 11 secretly brought it back to Earth.</span><br>
<span>在月球上发现了忍者手里剑，阿波罗11号将它带回了地球</span><br>
<span>NASAやペンタゴンも、ニンジャの脅威を知っています。</span><br>
<span>NASA and the Pentagon also know the threat of Ninja.</span><br>
<span>美国宇航局和五角大楼也知道忍者的威胁</span><br>
<span>नासा और पेंटागन भी निंजा के खतरे को जानते हैं।</span><br>
<span>ゴモラの都についてはよくわかっていません。</span><br>
<span>It is not sure about the city of Gomorrah.</span><br>
<span>关于哥莫拉之都并不清楚</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは会社から給料を得ます。</span><br>
<span>Ninja gets a salary from the dark mega-corp.</span><br>
<span>忍者从会社获得工资</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは他社の機密情報を盗み出します。</span><br>
<span>Ninja steals confidential information from other mega-corps.</span><br>
<span>忍者从他社盗走机密情报</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは未公開株券を奪って逃走しました。</span><br>
<span>Ninja ran away with an unlisted stock certificate.</span><br>
<span>忍者夺走了未公开股票后逃走</span><br>
<span>他の会社のニンジャと出会うと、アイサツします。</span><br>
<span>When a ninja meets another mega-corp’s ninja, they bow and introduce themselves.</span><br>
<span>和他社的忍者相遇，自我介绍</span><br>
<span>その後で、殺します。</span><br>
<span>Then kill.</span><br>
<span>然后杀了</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはいません。</span><br>
<span>Ninja does not exist.</span><br>
<span>忍者不存在</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは吸血鬼やドラゴンと同じ空想上の生き物です。</span><br>
<span>Ninjas are the same fantasy creatures as vampires and dragons.</span><br>
<span>忍者和吸血鬼和龙一样是空想上的生物</span><br>
<span>ニンジャの格好をしてヌンチャクを振り回していると、警察に逮捕されます。</span><br>
<span>If you dress like a ninja and wield Nunchaku, you will be arrested by the police.</span><br>
<span>以忍者的穿着挥舞双节棍，会被警察逮捕</span><br>
<span>人々は本能的にニンジャを恐れているからです。</span><br>
<span>Because people are instinctively afraid of ninja.</span><br>
<span>人本能地恐惧着忍者</span><br>
<span>琥珀に閉じ込められたスリケンが発見されました。</span><br>
<span>An ancient suriken found preserved in amber.</span><br>
<span>封着手里剑的琥珀被发现</span><br>
<span>その犬はニンジャです。</span><br>
<span>The dog is ninja.</span><br>
<span>这只犬也是忍者</span><br>
<span>ニンジャとニンジャの犬はテレパシーで会話します。</span><br>
<span>Ninja and the ninja dog talk by telepathy.</span><br>
<span>忍者和忍者的犬能以心灵感应对话</span><br>
<span>この蛸もニンジャです。</span><br>
<span>This octopus is also a ninja.</span><br>
<span>这只章鱼也是忍者</span><br>
<span>ニンジャとニンジャの蛸はテレパシーで会話します。</span><br>
<span>Ninja and the ninja octopus talk by telepathy.</span><br>
<span>忍者和忍者的章鱼能以心灵感应对话</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは天井裏に隠れていました。</span><br>
<span>The ninja was hiding behind the ceiling.</span><br>
<span>忍者藏在天花板里侧</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは冷蔵庫の中に隠れていました。</span><br>
<span>Ninja was hiding in the refrigerator.</span><br>
<span>忍者藏在冰箱中</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはタクシー運転手に偽装していました。</span><br>
<span>Ninja was disguised as a taxi driver.</span><br>
<span>忍者伪装成taxi驾驶员</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは女子高の教師になりすましていました。</span><br>
<span>Ninja was impersonating a girl’s high school teacher.</span><br>
<span>忍者成为女子高中的教师</span><br>
<span>官房長官もニンジャでした。</span><br>
<span>The chief secretary was also a ninja.</span><br>
<span>官方长官也是忍者</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは他人の影の中に潜みます。</span><br>
<span>Ninja hides in shadows of others.</span><br>
<span>忍者潜入在他人的影中</span><br>
<span>ニンジャの投げたクナイが影に刺さると、あなたは金縛りになります。</span><br>
<span>Ninja throws a kunai dart into your shadow, you get paralyzed.</span><br>
<span>忍者投掷的苦无刺到影子，你会被金缚</span><br>
<span>ニンジャのジツでタワーマンションが影の触手に覆われ、通勤困難になりました。</span><br>
<span>The tower mansion was covered with shadow tentacles by ninja’s jitsu, making commuting difficult.</span><br>
<span>忍者的术的影之触手覆盖了塔公寓，造成通勤困难</span><br>
<span>ハデス神もニンジャ。</span><br>
<span>Hades is also a ninja.</span><br>
<span>哈迪斯神也是忍者</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはとても素早い生き物です。</span><br>
<span>Ninja is a very quick creature.</span><br>
<span>忍者是极为快速的生物</span><br>
<span>ニンジャの脚力はあなたの3倍以上あります。</span><br>
<span>Ninja's leg strength is more than three times yours.</span><br>
<span>忍者的脚力是你的3倍以上</span><br>
<span>全力疾走するニンジャは色付きの風に見えます。</span><br>
<span>A ninja sprinting at full speed looks like a colored wind.</span><br>
<span>全力疾走的忍者看上去就是带色的风</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはハイウェイを走る車と並走できます。</span><br>
<span>Ninja can run side by side with cars on the highway.</span><br>
<span>忍者和高速公路的车并跑</span><br>
<span>一定速度以下になると爆発する装置がニンジャに取り付けられました。</span><br>
<span>A device has been attached to the ninja that explodes when it is below a certain speed.</span><br>
<span>跑步慢于一定速度以下就会爆炸的装置被装在忍者身上</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは歴史の影に潜んでいます。</span><br>
<span>Ninjas lurk in the shadows of history.</span><br>
<span>忍者潜伏在历史的影中</span><br>
<span>関ヶ原の戦いでは両軍に多数のニンジャが参加しました。</span><br>
<span>Many ninjas participated in both sides during the Battle of Sekibahara.</span><br>
<span>关原之战两军多数的忍者参加</span><br>
<span>テキサス独立戦争にもニンジャが関与しています。</span><br>
<span>Ninjas are also involved in the Texas Revolutionary War.</span><br>
<span>德克萨斯独立战争也和忍者有关</span><br>
<span>明智光秀はニンジャ。</span><br>
<span>Akechi Mitsuhide is a ninja.</span><br>
<span>明智光秀是忍者</span><br>
<span>織田信長もニンジャ。</span><br>
<span>Oda Nobunaga is also a ninja.</span><br>
<span>织田信长也是忍者</span><br>
<span>グローバル企業の多くはニンジャを抱えています。</span><br>
<span>Many global mega-corps have ninjas.</span><br>
<span>国际企业拥有多数的忍者</span><br>
<span>CEOもニンジャでした。</span><br>
<span>The CEO is also a ninja.</span><br>
<span>CEO也是忍者</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは寿司屋から給料を得ます。</span><br>
<span>Ninja gets a salary from a sushi bar.</span><br>
<span>忍者从寿司屋获得工资</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはスシを握ります。</span><br>
<span>Ninja makes sushi.</span><br>
<span>忍者握寿司</span><br>
<span>負傷したニンジャは、スシを食べて栄養を補給しました。</span><br>
<span>Injured ninja ate sushi to regain vigor.</span><br>
<span>负伤的忍者，能通过吃寿司补给到营养</span><br>
<span>トロに含まれているDHAが、ニンジャの神経細胞を癒します。</span><br>
<span>DHA contained in Toro heals ninja's neurons.</span><br>
<span>鲔脂所含的DHA，能治愈忍者的神经细胞</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは側転で銃弾をよけます。</span><br>
<span>Ninjas can avoid bullets by cartwheeling.</span><br>
<span>忍者用侧翻躲过子弹</span><br>
<span>世界はニンジャによって操られています。</span><br>
<span>The world is manipulated by ninjas.</span><br>
<span>世界被忍者所操控</span><br>
<span>議会、報道機関、治安維持機構、軍産複合体、宗教法人、空手家の組合などは全てニンジャに支配されています。</span><br>
<span>Parliament, media, security organization, military-industrial complex, religious corporation, Karateka union, etc. are all manipulated by ninjas.</span><br>
<span>议会、报导机关、治安维持机构、军产复合体、宗教法人、空手家的组合灯全被忍者所支配</span><br>
<span>月面にもニンジャ基地が隠されています。</span><br>
<span>There is also a ninja base on the moon.</span><br>
<span>月面也隐藏着忍者基地</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは短距離テレポートを行います。</span><br>
<span>Ninja uses short jumps.</span><br>
<span>忍者能用短距离瞬间移动</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは長距離テレポート用のポータルを開きますが、高い確率で転送者の消滅事故が起こります。</span><br>
<span>Ninjas open a portal for long-distance teleports, but there is a high probability that transferers will disappear.</span><br>
<span>忍者虽然能打开长距离跳跃用的传送门，但是高机率发生传送者的消灭事故</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは天気を操れます。</span><br>
<span>Ninja can control the weather.</span><br>
<span>忍者操控天气</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは死ぬ前にハイクを詠みます。</span><br>
<span>Ninja recites a haiku before death.</span><br>
<span>忍者死前会咏颂俳句</span><br>
<span>ニンジャと金閣寺には深い関係性があります。</span><br>
<span>Ninjas and Kinkaku Temple have a causal connection.</span><br>
<span>忍者和金阁寺有很深的关联性</span><br>
<span>ニンジャの掌から出た神秘的な泡で警備員が溶かされました。</span><br>
<span>The guards were melted by a mysterious bubble from the palm of the ninja.</span><br>
<span>从忍者的掌发出的神秘的泡将警备员溶解了</span><br>
<span>ニンジャのジツのせいでが寒波にみまわれ、通勤困難になりました。</span><br>
<span>The city was hit by a cold wave because of Ninja’s Jitsu, making commuting difficult.</span><br>
<span>因为忍者的术的关系造成了寒波，造成通勤困难</span><br>
<span>ニンジャのジツにより、蟹が強くなりました。</span><br>
<span>The crab became stronger due to the Jitsu of the ninja.</span><br>
<span>忍者的术使蟹变强</span><br>
<span>ニンジャが地面に設置するマキビシは非人道兵器で、かつて大勢の無関係の被害者を生みました。</span><br>
<span>Makibishi, the object which was installed on the ground by ninja was an inhumane weapon and it created many unrelated victims.</span><br>
<span>忍者在地面设置的撒菱是非人道兵器，造成了大量无关系的被害者</span><br>
<span>それは古事記にも書かれています。</span><br>
<span>It is also written in the Kojiki, Records of Ancient Matters.</span><br>
<span>这在古事记也记载了</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはモーターサイクルの上に立って戦います。</span><br>
<span>Ninja stands on the motorcycle and fights.</span><br>
<span>忍者在机动单车上站立战斗</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは大凧に乗って空を飛びます。</span><br>
<span>Ninja flies in the sky with a big kite.</span><br>
<span>忍者用大风筝在空中飞行</span><br>
<span>ニンジャの運転するタクシーがビルに激突しました。</span><br>
<span>A taxi driven by ninja crashed into a building.</span><br>
<span>忍者驾驶的taxi和大楼激突</span><br>
<span>中にいたニンジャは無事でした。</span><br>
<span>The ninja who was inside was safe.</span><br>
<span>里面的忍者没有事</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは都知事の座を狙っています。</span><br>
<span>Ninja is aiming for Governor of the City.</span><br>
<span>忍者瞄准着都知事的座位</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはインターネットを禁止します。</span><br>
<span>Ninja bans the internet.</span><br>
<span>忍者禁止互联网</span><br>
<span>そのニンジャ投手は暗殺野球のプロフェッショナルでした。</span><br>
<span>The ninja pitcher was an assassin baseball professional.</span><br>
<span>这忍者的投手是暗杀棒球的专家</span><br>
<span>ニンジャとニンジャの犬は復讐のために共に戦います。</span><br>
<span>Ninja and the ninja dog fight together for revenge.</span><br>
<span>忍者和忍者的犬一同为复仇战斗</span><br>
<span>ニンジャの身長は20メートル近くあります。</span><br>
<span>The ninja is about 20 meters tall.</span><br>
<span>忍者的身高有今20米</span><br>
<span>殺すためです。</span><br>
<span>To kill.</span><br>
<span>为了杀</span><br>
<span>巨大なニンジャを実際に見ると、あなたは急性ニンジャリアリティショックを起こして発狂します。</span><br>
<span>When you actually see a gargantuan ninja, you will go mad with an Acute Ninja Reality Shock.</span><br>
<span>实际见到巨大的忍者，你会急性NRS（忍者真实性冲击）而发狂</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはチーターに匹敵する速度で匍匐前進しました。</span><br>
<span>The ninja crawled along at a high speed comparable to cheetahs.</span><br>
<span>忍者以和猎豹匹敌的速度匍匐前进</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはカラテチョップにより真っ二つに切断されました。</span><br>
<span>One ninja was cut into two by karate chop.</span><br>
<span>忍者被空手手刀从正中一分为二切断</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは様々な乗り物を乗りこなします。</span><br>
<span>Ninja rides various vehicles.</span><br>
<span>忍者乘在各种各样的载具上</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは高速飛行するVTOLの上に立っています。</span><br>
<span>Ninja stands on top of VTOL flying fast.</span><br>
<span>忍者站立在高速飞行的VTOL上</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは反重力バイクに乗って戦います。</span><br>
<span>Ninja fights on an anti-grav bike.</span><br>
<span>忍者乘着反重力摩托战斗</span><br>
<span>ニンジャがミサイルに乗って高速接近していますので注意してください。</span><br>
<span>WARNING!! A ninja is approaching fast, riding on a missile.</span><br>
<span>WARNING！！忍者乘着导弹高速接近请注意</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは発車直前のスペースシャトルに飛びついて乗りました。</span><br>
<span>Ninja jumped on the space shuttle just before departure.</span><br>
<span>忍者跳到发车直前的宇宙穿梭机</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは宇宙服を着ていたので無事でした。</span><br>
<span>The ninja was safe because wearing a space suit.</span><br>
<span>忍者穿着宇宙服所以没事</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは株式市場を背後から操作します。</span><br>
<span>Ninja controls the stock market from behind.</span><br>
<span>忍者在股票市场的背后进行操作</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは隠し持っていた銃で敵をヘッドショットしました。</span><br>
<span>Ninja made a headshot with a hidden gun.</span><br>
<span>忍者用隐藏的铳将敌人headshoot</span><br>
<span>ニンジャが触れるだけで、あなたは氷漬けになります。</span><br>
<span>Ninja touches, you get iced.</span><br>
<span>忍者只是触碰你，你就会冰冻</span><br>
<span>ニンジャが触れるだけで、あなたは原子分解します。</span><br>
<span>Ninja touches, you get disintegrated.</span><br>
<span>忍者只是触碰你，你就会原子分解</span><br>
<span>アケチ・ニンジャが勝利し、オダ・ニンジャの肉体の一部を奪いました。</span><br>
<span>Akechi Ninja won and took a part of Oda Ninja's body.</span><br>
<span>明智·忍者胜利，夺走了织田·忍者肉体的一部分</span><br>
<span>これが明智光秀が四本腕のニンジャである理由です。</span><br>
<span>This is why Akechi Mitsuhide is the ninja with four arms.</span><br>
<span>这是明智光秀有四支手臂的理由</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはSNSがあまり好きではありません。</span><br>
<span>Ninja doesn't like SNS.</span><br>
<span>忍者不喜欢SNS</span><br>
<span>織田信長のニンジャソウルは明智光秀から逃れ、キンカク・テンプルへと昇りました。</span><br>
<span>Oda's ninja soul escaped from Akechi' hand and ascended to the Golden Cube.</span><br>
<span>织田信长的忍者灵魂从明智光秀手中逃走，升到金阁·temple</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは情報戦を得意としています。</span><br>
<span>Ninja is good at information warfare.</span><br>
<span>忍者擅长情报战</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは周囲に存在するインターネットを知覚できます。</span><br>
<span>Ninja can perceive the Internet around.</span><br>
<span>忍者能感应到周围存在的互联网</span><br>
<span>インターネットを使う人間は惰弱だからです。</span><br>
<span>Because people who use the Internet are weak and pathetic.</span><br>
<span>使用互联网的人类是惰弱的</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは強大なるドラゴンの背にまたがって空に舞い上がります。</span><br>
<span>Ninja flies into the sky on the back of a mighty dragon.</span><br>
<span>忍者在强大的龙的背上飞舞在空中</span><br>
<span>誰にもニンジャを止めることできない。</span><br>
<span>No one can stop ninja.</span><br>
<span>谁都无法阻止忍者</span><br>
<span>伝説のカタナは古代エジプトのピラミッドの中に封印されていました。</span><br>
<span>The legendary katana was sealed in the ancient Egyptian pyramid.</span><br>
<span>传说的刀封印在古代埃及的金字塔中</span><br>
<span>聖なるヌンチャクは京都の地下遺跡に封印されていました。</span><br>
<span>The holy nunchaku was sealed in the ancient ruin in Kyoto.</span><br>
<span>圣双节棍封印在京都的地下遗迹中</span><br>
<span>聖なるヌンチャクはニンジャの三神器のひとつで、三神器が揃うと世界が滅びます。</span><br>
<span>The sacred nunchaku is one of the ninja's three sacred treasures. When all three sacred treasures are complete, the world will be destroyed.</span><br>
<span>圣双节棍是忍者的三神器之一，集齐三神器世界就会毁灭</span><br>
<span>ニンジャが光に弱いというのはただの迷信です。</span><br>
<span>Ninja's sensitivity to light is just superstition.</span><br>
<span>忍者怕光只是迷信</span><br>
<span>ニンジャの吸血鬼は日光が弱点です。</span><br>
<span>Ninja vampires are weak in sunlight.</span><br>
<span>忍者的吸血鬼的弱点是日光</span><br>
<span>ドラキュラのモデルとして有名なブラド・ツェペシュはニンジャです。</span><br>
<span>Brad Tzepesh, famous as a model of Dracula, is a ninja.</span><br>
<span>德古拉的原型有名的弗拉德·采佩什是忍者</span><br>
<span>徳川家康はニンジャではありません。</span><br>
<span>Tokugawa Ieyasu is not a ninja.</span><br>
<span>德川家康不是忍者</span><br>
<span>松尾芭蕉はニンジャではありませんが、彼の俳句はニンジャに滅びをもたらしました。</span><br>
<span>Matsuo Basho is not a ninja, but his haiku brought havoc to many ninjas.</span><br>
<span>松尾芭蕉不是忍者，他的俳句将忍者毁灭了</span><br>
<span>柳生ウォンジもニンジャではありませんが、彼は江戸時代に蘇った明智光秀を再び封印しました。</span><br>
<span>Yagyu Wonji is not a ninja, but he sent Akechi back to nether.</span><br>
<span>柳生王爾也不是忍者，他在江户时代将复苏的明智光秀再度封印</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは荒野で磔になります。</span><br>
<span>Ninja is crucified in the wilderness</span><br>
<span>忍者被磔在荒野</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは磔にした敵の前でスシを食べて拷問しました。</span><br>
<span>Ninja eats sushi and tortures in front of the crucified enemy.</span><br>
<span>忍者被磔他的敌人在其面前吃寿司来拷问</span><br>
<span>ニンジャの力を信じない場合、ホールから出て行ってください。</span><br>
<span>If you don't believe in the power of ninja, leave the hall.</span><br>
<span>不相信忍者的力量的场合，请从大厅出去</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはSNSに偽のレビュー情報を投稿します。</span><br>
<span>Ninja posts fake reviews on SNS.</span><br>
<span>忍者在SNS投稿虚伪的评价情报</span><br>
<span>ニンジャが電車内で戦ったせいで、通勤困難になりました。</span><br>
<span>The ninjas fought on the train, making commuting difficult.</span><br>
<span>忍者在电车内战斗，导致通勤困难</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはワームホールから反物質の武器を生み出します。</span><br>
<span>Ninja creates antimatter weapons from wormholes.</span><br>
<span>忍者从虫洞中生成反物质的武器</span><br>
<span>ニンジャの幽霊に触れられるとカラテを吸い取られます。</span><br>
<span>If you are touched by a ninja ghost, your karate will be drained.</span><br>
<span>忍者的幽灵通过触碰来吸取空手</span><br>
<span>ニンジャの幽霊は地面から数センチ浮いています。</span><br>
<span>Ninja ghosts are floating a few centimeters above the ground.</span><br>
<span>忍者的幽灵浮在地面上数厘米</span><br>
<span>ニンジャの幽霊なので、銃弾はその体を破壊することなく通過してしまいます。</span><br>
<span>Because they are ninja ghosts, bullets do not work.</span><br>
<span>忍者因为是幽灵，子弹无法破坏其身体只会穿过</span><br>
<span>ニンジャのスリケンとドラゴンの炎がすべてを破壊します。</span><br>
<span>Ninja's star and Dragon's flame shall destroy everything.</span><br>
<span>忍者的手里剑和龙的炎将一切破坏</span><br>
<span>ニンジャのジツのせいで、ショッピングモールにゾンビが溢れました。</span><br>
<span>The shopping mall was flooded with zombies because of the Ninja’s Jitsu.</span><br>
<span>因为忍者的术的关系，购物商场四溢着丧尸</span><br>
<span>ニンジャがボタンを押すと床が開き、失敗したビジネスマンが縦穴へ落下しました。</span><br>
<span>When Ninja pressed the button, the floor opened and the failed businessman fell into a pit.</span><br>
<span>忍者按下按钮地板打开，失败的businessman从纵穴落下</span><br>
<span>ピンク色のイルカですが、ニンジャです。</span><br>
<span>It is a pink dolphin, but it is a ninja.</span><br>
<span>粉色的海豚也是忍者</span><br>
<span>その恐竜はニンジャです。</span><br>
<span>The dinosaur is a ninja.</span><br>
<span>这恐龙也是忍者</span><br>
<span>さるかに合戦の猿と蟹はニンジャのメタファーです。</span><br>
<span>Monkey and crabs in the Monkey Crab War are ninja metaphors.</span><br>
<span>猿蟹合战是猿和蟹的忍者的隐喻</span><br>
<span>着地と同時にタイミングよく前転したので、ニンジャは無事でした。</span><br>
<span>Ninja was safe because it made a timely forward roll.</span><br>
<span>着地的同时时机把握好前翻的话，忍者就没事</span><br>
<span>「ニンジャスレイヤー™」はサイバーパンク・ニンジャアクション小説です。</span><br>
<span>NINJA SLAYER™ is a cyberpunk ninja action novel.</span><br>
<span>忍者杀手™是赛博朋克忍者动作小说</span><br>
<span>「ニンジャスレイヤー™」の読者はニンジャヘッズと呼ばれます。</span><br>
<span>The readers of NINJA SLAYER™ are called Ninja Headz.</span><br>
<span>忍者杀手™的读者被称为Ninja Headz</span><br>
<span>AIの試算によると、日本国内におけるニンジャヘッズの人数は５億人です。</span><br>
<span>According to the AI, the estimated number of Ninja Headz in Japan is 500 million.</span><br>
<span>AI试算下，日本国内的Ninja Headz有5亿人</span><br>
<span>江戸時代が終わるまでにニンジャはほぼ絶滅しました。</span><br>
<span>By the end of the Edo period, ninjas were almost extinct.</span><br>
<span>直到江户时代结束忍者几乎绝灭</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは武田信玄の埋蔵金伝説とも深い関係があります。</span><br>
<span>Ninja also has a deep connection with Takeda Shingen's buried gold legend.</span><br>
<span>忍者和武田信玄的埋藏金有很深的关系</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは一億円の入ったスポーツバッグを竹やぶに埋めました。</span><br>
<span>Ninja buried a sports bag containing 100 million yen in bamboo bush.</span><br>
<span>忍者将放着一亿円的运动包埋在竹林里</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは他社のデータセンター要塞に対して強行偵察を行い、旧世紀のIPアドレスを盗み出します。</span><br>
<span>Ninja conducts a forced reconnaissance against other mega-corps’ Data Center Fortresses and steals old century</span><br>
<span>IP addresses.</span><br>
<span>忍者从他社的数据中心要塞进行强行侦查，盗走旧世纪的IP地址</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは数千年生きられます。</span><br>
<span>Ninjas can live for thousands of years.</span><br>
<span>忍者能活数千年</span><br>
<span>ニンジャの数はドージョーで増える傾向があります。</span><br>
<span>Ninjas tend to increase their numbers by training in the dojo.</span><br>
<span>忍者的数量取决于道场的增加</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは絶滅の危機に瀕し、ドージョーの数は激減しました。</span><br>
<span>Ninjas were in danger of extinction, and the number of their dojos decreased sharply.</span><br>
<span>忍者濒临绝灭的危机时，道场的数量激减</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはSNSが大好き。</span><br>
<span>Ninja likes SNS.</span><br>
<span>忍者喜欢SNS</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはSNSにカラテの動画をアップします。</span><br>
<span>Ninja uploads the video of karate on SNS.</span><br>
<span>忍者在SNS上传空手视频</span><br>
<span>ニンジャのドージョーの位置がSNSにより露見しました。</span><br>
<span>The location of the ninja dojo was revealed because of SNS.</span><br>
<span>忍者的道场位置会被SNS显露</span><br>
<span>エジプトのピラミッドの棺にはニンジャが眠っています。</span><br>
<span>Ninja is sleeping in the Egyptian pyramid casket.</span><br>
<span>埃及的金字塔的棺材中沉眠着忍者</span><br>
<span>ニンジャは鐘乳石に偽装していました。</span><br>
<span>Ninja was disguised as a stalagmite.</span><br>
<span>忍者伪装成钟乳石</span><br>
<span>ニンジャのタイピング速度は素晴らしく早い。</span><br>
<span>Ninja typing speed is amazingly fast.</span><br>
<span>忍者的输入速度很快</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはUNIXとケーブル直結してタイピング速度を加速させます。</span><br>
<span>Ninja is wired to UNIX to boost the typing speed.</span><br>
<span>忍者用缆线和UNIX直连能加速输入速度</span><br>
<span>ニンジャが触れるだけで、あなたは人間爆弾になります。</span><br>
<span>Ninja touches, you become a human bomb.</span><br>
<span>忍者只是接触你，你就会变成人类爆弹</span><br>
<span>商談に逆らった会社には、ニンジャが送り込まれます。</span><br>
<span>Ninjas are sent to companies that have refused the business negotiations.</span><br>
<span>对于违逆商谈的会社，会送去忍者</span><br>
<span>ニンジャスレイヤーはクリスマスイブの夜に誕生しました。</span><br>
<span>Ninja Slayer was born on the night of Christmas Eve.</span><br>
<span>忍者杀手在圣诞夜诞生</span><br>
<span>ニンジャスレイヤーはニンジャを殺すニンジャです。</span><br>
<span>Ninja Slayer is a ninja that kills ninjas.</span><br>
<span>忍者杀手是杀死忍者的忍者</span><br>
</p><p><b>水边井: </b><br>
<span>太mind fuck了</span><br>
</p><p><b>kos_mos: </b><br>
<span>来点带图的</span><br>
<span>ニンジャはいます。</span><br>
<span>Ninja is real.</span><br>
<span>忍者是真实存在的</span><br>
<img src="http://wx1.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5yspi44lj20u011ib29.jpg" title="http://wx1.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5yspi44lj20u011ib29.jpg"><br>
<span>ニンジャはスシが大好き。</span><br>
<span>Ninja likes sushi, which is a perfect food.</span><br>
<span>忍者喜欢寿司，是完全食品</span><br>
<img src="http://wx3.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5yspt9bnj21900u0kjl.jpg" title="http://wx3.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5yspt9bnj21900u0kjl.jpg"><br>
<span>ニンジャ同士が出会うと、アイサツします。</span><br>
<span>When the ninjas meet, they bow and introduce themselves.</span><br>
<span>当忍者相遇时，他们自我介绍</span><br>
<span>जब नन्हें मिलते हैं, तो वे झुककर अपना परिचय देते हैं।</span><br>
<img src="http://wx1.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5yspytbsj20u0190x6p.jpg" title="http://wx1.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5yspytbsj20u0190x6p.jpg"><br>
<span>その後で、殺します。</span><br>
<span>Then kill.</span><br>
<span>然后杀了</span><br>
<span>फिर मार देते हैं।</span><br>
<img src="http://wx3.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5ysrb2blj21900u0b2b.jpg" title="http://wx3.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5ysrb2blj21900u0b2b.jpg"><br>
<span>ニンジャは死ぬと爆発四散します。</span><br>
<span>When ninja dies, it explodes.</span><br>
<span>当忍者死亡时，它会爆炸。</span><br>
<span>जब निंजा मर जाता है, तो यह विस्फोट हो जाता है।</span><br>
<img src="http://wx2.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5ysqzmlhj20u01907wj.jpg" title="http://wx2.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5ysqzmlhj20u01907wj.jpg"><br>
<span>ニンジャはいます。</span><br>
<span>Ninja is real.</span><br>
<span>忍者是真实存在的</span><br>
<img src="http://wx4.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5yxrbi8vj20u011i1ky.jpg" title="http://wx4.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5yxrbi8vj20u011i1ky.jpg"><br>
<span>ニンジャはスシが大好き。</span><br>
<span>Ninja likes sushi, which is a perfect food.</span><br>
<span>忍者喜欢寿司，是完全食品</span><br>
<img src="http://wx3.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5yxqz0xfj21900u0kjl.jpg" title="http://wx3.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5yxqz0xfj21900u0kjl.jpg"><br>
<span>ニンジャ同士が出会うと、アイサツします。</span><br>
<span>When the ninjas meet, they bow and introduce themselves.</span><br>
<span>忍者之间相遇会互相自我介绍</span><br>
<img src="http://wx1.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5yxreo29j21900u0u0x.jpg" title="http://wx1.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5yxreo29j21900u0u0x.jpg"><br>
<span>その後で、殺します。</span><br>
<span>Then kill.</span><br>
<span>然后杀了</span><br>
<img src="http://wx1.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5yxsrgmdj21900u07wj.jpg" title="http://wx1.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5yxsrgmdj21900u07wj.jpg"><br>
<span>ニンジャは死ぬと爆発四散します。</span><br>
<span>When ninja dies, it explodes.</span><br>
<span>忍者死了会爆発四散</span><br>
<img src="http://wx1.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5yxrju7dj21900u0x6p.jpg" title="http://wx1.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5yxrju7dj21900u0x6p.jpg"><br>
<span>ニンジャはいます。</span><br>
<span>Ninja is real.</span><br>
<span>忍者是真实存在的</span><br>
<img src="http://wx1.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z0x5jyuj20u011i1kx.jpg" title="http://wx1.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z0x5jyuj20u011i1kx.jpg"><br>
<span>ニンジャの大部分は、ほ乳類です。</span><br>
<span>The majority of ninjas are mammals.</span><br>
<span>忍者的大部分是哺乳类</span><br>
<img src="http://wx3.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z0wnp7uj21900u019d.jpg" title="http://wx3.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z0wnp7uj21900u019d.jpg"><br>
<span>ニンジャはスシが大好き。</span><br>
<span>Ninja likes sushi, which is a perfect food.</span><br>
<span>忍者喜欢寿司，是完全食品</span><br>
<img src="http://wx1.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z16d0fnj21900u0kjl.jpg" title="http://wx1.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z16d0fnj21900u0kjl.jpg"><br>
<span>ニンジャ同士が出会うと、アイサツします。</span><br>
<span>When the ninjas meet, they bow and introduce themselves.</span><br>
<span>忍者之间相遇时会互相自我介绍</span><br>
<img src="http://wx4.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z0xwr20j20u0190x6p.jpg" title="http://wx4.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z0xwr20j20u0190x6p.jpg"><br>
<span>その後で、殺します。</span><br>
<span>Then kill.</span><br>
<span>然后杀了</span><br>
<img src="http://wx2.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z1nyvdxj20u011ib29.jpg" title="http://wx2.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z1nyvdxj20u011ib29.jpg"><br>
<span>ニンジャは死ぬと爆発四散します。</span><br>
<span>When ninja dies, it explodes.</span><br>
<span>忍者死了会爆発四散</span><br>
<img src="http://wx3.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z0xkpexj21900u0x6p.jpg" title="http://wx3.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z0xkpexj21900u0x6p.jpg"><br>
<span>ニンジャはいます。</span><br>
<span>Ninja is real.</span><br>
<span>忍者是真实存在的</span><br>
<img src="http://wx4.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z5779zdj20u01b7hdt.jpg" title="http://wx4.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z5779zdj20u01b7hdt.jpg"><br>
<span>ニンジャの大部分は、ほ乳類です。</span><br>
<span>The majority of ninjas are mammals.</span><br>
<span>忍者的大部分是哺乳类</span><br>
<img src="http://wx3.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z4wxz33j21900u0kjl.jpg" title="http://wx3.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z4wxz33j21900u0kjl.jpg"><br>
<span>その犬はニンジャです。</span><br>
<span>The dog is ninja.</span><br>
<span>这只犬是忍者</span><br>
<img src="http://wx4.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z4ytwlej20u0190e83.jpg" title="http://wx4.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z4ytwlej20u0190e83.jpg"><br>
<span>ニンジャとニンジャの犬はテレパシーで会話します。</span><br>
<span>Ninja and the ninja dog talk by telepathy.</span><br>
<span>忍者和忍者的犬能以心灵感应对话</span><br>
<img src="http://wx2.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z4zhhq5j20u0190npg.jpg" title="http://wx2.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z4zhhq5j20u0190npg.jpg"><br>
<span>ニンジャとニンジャの犬は復讐のために共に戦います。</span><br>
<span>Ninja and Ninja dogs fight together for revenge.</span><br>
<span>忍者和忍者的犬一同为了复仇战斗</span><br>
<img src="http://wx3.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z4x2au7j20u0140b29.jpg" title="http://wx3.sinaimg.cn/large/8165d3c2gy1gg5z4x2au7j20u0140b29.jpg"><br>
</p><p><b>若菜: </b><br>
<span>过于生草，粉红色的海豚也是忍者</span><br>
</p><p><b>kos_mos: </b><br>
<span>若菜 发表于 2020-6-26 21:16</span><br>
<span>过于生草，粉红色的海豚也是忍者</span><br>
<span>◆忍◆ ニンジャ名鑑#0148 【マインドキル】 ◆殺◆</span><br>
<span>サワタリ・カンパニー社員。ピンクのイルカ型バイオニンジャで、マインド攻撃の力を持つ。非ニンジャの社員、モニカと強い信頼関係を築いている。普段のコミュニケーションはヘッドギアから頭上に投射する漢字ホロ装置を用いる。</span><br>
<span>◆忍◆ 忍者名鑑#0148 【Mind kill】 ◆殺◆</span><br>
<span>沢渡·company社员，粉色的海豚型生化忍者，拥有Mind攻击的力量。与非忍者的社员，莫妮卡构筑了强力的信赖关系。平时交流用head gear从头上投射汉字全息投影装置。</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1944012[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
