<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>穿越小说归外野：杰里·波奈尔的耶尼切里系列有中文版吗？</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>穿越小说归外野：杰里·波奈尔的耶尼切里系列有中文版吗？</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 18:17:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>穿越小说归外野：杰里·波奈尔的耶尼切里系列有中文版吗？[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1853812-1-1.html</link>
      <description>穿越小说归外野：杰里·波奈尔的耶尼切里系列有中文版吗？&#13;
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Janissaries_series
&#13;
A small force of mostly American troops, mercenaries under a secret CIA contract in Africa during the Cold War about to be annihilated by a Cuban military force, is "rescued" by the Shalnukskis, extraterrestrial beings part of an interstellar Confederation who offer them their lives in exchange for service on a primitive planet raising surinomaz ("madweed"), a plant used to produce a recreational drug. The primitive planet, called Tran, is populated by other humans of terrestrial origin, who have been secretly brought there at 600 year intervals over the past several thousand years of Earth history for the same purpose. In the Confederation, humans are a slave soldier and administrator class vaguely similar to the Janissary soldiers of the Ottoman Turkish Empire, hence the name of the first novel and the series.
&#13;
The series of novels describe how these 20th-century soldiers proceed to both integrate with the existing cultures on Tran and use them to establish a base of operations for growing and harvesting of the surinomaz plant, which only becomes sufficiently potent for use as a recreational drug for a couple of decades out of every 600 Earth years. The first book shows how the soldiers use a combination of modern weaponry, knowledge of technology, and advanced military tactics to carve out a political enclave that will enable them to fulfill the rest of their mission, to raise the madweed they are expected to provide to the extraterrestrials who brought them to Tran. The subsequent books illustrate the further adventures of the human soldiers as they perform their mission, but also begin to raise the standard of civilization and the level of technology among the disparate cultures of the humans on Tran.
&#13;
As the mercenaries learn more of the history of Tran, it also becomes clear that they will eventually be betrayed by their benefactors, as this has been the fate of each generation of imported soldiers in turn. Their leader, Rick Galloway, begins to plan how they, and more important, the knowledge they have brought to Tran, will survive that betrayal, which involves the Shalnukskis using atomic bombs to destroy the areas of the planet controlled by the mercenaries. There are local legends of sky gods who bring gifts, but always take them back again; dragons melting a city with skyfire (a tapestry in the Great Hall of a castle prominently features this); and taboo places, including a lake with a glass bottom. Galloway, his native wife Tylara (the Eqetassa of Chelm), and the "wife" of the human pilot who brought the Terrans to Tran, Gwen Tremaine, are determined that the knowledge that will allow Tran to climb beyond the Late Roman Empire level will survive the inevitable bombings. Once the Shalnukskis have gone, they will not return for 600 years; and as Galloway points out, in 100 years Earth went from the steam engine to landing on the Moon.
&#13;
At the same time, forces beyond their control and of which they have no knowledge begin to plan for what appears to be a possible revolt of all humans in the Confederation, which would have drastic consequences for Earth. 　　剧情概要：镜像版的《光明王》——人类被外星人从地球掠到外星上当屯田兵然后每六百年被外星人用核弹轰炸一轮，直到有一天外星人不长眼抓了一伙CIA的雇佣兵、然后这伙人开始带领人类屯田兵造反的故事。
&#13;
　　这个三部曲有中文版吗？</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>heisenberg: </b><br>
<span>穿越小说归外野：杰里·波奈尔的耶尼切里系列有中文版吗？</span><br>
<span>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Janissaries_series</span><br>
<span>A small force of mostly American troops, mercenaries under a secret CIA contract in Africa during the Cold War about to be annihilated by a Cuban military force, is "rescued" by the Shalnukskis, extraterrestrial beings part of an interstellar Confederation who offer them their lives in exchange for service on a primitive planet raising surinomaz ("madweed"), a plant used to produce a recreational drug. The primitive planet, called Tran, is populated by other humans of terrestrial origin, who have been secretly brought there at 600 year intervals over the past several thousand years of Earth history for the same purpose. In the Confederation, humans are a slave soldier and administrator class vaguely similar to the Janissary soldiers of the Ottoman Turkish Empire, hence the name of the first novel and the series.</span><br>
<span>The series of novels describe how these 20th-century soldiers proceed to both integrate with the existing cultures on Tran and use them to establish a base of operations for growing and harvesting of the surinomaz plant, which only becomes sufficiently potent for use as a recreational drug for a couple of decades out of every 600 Earth years. The first book shows how the soldiers use a combination of modern weaponry, knowledge of technology, and advanced military tactics to carve out a political enclave that will enable them to fulfill the rest of their mission, to raise the madweed they are expected to provide to the extraterrestrials who brought them to Tran. The subsequent books illustrate the further adventures of the human soldiers as they perform their mission, but also begin to raise the standard of civilization and the level of technology among the disparate cultures of the humans on Tran.</span><br>
<span>As the mercenaries learn more of the history of Tran, it also becomes clear that they will eventually be betrayed by their benefactors, as this has been the fate of each generation of imported soldiers in turn. Their leader, Rick Galloway, begins to plan how they, and more important, the knowledge they have brought to Tran, will survive that betrayal, which involves the Shalnukskis using atomic bombs to destroy the areas of the planet controlled by the mercenaries. There are local legends of sky gods who bring gifts, but always take them back again; dragons melting a city with skyfire (a tapestry in the Great Hall of a castle prominently features this); and taboo places, including a lake with a glass bottom. Galloway, his native wife Tylara (the Eqetassa of Chelm), and the "wife" of the human pilot who brought the Terrans to Tran, Gwen Tremaine, are determined that the knowledge that will allow Tran to climb beyond the Late Roman Empire level will survive the inevitable bombings. Once the Shalnukskis have gone, they will not return for 600 years; and as Galloway points out, in 100 years Earth went from the steam engine to landing on the Moon.</span><br>
<span>At the same time, forces beyond their control and of which they have no knowledge begin to plan for what appears to be a possible revolt of all humans in the Confederation, which would have drastic consequences for Earth. 　　剧情概要：镜像版的《光明王》——人类被外星人从地球掠到外星上当屯田兵然后每六百年被外星人用核弹轰炸一轮，直到有一天外星人不长眼抓了一伙CIA的雇佣兵、然后这伙人开始带领人类屯田兵造反的故事。</span><br>
<span>　　这个三部曲有中文版吗？</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1853812[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
