<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>如果中国、巴基斯坦和斯里兰卡同时攻击印度，他们要花...</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>如果中国、巴基斯坦和斯里兰卡同时攻击印度，他们要花...</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 19:36:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>如果中国、巴基斯坦和斯里兰卡同时攻击印度，他们要花...[100-150]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1841166-1-1.html</link>
      <description>如果中国、巴基斯坦和斯里兰卡同时攻击印度，他们要花...&#13;
If China, Pakistan and Sri Lanka attack India at the same time, how long will it take them to defeat India?
&#13;
如果中国、巴基斯坦和斯里兰卡同时攻击印度，他们要花多长时间才能打败印度？
&#13;
http://img.ltaaa.com/uploadfile/thumb/2019/06/21//1561080505845.jpg
&#13;
评论翻译
&#13;
原创翻译：龙腾网 http://www.ltaaa.com 翻译：squart 转载请注明出处
&#13;
论坛地址：http://www.ltaaa.com/bbs/thread-486873-1-1.html
&#13;
接上篇：如果中国和巴基斯坦同时进攻印度，印度会怎么样？类似提问，但是加上了斯里兰卡。
&#13;
回答一：
&#13;
Balaji Viswanathan
&#13;
The result will be a stalemate. Here iswhy:
&#13;
这场战争最终会演变成一场僵局。原因如下：
&#13;
First, let us take the low hanging fruit:Sri Lanka. Lankans received massive help from India to prevail over LTTE andend the civil war. The help included military (logistics, patrolling, arms),diplomatic (banning LTTE in Western nations) and political (prevailing overTamilnadu's political parties). Indian central government is the only that canprevail over certain jigoist Tamil groups. Thus, if SL distracts Indian centralgovernment in any way, Tamil nationalist groups could send SL into a massivechaos and civil war. Thus, no way SL would mess with India.
&#13;
首先，我们从最容易实现的目标开始：斯里兰卡。在印度的大力帮助下，斯里兰卡人战胜了泰米尔猛虎组织，结束了内战，印度的帮助包括军事上（后勤、巡逻、武器）、外交上（在西方国家，禁止了猛虎组织）和政治上（让泰米尔纳德邦政党承认这一点）。印度中央政府是唯一能控制某些泰米尔极端组织的政府。因此，如果斯里兰卡敢用任何方式来对印度施加压力，泰米尔民族主义组织可能会给斯里兰卡送上一场大规模的混乱和内战。因此，斯里兰卡是没有办法干扰印度的。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/85/28785/comment-1.jpg
&#13;
Thus, a Pakistan-China axis will neverreally work against India. The resulting mutual destruction is what preventingsuch an alliance from already happening.
&#13;
因此，中国和巴基斯坦永远不会真正攻击印度，这种行为会产生的破坏性后果正是阻止这种事情发生的原因。
&#13;
回答二：
&#13;
Chaitanya Belwal
&#13;
Chaitanya Belwal, Experienced withTechnology and Defense matters
&#13;
While this may me a hypothetical scenario,it figures quite prominently in the Indian military's war scenario. Past newssuggest that the Indian military has always accounted for a 2-front war withChina and Pakistan.
&#13;
Let’s keep Sri Lanka outof this since its military is not large enough to pose a serious threat (Nooffence to the Sri Lankans, but it took them 30 years to get rid of the LTTE,an objective that was almost achieved in 3 years by 4 divisions of the Indianarmy. Contrary to popular perceptions (as presented here) the reality of aSino-Pak-Indo conflict are quite different.
&#13;
虽然这只是一种假设的情况，但在印度军方的预案里，这是最常见的假设。过去的消息表明，印度军方一直在为同时与中国和巴基斯坦两线作战做准备。
&#13;
我们先把斯里兰卡排除出去，因为斯里兰卡的军事实力不够，没法对印度构成威胁。（没有冒犯斯里兰卡人的意思，但斯里兰卡花了30年时间，才解决掉泰米尔猛虎组织。而几乎是一样的目标，印度陆军的4个师只用了3年时间就做到了这一点。）
&#13;
但与大部分人的看法不一样的是，印度与中国和巴基斯坦的冲突情况可能不太一样：
&#13;
First I differ with one poster who comparesthe Chinese Military (CM) as a world-class boxer, India as street cop andPakistan as a brother to the street cop. If there is one 1000 lb Gorilla (orthe boxer) in the room of world's military powers, it is the US military. Therest, including China, are nothing but street cops with varying degree ofweapons and strength. To reason why, one only has to see that each US Navy CVN(Nuclear carrier) is the 20th largest air force in the world, having some ofthe most sophisticated aircraft , and there are 11 of them. And we are not eventalking about the USAF.
&#13;
首先，我有一个和大家不太一样的比喻，中国军队，我把它比作是世界级别的拳击手，印度，街头警察，巴基斯坦，同样是街头警察。如果，这些世界军事强国所处的房间里有一只1000磅的大猩猩的话，那就是美国军队。其他国家，包括中国，只不过是拥有不同级别武器和力量的街头警察。我解释一下，我们只需要看一下美国海军的核动力航空母舰，每一艘核动力航空母舰都是世界排名第20的空军，拥有一些最先进的飞机，而美国这样的航空母舰就有11艘，这还没有说道美国的空军。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/85/28785/comment-2.jpg
&#13;
Regarding the Navy, though China may have adecent blue water capability it does not yet have the numbers or the experienceto sustain operations in the backyard of the Indian Navy, the 2nd largest Navyin Asia. Indian Navy's 2 Carrier Battle Groups will pose a serious offensivethreat to the surface fleet of both the Pakistan and Chinese navies. A naval blockadeof India is unthinkable since this will bring the entire surface fleet of thePLAN and PN within strike range of shore based bombers and strike aircraft ofthe Indian Navy and air force. Unlike the US Navy or even the Royal Navy, PLANlacks the air support firepower needed to protect its fleet from offensiveground based air operations.
&#13;
在海军方面，虽然中国有一定的蓝海海军实力，但它如果想要在印度海军（亚洲第二大海军）的后院维持作战的话，它的数量和经验都不足够。印度海军的2个航母战斗群将对巴基斯坦和中国海军的水面舰队构成严重的威胁，而且，想要对印度海军进行封锁也是不可能的，因为实施封锁的水面舰艇会进入印度海军和空军的轰炸机和攻击机的打击范围之内，（它们）与美国海军甚至是英国皇家海军不同的是，它们缺乏保护其舰队免受地面攻击所需的空中支援火力。
&#13;
The PLAAF has a distinct advantage, atleast on paper. With 3000+ combat aircraft supported by mid-air refuellers thePLAAF is a force to recon with. However apart from 250+ SU30MKK’s, 200+Su-27s and 200+ JF-17’s rest of these aircraft are vintage Chinese variants of MiG 19 andMiG 21s. In the context of Sino-Indian conflict, China has primarily 6 airbasesto launch strike aircraft from. However, all of these have altitudes in excessof 4000 ft, which means the strike aircraft taking off will be carrying lesserpayload. A PLAAF Su-30MKK for example, will take off with 6 AA missiles ratherthan 8. All IAF airbases bordering China primarily those in Bareilly, Tezpur,Hindon and Bagdodra, are at near sea level allowing Indian Su30MKI to takeoffat full payload.
&#13;
至少在纸面数据上，中国空军具有明显的优势，它们拥有3000多架战斗机，有空中加油机能够提供支援。然而，除了250多架苏30、200多架苏27以及200多架JF-17之外，其余的飞机都是中国由米格19和米格21改型来的老旧机种。如果中国和印度发生冲突，中国的战斗机将在6个主要的空军基地起飞，然而，这些基地海拔都在1000米以上，这意味着这些飞机起飞时的有效载荷有限。比如中国军队的苏30只能搭载6枚防空导弹，而不是8枚，而所有与中国接壤的印度空军基地，主要包括巴雷利、泰兹普尔、印顿和巴格杜德拉，水平高度都和海平面接近，这使得印度空军的苏30战机能够满负荷起飞。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/85/28785/comment-3.jpg
&#13;
To conclude India vs China-Pakistan warwill end in stalemate at best, and won’t give any tacticalor strategic advantage to any nation. So much so that it’s motivationitself will be in doubt.
&#13;
所以，印度和中国以及巴基斯坦的战争，最终会是一场僵局，不会给任何国家带来任何方面的好处。所以这场战争发动的动机本身就会让人质疑。
&#13;
Mark Harrison
&#13;
Mark Harrison, CTO, werarewe
&#13;
Let us review the relative militarystrengths:
&#13;
China is a world class power, with astructured and trained military
&#13;
India has a military force more accustomedto 'local enforcement' actions, but not world-class
&#13;
Pakistan is like a scaled down version ofIndia, aggressive, but less disciplined.
&#13;
Sri Lanka has little military power.
&#13;
Now, suppose Pakistan, China and Sri Lankadecided to invade India. India would be most worried by China.
&#13;
让我们来看一下相关国家的军事实力：
&#13;
中国是一个世界级的大国，拥有一支训练有素的军队。
&#13;
印度的军事力量更倾向于“地方执法”级别，还达不到世界级的水平。
&#13;
巴基斯坦类似一个缩小版的印度，侵略性强，但纪律性差。
&#13;
斯里兰卡几乎就没有军事力量。
&#13;
现在，假设巴基斯坦、中国和斯里兰卡决定入侵印度。印度最担心的会是中国。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-1.jpg
&#13;
However, suppose that this is not the case.Then it's a full offensive for strategic goals, with China determined to causemajor damage to India. India would be determined not to surrender. However,India might, in confusion, launch a larger than intended strike against SriLanka causing major damage. It is also likely that some Chinese offensiveswould cause collateral damage to Pakistan, which would combine with some Indiancounter-attack.
&#13;
但如果，情况并非假设的这样，中国下定决心要对印度造成重大伤害，发动对战略目标的全面进攻的话，印度将不会投降。混乱之中，印度可能会对斯里兰卡发动一场比预期更大的打击，造成重大的伤害，中国的一些进攻也可能会对巴基斯坦造成附带伤害。
&#13;
The Indian leadership would realise that,if they continued to fight China, the damage would be permanent. However, theyare a nuclear power. But then, China isa nuclear power too. Both of them would issue warnings about their intentionsto deploy nuclear weapons. Pakistan would also warn about its intentions todeploy nuclear weapons. India and China would not take this threat seriously,but Pakistan would repeat its threats. Again, India and China would point outthat nuclear weapons had a mutually assured destruction capability, but bothwould be nervous of Pakistans willingness to engage in such a strategy. Chinesecollateral damage against Pakistan would increase. As the situation escalated,the conventional battle between India and China would intensify, but both wouldremain non-nuclear.
&#13;
印度领导人这时候会意识到，如果他们继续与中国作战，将会带来永久性的伤害。然而，他们是一个核武器国家，但中国也是一个核大国。两个国家都会对对方试图使用核武器发出警告，巴基斯坦也会威胁使用核武器，但印度和中国都不会认真地对待这一威胁，巴基斯坦会一再重复它的威胁，印度和中国会不断的重申：核武器具有相互摧毁的能力，但这两个国家都会对巴基斯坦的这种姿态感到紧张。中国对巴基斯坦的附带伤害将会增加，随着局势的升级，印度和中国之间的常规战争会加剧，但两个国家都不会使用核武器。
&#13;
At this point, three other powers need tobe considered - the USA, the UK, and Russia. The USA is hostile to China andits policy towards Pakistan has swung. The USA, dominant in global militaryterms, has demonstrated this against countries like Iraq and Afghanistan, andits troops have actual military experience. So, America is feared. The UK andRussia, by comparison, have reputations, but little interest in engagingin-theatre. They are all, however, unhappy with China because of its economicdominance.
&#13;
这种情况下，还需要考虑其他三个大国的态度——美国、英国和俄罗斯。美国对中国怀有敌意，对巴基斯坦的政策也有所改变。美国在军事实力上占主导地位，在伊拉克和阿富汗等国家已经证明了这一点，它们的军队拥有实战经验。相比之下，英国和俄罗斯也有强大实力，但是对参与的兴趣很低，不过，他们都对中国的经济优势感到不满。
&#13;
Now, they realise that with India damaged,China will be dominant in Asia. They realise that this would make China adirect threat to their own strategic interests. They also know that Chinaultimately aims to take full control of Asia. They are also aware that thenuclear option would cause global devastation.
&#13;
现在，他们意识到，随着印度的受伤，中国将在亚洲占主导地位，这会让中国直接威胁到他们自己的战略利益。他们还知道，中国最终的目标是全面控制亚洲，而且他们还意识到，核战争会导致全世界的毁灭。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-2.jpg
&#13;
There is structural damage to both Indiaand China. One fourth of India needs rebuilding, but it retains sovereigntyover the land. Sri Lanka is defeated. Nepal has also taken major damage.
&#13;
印度和中国都受到了结构性的破坏，四分之一的印度需要重建，但它保留了对这片土地的主权，斯里兰卡被打败了，尼泊尔也遭受了重大损失。
&#13;
Meanwhile, Japan and Germany are rejoicingat the fact that Chinese competition has been put out of business.
&#13;
同时，日本和德国对将中国从国际贸易中挤出去感到高兴。
&#13;
Strikes me as a serious description...maybe the metaphor was unfortunate, and there may be holes in the scenario...but not a joke answer...
&#13;
我最在意的是，也许我的这个答案有点悲惨，这些假想可能有漏洞…但这个答案我不是在开玩笑。
&#13;
回答四：
&#13;
Siddhesh Shivraj
&#13;
Siddhesh Shivraj, growing up
&#13;
In the modern era i don't think it shouldlast for more than 10 days. Since this being a hypothetical question, I wouldgive it a hypothetical build up which lasts for a few days.
&#13;
DAY 1:
&#13;
In a war i guess it would be Pakistan whichwould be the first to attack India, even if all 3 wage a war together,considering Pakistan being the closest and the being a childhood rival toIndia. On the very first day, Pakistan's strategy would be using POK to makein-roads into India. Their first strategy would be using the land-ways to makeinroads to Kashmir valley.
&#13;
在现代战争中，这样的战争持续时间不会超过10天，因为这是一个假设性的问题，所以我假想一下这场战争接下来几天的走向。
&#13;
战争的第1天：
&#13;
在这场战争中，就算这三个国家是联手发动对印度的战争，但我认为巴基斯坦会是第一个攻击印度的国家，因为巴基斯坦离印度最近，也是印度一直以来的对手。在第一天时间里，巴基斯坦会直接打通一条进入印度的通道，他们的策略是通过陆路进入克什米尔山谷。
&#13;
This beginning at the start of DAY 1, alongwith invasion on the lines of Punjab and rajasthan as well, all done by thePakistan Army. Now in kashmir, The pakistani army would have to face the IndianArmy. Now moving on all ground forces are engaged in battle,meanwhile CHINA ispreparing to come onto INDIA by moving their armed forces in a hurry to thenorth-indian border.
&#13;
第一天开始，巴基斯坦军队入侵旁遮普和拉贾斯坦邦，然后在克什米尔，巴基斯坦军队遇到了印度军队。现在，所有的地面部队都参与了战斗，与此同时，中国准备把他们的武装部队快速地转移到印度北部边界地区，进入印度。
&#13;
It's a huge movement of troops which shouldtake a complete day, if not prepared in advanced. Since China is going to beinvolved in action by day 2 only as they have to move across tibet. On DAY 1itself we are having an intensified battles at the border. We have stationedour ARJUN MBT's and are using our BOFORS for shelling. By the end of DAY 1, noside has made any marginal gains not india or pakistan. China is still movingits troops into tibet, Sri Lanka on the other hand is still contemplating ifthey should resurrect a country savaged by civil war or jump into another war.
&#13;
这会是一次大规模的部队调动，如果没有提前做好准备，这需要一整天的时间，所以，中国会在第二天才开始采取大规模行动。第一天，在边境地区我们展开了一场激战，我们有阿琼主战坦克，并使用防空炮进行炮击。
&#13;
到当天结束的时候，双方在边境上都没有任何进展，当然了，印度和巴基斯坦边境除外，中国仍在调遣军队，而斯里兰卡仍在考虑是否让自己国家重新陷入内战之中，或者发动另一场战争。
&#13;
DAY 2:
&#13;
By the beginning of day 2, Pakistan hasbeen contemplating launching thier missiles, onto major Indian cities targetingcities like Delhi,Mumbai and kolkata.They would be trying to target deep intothe Indian territory. But here is the biggest problem for Pakistan. They needthier mobile launchers to be as close to the Indian territory as possible. I am petty sure they would try to usertheir missiles Ghauri and the missile systems, now these need mobile launchersas they are not compatible to be fired from a aircraft or frigate or adestroyer.
&#13;
战争的第2天：
&#13;
到了战争的第二天，巴基斯坦考虑向印度的主要城市，如德里、孟买和加尔各答发射导弹。他们会把导弹对准印度内部，但这里巴基斯坦面临的最大问题是：他们需要让导弹发射系统尽可能地靠近印度。我可以肯定，巴基斯坦会使用自己的导弹，现在，他们需要让他们的发射装置移动起来，因为这些导弹不能从战斗机或者军舰上发射。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-3.jpg
&#13;
Brahmos is the world fastest supersonicmissile which can cruise at 3 Mach easily and has a range of 300 KMS. Sukhoi 30MKI (are multi-role fighters) are primarily air to air superiority fighters andwill be flanked by our Dassault Mirage and Mig 29's for air to ground bombingwiping out SAM systems of pak. We have 180 Sukhoi 30 MKI operational at any given time and say weengage 40 to engage with Pakistan Air force along with ground force. Indiastartegy would be using 20 Sukhoi's for BRAHMOS strikes and rest 20 to backthese sukhoi's while enegaging the PAF and thier j-10's and f-16's. Our rafaleand MIG 29 are capable of handling j-10's and f-16's. PAF j10 and f-16 are notbe compared with sukoi 30 MKI whcih is a generation ahead in avionics, they candeal with our rafale and mig 29. An intense Air warfare would lead to Sukhoitaking out the missile bases at a hit rate of 90% because of brahmos missilespurely. The maximum loses which can take is lossing rafale's and sukhoi whoacted as interceptor's while 20 other sukhoi's delivered the brahmos package.
&#13;
布拉莫斯是世界上速度最快的超音速导弹，可以轻松地以3马赫的速度巡航，射程为300公里。苏30MKI多功能战斗机主要是空优战斗机，将在幻影和米格29的配合下，进行空对地轰炸，消灭巴基斯坦的导弹系统。
&#13;
我们有180架能随时参战的苏30MKI战斗机，这意味着我们可以在与巴基斯坦空战的的同时，出动40架战斗机对地面攻击。20架苏30战斗机将直接发射布拉莫斯导弹，剩下的20架战斗机在一边进行支援，同时防范中国和巴基斯坦的歼10和F16。
&#13;
我们的阵风战斗机和米格 29战斗机能够搞定歼10和F16战斗机，而苏30因为在航电方面领先一代，它可以和我们的阵风以及米格29一起，对付歼10和F16。
&#13;
由于布拉莫斯导弹的存在，一场激烈的空战之后，苏霍伊战斗机会以90%的命中率摧毁巴基斯坦的导弹基地，我们受到的最大损失可能就是那些担当截击任务的苏霍伊战斗机。
&#13;
With the Missile bases wiped out and takinga deadly hit in aerial warfare Pakistan is on its back heels on day 2 itself.pre-emptive nuclear strike is out of the question now.
&#13;
随着巴基斯坦的导弹基地被摧毁，并且在空战之中遭受到的致命打击，战争的第二天，巴基斯坦的局势已经不太好了，先发制人的核打击现在不太可能了。
&#13;
Day 3:
&#13;
Pakistan on the backfoot. Its naval forcestry to take on the Indian navy ; fails miserably because Indian Air forceswould again come into picture while handling out air to ground bombs on PNFwhile INF will use it submarines which are brahmos capable to neutralise PNF (Pakistan Naval FOrce ). Historcally Pakistan never had a great naval force.They have a good Air force but completely outdated f-16 which were superior toour force in the 90's; not now, because we have AWACS, Israeli avionics in oursystems along with our in-house BARS radar systems.
&#13;
战争的第3天：
&#13;
巴基斯坦已经落在下风了。巴基斯坦海军试图与印度海军交战，但惨遭失败，印度空军攻击巴基斯坦导弹基地的画面会重现，印度海军的布拉莫斯潜射导弹，会消灭巴基斯坦海军。巴基斯坦历史上海军实力一直不咋的，他们的空军还不错，但F16已经过时了，在90年代，他们比我们先进，现在不是了，因为我们的武器系统中预警机、以色列的航电设备以及我们自己的雷达系统。
&#13;
Air-war with china will again put thebalance in favour of Indians though china has a huge Air force, most of theplanes are the redundant. They have 200 j-10's , 70 sukhoi 30mkk, 140 j-11'sand another 70 sukhoi su-27.The j-10's and j-11's are home grown aircrafts withdomestic avionics. I strongly believe that our Sukhoi Squadron with avionicsand its BVR capability will be easily able to take over the j10 and j11's ifPLAAF plans to deploy them.
&#13;
尽管中国的空军规模庞大，但如果印度与中国进行空战，印度会再次处于有利的位置，中国大多数的战斗机都是没啥用的多余飞机，他们有200架歼10、70架苏30MKK、140架歼11，还有70架苏27战斗机。歼10和歼11是中国国产的飞机，配备了中国国产的航空电子设备。我坚信，如果中国计划部署这些飞机，拥有航电设备和超视距侦察能力的苏霍伊战斗机中队会很容易地搞定歼10 和歼11。
&#13;
But since china is smart it would surelynot use its air-force but its missile systems with full effect.China has themost feared missile systems. Below is the list of missiles they will use tocripple India’s strength points:
&#13;
Dong Feng 31 (10,000+ km)
&#13;
DF-5 (10,000+ km)
&#13;
DF-41 (10,000+ km)
&#13;
但是，中国很聪明，它肯定不会使用空军，而是充分地发挥导弹的作用。中国拥有最令人恐bu的导弹系统。
&#13;
下面是他们可以用来削弱印度实力的导弹清单：
&#13;
东风31（射程1万公里以上）
&#13;
东风-5（射程1万公里以上）
&#13;
东风41（射程1万公里以上）
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-4.jpg
&#13;
Day 4:
&#13;
By the start of day 4 we have lost majorcities in the world like delhi,beijing,shanghai and mumbai to nuclear war-fare.With the help of world diplomacy this war fare is brought to an end, a treatywould be designed between indians and chinese.
&#13;
Pakistan starts re-building the forces,prepares a retreat and china does the same on the north-east frontiers ofIndia.
&#13;
战争的第4天：
&#13;
到了这一天，因为核战争的原因，世界上一些主要城市已经没有了，比如德里、北京、上海和孟买。在全世界外交行动的帮助下，这场战争结束了。中国和印度之间将签订一项条约。
&#13;
巴基斯坦开始重整部队，准备撤退，在印度东北边境，中国也会这样做。
&#13;
Day 5
&#13;
Re building of life in all 3 countries,Human lives lost are upto 100 millions thanks to nuclear warfare.
&#13;
Reasons on why i did not even considerSri-lanka:
&#13;
1) The country has its own problems ofcivil war.
&#13;
2) Thier armed forces can reach india onlyvia sea via thier own naval forces.
&#13;
3) Sri lanka is 50 years behind India,chinaand Pak in consideration to Naval War-fare and air-warfare.
&#13;
到了第5天：
&#13;
这三个国家，都开始重建，由于核战争的发生，伤亡人数高达1亿。
&#13;
为什么我从头到尾没有考虑斯里兰卡呢？
&#13;
1、 这个国家自己有内战。
&#13;
2、 他们的武装部队只能通过他们自己的海军到达印度。
&#13;
3、 参考海战和空战，斯里兰卡落后印度、中国和巴基斯坦50年以上。</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>wuxan94: </b><br>
<span>ftqwer 发表于 2019-6-23 01:25</span><br>
<span>就美军自己的统计数据都没那么夸张。</span><br>
<span>为啥你会有王师以外的两脚牲口算人的幻觉～</span><br>
</p><p><b>松开的鞋带: </b><br>
<span>water 发表于 2019-6-21 15:51</span><br>
<span>有一点倒是没说错，阿三的坦克只需要对付巴基斯坦，中国人的坦克很难翻山过去。</span><br>
<span>即使有投入作战的，也是轻 ...</span><br>
<span>中国的新轻坦已经是怪物了吧…？</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Razer Phone, Android 8.1.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>koodooliz: </b><br>
<span>朱诺安娜 发表于 2019-6-21 18:21</span><br>
<span>说的好像三哥的米格21自己有能力升级似的</span><br>
<span>三哥的米格21bison已经升级成能打R-73和R-77的了，虽然小头椎雷达的探测距离只有60公里。</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HMD Global TA-1054, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>koodooliz: </b><br>
<span>国内还保留有不少的J-7（mig-21）。</span><br>
<span>至于Mig-19……最后的改型强-5已经在几年前全部退役了。</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HMD Global TA-1054, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>杜黑2号: </b><br>
<span>中国还有大量的米格19？？？？？强五都退役了</span><br>
</p><p><b>按时上班: </b><br>
<span>公子无咎 发表于 2019-6-22 22:41</span><br>
<span>阿三的核弹我还是有点怕的</span><br>
<span>它瞄准你的时候你不用怕，它瞄准别人的时候你才应该害怕</span><br>
</p><p><b>茗夜雨: </b><br>
<span>water 发表于 2019-6-23 00:42</span><br>
<span>抛开数量和后勤谈这个毫无意义，天国的鼠式和V型坦克还少么。</span><br>
<span>由于青藏高原的存在，注定TG无法在恒河平 ...</span><br>
<span>15这种能压倒其他主战坦克还能快反的坦克更适合这种小规模冲突</span><br>
<span>大规模高烈度战争老老实实上99系</span><br>
</p><p><b>茗夜雨: </b><br>
<span>松开的鞋带 发表于 2019-6-23 15:02</span><br>
<span>中国的新轻坦已经是怪物了吧…？</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Razer Phone, Android 8.1.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2 ...</span><br>
<span>战斗力压倒绝大多数国家主战坦克的“轻型”坦克</span><br>
</p><p><b>charjohnborne: </b><br>
<span>为什么要炸上海</span><br>
</p><p><b>phorcys02: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 phorcys02 于 2019-6-24 16:23 编辑 </span><br>
<span>water 发表于 2019-6-21 15:51</span><br>
<span>有一点倒是没说错，阿三的坦克只需要对付巴基斯坦，中国人的坦克很难翻山过去。</span><br>
<span>即使有投入作战的，也是轻 ...</span><br>
<span>9012年了阿</span><br>
<span>15式都开始全面列装了</span><br>
<span>海拔4000米 可以70km/h行进，正面杠 t90 轻松</span><br>
<span>快速反应部队24h从四川部署到拉萨，48h从河南河北部署到拉萨</span><br>
<span>有铁路运力，有野战机场有小100大型运输机阿克赛钦地区我军已经演习了好几次 500km突进了</span><br>
<span>真要开打怕不是48hPLA履带就碾到新德里了</span><br>
<span>还扯什么我军坦克过不了高原的， 快点去医院看看脑子...</span><br>
</p><p><b>乘风除火: </b><br>
<span>如此乐观的三哥都只敢YY打平</span><br>
</p><p><b>WDLEZ: </b><br>
<span>samsoncheng 发表于 2019-6-21 18:18</span><br>
<span>歼六都退役了吧，那还有歼六</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 nubia NX595J, Android 7.1.1上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2 ...</span><br>
<span>有的，土鳖至少有一千套的奸六无人机改装套件。</span><br>
</p><p><b>FuManchu: </b><br>
<span>water 发表于 2019-6-23 00:42</span><br>
<span>抛开数量和后勤谈这个毫无意义，天国的鼠式和V型坦克还少么。</span><br>
<span>由于青藏高原的存在，注定TG无法在恒河平 ...</span><br>
<span>中印并不只在西藏接壤</span><br>
</p><p><b>water: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 water 于 2019-6-24 20:30 编辑 </span><br>
<span>phorcys02 发表于 2019-6-24 16:19</span><br>
<span>water 发表于 2019-6-21 15:51</span><br>
<span>有一点倒是没说错，阿三的坦克只需要对付巴基斯坦，中国人的坦克很难翻山过 ...</span><br>
<span>运输能力是多少？</span><br>
<span>补给保障能支持多久？</span><br>
<span>能支持展开多大正面？</span><br>
<span>过去十辆轻坦加两个步兵连被一百辆重型坦克加武直围殴嘛？</span><br>
<span>劝别人看脑子前多读两本书，思考两遍再来发言。</span><br>
</p><p><b>凡人一名: </b><br>
<span>给我国军队免费的导弹实弹训练机会</span><br>
</p><p><b>phorcys02: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 phorcys02 于 2019-6-25 15:08 编辑 </span><br>
<span>water 发表于 2019-6-24 20:29</span><br>
<span>运输能力是多少？</span><br>
<span>补给保障能支持多久？</span><br>
<span>能支持展开多大正面？</span><br>
<span>像你这样的蠢货能理解啥叫补给？</span><br>
<span>西部战区在中印西部通道附近演习已经持续好几年了</span><br>
<span>每次都是机动 500km+，单位至少一个旅，</span><br>
<span>有几次甚至从中部战区一直机动到接近阿里地区</span><br>
<span>我军一个合成旅有多少战力你都不知道，逼逼个鸡儿的10辆轻坦？搞笑呢西部战区合成旅还有陆航部队</span><br>
<span>印度有个鬼重坦？t90？还不是被 15式摩擦</span><br>
<span>写作轻坦，你就以为弱了？</span><br>
<span>智障玩意</span><br>
<span>2002年的账号蠢成这样，</span><br>
</p><p><b>SilentZephyrus: </b><br>
<span>啥也别说了,Jai Hind!</span><br>
</p><p><b>stmule: </b><br>
<span>？</span><br>
<span>记得老仙的目标不是同时打一场全面战争和两场局部战争么，当真赶时间</span><br>
</p><p><b>jctc: </b><br>
<span>中国肯定失败</span><br>
<span>因为中国没有民主自由的思想</span><br>
<span>你看我这句话能拿卢比不？</span><br>
</p><p><b>响音: </b><br>
<span>water 发表于 2019-6-24 20:29</span><br>
<span>运输能力是多少？</span><br>
<span>补给保障能支持多久？</span><br>
<span>能支持展开多大正面？</span><br>
<span>你是不是看不起西部战区的努力</span><br>
<span>四川到西藏的线只要不被切断能顶整个西部战区一波流压上</span><br>
<span>那次郎动的事，几天内前线就给加强非常可怕的程度了比如超过3位数的中程和防空</span><br>
</p><p><b>water: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 water 于 2019-6-25 21:58 编辑 </span><br>
<span>phorcys02 发表于 2019-6-25 15:06</span><br>
<span>water 发表于 2019-6-24 20:29</span><br>
<span>运输能力是多少？</span><br>
<span>补给保障能支持多久？</span><br>
<span>智障玩意，</span><br>
<span>谈战争不谈补给、谈战术不谈展开面、纵深，你谈个毛战争战斗啊，纸上谈兵的中二少年。</span><br>
<span>纵深500KM+，至少一个旅以上兵力，你跟我谈和印度这种南亚大国的局部战争？你还活在1800年吧。</span><br>
<span>2015年大学还没毕业的先多读两本书再来谈战争。</span><br>
<span>惹人发笑。</span><br>
</p><p><b>water: </b><br>
<span>响音 发表于 2019-6-25 16:26</span><br>
<span>你是不是看不起西部战区的努力</span><br>
<span>四川到西藏的线只要不被切断能顶整个西部战区一波流压上</span><br>
<span>我相信以现在TG的动员力和备战水平，能支持一场对印局部战争并保证战斗胜利。</span><br>
<span>但是由于有青藏高原的天险存在，注定只能是一场局部战争。</span><br>
<span>所以印度的主要敌人还是体量不足一半的巴基斯坦，在这个前提下，印度想要取得战略胜利并不困难，就如同现在TG对蒙古或者越南一样。</span><br>
<span>再说，TG的短期战略目标并不是称霸亚洲，而是称霸东南亚。</span><br>
<span>在这个前提下，TG对印并不会投入太多资源。也注定不会是一场举国的总体战。</span><br>
</p><p><b>响音: </b><br>
<span>water 发表于 2019-6-25 22:13</span><br>
<span>我相信以现在TG的动员力和备战水平，能支持一场对印局部战争并保证战斗胜利。</span><br>
<span>但是由于有青藏高原的天险 ...</span><br>
<span>蛤？打印度战线可能不会是全线的</span><br>
<span>但是别的方向肯定是全力的</span><br>
<span>印度想要的战略胜利被某人一封信后就永远拿不到了</span><br>
<span>中国不会主动挑起战争，但是开打必然是倾国重拳一击而下，而目前来看，后勤完全可以保障</span><br>
</p><p><b>water: </b><br>
<span>响音 发表于 2019-6-25 22:33</span><br>
<span>蛤？打印度战线可能不会是全线的</span><br>
<span>但是别的方向肯定是全力的</span><br>
<span>醒醒，你去过海拔4000以上的高原么。</span><br>
<span>还全力一击，好好做你的暑假作业吧。</span><br>
</p><p><b>阿鲁卡多: </b><br>
<span>高原兵普通单兵素质可能比不过阿三 这是前线下来休病假的普通士官和我聊天透露的</span><br>
</p><p><b>solaris16661: </b><br>
<span>water 发表于 2019-6-25 22:40</span><br>
<span>醒醒，你去过海拔4000以上的高原么。</span><br>
<span>还全力一击，好好做你的暑假作业吧。 ...</span><br>
<span>我说怎么会翻起来，原来是有人吵架啊，居然5页了都没有人给你提雷霆反击又称国家意志真是外野奇迹，另外我军既定的攻击印度的大前提是三哥自己国防体系出了问题，藏南山地防御体系的山地师调出西里古里走廊并且在短期内无法返回，国际形势有利于我国收回藏南并对三哥北方国防体系可以形成一系列缓冲带的情况下，才考虑对印作战.另外，开打后20个小时如果战场海拔还有4000米算我们输，三哥赢</span><br>
</p><p><b>响音: </b><br>
<span>water 发表于 2019-6-25 22:40</span><br>
<span>醒醒，你去过海拔4000以上的高原么。</span><br>
<span>还全力一击，好好做你的暑假作业吧。 ...</span><br>
<span>笑话</span><br>
<span>你以为你不行pla就不行</span><br>
</p><p><b>water: </b><br>
<span>响音 发表于 2019-6-26 00:44</span><br>
<span>笑话</span><br>
<span>你以为你不行pla就不行</span><br>
<span>笑话。</span><br>
<span>你以为海拔4000米就像家门口小山包，喘两口气就上去了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>water: </b><br>
<span>solaris16661 发表于 2019-6-26 00:39</span><br>
<span>我说怎么会翻起来，原来是有人吵架啊，居然5页了都没有人给你提雷霆反击又称国家意志真是外野奇迹，另外 ...</span><br>
<span>我军既定的攻击印度的大前提是三哥自己国防体系出了问题。</span><br>
<span>这个讨论里并没有说到这个前提，而是说正常情况下的多方面作战。</span><br>
<span>如果是在正常情况下作战，我不认为TG会赢得战争的胜利：</span><br>
<span>因为青藏高原的存在，注定了补给困难；</span><br>
<span>补给的困难，注定了无法长期占据，而只会是惩戒性的闪电战。</span><br>
<span>而这种闪电战，注定会让TG在国际舆论上处于不利地位。</span><br>
<span>所以战争的目标：惩戒印度人，赢得国际地位提高，甚至于收复藏南，是比较难以达成的。</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1841166[100-150]</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>如果中国、巴基斯坦和斯里兰卡同时攻击印度，他们要花...[50-100]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1841166-1-1.html</link>
      <description>如果中国、巴基斯坦和斯里兰卡同时攻击印度，他们要花...&#13;
If China, Pakistan and Sri Lanka attack India at the same time, how long will it take them to defeat India?
&#13;
如果中国、巴基斯坦和斯里兰卡同时攻击印度，他们要花多长时间才能打败印度？
&#13;
http://img.ltaaa.com/uploadfile/thumb/2019/06/21//1561080505845.jpg
&#13;
评论翻译
&#13;
原创翻译：龙腾网 http://www.ltaaa.com 翻译：squart 转载请注明出处
&#13;
论坛地址：http://www.ltaaa.com/bbs/thread-486873-1-1.html
&#13;
接上篇：如果中国和巴基斯坦同时进攻印度，印度会怎么样？类似提问，但是加上了斯里兰卡。
&#13;
回答一：
&#13;
Balaji Viswanathan
&#13;
The result will be a stalemate. Here iswhy:
&#13;
这场战争最终会演变成一场僵局。原因如下：
&#13;
First, let us take the low hanging fruit:Sri Lanka. Lankans received massive help from India to prevail over LTTE andend the civil war. The help included military (logistics, patrolling, arms),diplomatic (banning LTTE in Western nations) and political (prevailing overTamilnadu's political parties). Indian central government is the only that canprevail over certain jigoist Tamil groups. Thus, if SL distracts Indian centralgovernment in any way, Tamil nationalist groups could send SL into a massivechaos and civil war. Thus, no way SL would mess with India.
&#13;
首先，我们从最容易实现的目标开始：斯里兰卡。在印度的大力帮助下，斯里兰卡人战胜了泰米尔猛虎组织，结束了内战，印度的帮助包括军事上（后勤、巡逻、武器）、外交上（在西方国家，禁止了猛虎组织）和政治上（让泰米尔纳德邦政党承认这一点）。印度中央政府是唯一能控制某些泰米尔极端组织的政府。因此，如果斯里兰卡敢用任何方式来对印度施加压力，泰米尔民族主义组织可能会给斯里兰卡送上一场大规模的混乱和内战。因此，斯里兰卡是没有办法干扰印度的。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/85/28785/comment-1.jpg
&#13;
Thus, a Pakistan-China axis will neverreally work against India. The resulting mutual destruction is what preventingsuch an alliance from already happening.
&#13;
因此，中国和巴基斯坦永远不会真正攻击印度，这种行为会产生的破坏性后果正是阻止这种事情发生的原因。
&#13;
回答二：
&#13;
Chaitanya Belwal
&#13;
Chaitanya Belwal, Experienced withTechnology and Defense matters
&#13;
While this may me a hypothetical scenario,it figures quite prominently in the Indian military's war scenario. Past newssuggest that the Indian military has always accounted for a 2-front war withChina and Pakistan.
&#13;
Let’s keep Sri Lanka outof this since its military is not large enough to pose a serious threat (Nooffence to the Sri Lankans, but it took them 30 years to get rid of the LTTE,an objective that was almost achieved in 3 years by 4 divisions of the Indianarmy. Contrary to popular perceptions (as presented here) the reality of aSino-Pak-Indo conflict are quite different.
&#13;
虽然这只是一种假设的情况，但在印度军方的预案里，这是最常见的假设。过去的消息表明，印度军方一直在为同时与中国和巴基斯坦两线作战做准备。
&#13;
我们先把斯里兰卡排除出去，因为斯里兰卡的军事实力不够，没法对印度构成威胁。（没有冒犯斯里兰卡人的意思，但斯里兰卡花了30年时间，才解决掉泰米尔猛虎组织。而几乎是一样的目标，印度陆军的4个师只用了3年时间就做到了这一点。）
&#13;
但与大部分人的看法不一样的是，印度与中国和巴基斯坦的冲突情况可能不太一样：
&#13;
First I differ with one poster who comparesthe Chinese Military (CM) as a world-class boxer, India as street cop andPakistan as a brother to the street cop. If there is one 1000 lb Gorilla (orthe boxer) in the room of world's military powers, it is the US military. Therest, including China, are nothing but street cops with varying degree ofweapons and strength. To reason why, one only has to see that each US Navy CVN(Nuclear carrier) is the 20th largest air force in the world, having some ofthe most sophisticated aircraft , and there are 11 of them. And we are not eventalking about the USAF.
&#13;
首先，我有一个和大家不太一样的比喻，中国军队，我把它比作是世界级别的拳击手，印度，街头警察，巴基斯坦，同样是街头警察。如果，这些世界军事强国所处的房间里有一只1000磅的大猩猩的话，那就是美国军队。其他国家，包括中国，只不过是拥有不同级别武器和力量的街头警察。我解释一下，我们只需要看一下美国海军的核动力航空母舰，每一艘核动力航空母舰都是世界排名第20的空军，拥有一些最先进的飞机，而美国这样的航空母舰就有11艘，这还没有说道美国的空军。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/85/28785/comment-2.jpg
&#13;
Regarding the Navy, though China may have adecent blue water capability it does not yet have the numbers or the experienceto sustain operations in the backyard of the Indian Navy, the 2nd largest Navyin Asia. Indian Navy's 2 Carrier Battle Groups will pose a serious offensivethreat to the surface fleet of both the Pakistan and Chinese navies. A naval blockadeof India is unthinkable since this will bring the entire surface fleet of thePLAN and PN within strike range of shore based bombers and strike aircraft ofthe Indian Navy and air force. Unlike the US Navy or even the Royal Navy, PLANlacks the air support firepower needed to protect its fleet from offensiveground based air operations.
&#13;
在海军方面，虽然中国有一定的蓝海海军实力，但它如果想要在印度海军（亚洲第二大海军）的后院维持作战的话，它的数量和经验都不足够。印度海军的2个航母战斗群将对巴基斯坦和中国海军的水面舰队构成严重的威胁，而且，想要对印度海军进行封锁也是不可能的，因为实施封锁的水面舰艇会进入印度海军和空军的轰炸机和攻击机的打击范围之内，（它们）与美国海军甚至是英国皇家海军不同的是，它们缺乏保护其舰队免受地面攻击所需的空中支援火力。
&#13;
The PLAAF has a distinct advantage, atleast on paper. With 3000+ combat aircraft supported by mid-air refuellers thePLAAF is a force to recon with. However apart from 250+ SU30MKK’s, 200+Su-27s and 200+ JF-17’s rest of these aircraft are vintage Chinese variants of MiG 19 andMiG 21s. In the context of Sino-Indian conflict, China has primarily 6 airbasesto launch strike aircraft from. However, all of these have altitudes in excessof 4000 ft, which means the strike aircraft taking off will be carrying lesserpayload. A PLAAF Su-30MKK for example, will take off with 6 AA missiles ratherthan 8. All IAF airbases bordering China primarily those in Bareilly, Tezpur,Hindon and Bagdodra, are at near sea level allowing Indian Su30MKI to takeoffat full payload.
&#13;
至少在纸面数据上，中国空军具有明显的优势，它们拥有3000多架战斗机，有空中加油机能够提供支援。然而，除了250多架苏30、200多架苏27以及200多架JF-17之外，其余的飞机都是中国由米格19和米格21改型来的老旧机种。如果中国和印度发生冲突，中国的战斗机将在6个主要的空军基地起飞，然而，这些基地海拔都在1000米以上，这意味着这些飞机起飞时的有效载荷有限。比如中国军队的苏30只能搭载6枚防空导弹，而不是8枚，而所有与中国接壤的印度空军基地，主要包括巴雷利、泰兹普尔、印顿和巴格杜德拉，水平高度都和海平面接近，这使得印度空军的苏30战机能够满负荷起飞。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/85/28785/comment-3.jpg
&#13;
To conclude India vs China-Pakistan warwill end in stalemate at best, and won’t give any tacticalor strategic advantage to any nation. So much so that it’s motivationitself will be in doubt.
&#13;
所以，印度和中国以及巴基斯坦的战争，最终会是一场僵局，不会给任何国家带来任何方面的好处。所以这场战争发动的动机本身就会让人质疑。
&#13;
Mark Harrison
&#13;
Mark Harrison, CTO, werarewe
&#13;
Let us review the relative militarystrengths:
&#13;
China is a world class power, with astructured and trained military
&#13;
India has a military force more accustomedto 'local enforcement' actions, but not world-class
&#13;
Pakistan is like a scaled down version ofIndia, aggressive, but less disciplined.
&#13;
Sri Lanka has little military power.
&#13;
Now, suppose Pakistan, China and Sri Lankadecided to invade India. India would be most worried by China.
&#13;
让我们来看一下相关国家的军事实力：
&#13;
中国是一个世界级的大国，拥有一支训练有素的军队。
&#13;
印度的军事力量更倾向于“地方执法”级别，还达不到世界级的水平。
&#13;
巴基斯坦类似一个缩小版的印度，侵略性强，但纪律性差。
&#13;
斯里兰卡几乎就没有军事力量。
&#13;
现在，假设巴基斯坦、中国和斯里兰卡决定入侵印度。印度最担心的会是中国。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-1.jpg
&#13;
However, suppose that this is not the case.Then it's a full offensive for strategic goals, with China determined to causemajor damage to India. India would be determined not to surrender. However,India might, in confusion, launch a larger than intended strike against SriLanka causing major damage. It is also likely that some Chinese offensiveswould cause collateral damage to Pakistan, which would combine with some Indiancounter-attack.
&#13;
但如果，情况并非假设的这样，中国下定决心要对印度造成重大伤害，发动对战略目标的全面进攻的话，印度将不会投降。混乱之中，印度可能会对斯里兰卡发动一场比预期更大的打击，造成重大的伤害，中国的一些进攻也可能会对巴基斯坦造成附带伤害。
&#13;
The Indian leadership would realise that,if they continued to fight China, the damage would be permanent. However, theyare a nuclear power. But then, China isa nuclear power too. Both of them would issue warnings about their intentionsto deploy nuclear weapons. Pakistan would also warn about its intentions todeploy nuclear weapons. India and China would not take this threat seriously,but Pakistan would repeat its threats. Again, India and China would point outthat nuclear weapons had a mutually assured destruction capability, but bothwould be nervous of Pakistans willingness to engage in such a strategy. Chinesecollateral damage against Pakistan would increase. As the situation escalated,the conventional battle between India and China would intensify, but both wouldremain non-nuclear.
&#13;
印度领导人这时候会意识到，如果他们继续与中国作战，将会带来永久性的伤害。然而，他们是一个核武器国家，但中国也是一个核大国。两个国家都会对对方试图使用核武器发出警告，巴基斯坦也会威胁使用核武器，但印度和中国都不会认真地对待这一威胁，巴基斯坦会一再重复它的威胁，印度和中国会不断的重申：核武器具有相互摧毁的能力，但这两个国家都会对巴基斯坦的这种姿态感到紧张。中国对巴基斯坦的附带伤害将会增加，随着局势的升级，印度和中国之间的常规战争会加剧，但两个国家都不会使用核武器。
&#13;
At this point, three other powers need tobe considered - the USA, the UK, and Russia. The USA is hostile to China andits policy towards Pakistan has swung. The USA, dominant in global militaryterms, has demonstrated this against countries like Iraq and Afghanistan, andits troops have actual military experience. So, America is feared. The UK andRussia, by comparison, have reputations, but little interest in engagingin-theatre. They are all, however, unhappy with China because of its economicdominance.
&#13;
这种情况下，还需要考虑其他三个大国的态度——美国、英国和俄罗斯。美国对中国怀有敌意，对巴基斯坦的政策也有所改变。美国在军事实力上占主导地位，在伊拉克和阿富汗等国家已经证明了这一点，它们的军队拥有实战经验。相比之下，英国和俄罗斯也有强大实力，但是对参与的兴趣很低，不过，他们都对中国的经济优势感到不满。
&#13;
Now, they realise that with India damaged,China will be dominant in Asia. They realise that this would make China adirect threat to their own strategic interests. They also know that Chinaultimately aims to take full control of Asia. They are also aware that thenuclear option would cause global devastation.
&#13;
现在，他们意识到，随着印度的受伤，中国将在亚洲占主导地位，这会让中国直接威胁到他们自己的战略利益。他们还知道，中国最终的目标是全面控制亚洲，而且他们还意识到，核战争会导致全世界的毁灭。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-2.jpg
&#13;
There is structural damage to both Indiaand China. One fourth of India needs rebuilding, but it retains sovereigntyover the land. Sri Lanka is defeated. Nepal has also taken major damage.
&#13;
印度和中国都受到了结构性的破坏，四分之一的印度需要重建，但它保留了对这片土地的主权，斯里兰卡被打败了，尼泊尔也遭受了重大损失。
&#13;
Meanwhile, Japan and Germany are rejoicingat the fact that Chinese competition has been put out of business.
&#13;
同时，日本和德国对将中国从国际贸易中挤出去感到高兴。
&#13;
Strikes me as a serious description...maybe the metaphor was unfortunate, and there may be holes in the scenario...but not a joke answer...
&#13;
我最在意的是，也许我的这个答案有点悲惨，这些假想可能有漏洞…但这个答案我不是在开玩笑。
&#13;
回答四：
&#13;
Siddhesh Shivraj
&#13;
Siddhesh Shivraj, growing up
&#13;
In the modern era i don't think it shouldlast for more than 10 days. Since this being a hypothetical question, I wouldgive it a hypothetical build up which lasts for a few days.
&#13;
DAY 1:
&#13;
In a war i guess it would be Pakistan whichwould be the first to attack India, even if all 3 wage a war together,considering Pakistan being the closest and the being a childhood rival toIndia. On the very first day, Pakistan's strategy would be using POK to makein-roads into India. Their first strategy would be using the land-ways to makeinroads to Kashmir valley.
&#13;
在现代战争中，这样的战争持续时间不会超过10天，因为这是一个假设性的问题，所以我假想一下这场战争接下来几天的走向。
&#13;
战争的第1天：
&#13;
在这场战争中，就算这三个国家是联手发动对印度的战争，但我认为巴基斯坦会是第一个攻击印度的国家，因为巴基斯坦离印度最近，也是印度一直以来的对手。在第一天时间里，巴基斯坦会直接打通一条进入印度的通道，他们的策略是通过陆路进入克什米尔山谷。
&#13;
This beginning at the start of DAY 1, alongwith invasion on the lines of Punjab and rajasthan as well, all done by thePakistan Army. Now in kashmir, The pakistani army would have to face the IndianArmy. Now moving on all ground forces are engaged in battle,meanwhile CHINA ispreparing to come onto INDIA by moving their armed forces in a hurry to thenorth-indian border.
&#13;
第一天开始，巴基斯坦军队入侵旁遮普和拉贾斯坦邦，然后在克什米尔，巴基斯坦军队遇到了印度军队。现在，所有的地面部队都参与了战斗，与此同时，中国准备把他们的武装部队快速地转移到印度北部边界地区，进入印度。
&#13;
It's a huge movement of troops which shouldtake a complete day, if not prepared in advanced. Since China is going to beinvolved in action by day 2 only as they have to move across tibet. On DAY 1itself we are having an intensified battles at the border. We have stationedour ARJUN MBT's and are using our BOFORS for shelling. By the end of DAY 1, noside has made any marginal gains not india or pakistan. China is still movingits troops into tibet, Sri Lanka on the other hand is still contemplating ifthey should resurrect a country savaged by civil war or jump into another war.
&#13;
这会是一次大规模的部队调动，如果没有提前做好准备，这需要一整天的时间，所以，中国会在第二天才开始采取大规模行动。第一天，在边境地区我们展开了一场激战，我们有阿琼主战坦克，并使用防空炮进行炮击。
&#13;
到当天结束的时候，双方在边境上都没有任何进展，当然了，印度和巴基斯坦边境除外，中国仍在调遣军队，而斯里兰卡仍在考虑是否让自己国家重新陷入内战之中，或者发动另一场战争。
&#13;
DAY 2:
&#13;
By the beginning of day 2, Pakistan hasbeen contemplating launching thier missiles, onto major Indian cities targetingcities like Delhi,Mumbai and kolkata.They would be trying to target deep intothe Indian territory. But here is the biggest problem for Pakistan. They needthier mobile launchers to be as close to the Indian territory as possible. I am petty sure they would try to usertheir missiles Ghauri and the missile systems, now these need mobile launchersas they are not compatible to be fired from a aircraft or frigate or adestroyer.
&#13;
战争的第2天：
&#13;
到了战争的第二天，巴基斯坦考虑向印度的主要城市，如德里、孟买和加尔各答发射导弹。他们会把导弹对准印度内部，但这里巴基斯坦面临的最大问题是：他们需要让导弹发射系统尽可能地靠近印度。我可以肯定，巴基斯坦会使用自己的导弹，现在，他们需要让他们的发射装置移动起来，因为这些导弹不能从战斗机或者军舰上发射。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-3.jpg
&#13;
Brahmos is the world fastest supersonicmissile which can cruise at 3 Mach easily and has a range of 300 KMS. Sukhoi 30MKI (are multi-role fighters) are primarily air to air superiority fighters andwill be flanked by our Dassault Mirage and Mig 29's for air to ground bombingwiping out SAM systems of pak. We have 180 Sukhoi 30 MKI operational at any given time and say weengage 40 to engage with Pakistan Air force along with ground force. Indiastartegy would be using 20 Sukhoi's for BRAHMOS strikes and rest 20 to backthese sukhoi's while enegaging the PAF and thier j-10's and f-16's. Our rafaleand MIG 29 are capable of handling j-10's and f-16's. PAF j10 and f-16 are notbe compared with sukoi 30 MKI whcih is a generation ahead in avionics, they candeal with our rafale and mig 29. An intense Air warfare would lead to Sukhoitaking out the missile bases at a hit rate of 90% because of brahmos missilespurely. The maximum loses which can take is lossing rafale's and sukhoi whoacted as interceptor's while 20 other sukhoi's delivered the brahmos package.
&#13;
布拉莫斯是世界上速度最快的超音速导弹，可以轻松地以3马赫的速度巡航，射程为300公里。苏30MKI多功能战斗机主要是空优战斗机，将在幻影和米格29的配合下，进行空对地轰炸，消灭巴基斯坦的导弹系统。
&#13;
我们有180架能随时参战的苏30MKI战斗机，这意味着我们可以在与巴基斯坦空战的的同时，出动40架战斗机对地面攻击。20架苏30战斗机将直接发射布拉莫斯导弹，剩下的20架战斗机在一边进行支援，同时防范中国和巴基斯坦的歼10和F16。
&#13;
我们的阵风战斗机和米格 29战斗机能够搞定歼10和F16战斗机，而苏30因为在航电方面领先一代，它可以和我们的阵风以及米格29一起，对付歼10和F16。
&#13;
由于布拉莫斯导弹的存在，一场激烈的空战之后，苏霍伊战斗机会以90%的命中率摧毁巴基斯坦的导弹基地，我们受到的最大损失可能就是那些担当截击任务的苏霍伊战斗机。
&#13;
With the Missile bases wiped out and takinga deadly hit in aerial warfare Pakistan is on its back heels on day 2 itself.pre-emptive nuclear strike is out of the question now.
&#13;
随着巴基斯坦的导弹基地被摧毁，并且在空战之中遭受到的致命打击，战争的第二天，巴基斯坦的局势已经不太好了，先发制人的核打击现在不太可能了。
&#13;
Day 3:
&#13;
Pakistan on the backfoot. Its naval forcestry to take on the Indian navy ; fails miserably because Indian Air forceswould again come into picture while handling out air to ground bombs on PNFwhile INF will use it submarines which are brahmos capable to neutralise PNF (Pakistan Naval FOrce ). Historcally Pakistan never had a great naval force.They have a good Air force but completely outdated f-16 which were superior toour force in the 90's; not now, because we have AWACS, Israeli avionics in oursystems along with our in-house BARS radar systems.
&#13;
战争的第3天：
&#13;
巴基斯坦已经落在下风了。巴基斯坦海军试图与印度海军交战，但惨遭失败，印度空军攻击巴基斯坦导弹基地的画面会重现，印度海军的布拉莫斯潜射导弹，会消灭巴基斯坦海军。巴基斯坦历史上海军实力一直不咋的，他们的空军还不错，但F16已经过时了，在90年代，他们比我们先进，现在不是了，因为我们的武器系统中预警机、以色列的航电设备以及我们自己的雷达系统。
&#13;
Air-war with china will again put thebalance in favour of Indians though china has a huge Air force, most of theplanes are the redundant. They have 200 j-10's , 70 sukhoi 30mkk, 140 j-11'sand another 70 sukhoi su-27.The j-10's and j-11's are home grown aircrafts withdomestic avionics. I strongly believe that our Sukhoi Squadron with avionicsand its BVR capability will be easily able to take over the j10 and j11's ifPLAAF plans to deploy them.
&#13;
尽管中国的空军规模庞大，但如果印度与中国进行空战，印度会再次处于有利的位置，中国大多数的战斗机都是没啥用的多余飞机，他们有200架歼10、70架苏30MKK、140架歼11，还有70架苏27战斗机。歼10和歼11是中国国产的飞机，配备了中国国产的航空电子设备。我坚信，如果中国计划部署这些飞机，拥有航电设备和超视距侦察能力的苏霍伊战斗机中队会很容易地搞定歼10 和歼11。
&#13;
But since china is smart it would surelynot use its air-force but its missile systems with full effect.China has themost feared missile systems. Below is the list of missiles they will use tocripple India’s strength points:
&#13;
Dong Feng 31 (10,000+ km)
&#13;
DF-5 (10,000+ km)
&#13;
DF-41 (10,000+ km)
&#13;
但是，中国很聪明，它肯定不会使用空军，而是充分地发挥导弹的作用。中国拥有最令人恐bu的导弹系统。
&#13;
下面是他们可以用来削弱印度实力的导弹清单：
&#13;
东风31（射程1万公里以上）
&#13;
东风-5（射程1万公里以上）
&#13;
东风41（射程1万公里以上）
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-4.jpg
&#13;
Day 4:
&#13;
By the start of day 4 we have lost majorcities in the world like delhi,beijing,shanghai and mumbai to nuclear war-fare.With the help of world diplomacy this war fare is brought to an end, a treatywould be designed between indians and chinese.
&#13;
Pakistan starts re-building the forces,prepares a retreat and china does the same on the north-east frontiers ofIndia.
&#13;
战争的第4天：
&#13;
到了这一天，因为核战争的原因，世界上一些主要城市已经没有了，比如德里、北京、上海和孟买。在全世界外交行动的帮助下，这场战争结束了。中国和印度之间将签订一项条约。
&#13;
巴基斯坦开始重整部队，准备撤退，在印度东北边境，中国也会这样做。
&#13;
Day 5
&#13;
Re building of life in all 3 countries,Human lives lost are upto 100 millions thanks to nuclear warfare.
&#13;
Reasons on why i did not even considerSri-lanka:
&#13;
1) The country has its own problems ofcivil war.
&#13;
2) Thier armed forces can reach india onlyvia sea via thier own naval forces.
&#13;
3) Sri lanka is 50 years behind India,chinaand Pak in consideration to Naval War-fare and air-warfare.
&#13;
到了第5天：
&#13;
这三个国家，都开始重建，由于核战争的发生，伤亡人数高达1亿。
&#13;
为什么我从头到尾没有考虑斯里兰卡呢？
&#13;
1、 这个国家自己有内战。
&#13;
2、 他们的武装部队只能通过他们自己的海军到达印度。
&#13;
3、 参考海战和空战，斯里兰卡落后印度、中国和巴基斯坦50年以上。</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>samsoncheng: </b><br>
<span>憂鬱臺灣烏龜 发表于 2019-6-21 14:54</span><br>
<span>看他们的认知：</span><br>
<span>至少在纸面数据上，中国空军具有明显的优势，它们拥有3000多架战斗机，有空中加油机能够 ...</span><br>
<span>歼六都退役了吧，那还有歼六</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 nubia NX595J, Android 7.1.1上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>朱诺安娜: </b><br>
<span>说的好像三哥的米格21自己有能力升级似的</span><br>
</p><p><b>plypjy: </b><br>
<span>我国海军真有实力封锁印度洋吗</span><br>
</p><p><b>幽远ghofar: </b><br>
<span>至少在纸面数据上，中国空军具有明显的优势，它们拥有3000多架战斗机，有空中加油机能够提供支援。然而，除了250多架苏30、200多架苏27以及200多架JF-17之外，其余的飞机都是中国由米格19和米格21改型来的老旧机种。如果中国和印度发生冲突，中国的战斗机将在6个主要的空军基地起飞，然而，这些基地海拔都在1000米以上，这意味着这些飞机起飞时的有效载荷有限。比如中国军队的苏30只能搭载6枚防空导弹，而不是8枚，而所有与中国接壤的印度空军基地，主要包括巴雷利、泰兹普尔、印顿和巴格杜德拉，水平高度都和海平面接近，这使得印度空军的苏30战机能够满负荷起飞。</span><br>
<span>神他妈米格19和米格21，这些奇怪的知识都是从哪儿来的？</span><br>
<span>我经常觉得三哥和我们活在不同的世界线</span><br>
</p><p><b>永真: </b><br>
<span>Jai Hind!</span><br>
</p><p><b>蝶梦魂: </b><br>
<span>中国和斯里兰卡一起进攻   神秘假设</span><br>
</p><p><b>失业十年: </b><br>
<span>上亿级别的难民潮</span><br>
<span>想想都恐怖</span><br>
<span>这样一想美国佬真TM好地啊，谁都跑不过去</span><br>
</p><p><b>猫?魔铃: </b><br>
<span>0330 发表于 2019-6-21 16:41</span><br>
<span>印度一部摩托车就能装一个连的人，一列火车就能装一个方面军。这投送能力，TG只能跪下唱征服了 ...</span><br>
<span>然尔这列火车到前线,战争己经结束了</span><br>
<span>— from Xiaomi MIX 2, Android 9 of S1 Next Goose v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>废狗: </b><br>
<span>失业十年 发表于 2019-6-21 19:51</span><br>
<span>上亿级别的难民潮</span><br>
<span>想想都恐怖</span><br>
<span>这样一想美国佬真TM好地啊，谁都跑不过去 ...</span><br>
<span>海拔4000-5000的山口会过滤掉其中绝大部分的</span><br>
</p><p><b>Altriaus: </b><br>
<span>话说有没有大佬把国家意志翻译成英文丢到外网去让阿三巴铁们评论一番的</span><br>
</p><p><b>万宗模: </b><br>
<span>阿三不开挂的话，这仗没法打</span><br>
</p><p><b>心二: </b><br>
<span>mintpie 发表于 2019-6-21 16:40</span><br>
<span>为什么印度人不了解一下中国对印度方向的军力部署呢？根本就没把印度当盘菜好吗？ ...</span><br>
<span>看某中印专家辩论的节目，中方就这观点，把印方气得</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MIX 2, Android 8.0.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>月神的长弓: </b><br>
<span>samsoncheng 发表于 2019-6-21 18:18</span><br>
<span>歼六都退役了吧，那还有歼六</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 nubia NX595J, Android 7.1.1上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2 ...</span><br>
<span>也许还有歼侦六没退完的？不确定……</span><br>
</p><p><b>soulburner: </b><br>
<span>心二 发表于 2019-6-21 20:53</span><br>
<span>看某中印专家辩论的节目，中方就这观点，把印方气得</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MIX 2, Android 8.0.0上的 ...</span><br>
<span>什么节目，求个链接</span><br>
</p><p><b>Marsliu: </b><br>
<span>阿三子弹炮弹到底能自己造了没？打，拿什么打？</span><br>
</p><p><b>shuishin: </b><br>
<span>幽远ghofar 发表于 2019-6-21 19:18</span><br>
<span>神他妈米格19和米格21，这些奇怪的知识都是从哪儿来的？</span><br>
<span>我经常觉得三哥和我们活在不同的世界线 ...</span><br>
<span>湾湾的论坛上这种论调也很多</span><br>
<span>有的时候我真怀疑另外一条世界线确实存在…</span><br>
</p><p><b>偶像程序员POI: </b><br>
<span>转这些弱智评论除了自慰还有什么作用</span><br>
</p><p><b>憂鬱臺灣烏龜: </b><br>
<span>samsoncheng 发表于 2019-6-21 18:18</span><br>
<span>歼六都退役了吧，那还有歼六</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 nubia NX595J, Android 7.1.1上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2 ...</span><br>
<span>你去指出错误，看三哥们信不信</span><br>
</p><p><b>憂鬱臺灣烏龜: </b><br>
<span>月神的长弓 发表于 2019-6-21 21:09</span><br>
<span>也许还有歼侦六没退完的？不确定……歼6退了十五年应该有了，就别不确定了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>太极八爪鱼: </b><br>
<span>憂鬱臺灣烏龜 发表于 2019-6-21 15:51</span><br>
<span>歼6退了十五年应该有了，就别不确定了。</span><br>
<span>所有tg战斗机要么是Mig-19改要么是Mig-21改，不是小改就是大改。比如J-20，就是J-10大改（局座语），那个J-10一看就和J-7MF很像，所以那就是J-7大改。逻辑一脉相承了对不对</span><br>
</p><p><b>谎言: </b><br>
<span>mintpie 发表于 2019-06-21 16:40:23</span><br>
<span>为什么印度人不了解一下中国对印度方向的军力部署呢？根本就没把印度当盘菜好吗？ ...因为那个地方没法部署大规模军队啊，缺少高等级公路铁路和机场，部署多了后勤根本跟不上。常规力量跨过青藏高原入侵印度是不可能的任务。发展远程投送力量，快速占领几个大型港口鸽高吞吐机场，以此为跳板入侵印度，才比较现实一点。</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>憂鬱臺灣烏龜: </b><br>
<span>太极八爪鱼 发表于 2019-6-22 07:54</span><br>
<span>所有tg战斗机要么是Mig-19改要么是Mig-21改，不是小改就是大改。比如J-20，就是J-10大改（局座语），那个 ...哈哈哈那确实还没退役，我提议：双发的就是歼6改，单发的就是歼7改</span><br>
</p><p><b>憂鬱臺灣烏龜: </b><br>
<span>太极八爪鱼 发表于 2019-6-22 07:54</span><br>
<span>所有tg战斗机要么是Mig-19改要么是Mig-21改，不是小改就是大改。比如J-20，就是J-10大改（局座语），那个 ...</span><br>
<span>所以你说错了，双发的歼20是歼6大改，至少也是歼8大改，不是歼7改</span><br>
</p><p><b>hornisse: </b><br>
<span>憂鬱臺灣烏龜 发表于 2019-6-22 08:10</span><br>
<span>所以你说错了，双发的歼20是歼6大改，至少也是歼8大改，不是歼7改</span><br>
<span>J8I不就是双发J7</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HUAWEI LYA-AL00, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.0-play</span><br>
</p><p><b>cdm: </b><br>
<span>按时上班 发表于 2019-6-21 16:21</span><br>
<span>我怎么听说斯里兰卡的恐怖分子是印度扶持的，怎么变成印度帮斯里兰卡打击恐怖分子了 ...</span><br>
<span>一开始是扶持猛虎的</span><br>
<span>然后猛虎发展起来后不满足斯里兰卡范围内的民族独立，而同时谋求印度境内的民族独立</span><br>
<span>印度就主动出兵打击</span><br>
<span>打了几年没钱撤兵了</span><br>
<span>再然后，因为确实猛虎组织被受某大国指导训练下的政府军剿灭了</span><br>
<span>印度就把剿灭的功劳也算自己头上了</span><br>
</p><p><b>cdm: </b><br>
<span>dark_templar 发表于 2019-6-21 18:03</span><br>
<span>在印度的大力帮助下，斯里兰卡人战胜了泰米尔猛虎组织，结束了内战</span><br>
<span>——你们就不吐槽这个吗 ...</span><br>
<span>印度是帮助了啊，毕竟前期大力帮助猛虎组织闹独立，后期亲自出兵被猛虎也剿灭了不少，的确付出了很多代价，然后结果</span><br>
<span>斯里兰卡政府也战胜了猛虎组织结束了内战，虽然主要依赖某大国的训练和指导。</span><br>
<span>春秋笔法也就这样了</span><br>
</p><p><b>若闲: </b><br>
<span>在这种程度的意淫上，印度还是要找美国帮忙啊…</span><br>
<span>我对阿三改观了！</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>archcross: </b><br>
<span>这顶楼都没预设个胜利条件啊，如果只是占领新德里和孟买的话，那可能不需要一周……</span><br>
</p><p><b>rubicon: </b><br>
<span>jai hindi</span><br>
</p><p><b>youjh: </b><br>
<span>失业十年 发表于 2019-6-21 19:51</span><br>
<span>上亿级别的难民潮</span><br>
<span>想想都恐怖</span><br>
<span>这样一想美国佬真TM好地啊，谁都跑不过去 ...</span><br>
<span>难民潮也就跑去东南亚那些地方吧，难不成他们还敢去中东非洲？</span><br>
</p><p><b>yhmbgm: </b><br>
<span>神他妈的1962，难不成吓得说要亡国和迁都的是我们？</span><br>
</p><p><b>wszweill: </b><br>
<span>按时上班 发表于 2019-06-21 16:21:34</span><br>
<span>我怎么听说斯里兰卡的恐怖分子是印度扶持的，怎么变成印度帮斯里兰卡打击恐怖分子了 ...没有印度帮助斯里兰卡就没有恐怖分子打，因此印度是斯里兰卡打击恐怖分子的必要条件，没问题呀</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>hcmn: </b><br>
<span>中国没有布朗弹，打出去就是直接命中，动用什么常规部队</span><br>
</p><p><b>SEIREIEI: </b><br>
<span>万宗模 发表于 2019-6-21 20:05</span><br>
<span>阿三不开挂的话，这仗没法打</span><br>
<span>但是三哥出口恒河水了啊</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HUAWEI VTR-AL00, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>Comarade_Cyril: </b><br>
<span>三哥总是谜之自信，只能说他们开心就好吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>wuxan94: </b><br>
<span>valand 发表于 2019-6-21 14:56</span><br>
<span>老毛：我想了十天也没想明白尼赫鲁为什么要搞我们</span><br>
<span>谁叫你韩战跟人打出1：30的交换比……</span><br>
</p><p><b>wl42523: </b><br>
<span>一个基建极差没有什么拿的出手的资源还有十几亿人口的国家谁敢去打他。其他不说这数以亿计的难民你打算怎么处理。这可比捅了马蜂窝还可怕。</span><br>
</p><p><b>ebuw: </b><br>
<span>显然陆军全面入侵没什么好处。主要是寻求短时间内消灭印度海空军的有生力量，并且打掉来袭弹道导弹。剩下的印度又没有工厂恢复的能力，就是等死。</span><br>
</p><p><b>无奸不吹: </b><br>
<span>如果中国和巴基斯坦一起进攻印度，为什么中国不通过中巴公路运兵呢</span><br>
</p><p><b>火星飞船: </b><br>
<span>讲真我们周边这一圈邻国对我们不太友好的，没一支强大的远程投射部队（海空火箭）都威慑力不足。就是从中国打击难易度角度讲，鉴于挨历史这些国家总体来说陆上越离中国近的地区越对挑衅中国不感兴趣，倒是没直接领受过中国军队威力的内陆、沿海地区的政治势力喜欢对中国喊打喊杀，而这些地方中国陆军确实不容易打到。具体对印度来说，新德里、孟买、加尔各答这些地方的任何一条街被远程干掉1000人的政治轰动性比整个藏南地区的印度人被清光要大多了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>茗夜雨: </b><br>
<span>water 发表于 2019-6-21 15:51</span><br>
<span>有一点倒是没说错，阿三的坦克只需要对付巴基斯坦，中国人的坦克很难翻山过去。</span><br>
<span>即使有投入作战的，也是轻 ...</span><br>
<span>这还真不好说，兔子15轻坦火力压倒印度任何一种坦克，不论是火炮威力还是火控</span><br>
<span>机动也压倒印度任何一种坦克，只有防御稍差，但也比印度人手里的大部分坦克强了</span><br>
</p><p><b>公子无咎: </b><br>
<span>阿三的核弹我还是有点怕的</span><br>
</p><p><b>Holie: </b><br>
<span>wuxan94 发表于 2019-6-22 15:55</span><br>
<span>谁叫你韩战跟人打出1：30的交换比……</span><br>
<span>一个志愿军换三十个棒子吗</span><br>
</p><p><b>leleq: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 leleq 于 2019-6-22 23:19 编辑 </span><br>
<span>看标题我还以为内容是这样的</span><br>
<span>题目：</span><br>
<span>中印发生战争如果要打赢战争</span><br>
<span>从中国进攻印度需要65天</span><br>
<span>从巴基斯坦进攻印度需要110天</span><br>
<span>从斯里兰卡进攻印度需要175天</span><br>
<span>问如果中国、巴基斯坦和斯里兰卡同时攻击印度，要花多少天</span><br>
</p><p><b>qtk9599: </b><br>
<span>太极八爪鱼 发表于 2019-6-22 07:54</span><br>
<span>所有tg战斗机要么是Mig-19改要么是Mig-21改，不是小改就是大改。比如J-20，就是J-10大改（局座语），那个 ...</span><br>
<span>不是小改就是大改，不是大改就是魔改，666～</span><br>
</p><p><b>water: </b><br>
<span>茗夜雨 发表于 2019-6-22 22:25</span><br>
<span>这还真不好说，兔子15轻坦火力压倒印度任何一种坦克，不论是火炮威力还是火控</span><br>
<span>机动也压倒印度任何一种坦 ...</span><br>
<span>抛开数量和后勤谈这个毫无意义，天国的鼠式和V型坦克还少么。</span><br>
<span>由于青藏高原的存在，注定TG无法在恒河平原展开大规模兵力，两国只会有小规模冲突。</span><br>
</p><p><b>haarp: </b><br>
<span>dark_templar 发表于 2019-6-21 18:02</span><br>
<span>错了</span><br>
<span>15可以轻松摁死阿三的任何一种坦克</span><br>
<span>而且我军现在不用C17也能把主战坦克运过山了</span><br>
</p><p><b>haarp: </b><br>
<span>leleq 发表于 2019-6-22 23:18</span><br>
<span>看标题我还以为内容是这样的</span><br>
<span>题目：</span><br>
<span>这是一道送命题</span><br>
</p><p><b>ftqwer: </b><br>
<span>wuxan94 发表于 2019-6-22 15:55</span><br>
<span>谁叫你韩战跟人打出1：30的交换比……</span><br>
<span>就美军自己的统计数据都没那么夸张。</span><br>
</p><p><b>wuxan94: </b><br>
<span>Holie 发表于 2019-6-22 22:42</span><br>
<span>一个志愿军换三十个棒子吗</span><br>
<span>当然是王师牺牲三万歼灭中朝联军百万啦～</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1841166[50-100]</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>如果中国、巴基斯坦和斯里兰卡同时攻击印度，他们要花...[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1841166-1-1.html</link>
      <description>如果中国、巴基斯坦和斯里兰卡同时攻击印度，他们要花...&#13;
If China, Pakistan and Sri Lanka attack India at the same time, how long will it take them to defeat India?
&#13;
如果中国、巴基斯坦和斯里兰卡同时攻击印度，他们要花多长时间才能打败印度？
&#13;
http://img.ltaaa.com/uploadfile/thumb/2019/06/21//1561080505845.jpg
&#13;
评论翻译
&#13;
原创翻译：龙腾网 http://www.ltaaa.com 翻译：squart 转载请注明出处
&#13;
论坛地址：http://www.ltaaa.com/bbs/thread-486873-1-1.html
&#13;
接上篇：如果中国和巴基斯坦同时进攻印度，印度会怎么样？类似提问，但是加上了斯里兰卡。
&#13;
回答一：
&#13;
Balaji Viswanathan
&#13;
The result will be a stalemate. Here iswhy:
&#13;
这场战争最终会演变成一场僵局。原因如下：
&#13;
First, let us take the low hanging fruit:Sri Lanka. Lankans received massive help from India to prevail over LTTE andend the civil war. The help included military (logistics, patrolling, arms),diplomatic (banning LTTE in Western nations) and political (prevailing overTamilnadu's political parties). Indian central government is the only that canprevail over certain jigoist Tamil groups. Thus, if SL distracts Indian centralgovernment in any way, Tamil nationalist groups could send SL into a massivechaos and civil war. Thus, no way SL would mess with India.
&#13;
首先，我们从最容易实现的目标开始：斯里兰卡。在印度的大力帮助下，斯里兰卡人战胜了泰米尔猛虎组织，结束了内战，印度的帮助包括军事上（后勤、巡逻、武器）、外交上（在西方国家，禁止了猛虎组织）和政治上（让泰米尔纳德邦政党承认这一点）。印度中央政府是唯一能控制某些泰米尔极端组织的政府。因此，如果斯里兰卡敢用任何方式来对印度施加压力，泰米尔民族主义组织可能会给斯里兰卡送上一场大规模的混乱和内战。因此，斯里兰卡是没有办法干扰印度的。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/85/28785/comment-1.jpg
&#13;
Thus, a Pakistan-China axis will neverreally work against India. The resulting mutual destruction is what preventingsuch an alliance from already happening.
&#13;
因此，中国和巴基斯坦永远不会真正攻击印度，这种行为会产生的破坏性后果正是阻止这种事情发生的原因。
&#13;
回答二：
&#13;
Chaitanya Belwal
&#13;
Chaitanya Belwal, Experienced withTechnology and Defense matters
&#13;
While this may me a hypothetical scenario,it figures quite prominently in the Indian military's war scenario. Past newssuggest that the Indian military has always accounted for a 2-front war withChina and Pakistan.
&#13;
Let’s keep Sri Lanka outof this since its military is not large enough to pose a serious threat (Nooffence to the Sri Lankans, but it took them 30 years to get rid of the LTTE,an objective that was almost achieved in 3 years by 4 divisions of the Indianarmy. Contrary to popular perceptions (as presented here) the reality of aSino-Pak-Indo conflict are quite different.
&#13;
虽然这只是一种假设的情况，但在印度军方的预案里，这是最常见的假设。过去的消息表明，印度军方一直在为同时与中国和巴基斯坦两线作战做准备。
&#13;
我们先把斯里兰卡排除出去，因为斯里兰卡的军事实力不够，没法对印度构成威胁。（没有冒犯斯里兰卡人的意思，但斯里兰卡花了30年时间，才解决掉泰米尔猛虎组织。而几乎是一样的目标，印度陆军的4个师只用了3年时间就做到了这一点。）
&#13;
但与大部分人的看法不一样的是，印度与中国和巴基斯坦的冲突情况可能不太一样：
&#13;
First I differ with one poster who comparesthe Chinese Military (CM) as a world-class boxer, India as street cop andPakistan as a brother to the street cop. If there is one 1000 lb Gorilla (orthe boxer) in the room of world's military powers, it is the US military. Therest, including China, are nothing but street cops with varying degree ofweapons and strength. To reason why, one only has to see that each US Navy CVN(Nuclear carrier) is the 20th largest air force in the world, having some ofthe most sophisticated aircraft , and there are 11 of them. And we are not eventalking about the USAF.
&#13;
首先，我有一个和大家不太一样的比喻，中国军队，我把它比作是世界级别的拳击手，印度，街头警察，巴基斯坦，同样是街头警察。如果，这些世界军事强国所处的房间里有一只1000磅的大猩猩的话，那就是美国军队。其他国家，包括中国，只不过是拥有不同级别武器和力量的街头警察。我解释一下，我们只需要看一下美国海军的核动力航空母舰，每一艘核动力航空母舰都是世界排名第20的空军，拥有一些最先进的飞机，而美国这样的航空母舰就有11艘，这还没有说道美国的空军。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/85/28785/comment-2.jpg
&#13;
Regarding the Navy, though China may have adecent blue water capability it does not yet have the numbers or the experienceto sustain operations in the backyard of the Indian Navy, the 2nd largest Navyin Asia. Indian Navy's 2 Carrier Battle Groups will pose a serious offensivethreat to the surface fleet of both the Pakistan and Chinese navies. A naval blockadeof India is unthinkable since this will bring the entire surface fleet of thePLAN and PN within strike range of shore based bombers and strike aircraft ofthe Indian Navy and air force. Unlike the US Navy or even the Royal Navy, PLANlacks the air support firepower needed to protect its fleet from offensiveground based air operations.
&#13;
在海军方面，虽然中国有一定的蓝海海军实力，但它如果想要在印度海军（亚洲第二大海军）的后院维持作战的话，它的数量和经验都不足够。印度海军的2个航母战斗群将对巴基斯坦和中国海军的水面舰队构成严重的威胁，而且，想要对印度海军进行封锁也是不可能的，因为实施封锁的水面舰艇会进入印度海军和空军的轰炸机和攻击机的打击范围之内，（它们）与美国海军甚至是英国皇家海军不同的是，它们缺乏保护其舰队免受地面攻击所需的空中支援火力。
&#13;
The PLAAF has a distinct advantage, atleast on paper. With 3000+ combat aircraft supported by mid-air refuellers thePLAAF is a force to recon with. However apart from 250+ SU30MKK’s, 200+Su-27s and 200+ JF-17’s rest of these aircraft are vintage Chinese variants of MiG 19 andMiG 21s. In the context of Sino-Indian conflict, China has primarily 6 airbasesto launch strike aircraft from. However, all of these have altitudes in excessof 4000 ft, which means the strike aircraft taking off will be carrying lesserpayload. A PLAAF Su-30MKK for example, will take off with 6 AA missiles ratherthan 8. All IAF airbases bordering China primarily those in Bareilly, Tezpur,Hindon and Bagdodra, are at near sea level allowing Indian Su30MKI to takeoffat full payload.
&#13;
至少在纸面数据上，中国空军具有明显的优势，它们拥有3000多架战斗机，有空中加油机能够提供支援。然而，除了250多架苏30、200多架苏27以及200多架JF-17之外，其余的飞机都是中国由米格19和米格21改型来的老旧机种。如果中国和印度发生冲突，中国的战斗机将在6个主要的空军基地起飞，然而，这些基地海拔都在1000米以上，这意味着这些飞机起飞时的有效载荷有限。比如中国军队的苏30只能搭载6枚防空导弹，而不是8枚，而所有与中国接壤的印度空军基地，主要包括巴雷利、泰兹普尔、印顿和巴格杜德拉，水平高度都和海平面接近，这使得印度空军的苏30战机能够满负荷起飞。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/85/28785/comment-3.jpg
&#13;
To conclude India vs China-Pakistan warwill end in stalemate at best, and won’t give any tacticalor strategic advantage to any nation. So much so that it’s motivationitself will be in doubt.
&#13;
所以，印度和中国以及巴基斯坦的战争，最终会是一场僵局，不会给任何国家带来任何方面的好处。所以这场战争发动的动机本身就会让人质疑。
&#13;
Mark Harrison
&#13;
Mark Harrison, CTO, werarewe
&#13;
Let us review the relative militarystrengths:
&#13;
China is a world class power, with astructured and trained military
&#13;
India has a military force more accustomedto 'local enforcement' actions, but not world-class
&#13;
Pakistan is like a scaled down version ofIndia, aggressive, but less disciplined.
&#13;
Sri Lanka has little military power.
&#13;
Now, suppose Pakistan, China and Sri Lankadecided to invade India. India would be most worried by China.
&#13;
让我们来看一下相关国家的军事实力：
&#13;
中国是一个世界级的大国，拥有一支训练有素的军队。
&#13;
印度的军事力量更倾向于“地方执法”级别，还达不到世界级的水平。
&#13;
巴基斯坦类似一个缩小版的印度，侵略性强，但纪律性差。
&#13;
斯里兰卡几乎就没有军事力量。
&#13;
现在，假设巴基斯坦、中国和斯里兰卡决定入侵印度。印度最担心的会是中国。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-1.jpg
&#13;
However, suppose that this is not the case.Then it's a full offensive for strategic goals, with China determined to causemajor damage to India. India would be determined not to surrender. However,India might, in confusion, launch a larger than intended strike against SriLanka causing major damage. It is also likely that some Chinese offensiveswould cause collateral damage to Pakistan, which would combine with some Indiancounter-attack.
&#13;
但如果，情况并非假设的这样，中国下定决心要对印度造成重大伤害，发动对战略目标的全面进攻的话，印度将不会投降。混乱之中，印度可能会对斯里兰卡发动一场比预期更大的打击，造成重大的伤害，中国的一些进攻也可能会对巴基斯坦造成附带伤害。
&#13;
The Indian leadership would realise that,if they continued to fight China, the damage would be permanent. However, theyare a nuclear power. But then, China isa nuclear power too. Both of them would issue warnings about their intentionsto deploy nuclear weapons. Pakistan would also warn about its intentions todeploy nuclear weapons. India and China would not take this threat seriously,but Pakistan would repeat its threats. Again, India and China would point outthat nuclear weapons had a mutually assured destruction capability, but bothwould be nervous of Pakistans willingness to engage in such a strategy. Chinesecollateral damage against Pakistan would increase. As the situation escalated,the conventional battle between India and China would intensify, but both wouldremain non-nuclear.
&#13;
印度领导人这时候会意识到，如果他们继续与中国作战，将会带来永久性的伤害。然而，他们是一个核武器国家，但中国也是一个核大国。两个国家都会对对方试图使用核武器发出警告，巴基斯坦也会威胁使用核武器，但印度和中国都不会认真地对待这一威胁，巴基斯坦会一再重复它的威胁，印度和中国会不断的重申：核武器具有相互摧毁的能力，但这两个国家都会对巴基斯坦的这种姿态感到紧张。中国对巴基斯坦的附带伤害将会增加，随着局势的升级，印度和中国之间的常规战争会加剧，但两个国家都不会使用核武器。
&#13;
At this point, three other powers need tobe considered - the USA, the UK, and Russia. The USA is hostile to China andits policy towards Pakistan has swung. The USA, dominant in global militaryterms, has demonstrated this against countries like Iraq and Afghanistan, andits troops have actual military experience. So, America is feared. The UK andRussia, by comparison, have reputations, but little interest in engagingin-theatre. They are all, however, unhappy with China because of its economicdominance.
&#13;
这种情况下，还需要考虑其他三个大国的态度——美国、英国和俄罗斯。美国对中国怀有敌意，对巴基斯坦的政策也有所改变。美国在军事实力上占主导地位，在伊拉克和阿富汗等国家已经证明了这一点，它们的军队拥有实战经验。相比之下，英国和俄罗斯也有强大实力，但是对参与的兴趣很低，不过，他们都对中国的经济优势感到不满。
&#13;
Now, they realise that with India damaged,China will be dominant in Asia. They realise that this would make China adirect threat to their own strategic interests. They also know that Chinaultimately aims to take full control of Asia. They are also aware that thenuclear option would cause global devastation.
&#13;
现在，他们意识到，随着印度的受伤，中国将在亚洲占主导地位，这会让中国直接威胁到他们自己的战略利益。他们还知道，中国最终的目标是全面控制亚洲，而且他们还意识到，核战争会导致全世界的毁灭。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-2.jpg
&#13;
There is structural damage to both Indiaand China. One fourth of India needs rebuilding, but it retains sovereigntyover the land. Sri Lanka is defeated. Nepal has also taken major damage.
&#13;
印度和中国都受到了结构性的破坏，四分之一的印度需要重建，但它保留了对这片土地的主权，斯里兰卡被打败了，尼泊尔也遭受了重大损失。
&#13;
Meanwhile, Japan and Germany are rejoicingat the fact that Chinese competition has been put out of business.
&#13;
同时，日本和德国对将中国从国际贸易中挤出去感到高兴。
&#13;
Strikes me as a serious description...maybe the metaphor was unfortunate, and there may be holes in the scenario...but not a joke answer...
&#13;
我最在意的是，也许我的这个答案有点悲惨，这些假想可能有漏洞…但这个答案我不是在开玩笑。
&#13;
回答四：
&#13;
Siddhesh Shivraj
&#13;
Siddhesh Shivraj, growing up
&#13;
In the modern era i don't think it shouldlast for more than 10 days. Since this being a hypothetical question, I wouldgive it a hypothetical build up which lasts for a few days.
&#13;
DAY 1:
&#13;
In a war i guess it would be Pakistan whichwould be the first to attack India, even if all 3 wage a war together,considering Pakistan being the closest and the being a childhood rival toIndia. On the very first day, Pakistan's strategy would be using POK to makein-roads into India. Their first strategy would be using the land-ways to makeinroads to Kashmir valley.
&#13;
在现代战争中，这样的战争持续时间不会超过10天，因为这是一个假设性的问题，所以我假想一下这场战争接下来几天的走向。
&#13;
战争的第1天：
&#13;
在这场战争中，就算这三个国家是联手发动对印度的战争，但我认为巴基斯坦会是第一个攻击印度的国家，因为巴基斯坦离印度最近，也是印度一直以来的对手。在第一天时间里，巴基斯坦会直接打通一条进入印度的通道，他们的策略是通过陆路进入克什米尔山谷。
&#13;
This beginning at the start of DAY 1, alongwith invasion on the lines of Punjab and rajasthan as well, all done by thePakistan Army. Now in kashmir, The pakistani army would have to face the IndianArmy. Now moving on all ground forces are engaged in battle,meanwhile CHINA ispreparing to come onto INDIA by moving their armed forces in a hurry to thenorth-indian border.
&#13;
第一天开始，巴基斯坦军队入侵旁遮普和拉贾斯坦邦，然后在克什米尔，巴基斯坦军队遇到了印度军队。现在，所有的地面部队都参与了战斗，与此同时，中国准备把他们的武装部队快速地转移到印度北部边界地区，进入印度。
&#13;
It's a huge movement of troops which shouldtake a complete day, if not prepared in advanced. Since China is going to beinvolved in action by day 2 only as they have to move across tibet. On DAY 1itself we are having an intensified battles at the border. We have stationedour ARJUN MBT's and are using our BOFORS for shelling. By the end of DAY 1, noside has made any marginal gains not india or pakistan. China is still movingits troops into tibet, Sri Lanka on the other hand is still contemplating ifthey should resurrect a country savaged by civil war or jump into another war.
&#13;
这会是一次大规模的部队调动，如果没有提前做好准备，这需要一整天的时间，所以，中国会在第二天才开始采取大规模行动。第一天，在边境地区我们展开了一场激战，我们有阿琼主战坦克，并使用防空炮进行炮击。
&#13;
到当天结束的时候，双方在边境上都没有任何进展，当然了，印度和巴基斯坦边境除外，中国仍在调遣军队，而斯里兰卡仍在考虑是否让自己国家重新陷入内战之中，或者发动另一场战争。
&#13;
DAY 2:
&#13;
By the beginning of day 2, Pakistan hasbeen contemplating launching thier missiles, onto major Indian cities targetingcities like Delhi,Mumbai and kolkata.They would be trying to target deep intothe Indian territory. But here is the biggest problem for Pakistan. They needthier mobile launchers to be as close to the Indian territory as possible. I am petty sure they would try to usertheir missiles Ghauri and the missile systems, now these need mobile launchersas they are not compatible to be fired from a aircraft or frigate or adestroyer.
&#13;
战争的第2天：
&#13;
到了战争的第二天，巴基斯坦考虑向印度的主要城市，如德里、孟买和加尔各答发射导弹。他们会把导弹对准印度内部，但这里巴基斯坦面临的最大问题是：他们需要让导弹发射系统尽可能地靠近印度。我可以肯定，巴基斯坦会使用自己的导弹，现在，他们需要让他们的发射装置移动起来，因为这些导弹不能从战斗机或者军舰上发射。
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-3.jpg
&#13;
Brahmos is the world fastest supersonicmissile which can cruise at 3 Mach easily and has a range of 300 KMS. Sukhoi 30MKI (are multi-role fighters) are primarily air to air superiority fighters andwill be flanked by our Dassault Mirage and Mig 29's for air to ground bombingwiping out SAM systems of pak. We have 180 Sukhoi 30 MKI operational at any given time and say weengage 40 to engage with Pakistan Air force along with ground force. Indiastartegy would be using 20 Sukhoi's for BRAHMOS strikes and rest 20 to backthese sukhoi's while enegaging the PAF and thier j-10's and f-16's. Our rafaleand MIG 29 are capable of handling j-10's and f-16's. PAF j10 and f-16 are notbe compared with sukoi 30 MKI whcih is a generation ahead in avionics, they candeal with our rafale and mig 29. An intense Air warfare would lead to Sukhoitaking out the missile bases at a hit rate of 90% because of brahmos missilespurely. The maximum loses which can take is lossing rafale's and sukhoi whoacted as interceptor's while 20 other sukhoi's delivered the brahmos package.
&#13;
布拉莫斯是世界上速度最快的超音速导弹，可以轻松地以3马赫的速度巡航，射程为300公里。苏30MKI多功能战斗机主要是空优战斗机，将在幻影和米格29的配合下，进行空对地轰炸，消灭巴基斯坦的导弹系统。
&#13;
我们有180架能随时参战的苏30MKI战斗机，这意味着我们可以在与巴基斯坦空战的的同时，出动40架战斗机对地面攻击。20架苏30战斗机将直接发射布拉莫斯导弹，剩下的20架战斗机在一边进行支援，同时防范中国和巴基斯坦的歼10和F16。
&#13;
我们的阵风战斗机和米格 29战斗机能够搞定歼10和F16战斗机，而苏30因为在航电方面领先一代，它可以和我们的阵风以及米格29一起，对付歼10和F16。
&#13;
由于布拉莫斯导弹的存在，一场激烈的空战之后，苏霍伊战斗机会以90%的命中率摧毁巴基斯坦的导弹基地，我们受到的最大损失可能就是那些担当截击任务的苏霍伊战斗机。
&#13;
With the Missile bases wiped out and takinga deadly hit in aerial warfare Pakistan is on its back heels on day 2 itself.pre-emptive nuclear strike is out of the question now.
&#13;
随着巴基斯坦的导弹基地被摧毁，并且在空战之中遭受到的致命打击，战争的第二天，巴基斯坦的局势已经不太好了，先发制人的核打击现在不太可能了。
&#13;
Day 3:
&#13;
Pakistan on the backfoot. Its naval forcestry to take on the Indian navy ; fails miserably because Indian Air forceswould again come into picture while handling out air to ground bombs on PNFwhile INF will use it submarines which are brahmos capable to neutralise PNF (Pakistan Naval FOrce ). Historcally Pakistan never had a great naval force.They have a good Air force but completely outdated f-16 which were superior toour force in the 90's; not now, because we have AWACS, Israeli avionics in oursystems along with our in-house BARS radar systems.
&#13;
战争的第3天：
&#13;
巴基斯坦已经落在下风了。巴基斯坦海军试图与印度海军交战，但惨遭失败，印度空军攻击巴基斯坦导弹基地的画面会重现，印度海军的布拉莫斯潜射导弹，会消灭巴基斯坦海军。巴基斯坦历史上海军实力一直不咋的，他们的空军还不错，但F16已经过时了，在90年代，他们比我们先进，现在不是了，因为我们的武器系统中预警机、以色列的航电设备以及我们自己的雷达系统。
&#13;
Air-war with china will again put thebalance in favour of Indians though china has a huge Air force, most of theplanes are the redundant. They have 200 j-10's , 70 sukhoi 30mkk, 140 j-11'sand another 70 sukhoi su-27.The j-10's and j-11's are home grown aircrafts withdomestic avionics. I strongly believe that our Sukhoi Squadron with avionicsand its BVR capability will be easily able to take over the j10 and j11's ifPLAAF plans to deploy them.
&#13;
尽管中国的空军规模庞大，但如果印度与中国进行空战，印度会再次处于有利的位置，中国大多数的战斗机都是没啥用的多余飞机，他们有200架歼10、70架苏30MKK、140架歼11，还有70架苏27战斗机。歼10和歼11是中国国产的飞机，配备了中国国产的航空电子设备。我坚信，如果中国计划部署这些飞机，拥有航电设备和超视距侦察能力的苏霍伊战斗机中队会很容易地搞定歼10 和歼11。
&#13;
But since china is smart it would surelynot use its air-force but its missile systems with full effect.China has themost feared missile systems. Below is the list of missiles they will use tocripple India’s strength points:
&#13;
Dong Feng 31 (10,000+ km)
&#13;
DF-5 (10,000+ km)
&#13;
DF-41 (10,000+ km)
&#13;
但是，中国很聪明，它肯定不会使用空军，而是充分地发挥导弹的作用。中国拥有最令人恐bu的导弹系统。
&#13;
下面是他们可以用来削弱印度实力的导弹清单：
&#13;
东风31（射程1万公里以上）
&#13;
东风-5（射程1万公里以上）
&#13;
东风41（射程1万公里以上）
&#13;
http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-4.jpg
&#13;
Day 4:
&#13;
By the start of day 4 we have lost majorcities in the world like delhi,beijing,shanghai and mumbai to nuclear war-fare.With the help of world diplomacy this war fare is brought to an end, a treatywould be designed between indians and chinese.
&#13;
Pakistan starts re-building the forces,prepares a retreat and china does the same on the north-east frontiers ofIndia.
&#13;
战争的第4天：
&#13;
到了这一天，因为核战争的原因，世界上一些主要城市已经没有了，比如德里、北京、上海和孟买。在全世界外交行动的帮助下，这场战争结束了。中国和印度之间将签订一项条约。
&#13;
巴基斯坦开始重整部队，准备撤退，在印度东北边境，中国也会这样做。
&#13;
Day 5
&#13;
Re building of life in all 3 countries,Human lives lost are upto 100 millions thanks to nuclear warfare.
&#13;
Reasons on why i did not even considerSri-lanka:
&#13;
1) The country has its own problems ofcivil war.
&#13;
2) Thier armed forces can reach india onlyvia sea via thier own naval forces.
&#13;
3) Sri lanka is 50 years behind India,chinaand Pak in consideration to Naval War-fare and air-warfare.
&#13;
到了第5天：
&#13;
这三个国家，都开始重建，由于核战争的发生，伤亡人数高达1亿。
&#13;
为什么我从头到尾没有考虑斯里兰卡呢？
&#13;
1、 这个国家自己有内战。
&#13;
2、 他们的武装部队只能通过他们自己的海军到达印度。
&#13;
3、 参考海战和空战，斯里兰卡落后印度、中国和巴基斯坦50年以上。</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>废狗: </b><br>
<span>如果中国、巴基斯坦和斯里兰卡同时攻击印度，他们要花...</span><br>
<span>If China, Pakistan and Sri Lanka attack India at the same time, how long will it take them to defeat India?</span><br>
<span>如果中国、巴基斯坦和斯里兰卡同时攻击印度，他们要花多长时间才能打败印度？</span><br>
<img src="http://img.ltaaa.com/uploadfile/thumb/2019/06/21//1561080505845.jpg" title="http://img.ltaaa.com/uploadfile/thumb/2019/06/21//1561080505845.jpg"><br>
<span>评论翻译</span><br>
<span>原创翻译：龙腾网 http://www.ltaaa.com 翻译：squart 转载请注明出处</span><br>
<span>论坛地址：http://www.ltaaa.com/bbs/thread-486873-1-1.html</span><br>
<span>接上篇：如果中国和巴基斯坦同时进攻印度，印度会怎么样？类似提问，但是加上了斯里兰卡。</span><br>
<span>回答一：</span><br>
<span>Balaji Viswanathan</span><br>
<span>The result will be a stalemate. Here iswhy:</span><br>
<span>这场战争最终会演变成一场僵局。原因如下：</span><br>
<span>First, let us take the low hanging fruit:Sri Lanka. Lankans received massive help from India to prevail over LTTE andend the civil war. The help included military (logistics, patrolling, arms),diplomatic (banning LTTE in Western nations) and political (prevailing overTamilnadu's political parties). Indian central government is the only that canprevail over certain jigoist Tamil groups. Thus, if SL distracts Indian centralgovernment in any way, Tamil nationalist groups could send SL into a massivechaos and civil war. Thus, no way SL would mess with India.</span><br>
<span>首先，我们从最容易实现的目标开始：斯里兰卡。在印度的大力帮助下，斯里兰卡人战胜了泰米尔猛虎组织，结束了内战，印度的帮助包括军事上（后勤、巡逻、武器）、外交上（在西方国家，禁止了猛虎组织）和政治上（让泰米尔纳德邦政党承认这一点）。印度中央政府是唯一能控制某些泰米尔极端组织的政府。因此，如果斯里兰卡敢用任何方式来对印度施加压力，泰米尔民族主义组织可能会给斯里兰卡送上一场大规模的混乱和内战。因此，斯里兰卡是没有办法干扰印度的。</span><br>
<img src="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/85/28785/comment-1.jpg" title="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/85/28785/comment-1.jpg"><br>
<span>Thus, a Pakistan-China axis will neverreally work against India. The resulting mutual destruction is what preventingsuch an alliance from already happening.</span><br>
<span>因此，中国和巴基斯坦永远不会真正攻击印度，这种行为会产生的破坏性后果正是阻止这种事情发生的原因。</span><br>
<span>回答二：</span><br>
<span>Chaitanya Belwal</span><br>
<span>Chaitanya Belwal, Experienced withTechnology and Defense matters</span><br>
<span>While this may me a hypothetical scenario,it figures quite prominently in the Indian military's war scenario. Past newssuggest that the Indian military has always accounted for a 2-front war withChina and Pakistan.</span><br>
<span>Let’s keep Sri Lanka outof this since its military is not large enough to pose a serious threat (Nooffence to the Sri Lankans, but it took them 30 years to get rid of the LTTE,an objective that was almost achieved in 3 years by 4 divisions of the Indianarmy. Contrary to popular perceptions (as presented here) the reality of aSino-Pak-Indo conflict are quite different.</span><br>
<span>虽然这只是一种假设的情况，但在印度军方的预案里，这是最常见的假设。过去的消息表明，印度军方一直在为同时与中国和巴基斯坦两线作战做准备。</span><br>
<span>我们先把斯里兰卡排除出去，因为斯里兰卡的军事实力不够，没法对印度构成威胁。（没有冒犯斯里兰卡人的意思，但斯里兰卡花了30年时间，才解决掉泰米尔猛虎组织。而几乎是一样的目标，印度陆军的4个师只用了3年时间就做到了这一点。）</span><br>
<span>但与大部分人的看法不一样的是，印度与中国和巴基斯坦的冲突情况可能不太一样：</span><br>
<span>First I differ with one poster who comparesthe Chinese Military (CM) as a world-class boxer, India as street cop andPakistan as a brother to the street cop. If there is one 1000 lb Gorilla (orthe boxer) in the room of world's military powers, it is the US military. Therest, including China, are nothing but street cops with varying degree ofweapons and strength. To reason why, one only has to see that each US Navy CVN(Nuclear carrier) is the 20th largest air force in the world, having some ofthe most sophisticated aircraft , and there are 11 of them. And we are not eventalking about the USAF.</span><br>
<span>首先，我有一个和大家不太一样的比喻，中国军队，我把它比作是世界级别的拳击手，印度，街头警察，巴基斯坦，同样是街头警察。如果，这些世界军事强国所处的房间里有一只1000磅的大猩猩的话，那就是美国军队。其他国家，包括中国，只不过是拥有不同级别武器和力量的街头警察。我解释一下，我们只需要看一下美国海军的核动力航空母舰，每一艘核动力航空母舰都是世界排名第20的空军，拥有一些最先进的飞机，而美国这样的航空母舰就有11艘，这还没有说道美国的空军。</span><br>
<img src="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/85/28785/comment-2.jpg" title="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/85/28785/comment-2.jpg"><br>
<span>Regarding the Navy, though China may have adecent blue water capability it does not yet have the numbers or the experienceto sustain operations in the backyard of the Indian Navy, the 2nd largest Navyin Asia. Indian Navy's 2 Carrier Battle Groups will pose a serious offensivethreat to the surface fleet of both the Pakistan and Chinese navies. A naval blockadeof India is unthinkable since this will bring the entire surface fleet of thePLAN and PN within strike range of shore based bombers and strike aircraft ofthe Indian Navy and air force. Unlike the US Navy or even the Royal Navy, PLANlacks the air support firepower needed to protect its fleet from offensiveground based air operations.</span><br>
<span>在海军方面，虽然中国有一定的蓝海海军实力，但它如果想要在印度海军（亚洲第二大海军）的后院维持作战的话，它的数量和经验都不足够。印度海军的2个航母战斗群将对巴基斯坦和中国海军的水面舰队构成严重的威胁，而且，想要对印度海军进行封锁也是不可能的，因为实施封锁的水面舰艇会进入印度海军和空军的轰炸机和攻击机的打击范围之内，（它们）与美国海军甚至是英国皇家海军不同的是，它们缺乏保护其舰队免受地面攻击所需的空中支援火力。</span><br>
<span>The PLAAF has a distinct advantage, atleast on paper. With 3000+ combat aircraft supported by mid-air refuellers thePLAAF is a force to recon with. However apart from 250+ SU30MKK’s, 200+Su-27s and 200+ JF-17’s rest of these aircraft are vintage Chinese variants of MiG 19 andMiG 21s. In the context of Sino-Indian conflict, China has primarily 6 airbasesto launch strike aircraft from. However, all of these have altitudes in excessof 4000 ft, which means the strike aircraft taking off will be carrying lesserpayload. A PLAAF Su-30MKK for example, will take off with 6 AA missiles ratherthan 8. All IAF airbases bordering China primarily those in Bareilly, Tezpur,Hindon and Bagdodra, are at near sea level allowing Indian Su30MKI to takeoffat full payload.</span><br>
<span>至少在纸面数据上，中国空军具有明显的优势，它们拥有3000多架战斗机，有空中加油机能够提供支援。然而，除了250多架苏30、200多架苏27以及200多架JF-17之外，其余的飞机都是中国由米格19和米格21改型来的老旧机种。如果中国和印度发生冲突，中国的战斗机将在6个主要的空军基地起飞，然而，这些基地海拔都在1000米以上，这意味着这些飞机起飞时的有效载荷有限。比如中国军队的苏30只能搭载6枚防空导弹，而不是8枚，而所有与中国接壤的印度空军基地，主要包括巴雷利、泰兹普尔、印顿和巴格杜德拉，水平高度都和海平面接近，这使得印度空军的苏30战机能够满负荷起飞。</span><br>
<img src="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/85/28785/comment-3.jpg" title="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/85/28785/comment-3.jpg"><br>
<span>To conclude India vs China-Pakistan warwill end in stalemate at best, and won’t give any tacticalor strategic advantage to any nation. So much so that it’s motivationitself will be in doubt.</span><br>
<span>所以，印度和中国以及巴基斯坦的战争，最终会是一场僵局，不会给任何国家带来任何方面的好处。所以这场战争发动的动机本身就会让人质疑。</span><br>
<span>Mark Harrison</span><br>
<span>Mark Harrison, CTO, werarewe</span><br>
<span>Let us review the relative militarystrengths:</span><br>
<span>China is a world class power, with astructured and trained military</span><br>
<span>India has a military force more accustomedto 'local enforcement' actions, but not world-class</span><br>
<span>Pakistan is like a scaled down version ofIndia, aggressive, but less disciplined.</span><br>
<span>Sri Lanka has little military power.</span><br>
<span>Now, suppose Pakistan, China and Sri Lankadecided to invade India. India would be most worried by China.</span><br>
<span>让我们来看一下相关国家的军事实力：</span><br>
<span>中国是一个世界级的大国，拥有一支训练有素的军队。</span><br>
<span>印度的军事力量更倾向于“地方执法”级别，还达不到世界级的水平。</span><br>
<span>巴基斯坦类似一个缩小版的印度，侵略性强，但纪律性差。</span><br>
<span>斯里兰卡几乎就没有军事力量。</span><br>
<span>现在，假设巴基斯坦、中国和斯里兰卡决定入侵印度。印度最担心的会是中国。</span><br>
<img src="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-1.jpg" title="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-1.jpg"><br>
<span>However, suppose that this is not the case.Then it's a full offensive for strategic goals, with China determined to causemajor damage to India. India would be determined not to surrender. However,India might, in confusion, launch a larger than intended strike against SriLanka causing major damage. It is also likely that some Chinese offensiveswould cause collateral damage to Pakistan, which would combine with some Indiancounter-attack.</span><br>
<span>但如果，情况并非假设的这样，中国下定决心要对印度造成重大伤害，发动对战略目标的全面进攻的话，印度将不会投降。混乱之中，印度可能会对斯里兰卡发动一场比预期更大的打击，造成重大的伤害，中国的一些进攻也可能会对巴基斯坦造成附带伤害。</span><br>
<span>The Indian leadership would realise that,if they continued to fight China, the damage would be permanent. However, theyare a nuclear power. But then, China isa nuclear power too. Both of them would issue warnings about their intentionsto deploy nuclear weapons. Pakistan would also warn about its intentions todeploy nuclear weapons. India and China would not take this threat seriously,but Pakistan would repeat its threats. Again, India and China would point outthat nuclear weapons had a mutually assured destruction capability, but bothwould be nervous of Pakistans willingness to engage in such a strategy. Chinesecollateral damage against Pakistan would increase. As the situation escalated,the conventional battle between India and China would intensify, but both wouldremain non-nuclear.</span><br>
<span>印度领导人这时候会意识到，如果他们继续与中国作战，将会带来永久性的伤害。然而，他们是一个核武器国家，但中国也是一个核大国。两个国家都会对对方试图使用核武器发出警告，巴基斯坦也会威胁使用核武器，但印度和中国都不会认真地对待这一威胁，巴基斯坦会一再重复它的威胁，印度和中国会不断的重申：核武器具有相互摧毁的能力，但这两个国家都会对巴基斯坦的这种姿态感到紧张。中国对巴基斯坦的附带伤害将会增加，随着局势的升级，印度和中国之间的常规战争会加剧，但两个国家都不会使用核武器。</span><br>
<span>At this point, three other powers need tobe considered - the USA, the UK, and Russia. The USA is hostile to China andits policy towards Pakistan has swung. The USA, dominant in global militaryterms, has demonstrated this against countries like Iraq and Afghanistan, andits troops have actual military experience. So, America is feared. The UK andRussia, by comparison, have reputations, but little interest in engagingin-theatre. They are all, however, unhappy with China because of its economicdominance.</span><br>
<span>这种情况下，还需要考虑其他三个大国的态度——美国、英国和俄罗斯。美国对中国怀有敌意，对巴基斯坦的政策也有所改变。美国在军事实力上占主导地位，在伊拉克和阿富汗等国家已经证明了这一点，它们的军队拥有实战经验。相比之下，英国和俄罗斯也有强大实力，但是对参与的兴趣很低，不过，他们都对中国的经济优势感到不满。</span><br>
<span>Now, they realise that with India damaged,China will be dominant in Asia. They realise that this would make China adirect threat to their own strategic interests. They also know that Chinaultimately aims to take full control of Asia. They are also aware that thenuclear option would cause global devastation.</span><br>
<span>现在，他们意识到，随着印度的受伤，中国将在亚洲占主导地位，这会让中国直接威胁到他们自己的战略利益。他们还知道，中国最终的目标是全面控制亚洲，而且他们还意识到，核战争会导致全世界的毁灭。</span><br>
<img src="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-2.jpg" title="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-2.jpg"><br>
<span>There is structural damage to both Indiaand China. One fourth of India needs rebuilding, but it retains sovereigntyover the land. Sri Lanka is defeated. Nepal has also taken major damage.</span><br>
<span>印度和中国都受到了结构性的破坏，四分之一的印度需要重建，但它保留了对这片土地的主权，斯里兰卡被打败了，尼泊尔也遭受了重大损失。</span><br>
<span>Meanwhile, Japan and Germany are rejoicingat the fact that Chinese competition has been put out of business.</span><br>
<span>同时，日本和德国对将中国从国际贸易中挤出去感到高兴。</span><br>
<span>Strikes me as a serious description...maybe the metaphor was unfortunate, and there may be holes in the scenario...but not a joke answer...</span><br>
<span>我最在意的是，也许我的这个答案有点悲惨，这些假想可能有漏洞…但这个答案我不是在开玩笑。</span><br>
<span>回答四：</span><br>
<span>Siddhesh Shivraj</span><br>
<span>Siddhesh Shivraj, growing up</span><br>
<span>In the modern era i don't think it shouldlast for more than 10 days. Since this being a hypothetical question, I wouldgive it a hypothetical build up which lasts for a few days.</span><br>
<span>DAY 1:</span><br>
<span>In a war i guess it would be Pakistan whichwould be the first to attack India, even if all 3 wage a war together,considering Pakistan being the closest and the being a childhood rival toIndia. On the very first day, Pakistan's strategy would be using POK to makein-roads into India. Their first strategy would be using the land-ways to makeinroads to Kashmir valley.</span><br>
<span>在现代战争中，这样的战争持续时间不会超过10天，因为这是一个假设性的问题，所以我假想一下这场战争接下来几天的走向。</span><br>
<span>战争的第1天：</span><br>
<span>在这场战争中，就算这三个国家是联手发动对印度的战争，但我认为巴基斯坦会是第一个攻击印度的国家，因为巴基斯坦离印度最近，也是印度一直以来的对手。在第一天时间里，巴基斯坦会直接打通一条进入印度的通道，他们的策略是通过陆路进入克什米尔山谷。</span><br>
<span>This beginning at the start of DAY 1, alongwith invasion on the lines of Punjab and rajasthan as well, all done by thePakistan Army. Now in kashmir, The pakistani army would have to face the IndianArmy. Now moving on all ground forces are engaged in battle,meanwhile CHINA ispreparing to come onto INDIA by moving their armed forces in a hurry to thenorth-indian border.</span><br>
<span>第一天开始，巴基斯坦军队入侵旁遮普和拉贾斯坦邦，然后在克什米尔，巴基斯坦军队遇到了印度军队。现在，所有的地面部队都参与了战斗，与此同时，中国准备把他们的武装部队快速地转移到印度北部边界地区，进入印度。</span><br>
<span>It's a huge movement of troops which shouldtake a complete day, if not prepared in advanced. Since China is going to beinvolved in action by day 2 only as they have to move across tibet. On DAY 1itself we are having an intensified battles at the border. We have stationedour ARJUN MBT's and are using our BOFORS for shelling. By the end of DAY 1, noside has made any marginal gains not india or pakistan. China is still movingits troops into tibet, Sri Lanka on the other hand is still contemplating ifthey should resurrect a country savaged by civil war or jump into another war.</span><br>
<span>这会是一次大规模的部队调动，如果没有提前做好准备，这需要一整天的时间，所以，中国会在第二天才开始采取大规模行动。第一天，在边境地区我们展开了一场激战，我们有阿琼主战坦克，并使用防空炮进行炮击。</span><br>
<span>到当天结束的时候，双方在边境上都没有任何进展，当然了，印度和巴基斯坦边境除外，中国仍在调遣军队，而斯里兰卡仍在考虑是否让自己国家重新陷入内战之中，或者发动另一场战争。</span><br>
<span>DAY 2:</span><br>
<span>By the beginning of day 2, Pakistan hasbeen contemplating launching thier missiles, onto major Indian cities targetingcities like Delhi,Mumbai and kolkata.They would be trying to target deep intothe Indian territory. But here is the biggest problem for Pakistan. They needthier mobile launchers to be as close to the Indian territory as possible. I am petty sure they would try to usertheir missiles Ghauri and the missile systems, now these need mobile launchersas they are not compatible to be fired from a aircraft or frigate or adestroyer.</span><br>
<span>战争的第2天：</span><br>
<span>到了战争的第二天，巴基斯坦考虑向印度的主要城市，如德里、孟买和加尔各答发射导弹。他们会把导弹对准印度内部，但这里巴基斯坦面临的最大问题是：他们需要让导弹发射系统尽可能地靠近印度。我可以肯定，巴基斯坦会使用自己的导弹，现在，他们需要让他们的发射装置移动起来，因为这些导弹不能从战斗机或者军舰上发射。</span><br>
<img src="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-3.jpg" title="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-3.jpg"><br>
<span>Brahmos is the world fastest supersonicmissile which can cruise at 3 Mach easily and has a range of 300 KMS. Sukhoi 30MKI (are multi-role fighters) are primarily air to air superiority fighters andwill be flanked by our Dassault Mirage and Mig 29's for air to ground bombingwiping out SAM systems of pak. We have 180 Sukhoi 30 MKI operational at any given time and say weengage 40 to engage with Pakistan Air force along with ground force. Indiastartegy would be using 20 Sukhoi's for BRAHMOS strikes and rest 20 to backthese sukhoi's while enegaging the PAF and thier j-10's and f-16's. Our rafaleand MIG 29 are capable of handling j-10's and f-16's. PAF j10 and f-16 are notbe compared with sukoi 30 MKI whcih is a generation ahead in avionics, they candeal with our rafale and mig 29. An intense Air warfare would lead to Sukhoitaking out the missile bases at a hit rate of 90% because of brahmos missilespurely. The maximum loses which can take is lossing rafale's and sukhoi whoacted as interceptor's while 20 other sukhoi's delivered the brahmos package.</span><br>
<span>布拉莫斯是世界上速度最快的超音速导弹，可以轻松地以3马赫的速度巡航，射程为300公里。苏30MKI多功能战斗机主要是空优战斗机，将在幻影和米格29的配合下，进行空对地轰炸，消灭巴基斯坦的导弹系统。</span><br>
<span>我们有180架能随时参战的苏30MKI战斗机，这意味着我们可以在与巴基斯坦空战的的同时，出动40架战斗机对地面攻击。20架苏30战斗机将直接发射布拉莫斯导弹，剩下的20架战斗机在一边进行支援，同时防范中国和巴基斯坦的歼10和F16。</span><br>
<span>我们的阵风战斗机和米格 29战斗机能够搞定歼10和F16战斗机，而苏30因为在航电方面领先一代，它可以和我们的阵风以及米格29一起，对付歼10和F16。</span><br>
<span>由于布拉莫斯导弹的存在，一场激烈的空战之后，苏霍伊战斗机会以90%的命中率摧毁巴基斯坦的导弹基地，我们受到的最大损失可能就是那些担当截击任务的苏霍伊战斗机。</span><br>
<span>With the Missile bases wiped out and takinga deadly hit in aerial warfare Pakistan is on its back heels on day 2 itself.pre-emptive nuclear strike is out of the question now.</span><br>
<span>随着巴基斯坦的导弹基地被摧毁，并且在空战之中遭受到的致命打击，战争的第二天，巴基斯坦的局势已经不太好了，先发制人的核打击现在不太可能了。</span><br>
<span>Day 3:</span><br>
<span>Pakistan on the backfoot. Its naval forcestry to take on the Indian navy ; fails miserably because Indian Air forceswould again come into picture while handling out air to ground bombs on PNFwhile INF will use it submarines which are brahmos capable to neutralise PNF (Pakistan Naval FOrce ). Historcally Pakistan never had a great naval force.They have a good Air force but completely outdated f-16 which were superior toour force in the 90's; not now, because we have AWACS, Israeli avionics in oursystems along with our in-house BARS radar systems.</span><br>
<span>战争的第3天：</span><br>
<span>巴基斯坦已经落在下风了。巴基斯坦海军试图与印度海军交战，但惨遭失败，印度空军攻击巴基斯坦导弹基地的画面会重现，印度海军的布拉莫斯潜射导弹，会消灭巴基斯坦海军。巴基斯坦历史上海军实力一直不咋的，他们的空军还不错，但F16已经过时了，在90年代，他们比我们先进，现在不是了，因为我们的武器系统中预警机、以色列的航电设备以及我们自己的雷达系统。</span><br>
<span>Air-war with china will again put thebalance in favour of Indians though china has a huge Air force, most of theplanes are the redundant. They have 200 j-10's , 70 sukhoi 30mkk, 140 j-11'sand another 70 sukhoi su-27.The j-10's and j-11's are home grown aircrafts withdomestic avionics. I strongly believe that our Sukhoi Squadron with avionicsand its BVR capability will be easily able to take over the j10 and j11's ifPLAAF plans to deploy them.</span><br>
<span>尽管中国的空军规模庞大，但如果印度与中国进行空战，印度会再次处于有利的位置，中国大多数的战斗机都是没啥用的多余飞机，他们有200架歼10、70架苏30MKK、140架歼11，还有70架苏27战斗机。歼10和歼11是中国国产的飞机，配备了中国国产的航空电子设备。我坚信，如果中国计划部署这些飞机，拥有航电设备和超视距侦察能力的苏霍伊战斗机中队会很容易地搞定歼10 和歼11。</span><br>
<span>But since china is smart it would surelynot use its air-force but its missile systems with full effect.China has themost feared missile systems. Below is the list of missiles they will use tocripple India’s strength points:</span><br>
<span>Dong Feng 31 (10,000+ km)</span><br>
<span>DF-5 (10,000+ km)</span><br>
<span>DF-41 (10,000+ km)</span><br>
<span>但是，中国很聪明，它肯定不会使用空军，而是充分地发挥导弹的作用。中国拥有最令人恐bu的导弹系统。</span><br>
<span>下面是他们可以用来削弱印度实力的导弹清单：</span><br>
<span>东风31（射程1万公里以上）</span><br>
<span>东风-5（射程1万公里以上）</span><br>
<span>东风41（射程1万公里以上）</span><br>
<img src="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-4.jpg" title="http://www.ltaaa.com/postmake/86/28786/comment-4.jpg"><br>
<span>Day 4:</span><br>
<span>By the start of day 4 we have lost majorcities in the world like delhi,beijing,shanghai and mumbai to nuclear war-fare.With the help of world diplomacy this war fare is brought to an end, a treatywould be designed between indians and chinese.</span><br>
<span>Pakistan starts re-building the forces,prepares a retreat and china does the same on the north-east frontiers ofIndia.</span><br>
<span>战争的第4天：</span><br>
<span>到了这一天，因为核战争的原因，世界上一些主要城市已经没有了，比如德里、北京、上海和孟买。在全世界外交行动的帮助下，这场战争结束了。中国和印度之间将签订一项条约。</span><br>
<span>巴基斯坦开始重整部队，准备撤退，在印度东北边境，中国也会这样做。</span><br>
<span>Day 5</span><br>
<span>Re building of life in all 3 countries,Human lives lost are upto 100 millions thanks to nuclear warfare.</span><br>
<span>Reasons on why i did not even considerSri-lanka:</span><br>
<span>1) The country has its own problems ofcivil war.</span><br>
<span>2) Thier armed forces can reach india onlyvia sea via thier own naval forces.</span><br>
<span>3) Sri lanka is 50 years behind India,chinaand Pak in consideration to Naval War-fare and air-warfare.</span><br>
<span>到了第5天：</span><br>
<span>这三个国家，都开始重建，由于核战争的发生，伤亡人数高达1亿。</span><br>
<span>为什么我从头到尾没有考虑斯里兰卡呢？</span><br>
<span>1、 这个国家自己有内战。</span><br>
<span>2、 他们的武装部队只能通过他们自己的海军到达印度。</span><br>
<span>3、 参考海战和空战，斯里兰卡落后印度、中国和巴基斯坦50年以上。</span><br>
</p><p><b>Liveforlong哀哉: </b><br>
<span>三国只需要担心难民多久踏破边界，印度军队是指望不上了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>Yurica: </b><br>
<span>讨论这个不如讨论印度会裂成多少块</span><br>
</p><p><b>兰开夏: </b><br>
<span>棋逢对手</span><br>
</p><p><b>kuleisite1992: </b><br>
<span>相对实力对比上，大概是91-92年的双方削弱版我国对上美帝的感觉？理论上有三位一体核力量，军力看着也像个样。现在回过神来，复盘的话，实际上打起来，大家心里都明白。真不知道当年咋想的……</span><br>
</p><p><b>20044538: </b><br>
<span>印度可是宇宙第一强国，你们简直蚍蜉撼大树，自作孽不可活。</span><br>
</p><p><b>jam0206: </b><br>
<span>我宣布印度精神胜利了 jal hind!</span><br>
</p><p><b>soulogic: </b><br>
<span>印度：你们一起上，我赶时间，Jai Hind！</span><br>
</p><p><b>StarsPlatinum: </b><br>
<span>印度和中国以及巴基斯坦的战争，最终会是一场僵局，不会给任何国家带来任何方面的好处。所以这场战争发动的动机本身就会让人质疑</span><br>
<span>难得的明白人</span><br>
</p><p><b>寒蝉: </b><br>
<span>为什么要打这么一场战争？</span><br>
</p><p><b>walkerman: </b><br>
<span>这分析在某些细节上有点不靠谱，其他的我觉得都没啥太大的误差，肯定是僵局，要在局部战争这种打赢印度不难，要彻底毁灭印度基本是不可能的，这个我觉得和美国怼中国的战略差不多，武力是不可能的，只能寄希望经济手段+内部分裂了</span><br>
</p><p><b>cpuisme: </b><br>
<span> 中国为什么要去炸粪坑。</span><br>
</p><p><b>crazyt: </b><br>
<span>站在屎坑旁边丢石头是图什么呢？</span><br>
</p><p><b>废狗: </b><br>
<span>寒蝉 发表于 2019-6-21 14:39</span><br>
<span>为什么要打这么一场战争？</span><br>
<span>三哥：快说我打得过中国！</span><br>
</p><p><b>憂鬱臺灣烏龜: </b><br>
<span>kuleisite1992 发表于 2019-6-21 14:17</span><br>
<span>相对实力对比上，大概是91-92年的双方削弱版我国对上美帝的感觉？理论上有三位一体核力量，军力看着也像个 ...</span><br>
<span>看他们的认知：</span><br>
<span>至少在纸面数据上，中国空军具有明显的优势，它们拥有3000多架战斗机，有空中加油机能够提供支援。然而，除了250多架苏30、200多架苏27以及200多架JF-17之外，其余的飞机都是中国由米格19和米格21改型来的老旧机种。</span><br>
</p><p><b>jdd46820: </b><br>
<span>面对四倍于自身的国家印度人还这么有自信也是不容易。</span><br>
</p><p><b>大哀之君: </b><br>
<span>那么斯里兰卡为什么要侵略印度，好歹换成孟加拉吧</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>zypyong: </b><br>
<span>jai hind</span><br>
</p><p><b>valand: </b><br>
<span>寒蝉 发表于 2019-6-21 14:39</span><br>
<span>为什么要打这么一场战争？</span><br>
<span>老毛：我想了十天也没想明白尼赫鲁为什么要搞我们</span><br>
</p><p><b>newdasemo: </b><br>
<span>kuleisite1992 发表于 2019-6-21 14:17</span><br>
<span>相对实力对比上，大概是91-92年的双方削弱版我国对上美帝的感觉？理论上有三位一体核力量，军力看着也像个 ...</span><br>
<span>我们可从没指望加拿大墨西哥一起打美帝啊……</span><br>
</p><p><b>龙与俯卧撑: </b><br>
<span>莫迪老仙法力无边，阿三士兵跳着舞就把三家灭了</span><br>
</p><p><b>Okumur: </b><br>
<span>jdd46820 发表于 2019-6-21 14:55</span><br>
<span>面对四倍于自身的国家印度人还这么有自信也是不容易。</span><br>
<span>∵中国只是比印度早改开10年</span><br>
<span>∴印度迟早会达到中国规模</span><br>
<span>又∵印度更年轻化，更民主</span><br>
<span>∴印度达到中国规模后还会超越中国</span><br>
</p><p><b>blackjeo1: </b><br>
<span>   原来阿三还以为是他们帮助斯里兰卡打赢猛虎组织的</span><br>
</p><p><b>maltose_jmy: </b><br>
<span>中国巴基斯坦斯里兰卡，我与科比合砍系列</span><br>
</p><p><b>water: </b><br>
<span>有一点倒是没说错，阿三的坦克只需要对付巴基斯坦，中国人的坦克很难翻山过去。</span><br>
<span>即使有投入作战的，也是轻量坦克为主，在大平原上不是主战坦克的对手。</span><br>
<span>由于有青藏高原的存在，中方易守难攻，同时受到各种影响，也无法离开高原长距离作战。</span><br>
<span>印度陆军的主要敌人主要是力量相差较远的巴基斯坦陆军，是有一定的优势的。</span><br>
</p><p><b>乐哈哈: </b><br>
<span>water 发表于 2019-6-21 15:51</span><br>
<span>有一点倒是没说错，阿三的坦克只需要对付巴基斯坦，中国人的坦克很难翻山过去。</span><br>
<span>即使有投入作战的，也是轻 ...</span><br>
<span>可是现代战争不是单一兵种的对抗啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>少女人形: </b><br>
<span>三哥是怎么觉得他们的航母战斗群能给兔子海军构成威胁的，还是说威胁是指的灭火和人道主义救援？</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>muyefytte: </b><br>
<span>阿三开心就好 </span><br>
</p><p><b>rubyture: </b><br>
<span>中国为什么要跑去屎坑逗蛆玩呢，有苍蝇的话拍死不就行了吗</span><br>
</p><p><b>honeypj: </b><br>
<span>丢核弹，简单省事省时。</span><br>
</p><p><b>sanxgh571: </b><br>
<span>为什么会假设中国开航母去打印度？嫌油多？</span><br>
</p><p><b>按时上班: </b><br>
<span>我怎么听说斯里兰卡的恐怖分子是印度扶持的，怎么变成印度帮斯里兰卡打击恐怖分子了</span><br>
</p><p><b>红色福音: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 红色福音 于 2019-6-21 16:32 编辑 </span><br>
<span>sanxgh571 发表于 2019-6-21 16:21</span><br>
<span>为什么会假设中国开航母去打印度？嫌油多？</span><br>
<span>恩……说实话，如果把斯里兰卡作为舰队的后盾的话，航母战斗群依托斯里兰卡的军事基地还是能发挥不错的作用……吧？</span><br>
</p><p><b>mintpie: </b><br>
<span>为什么印度人不了解一下中国对印度方向的军力部署呢？根本就没把印度当盘菜好吗？</span><br>
</p><p><b>0330: </b><br>
<span>印度一部摩托车就能装一个连的人，一列火车就能装一个方面军。这投送能力，TG只能跪下唱征服了</span><br>
</p><p><b>hipper: </b><br>
<span>说来说去，陆军避而不谈</span><br>
</p><p><b>KA0827: </b><br>
<span>对中国来说，印度保持政治稳定，经济发展起来的状态并不是坏事吧。地势上中方并不担心印度的地面进攻。印度成为敌人根本只是理论上的情况，既然如此，往朋友方向努力不是更好嘛，一个发达的印度一定会谋求扩散地区影响力，正好可以成为中国与中亚之间的缓冲。中亚那地方是个大火药桶，是俄罗斯、欧洲大陆、英国、美国各国力量的斗兽场，中国也在往那边投入力量，相对于支持当地各种弱鸡，把一个根本不会对我国造成破坏的印度放进去不是更好嘛</span><br>
</p><p><b>muckenberger2: </b><br>
<span>首先，我们从最容易实现的目标开始：斯里兰卡。在印度的大力帮助下，斯里兰卡人战……卧槽！中国人用弹道导弹袭击了印度核基地！</span><br>
</p><p><b>dark_templar: </b><br>
<span>water 发表于 2019-6-21 15:51</span><br>
<span>有一点倒是没说错，阿三的坦克只需要对付巴基斯坦，中国人的坦克很难翻山过去。</span><br>
<span>即使有投入作战的，也是轻 ...</span><br>
<span>错了</span><br>
<span>15可以轻松摁死阿三的任何一种坦克</span><br>
</p><p><b>dark_templar: </b><br>
<span>在印度的大力帮助下，斯里兰卡人战胜了泰米尔猛虎组织，结束了内战</span><br>
<span>——你们就不吐槽这个吗</span><br>
</p><p><b>打倒一切反动派: </b><br>
<span>天国的猛虎组织变成三哥干死的了？！</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>Demi.Albertini: </b><br>
<span>印度大力帮助了猛虎组织，然后猛虎组织就被干掉了，没毛病</span><br>
</p><p><b>自古论坛多奇葩: </b><br>
<span>猛虎组织是印度搞定的？</span><br>
</p><p><b>mu1: </b><br>
<span>“在印度的大力帮助下，斯里兰卡人战胜了泰米尔猛虎组织”</span><br>
<span>这是相声节目么</span><br>
</p><p><b>灬猫之优雅灬: </b><br>
<span>Okumur 发表于 2019-6-21 15:11</span><br>
<span>∵中国只是比印度早改开10年</span><br>
<span>∴印度迟早会达到中国规模</span><br>
<span>又∵印度更年轻化，更民主</span><br>
<span>好消息：印度将会超过中国</span><br>
<span>坏消息：战争明天开打</span><br>
</p><p><b>韶华白首: </b><br>
<span>赔本买卖</span><br>
</p><p><b>大哀之君: </b><br>
<span>KA0827 发表于 2019-06-21 17:42:58</span><br>
<span>对中国来说，印度保持政治稳定，经济发展起来的状态并不是坏事吧。地势上中方并不担心印度的地面进攻。印度 ...首先一个强势的印度可以掐断中国到中东和欧洲的的航运路线，第二中国也根本没虚弱到要在中亚搞什么以夷制夷。在可见的未来，中国继续联合巴基斯坦把印度堵在次大陆上才是最省事的</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>Kozakai: </b><br>
<span>Yurica 发表于 2019-6-21 14:14</span><br>
<span>讨论这个不如讨论印度会裂成多少块</span><br>
<span>你指出了一条让印度强大的道路</span><br>
</p><p><b>podbots: </b><br>
<span>这个动物王国大概率要经历一次大规模种族灭绝事件</span><br>
</p><p><b>废狗: </b><br>
<span>KA0827 发表于 2019-6-21 17:42</span><br>
<span>对中国来说，印度保持政治稳定，经济发展起来的状态并不是坏事吧。地势上中方并不担心印度的地面进攻。印度 ...</span><br>
<span>乳印了</span><br>
<span>正确态度是整散架拉倒</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1841166[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
