<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>文在寅光复节演说（韩联社中日双语版）</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>文在寅光复节演说（韩联社中日双语版）</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 18:18:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>文在寅光复节演说（韩联社中日双语版）[50-100]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1853629-1-1.html</link>
      <description>文在寅光复节演说（韩联社中日双语版）&#13;
 本帖最后由 chenzj8309 于 2019-8-15 15:59 编辑 

尊敬的全体国民，独立有功人士和其家属，以及旅外同胞们：在迎来三一独立运动和临时政府成立100周年的今天，我们在独立纪念馆举行光复74周年纪念仪式，意义深远。今天的大韩民国是先烈们以百折不挠、坚韧不拔的精神造就的。他们渴望"三角山翩翩跳舞，汉江水喷涌而出的那一天"到来，奉献自己一切的那股精神永远活在国民心中。今天，我要向先烈们、有功人士及其家属致以深深的敬意，和全体国民一道描绘祖国光复那天普罗大众以激动的心情梦想的国家，继承先贤遗志共同建设理想国度。我们所梦想的国家是一起幸福生活的国家，是所有人都有公平的机会，即使失败了也能重新站起来的国家。我们所梦想的国家是韩国西部莞岛的少女在东部蔚山学习氢工业，去朝鲜南浦创业，向蒙古和西伯利亚出口环保汽车的国家；是在朝鲜会宁长大的少年在韩国釜山海洋大学读书，毕业后成为一名船舶驾驶员，驾驶一艘集装箱船前往东盟国家、印度洋、南美智利的国家；是农业专业的青年在阿穆尔江畔与韩朝俄三国的农夫一起耕种大面积的豆田，而身在韩国瑞山的弟弟用哥哥生产的豆子喂牛的国家；是跨越豆满江通往大陆，横跨太平洋前往东盟国家和印度，生活与想象力被无限放大的国家；是经济活动范围超出韩半岛南方一侧，与周边国家合作共赢的国家。"点起熔炉之火，在新国家的心脏抽铁丝，添钢筋，搭铁板，在混凝土、铁和希望之上建设一个谁都无法动摇的新的国家。"解放后，一位诗人如此歌颂迎来光复的新国家之梦。"谁都无法动摇的新的国家"，这是摆脱外来势力的侵略和统治的新生独立国家本该拥有的梦想。从那之后74年后的今天，我们成为世界第6大制造强国和第6大出口强国，具备强有力的经济实力。我们开启了人均收入3万美元时代，并在逐渐实现金九先生所追求的"文化国家"的梦想。但我们还没能建设"谁都无法动摇的国家"，这是因为我们还不够强大，祖国仍处于分裂状态。看到以毅然的态度面对一切危机的国民，今天我再次下决心，定要把祖国建设成我们所梦想的"谁都无法动摇的国家"。尊敬的全体国民！我们遵守自由贸易秩序，集中发展了半导体、IT、生物等我们可以做好的产业。在国际分工体系中，任何一个国家都能梦想凭借自身优势获得成功。在近代化过程中一度落后的东亚基于分工和协作再次实现经济腾飞，全球称之为"东亚的奇迹"。东亚有过侵略和战争，但与之相比，人员交流和贸易往来的历史更长。从青铜器文化到现代文明，东亚各国互相传播文化和共享文明，实现了人类历史上最长时间的交流与合作。光复节不光是我们的好日子，也是甲午战争、俄日战争、满洲事变、中日战争、太平洋战争这60多年一系列战争结束的日子，是整个东亚光复的日子。日本国民同样摆脱军国主义的压迫，从侵略战争中解放出来。我们没有停留在过去，而是不断与日本在安全、经济领域开展合作，尝试与日本一道疗愈日本殖民统治时期受害者的伤痛，我们以史为镜，坚持携手合作的立场。反省历史并不意味着停留在过去，而是要摆脱历史走向未来。我们希望日本反省给邻国带去的不幸历史，与我们一道引领东亚的和平与繁荣。只有合作才能携手发展，才能实现可持续发展。世界通过高度的分工机制实现了共同繁荣，日本经济也同样在自由贸易的秩序中实现分工和发展。在国际分工机制中，任何国家若把自身优势领域作为武器，就无法维持和平的自由贸易秩序，先发展起来的国家绝不能剥夺后起发展国家的机会。若日本此刻走对话与合作之路，我们愿意配合，并将与其一道打造公平贸易与合作的东亚。去年韩国举办了平昌冬奥会，明年日本将办东京奥运，2022年中国将办北京冬奥会，这是奥运历史上首次由东亚地区接力办赛。这将是东亚巩固友好合作基础，走向共同繁荣之路的良机。正如全世界人民在平昌见证了"和平韩半岛"一般，希望东京奥运会也能带来友好与合作的希望。为了让东亚的下一代看到通过合作实现繁荣，我们将竭尽所能。尊敬的全体国民!今天的大韩民国已非昔日的大韩民国，而是克服无数挑战和折磨变得更加坚强和成熟的大韩民国。为了建设我们所梦想的"全新的韩半岛——谁都无法动摇的国家"，我提出如下三个目标:——第一，作为负责任的经济强国，维护全球自由贸易秩序，促进东亚地区的平等合作。韩国国民造就了奇迹般的经济发展，其成果和潜力可与世分享，但不能被夺走。我们只有掌握经济主权，才能作为韩半岛命运的主宰者，不为外力所动摇。全体国民凝聚力量将危机化为机遇，挑战会让我们变得更强大。无论是中东炙热的沙漠，还是太平洋的大浪，我们都毫不畏惧，一心实现经济发展。我们先后发展轻工业、重化工业、信息通信产业，最终成为了名副其实的IT强国，如今还引领5G等全球技术标准。过去，我们努力追赶发达国家，而今率先迎接挑战，逐步实现经济领先。面对日本政府不当的限贸措施，我们坚持走负责任的经济强国之路。政府将把现有经济结构转变为"包容、共赢"的经济生态系统，通过促进大中小企业之间、劳资之间的合作，提升材料、零部件、设备产业的国际竞争力。我们还将营造鼓励科学家和技术工人敢于挑战、包容失败的社会氛围，打造谁都无法动摇的经济强国。我相信，只要审视自己的不足，不自卑，互励共勉，就能做到这一切。我们将以与经济实力相应的责任感，进一步扩大开放合作，与邻国共同发展。——第二，连接大陆与海洋，为实现全球和平与繁荣发挥桥梁作用。从地缘政治角度看，韩国是世界上唯一一个被四大强国包围环绕的国家。当我们的力量渺小时，无论在陆地还是在海洋都被排挤在边缘，有时甚至沦为强国角逐的角斗场。这就是我们经历过的历史。不过，只要我们拥有力量，就能成为连接大陆和海洋、引导东北亚和平与繁荣的领袖国家。我们应把地缘政治上的劣势转化为优势，并制定明确的目标，主动开辟未来，而不是被外力所左右。大韩民国临时政府要人赵素昻先生曾提倡人与人、民族与民族、国与国之间建立平等关系。这是我们追求和平与繁荣的基本精神。面对日本的经济报复措施，全体国民齐心协力守护国家利益，同时保证两国友好关系不受损害，这是因为韩国国民拥有成熟的公民意识。韩国政府所推进的"以人为本、互利共赢的和平共同体"旨在实现韩半岛、东亚乃至世界的和平与繁荣。"新北方政策"是开辟通往大陆之路的远大构想。除了中国和俄罗斯之外，我们将把合作范围扩展至中亚和欧洲地区，并通过东北亚铁路共同体奠定多边合作、多边安保的基础。"新南方政策"是开辟通往海洋之路的远大构想。我们将与东盟和印度的双边关系升级为与周边主要国家相同的水平，发展成互利共赢的合作关系。今年11月，韩国-东盟特别峰会和韩国-湄公峰会将在釜山举行，这将是推动韩国与东盟、韩国与湄公国家关系发展的又一划时代的里程碑。连接韩朝铁路和公路是韩国为实现东北亚和平与繁荣迈出的第一步。若韩朝实现陆、海、空全方位互联互通，打通物流动脉，恢复人员往来，半岛将变成连接亚欧大陆、太平洋、东盟以及印度洋的重要关口。届时，亚洲共同体将会绽放合作之花，而非由任何一国主导。——第三，通过构建以和平促繁荣的和平经济，以统一实现完整的光复。我们要克服分裂，将民族的能量升华为实现未来繁荣的动力。和平经济是基于半岛完全无核化，始于通过对话与合作让朝鲜弃核并选择走向繁荣的战略。在过去的1年8个月间，韩朝美三方始终保持对话势头。近来，朝鲜几番做出令人担忧的行为，但对话的势头没有因此受到影响，这是韩国政府推进构建韩半岛和平进程的一个巨大成果，也明显不同于过去朝鲜一发起挑衅即撼动韩半岛局势的情况。虽然国内外仍有不少煽动对抗的势力，但正是全体国民对和平殷切的期盼推动我们走到今天这个阶段。韩朝美领导人6月底在板门店会晤后，朝美尝试进行工作层磋商讨论第三次首脑会谈事宜。这可能是韩半岛实现无核化和构建和平机制的过程中最重要的关卡。当下，韩朝美应集中力量推动朝美早日举行工作层磋商。哪怕事有不如意，但打破对话局面或设限让对话变得困难的做法不值得提倡。如果有不满意也应在对话的框架下提出问题，并讨论解决方案。希望全民万众一心，推动对话顺利通过最后一个关卡。若顺利通过这一关，韩半岛将朝着无核化的目标迈近一大步，韩朝关系也将取得重大进展。待经济合作提速、和平经济时代开启后，统一也会自然而然地实现。国际货币基金组织预测韩国将引领第四次工业革命，2024年左右人均收入将超过4万美元。如果韩朝在维持各自体制的基础上合聚力量，我们将能开启8000万民族市场，韩半岛统一后有望成为全球第6大经济体。国内外研究显示，人均收入到2050年左右可以达到7-8万美元。无可置疑，和平与统一带来的经济利益是巨大的。韩朝企业也将迎来全新的市场和机会。韩朝不仅可以省下巨额国防费用，还可以减少"韩国折价"（Korea Discount）这种无形的分裂费用，找到低增长、低生育、老龄化的解决方案。最重要的是，要像迎来光复那天那样在全民心中种下希望与热情，没有比这个更大的经济增长动力。从釜山到蔚山、浦项、东海、江陵、束草、元山、罗津、先锋的环东海经济圈将经符拉迪沃斯托克与大陆经济、北极航线、日本相连，实现海洋经济发展；从丽水、木浦、群山、仁川到海州、南浦、新义州的环黄海经济圈将把全罗南道"蓝色经济"、"新万金"的环保新产业与开城工业园区、南浦、新义州对接，推进高端产业园建设，最终完成面向中国、东盟、印度市场的宏伟的经济战略布局。朝鲜也调整了国家战略，引入市场经济体制，大力推动经济建设。国际社会承诺，只要朝鲜弃核，将大力支援其经济发展。我们不是要单方面向朝鲜提供帮助，而是维持各自现有体制，携手奔向互利共赢的康庄大道，从而为全球增长做出贡献。政府将通过发展和平经济打造新增长动力。我们不能再将精力耗费在分裂的历史上，而是要把所有力量投入到发展和平经济，开启"新韩半岛"之门。如果韩朝携起手勇下主导韩半岛命运的决心，我们定能获得成功。只有结束分裂，我们的光复才算完整，我们的国家才能任谁都无法动摇。有人说，朝鲜不断射弹谈何和平经济，然而我们拥有强大无比的防卫力量。我们严密注视倾力防备，不让韩半岛紧张局势升级，我们最终的目标不是对抗，而是对话。希望大家认识到，目前美国和朝鲜持续进行对话，日本也在推进与朝对话，希望我们不要成为固执于意识形态的落伍者。我们需要国民团结一致的力量，希望全体国民同心协力，同舟共济。尊敬的全体国民，独立有功人士和其家属，以及旅外同胞们！在今天光复节之际，我决心在任期内巩固推进无核化与和平机制，并在此基础上开启和平经济，走向统一。为了让韩朝一道播下的"和平之春"的种子茁壮成长为"繁荣之树"，我们要发展对话推进合作。我承诺，为了在2032年由首尔和平壤成功联办奥运会，在2045年迎接光复节100周年时让和平统一的国家（One Korea）屹立于世界之林而奠定稳固的基础。临时政府确立"大韩民国"国号和宣布"民主共和国"成立已有百年。我们在这百年间不断反思，变得成熟。如今我们拥有能战胜任何危机的自信，实现韩半岛和平与繁荣的国民力量无比壮大，能够建立"谁都无法动摇的国家"。南岗李昇薰先生说过"我从未见过种子穿透层层重土发芽成长时，不靠自己，而是借助其他力量"。靠我们的力量战胜分裂走向和平统一之路，是发展为负责任的经济强国的捷径，也是我们赶超日本，将日本引导至东亚合作秩序的道路。引领韩半岛、东亚乃至世界和平与繁荣的"新韩半岛"正在等待我们。我们能够做到！谢谢！
&#13;
(8.15) 第74周年光復節慶祝辞
&#13;
　尊敬する国民の皆様、
&#13;
　独立有功者とそのご遺族の皆様、
&#13;
　海外同胞の皆様、
&#13;
　3.1独立運動と臨時政府樹立100周年となる今年、光復74周年記念式が特別に独立記念館で行われることを大変意義深いものであると考えております。
&#13;
　今日の大韓民国はいかなる苦難にも屈することなく、あきらめなかった独立先烈の強い精神が作り出したものです。
&#13;
「三角山が起きあがり、肩を踊らせて舞い、漢江の水が逆巻きたぎり立つその日」を渇望しながらすべてを捧げた先烈の熱い精神は、今この瞬間にも国民の胸に息づいています。
&#13;
　私は本日、独立先烈と有功者、そのご遺族の方々に深く敬意を表すると共に、光復のその日にあふれる気持ちで築き上げようとした国、そして本日、われわれがその意志を継承して作っていこうとする国を国民の皆様と一緒に描いてみようと思います。
&#13;
　われわれが夢見る国は「共に豊かになる国」、誰もが公正な機会に恵まれ失敗しても立ち直ることのできる国です。
&#13;
　われわれが夢見る国は、莞島(ワンド)に暮らす島村の少女が(南の)蔚山で水素産業を学び、(北の)南浦で起業してモンゴルやシベリアにエコカーを輸出する国です。(北の)会寧で育った少年が釜山の海洋学校を卒業し、アセアンとインド洋、南米のチリまでをつなぐコンテナ船の航海士になる国です。
&#13;
農業を専攻した青年がアムール川辺で南北とロシアの農民たちと大規模な大豆栽培を行い、その青年の弟は(南の)瑞山で兄の大豆を餌にして牛を育てる国です。
&#13;
　豆満江を渡り大陸へと、太平洋を越えてアセアンとインドへと、われわれの暮らしと想像力が広がる国です。われわれの経済活動エリアが韓半島南部を超え、隣国と協力しながら共に繁栄していく国です。
&#13;
　「溶鉱炉に火をつけよ、新しい国の心臓に鉄線を引いて鉄筋を伸ばし鉄板も延ばそう。セメントと鉄と希望の上に誰も揺るがすことのできない新しい国を築いていこう」
&#13;
　解放直後、ある詩人は光復を迎えた新しい国の夢についてこう詠いました。
&#13;
　「誰も揺るがすことのできない新しい国」。それは外国の侵略や支配から解放された新興独立国として持つべき当然の夢でした。
&#13;
　そして74年が経った今、われわれは世界トップ6の製造大国、世界トップ6の輸出大国の立派な経済力を持つようになりました。国民所得3万ドル時代を切り開き、金九先生が願望していた文化国家という夢も実現しつつあります。
&#13;
　しかし「誰も揺るがすことのできない国」はまだ実現できていません。それはわれわれがまだ十分強くないためであり、われわれがまだ分断状態にあるためです。
&#13;
　私は本日、改めていかなる危機にも毅然として対処してきた国民を思いながら、われわれが作りたい国、「誰も揺るがすことのできない国」を誓います。
&#13;
　尊敬する国民の皆様、われわれは自由貿易秩序に基づいて半導体、IT、バイオなどわれわれの得意な産業に集中することができました。国際分業体制の下でどの国も自国の強みを活かして成功を夢見ることができました。
&#13;
　近代化に立ち遅れていた東アジアは分業と協業により再び経済発展を成し遂げました。世界はそれを「東アジアの奇跡」と呼びました。
&#13;
　侵略と紛争の時期がなかったわけではありませんが、東アジアにはそれよりはるかに長い交流と貿易の歴史があります。青銅器文化から現代文明にいたるまで東アジアは互いに伝播し、共有し合いました。人類歴史の中でもっとも長い交流と協力が行われ、共に文明の発展を果たしました。
&#13;
　光復はわれわれだけに嬉しいものではありませんでした。清日戦争と露日戦争、満州事変と中日戦争、太平洋戦争にいたるまで、60年以上にわたる長い戦争が終わった日であり、東アジア独立の日でもありました。日本国民も軍国主義の抑圧から抜け出し侵略戦争から解放されました。
&#13;
　われわれは過去に留まることなく日本と安保・経済協力を続けてきました。日本と共に日帝強制占領期における被害者の苦しみを実質的に癒すために取り組み、歴史を鏡とし固く手を結ぼうとする立場を堅持してきました。
&#13;
　過去を省察するのは過去にこだわることではなく過去から立ち直り未来へと進むことです。日本が隣国を不幸にした過去を省察する中で、東アジアの平和と繁栄を共にけん引していくことをわれわれは望んでいます。
&#13;
　協力してこそ共に発展し、その発展が持続できるものです。世界は高度の分業体制により共同繁栄を実現してきました。日本経済も自由貿易の秩序の下で分業を行い、発展してきました。
&#13;
　国際分業体制の下で、どの国であろうと自国が優位にある部門を武器化すれば平和な自由貿易秩序は壊れてしまいます。先に成長を達成した国がその後を追って成長している国のハシゴを蹴り飛ばしてはいけません。
&#13;
　今からでも日本が対話と協力の道へと出るのであれば、われわれは快くその手を握るはずです。公正に貿易して協力する東アジアを一緒に作っていきます。
&#13;
　昨年の平昌冬季五輪に続き来年には東京夏季五輪、2022年には北京冬季五輪が開催されます。五輪史上初の東アジアでのリレー開催です。東アジアが友好と協力の土台をしっかりと固め共同繁栄の道へと進む絶好のチャンスです。
&#13;
　世界の人々が平昌で「平和の韓半島」を目撃したように、東京五輪で友好と協力の希望を持てるようになることを願います。
&#13;
　われわれは東アジアの未来世代が協力による繁栄を経験できるように、われわれに与えられた責任を果たします。
&#13;
　尊敬する国民の皆様、今日のわれわれは過去のわれわれではありません。今日の大韓民国は数多くの挑戦と試練を乗り越え、さらに強くなり、成熟した大韓民国です。
&#13;
　私は本日「誰も揺るがすことのできない国」、われわれが作りたい「新しい韓半島」を目指して３つの目標を提案します。
&#13;
　第一に、責任ある経済大国として自由貿易の秩序を守り、東アジアの平等な協力を引き出したいと思います。
&#13;
　わが国民が奇跡のように成し遂げた経済発展の成果と底力は分け合うことはできても、奪われるわけにはいきません。経済での主権がしっかりしているとき、われわれは自らの運命の主人となり、ぐらつかなくなります。
&#13;
　統合された国民の力は危機を機会へと変え、挑戦はわれわれをさらに強く、大きくしました。
&#13;
　われわれは中東の熱砂も、太平洋の波も恐れることなく経済を成長させました。軽工業、重化学工業、情報通信産業を次々と育成し、世界的なIT大国となりました。今や5Gなど世界の技術標準をリードする国となりました。
&#13;
　今までわれわれは先進国を追いかけてきましたが、今は率先して挑戦し、先導する経済へと生まれ変わりつつあります。日本の不当な輸出規制に立ち向かい、われわれは責任ある経済大国への道を地道に歩んで参ります。
&#13;
　わが国の経済構造を包容と共生の生態系へと変化させます。大中小企業と労使の共生協力により素材・部品・装備産業の競争力強化に力を入れます。科学者と技術者の挑戦を応援し、失敗を尊重することにより誰も揺るがすことのできない経済を作ります。
&#13;
　われわれに不備があるところを省察しながらも自らを卑下せず共に激励し合うとき、われわれは目標を成し遂げることができると信じています。
&#13;
　われわれは経済力にふさわしい責任を持ってより大きく協力し、より広く開放することで隣国と共に成長していきます。
&#13;
　第二に、大陸と海洋を問わず平和と繁栄を先導する橋梁国家になろうとしています。
&#13;
　地政学的に4国もの大国に囲まれた国は世界にわれわれしかありません。われわれがみすぼらしく力がないときは、韓半島は大陸でも海洋でも辺境になり、ときには諸大国が角逐する場となりました。それがわれわれが経験した過去の歴史でした。
&#13;
　しかし、われわれが力をもつと大陸と海洋をつなぐ国、北東アジアの平和と繁栄の秩序を先導する国になれます。われわれは地政学的位置をわれわれの強みに変えていかなければなりません。これ以上、他に振り回されず主導していくというしっかりとした目標をもつべきです。
&#13;
　かつて臨時政府の趙素昻先生は人と人、民族と民族、国と国の間の均等を唱えました。それが平和と繁栄に向けたわれわれの基本精神です。
&#13;
　わが国民が日本の経済報復に対して成熟した対応を示しているのもまた、わが国の経済を護り抜こうとする強い意志を持ちながらも、両国国民同士では友好が損なわれないことを願う高い水準の国民意識があるからです。
&#13;
　わが政府が推進する「人間中心の共生繁栄に向けた平和共同体」は、われわれからスタートして韓半島全体と東アジア、さらには世界の平和と繁栄にまで拡大していこうとするものです。
&#13;
　新北方政策は大陸に向かって走っていくわれわれの抱負です。中国やロシアだけでなく、中央アジアと欧州にまで協力の土台を拡大し、北東アジア鉄道共同体により多国間協力、多国間安保の礎を築きます。
&#13;
　新南方政策は海洋に向かって走っていくわれわれの抱負です。アセアンおよびインドとの関係を主要周辺国レベルまで格上げし、共同繁栄の協力関係へと発展させていきます。
&#13;
　今年11月には韓-アセアン特別首脳会議と韓-メコン首脳会議が釜山で開かれます。それらはアセアンおよびメコン諸国との画期的な関係発展を図る道しるべになるはずです。
&#13;
　南北の間で途絶えた鉄路と道路をつなぐことは、東アジアの平和と繁栄を先導する橋梁国家へと進む第一歩です。韓半島の地と空、海に人や物流が行き来する血脈(道)をつなぎ、南北が大陸と海洋を自由に出入りすることができれば、韓半島はユーラシアと太平洋、アセアン、インド洋をつなぐ繁栄の土台になるはずです。
&#13;
　アジア共同体はある1国が主導する共同体でなく、平等な国同士の多様な協力が花開く共同体になることでしょう。
&#13;
　第三に、平和により繁栄を実現する平和経済を構築し、統一によって独立を完成していきたいと思います。
&#13;
　分断体制を乗り越え、民族のエネルギーを未来繁栄の動力にしていかなければなりません。
&#13;
　平和経済は、韓半島の完全なる非核化を土台に、北韓が核ではなく経済と繁栄を選ぶよう対話と協力を続けていくことから始まります。
&#13;
　南北と米国は、この1年8ヶ月間、対話の局面を続けました。最近北韓による数回の懸念すべき行動にもかかわらず対話ムードが揺らいでいないことこそ、政府が進めてきた韓半島平和プロセスの大きな成果であります。一度の北韓の挑発により韓半島が揺さぶられたこれまでの状況とは大きく様変わりしています。 依然として対立を煽る勢力が国内外に少なからず存在しますが、わが国民の平和への切実な願望に支えられ、ここまで辿り着くことができました。
&#13;
　今年6月末の板門店会談以降、第3回北米首脳会談に向けた北米間の実務者交渉が模索されています。おそらくこれは、韓半島の非核化と平和構築に向けた全過程における最も重大な山場になると思います。南・北・米の三国が、北米の実務者交渉の早期開催に力を集中しなければならない時期です。
&#13;
　不満なところがあるとしても、対話ムードを壊したり、壁を立てて対話を妨げたりするのは決して望ましくありません。不満があるならば、それも対話の場で問題を提起し、議論すべきであります。国民の皆様にも、対話の最後の山を乗り切ることができるよう、ご声援のほど、よろしくお願いいたします。
&#13;
　この危機を乗り越えれば韓半島の非核化がより一層近付き、南北関係も大きく前進するはずです。経済協力が加速し、平和経済が始まれば、いずれ自ずと統一は目の前の現実になると思います。
&#13;
　IMF(国際通貨基金)は、韓国が第4次産業革命をリードし、2024年頃には一人当たり国民所得が4万ドルを突破するとの見通しを示しています。
&#13;
　そこに南北の能力を合わせれば、それぞれの体制を維持しながらも8千万人規模の単一市場を生み出すことができます。韓半島が統一を果たすことになれば、世界第6位圏の経済大国になるとの見通しを示しています。2050年頃には国民所得7万~8万ドル時代を達成できるという国内外の研究結果も出ています。
&#13;
　平和と統一がもたらす経済利益が非常に大きくなるということは明らかです。南北の企業にも新しい市場とチャンスが広がります。南北はいずれも膨大な国防費はもちろん、「コリアディスカウント」という無形の分断費用を削減することができます。今われわれが経験している低成長、少子高齢化の解決策も見出せるはずです。
&#13;
　しかし、何よりも光復のあの日のように、わが民族の心に芽生える希望と情熱が大事です。希望と情熱より大きな経済の成長エンジンはありません。
&#13;
　釜山からスタートして蔚山と浦項、東海と江陵、束草、元山と羅津・先鋒へと続く環東海経済は、ウラジオストクを経由する大陸経済、北極航路と日本をつなぐ海洋経済へ伸びていくはずです。
&#13;
　麗水と木浦からスタートして群山、仁川を経て海州と南浦、新義州へと続く環黄海経済は、全羅南道のブルーエコノミーやセマングムの再生可能エネルギー新産業、そして開城工業団地と南浦、新義州へと続く先端産業団地の育成により、中国・アセアン・インドに向けた雄大な経済戦略を完成することになります。
&#13;
　北韓も経済建設総路線へと国家政策を切り替え、市場経済の導入が行われています。国際社会も北韓が核を放棄すれば、経済成長を支援すると約束しています。
&#13;
　北韓を一方的に助けようとするわけではありません。互いの体制の安全を保障しながら、南北両方の利益を図り、両方の繁栄を目指そうということです。世界経済の発展に、南北が一緒に貢献したいということです。
&#13;
　平和経済を通じてわが国経済の新成長エンジンを作っていきます。われわれの力をこれ以上、分断に消耗するわけにはいきません。平和経済にわれわれがもつ全てを注ぎ込んで、「新しい韓半島」の扉を切り開いていきます。
&#13;
　南北が手を携えて韓半島の運命を主導しようとする意志があれば実現できることです。分断を乗り越えるときに、ようやくわれわれの光復は完成し、誰も揺るがすことのできない国になるはずです。
&#13;
　「北韓はミサイルを打ち上げるのに平和経済を語るのか」と反論する人たちがいます。しかし、われわれはあちらより強力な防衛力を保有しています。
&#13;
われわれは状況を注視しながら、韓半島の緊張が高まらないように管理に万全を期していますが、それも究極の目標は対立ではなく、対話にあります。
&#13;
米国が動揺せず北韓と対話を続け、日本も対話を進めているという現実を直視していただきたいと思います。理念にとらわれて自ら孤立しないでいただきたいと思います。
&#13;
　われわれの団結した力が絶対に必要です。国民の皆様も志を同じくして、同行してください。
&#13;
　尊敬する国民の皆様、
&#13;
　独立有功者とご遺族の皆様、
&#13;
　海外同胞の皆様、
&#13;
　私は本日、光復節を迎え任期内に非核化と平和体制を確固たるものにすると誓います。
&#13;
その土台の上で平和経済に着手し、統一に向けて歩んでいきます。
&#13;
　北韓と共に「平和の春」に蒔いた種が「繁栄の木」に育つように、対話と協力を発展させていきます。
&#13;
　2032年にはソウルー平壌共同五輪を成功開催し、2045年の光復100周年には平和と統一で一つになった国(One Korea)として世界にしっかり位置づけられるよう、その土台を強固に築いていくと約束します。
&#13;
　臨時政府が「大韓民国」という国号とともに「民主共和国」を宣布してから100年が経ちました。
&#13;
　われわれは100年間省察し、成熟しました。もはやどのような危機も乗り越えられる自信を持てるようになり、平和と繁栄の韓半島を実現するための国民の能力が高まりました。われわれは「誰も揺るがすことのできない国」をつくることができます。
&#13;
　南岡・李昇薫先生のお言葉をかみ締めます。
&#13;
　「私は種が地の下から重い土を持ち上げて芽立つ時、自分の力でない他の力を借りて上がってくるのを見たことがない」
&#13;
　われわれの力で分断を乗り越え、平和と統一へ進む道こそ、責任ある経済大国への近道となります。われわれが日本を追い越す道であり、日本を東アジア協力の秩序へと導く道です。
&#13;
　韓半島と東アジア、世界の平和と繁栄をけん引する「新しい韓半島」がわれわれを待っています。
&#13;
　われわれはできます。
&#13;
　ありがとうございました。</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>戴里克·伯格: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 戴里克·伯格 于 2019-8-16 12:10 编辑 </span><br>
<span>佐塚間桐 发表于 2019-8-16 11:34</span><br>
<span>是通报了所谓的日本朝鲜通讯社。</span><br>
<span>只是BBC没有直接引用朝中社的信息源而已，是这个所谓的日本朝鲜通讯社看到朝中社的消息写了个稿</span><br>
<span>金正恩的名字是2010年10月8日正式对外公布的，劳动党第三次全国代表大会</span><br>
<span>http://news.cntv.cn/world/20101009/102438.shtml</span><br>
<span>作为明显更加亲密的相关方，CCTV9日就进行了报道，并且提到了金正恩的官方名，还早于10日BBC的转发报道</span><br>
<span>另外作为一个神弃之地朝鲜半岛相关问题的前研究员，我可以负责的告诉你，朝鲜所有官员的汉字名只有外交部和外联部能比朝中社的官方更早知道，甚至韩国统一部和国情院对外公布资料中（可以对比https://www.unikorea.go.kr/cn_unikorea/和www.kcna.kp在朝鲜人民议会选举时出现的官员名称），朝鲜官员的中文汉字写法对比下都不够正确，日媒从来都没被当做过朝鲜对外沟通的窗口呢</span><br>
</p><p><b>机动妖精: </b><br>
<span>文总统也要平三藩</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 有消息提醒的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>semerita: </b><br>
<span>chenzj8309 发表于 2019-8-15 20:06</span><br>
<span>这么说吧：</span><br>
<span>北方人均国民生产总值只有南方的4%</span><br>
<span>悲观的人一看：靠，北方佬那么穷，怎么能消费我们南方的产 ...</span><br>
<span>其实这种都是一个硬币的两个面。你说的是好的一面，我想说的是还有坏的一面。</span><br>
<span>朝鲜想要生产，南边要投资，要有外资投资法。现阶段朝鲜压根就没有外资投资相关的法律和基本意识，也就是说比如南边的工厂要去北面生产招工，工人要有自主就业的意识才行。现阶段朝鲜工作都是国家分配制，如果要调动积极性利用资本主义制度的优越性，那么势必要进行改革。在中国改革阶段出现过的问题，朝鲜一个不可能少。腐败贪污，双轨制，户口制，乃至国民基层组织的退出，都是影响到朝鲜国本的问题。</span><br>
<span>就算是中国的改革开放，也不是一蹴而就的。按朝鲜的体制，要搞类似于中国的改革开放是很难的，完全取决于某领导人的想法。在解决这一系列问题之前就大谈基建，投资合作，一带一路，振兴远东，新北方政策。是不是有点步子迈的太大了点。</span><br>
</p><p><b>卫星露天咖啡屋: </b><br>
<span>上面几楼的三语大乱斗给我看傻了都</span><br>
</p><p><b>王怡人: </b><br>
<span>卫星露天咖啡屋 发表于 2019-8-16 12:35</span><br>
<span>上面几楼的三语大乱斗给我看傻了都</span><br>
<span>因为似乎有个真的朝鲜问题专家......</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1853629[50-100]</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>文在寅光复节演说（韩联社中日双语版）[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1853629-1-1.html</link>
      <description>文在寅光复节演说（韩联社中日双语版）&#13;
 本帖最后由 chenzj8309 于 2019-8-15 15:59 编辑 

尊敬的全体国民，独立有功人士和其家属，以及旅外同胞们：在迎来三一独立运动和临时政府成立100周年的今天，我们在独立纪念馆举行光复74周年纪念仪式，意义深远。今天的大韩民国是先烈们以百折不挠、坚韧不拔的精神造就的。他们渴望"三角山翩翩跳舞，汉江水喷涌而出的那一天"到来，奉献自己一切的那股精神永远活在国民心中。今天，我要向先烈们、有功人士及其家属致以深深的敬意，和全体国民一道描绘祖国光复那天普罗大众以激动的心情梦想的国家，继承先贤遗志共同建设理想国度。我们所梦想的国家是一起幸福生活的国家，是所有人都有公平的机会，即使失败了也能重新站起来的国家。我们所梦想的国家是韩国西部莞岛的少女在东部蔚山学习氢工业，去朝鲜南浦创业，向蒙古和西伯利亚出口环保汽车的国家；是在朝鲜会宁长大的少年在韩国釜山海洋大学读书，毕业后成为一名船舶驾驶员，驾驶一艘集装箱船前往东盟国家、印度洋、南美智利的国家；是农业专业的青年在阿穆尔江畔与韩朝俄三国的农夫一起耕种大面积的豆田，而身在韩国瑞山的弟弟用哥哥生产的豆子喂牛的国家；是跨越豆满江通往大陆，横跨太平洋前往东盟国家和印度，生活与想象力被无限放大的国家；是经济活动范围超出韩半岛南方一侧，与周边国家合作共赢的国家。"点起熔炉之火，在新国家的心脏抽铁丝，添钢筋，搭铁板，在混凝土、铁和希望之上建设一个谁都无法动摇的新的国家。"解放后，一位诗人如此歌颂迎来光复的新国家之梦。"谁都无法动摇的新的国家"，这是摆脱外来势力的侵略和统治的新生独立国家本该拥有的梦想。从那之后74年后的今天，我们成为世界第6大制造强国和第6大出口强国，具备强有力的经济实力。我们开启了人均收入3万美元时代，并在逐渐实现金九先生所追求的"文化国家"的梦想。但我们还没能建设"谁都无法动摇的国家"，这是因为我们还不够强大，祖国仍处于分裂状态。看到以毅然的态度面对一切危机的国民，今天我再次下决心，定要把祖国建设成我们所梦想的"谁都无法动摇的国家"。尊敬的全体国民！我们遵守自由贸易秩序，集中发展了半导体、IT、生物等我们可以做好的产业。在国际分工体系中，任何一个国家都能梦想凭借自身优势获得成功。在近代化过程中一度落后的东亚基于分工和协作再次实现经济腾飞，全球称之为"东亚的奇迹"。东亚有过侵略和战争，但与之相比，人员交流和贸易往来的历史更长。从青铜器文化到现代文明，东亚各国互相传播文化和共享文明，实现了人类历史上最长时间的交流与合作。光复节不光是我们的好日子，也是甲午战争、俄日战争、满洲事变、中日战争、太平洋战争这60多年一系列战争结束的日子，是整个东亚光复的日子。日本国民同样摆脱军国主义的压迫，从侵略战争中解放出来。我们没有停留在过去，而是不断与日本在安全、经济领域开展合作，尝试与日本一道疗愈日本殖民统治时期受害者的伤痛，我们以史为镜，坚持携手合作的立场。反省历史并不意味着停留在过去，而是要摆脱历史走向未来。我们希望日本反省给邻国带去的不幸历史，与我们一道引领东亚的和平与繁荣。只有合作才能携手发展，才能实现可持续发展。世界通过高度的分工机制实现了共同繁荣，日本经济也同样在自由贸易的秩序中实现分工和发展。在国际分工机制中，任何国家若把自身优势领域作为武器，就无法维持和平的自由贸易秩序，先发展起来的国家绝不能剥夺后起发展国家的机会。若日本此刻走对话与合作之路，我们愿意配合，并将与其一道打造公平贸易与合作的东亚。去年韩国举办了平昌冬奥会，明年日本将办东京奥运，2022年中国将办北京冬奥会，这是奥运历史上首次由东亚地区接力办赛。这将是东亚巩固友好合作基础，走向共同繁荣之路的良机。正如全世界人民在平昌见证了"和平韩半岛"一般，希望东京奥运会也能带来友好与合作的希望。为了让东亚的下一代看到通过合作实现繁荣，我们将竭尽所能。尊敬的全体国民!今天的大韩民国已非昔日的大韩民国，而是克服无数挑战和折磨变得更加坚强和成熟的大韩民国。为了建设我们所梦想的"全新的韩半岛——谁都无法动摇的国家"，我提出如下三个目标:——第一，作为负责任的经济强国，维护全球自由贸易秩序，促进东亚地区的平等合作。韩国国民造就了奇迹般的经济发展，其成果和潜力可与世分享，但不能被夺走。我们只有掌握经济主权，才能作为韩半岛命运的主宰者，不为外力所动摇。全体国民凝聚力量将危机化为机遇，挑战会让我们变得更强大。无论是中东炙热的沙漠，还是太平洋的大浪，我们都毫不畏惧，一心实现经济发展。我们先后发展轻工业、重化工业、信息通信产业，最终成为了名副其实的IT强国，如今还引领5G等全球技术标准。过去，我们努力追赶发达国家，而今率先迎接挑战，逐步实现经济领先。面对日本政府不当的限贸措施，我们坚持走负责任的经济强国之路。政府将把现有经济结构转变为"包容、共赢"的经济生态系统，通过促进大中小企业之间、劳资之间的合作，提升材料、零部件、设备产业的国际竞争力。我们还将营造鼓励科学家和技术工人敢于挑战、包容失败的社会氛围，打造谁都无法动摇的经济强国。我相信，只要审视自己的不足，不自卑，互励共勉，就能做到这一切。我们将以与经济实力相应的责任感，进一步扩大开放合作，与邻国共同发展。——第二，连接大陆与海洋，为实现全球和平与繁荣发挥桥梁作用。从地缘政治角度看，韩国是世界上唯一一个被四大强国包围环绕的国家。当我们的力量渺小时，无论在陆地还是在海洋都被排挤在边缘，有时甚至沦为强国角逐的角斗场。这就是我们经历过的历史。不过，只要我们拥有力量，就能成为连接大陆和海洋、引导东北亚和平与繁荣的领袖国家。我们应把地缘政治上的劣势转化为优势，并制定明确的目标，主动开辟未来，而不是被外力所左右。大韩民国临时政府要人赵素昻先生曾提倡人与人、民族与民族、国与国之间建立平等关系。这是我们追求和平与繁荣的基本精神。面对日本的经济报复措施，全体国民齐心协力守护国家利益，同时保证两国友好关系不受损害，这是因为韩国国民拥有成熟的公民意识。韩国政府所推进的"以人为本、互利共赢的和平共同体"旨在实现韩半岛、东亚乃至世界的和平与繁荣。"新北方政策"是开辟通往大陆之路的远大构想。除了中国和俄罗斯之外，我们将把合作范围扩展至中亚和欧洲地区，并通过东北亚铁路共同体奠定多边合作、多边安保的基础。"新南方政策"是开辟通往海洋之路的远大构想。我们将与东盟和印度的双边关系升级为与周边主要国家相同的水平，发展成互利共赢的合作关系。今年11月，韩国-东盟特别峰会和韩国-湄公峰会将在釜山举行，这将是推动韩国与东盟、韩国与湄公国家关系发展的又一划时代的里程碑。连接韩朝铁路和公路是韩国为实现东北亚和平与繁荣迈出的第一步。若韩朝实现陆、海、空全方位互联互通，打通物流动脉，恢复人员往来，半岛将变成连接亚欧大陆、太平洋、东盟以及印度洋的重要关口。届时，亚洲共同体将会绽放合作之花，而非由任何一国主导。——第三，通过构建以和平促繁荣的和平经济，以统一实现完整的光复。我们要克服分裂，将民族的能量升华为实现未来繁荣的动力。和平经济是基于半岛完全无核化，始于通过对话与合作让朝鲜弃核并选择走向繁荣的战略。在过去的1年8个月间，韩朝美三方始终保持对话势头。近来，朝鲜几番做出令人担忧的行为，但对话的势头没有因此受到影响，这是韩国政府推进构建韩半岛和平进程的一个巨大成果，也明显不同于过去朝鲜一发起挑衅即撼动韩半岛局势的情况。虽然国内外仍有不少煽动对抗的势力，但正是全体国民对和平殷切的期盼推动我们走到今天这个阶段。韩朝美领导人6月底在板门店会晤后，朝美尝试进行工作层磋商讨论第三次首脑会谈事宜。这可能是韩半岛实现无核化和构建和平机制的过程中最重要的关卡。当下，韩朝美应集中力量推动朝美早日举行工作层磋商。哪怕事有不如意，但打破对话局面或设限让对话变得困难的做法不值得提倡。如果有不满意也应在对话的框架下提出问题，并讨论解决方案。希望全民万众一心，推动对话顺利通过最后一个关卡。若顺利通过这一关，韩半岛将朝着无核化的目标迈近一大步，韩朝关系也将取得重大进展。待经济合作提速、和平经济时代开启后，统一也会自然而然地实现。国际货币基金组织预测韩国将引领第四次工业革命，2024年左右人均收入将超过4万美元。如果韩朝在维持各自体制的基础上合聚力量，我们将能开启8000万民族市场，韩半岛统一后有望成为全球第6大经济体。国内外研究显示，人均收入到2050年左右可以达到7-8万美元。无可置疑，和平与统一带来的经济利益是巨大的。韩朝企业也将迎来全新的市场和机会。韩朝不仅可以省下巨额国防费用，还可以减少"韩国折价"（Korea Discount）这种无形的分裂费用，找到低增长、低生育、老龄化的解决方案。最重要的是，要像迎来光复那天那样在全民心中种下希望与热情，没有比这个更大的经济增长动力。从釜山到蔚山、浦项、东海、江陵、束草、元山、罗津、先锋的环东海经济圈将经符拉迪沃斯托克与大陆经济、北极航线、日本相连，实现海洋经济发展；从丽水、木浦、群山、仁川到海州、南浦、新义州的环黄海经济圈将把全罗南道"蓝色经济"、"新万金"的环保新产业与开城工业园区、南浦、新义州对接，推进高端产业园建设，最终完成面向中国、东盟、印度市场的宏伟的经济战略布局。朝鲜也调整了国家战略，引入市场经济体制，大力推动经济建设。国际社会承诺，只要朝鲜弃核，将大力支援其经济发展。我们不是要单方面向朝鲜提供帮助，而是维持各自现有体制，携手奔向互利共赢的康庄大道，从而为全球增长做出贡献。政府将通过发展和平经济打造新增长动力。我们不能再将精力耗费在分裂的历史上，而是要把所有力量投入到发展和平经济，开启"新韩半岛"之门。如果韩朝携起手勇下主导韩半岛命运的决心，我们定能获得成功。只有结束分裂，我们的光复才算完整，我们的国家才能任谁都无法动摇。有人说，朝鲜不断射弹谈何和平经济，然而我们拥有强大无比的防卫力量。我们严密注视倾力防备，不让韩半岛紧张局势升级，我们最终的目标不是对抗，而是对话。希望大家认识到，目前美国和朝鲜持续进行对话，日本也在推进与朝对话，希望我们不要成为固执于意识形态的落伍者。我们需要国民团结一致的力量，希望全体国民同心协力，同舟共济。尊敬的全体国民，独立有功人士和其家属，以及旅外同胞们！在今天光复节之际，我决心在任期内巩固推进无核化与和平机制，并在此基础上开启和平经济，走向统一。为了让韩朝一道播下的"和平之春"的种子茁壮成长为"繁荣之树"，我们要发展对话推进合作。我承诺，为了在2032年由首尔和平壤成功联办奥运会，在2045年迎接光复节100周年时让和平统一的国家（One Korea）屹立于世界之林而奠定稳固的基础。临时政府确立"大韩民国"国号和宣布"民主共和国"成立已有百年。我们在这百年间不断反思，变得成熟。如今我们拥有能战胜任何危机的自信，实现韩半岛和平与繁荣的国民力量无比壮大，能够建立"谁都无法动摇的国家"。南岗李昇薰先生说过"我从未见过种子穿透层层重土发芽成长时，不靠自己，而是借助其他力量"。靠我们的力量战胜分裂走向和平统一之路，是发展为负责任的经济强国的捷径，也是我们赶超日本，将日本引导至东亚合作秩序的道路。引领韩半岛、东亚乃至世界和平与繁荣的"新韩半岛"正在等待我们。我们能够做到！谢谢！
&#13;
(8.15) 第74周年光復節慶祝辞
&#13;
　尊敬する国民の皆様、
&#13;
　独立有功者とそのご遺族の皆様、
&#13;
　海外同胞の皆様、
&#13;
　3.1独立運動と臨時政府樹立100周年となる今年、光復74周年記念式が特別に独立記念館で行われることを大変意義深いものであると考えております。
&#13;
　今日の大韓民国はいかなる苦難にも屈することなく、あきらめなかった独立先烈の強い精神が作り出したものです。
&#13;
「三角山が起きあがり、肩を踊らせて舞い、漢江の水が逆巻きたぎり立つその日」を渇望しながらすべてを捧げた先烈の熱い精神は、今この瞬間にも国民の胸に息づいています。
&#13;
　私は本日、独立先烈と有功者、そのご遺族の方々に深く敬意を表すると共に、光復のその日にあふれる気持ちで築き上げようとした国、そして本日、われわれがその意志を継承して作っていこうとする国を国民の皆様と一緒に描いてみようと思います。
&#13;
　われわれが夢見る国は「共に豊かになる国」、誰もが公正な機会に恵まれ失敗しても立ち直ることのできる国です。
&#13;
　われわれが夢見る国は、莞島(ワンド)に暮らす島村の少女が(南の)蔚山で水素産業を学び、(北の)南浦で起業してモンゴルやシベリアにエコカーを輸出する国です。(北の)会寧で育った少年が釜山の海洋学校を卒業し、アセアンとインド洋、南米のチリまでをつなぐコンテナ船の航海士になる国です。
&#13;
農業を専攻した青年がアムール川辺で南北とロシアの農民たちと大規模な大豆栽培を行い、その青年の弟は(南の)瑞山で兄の大豆を餌にして牛を育てる国です。
&#13;
　豆満江を渡り大陸へと、太平洋を越えてアセアンとインドへと、われわれの暮らしと想像力が広がる国です。われわれの経済活動エリアが韓半島南部を超え、隣国と協力しながら共に繁栄していく国です。
&#13;
　「溶鉱炉に火をつけよ、新しい国の心臓に鉄線を引いて鉄筋を伸ばし鉄板も延ばそう。セメントと鉄と希望の上に誰も揺るがすことのできない新しい国を築いていこう」
&#13;
　解放直後、ある詩人は光復を迎えた新しい国の夢についてこう詠いました。
&#13;
　「誰も揺るがすことのできない新しい国」。それは外国の侵略や支配から解放された新興独立国として持つべき当然の夢でした。
&#13;
　そして74年が経った今、われわれは世界トップ6の製造大国、世界トップ6の輸出大国の立派な経済力を持つようになりました。国民所得3万ドル時代を切り開き、金九先生が願望していた文化国家という夢も実現しつつあります。
&#13;
　しかし「誰も揺るがすことのできない国」はまだ実現できていません。それはわれわれがまだ十分強くないためであり、われわれがまだ分断状態にあるためです。
&#13;
　私は本日、改めていかなる危機にも毅然として対処してきた国民を思いながら、われわれが作りたい国、「誰も揺るがすことのできない国」を誓います。
&#13;
　尊敬する国民の皆様、われわれは自由貿易秩序に基づいて半導体、IT、バイオなどわれわれの得意な産業に集中することができました。国際分業体制の下でどの国も自国の強みを活かして成功を夢見ることができました。
&#13;
　近代化に立ち遅れていた東アジアは分業と協業により再び経済発展を成し遂げました。世界はそれを「東アジアの奇跡」と呼びました。
&#13;
　侵略と紛争の時期がなかったわけではありませんが、東アジアにはそれよりはるかに長い交流と貿易の歴史があります。青銅器文化から現代文明にいたるまで東アジアは互いに伝播し、共有し合いました。人類歴史の中でもっとも長い交流と協力が行われ、共に文明の発展を果たしました。
&#13;
　光復はわれわれだけに嬉しいものではありませんでした。清日戦争と露日戦争、満州事変と中日戦争、太平洋戦争にいたるまで、60年以上にわたる長い戦争が終わった日であり、東アジア独立の日でもありました。日本国民も軍国主義の抑圧から抜け出し侵略戦争から解放されました。
&#13;
　われわれは過去に留まることなく日本と安保・経済協力を続けてきました。日本と共に日帝強制占領期における被害者の苦しみを実質的に癒すために取り組み、歴史を鏡とし固く手を結ぼうとする立場を堅持してきました。
&#13;
　過去を省察するのは過去にこだわることではなく過去から立ち直り未来へと進むことです。日本が隣国を不幸にした過去を省察する中で、東アジアの平和と繁栄を共にけん引していくことをわれわれは望んでいます。
&#13;
　協力してこそ共に発展し、その発展が持続できるものです。世界は高度の分業体制により共同繁栄を実現してきました。日本経済も自由貿易の秩序の下で分業を行い、発展してきました。
&#13;
　国際分業体制の下で、どの国であろうと自国が優位にある部門を武器化すれば平和な自由貿易秩序は壊れてしまいます。先に成長を達成した国がその後を追って成長している国のハシゴを蹴り飛ばしてはいけません。
&#13;
　今からでも日本が対話と協力の道へと出るのであれば、われわれは快くその手を握るはずです。公正に貿易して協力する東アジアを一緒に作っていきます。
&#13;
　昨年の平昌冬季五輪に続き来年には東京夏季五輪、2022年には北京冬季五輪が開催されます。五輪史上初の東アジアでのリレー開催です。東アジアが友好と協力の土台をしっかりと固め共同繁栄の道へと進む絶好のチャンスです。
&#13;
　世界の人々が平昌で「平和の韓半島」を目撃したように、東京五輪で友好と協力の希望を持てるようになることを願います。
&#13;
　われわれは東アジアの未来世代が協力による繁栄を経験できるように、われわれに与えられた責任を果たします。
&#13;
　尊敬する国民の皆様、今日のわれわれは過去のわれわれではありません。今日の大韓民国は数多くの挑戦と試練を乗り越え、さらに強くなり、成熟した大韓民国です。
&#13;
　私は本日「誰も揺るがすことのできない国」、われわれが作りたい「新しい韓半島」を目指して３つの目標を提案します。
&#13;
　第一に、責任ある経済大国として自由貿易の秩序を守り、東アジアの平等な協力を引き出したいと思います。
&#13;
　わが国民が奇跡のように成し遂げた経済発展の成果と底力は分け合うことはできても、奪われるわけにはいきません。経済での主権がしっかりしているとき、われわれは自らの運命の主人となり、ぐらつかなくなります。
&#13;
　統合された国民の力は危機を機会へと変え、挑戦はわれわれをさらに強く、大きくしました。
&#13;
　われわれは中東の熱砂も、太平洋の波も恐れることなく経済を成長させました。軽工業、重化学工業、情報通信産業を次々と育成し、世界的なIT大国となりました。今や5Gなど世界の技術標準をリードする国となりました。
&#13;
　今までわれわれは先進国を追いかけてきましたが、今は率先して挑戦し、先導する経済へと生まれ変わりつつあります。日本の不当な輸出規制に立ち向かい、われわれは責任ある経済大国への道を地道に歩んで参ります。
&#13;
　わが国の経済構造を包容と共生の生態系へと変化させます。大中小企業と労使の共生協力により素材・部品・装備産業の競争力強化に力を入れます。科学者と技術者の挑戦を応援し、失敗を尊重することにより誰も揺るがすことのできない経済を作ります。
&#13;
　われわれに不備があるところを省察しながらも自らを卑下せず共に激励し合うとき、われわれは目標を成し遂げることができると信じています。
&#13;
　われわれは経済力にふさわしい責任を持ってより大きく協力し、より広く開放することで隣国と共に成長していきます。
&#13;
　第二に、大陸と海洋を問わず平和と繁栄を先導する橋梁国家になろうとしています。
&#13;
　地政学的に4国もの大国に囲まれた国は世界にわれわれしかありません。われわれがみすぼらしく力がないときは、韓半島は大陸でも海洋でも辺境になり、ときには諸大国が角逐する場となりました。それがわれわれが経験した過去の歴史でした。
&#13;
　しかし、われわれが力をもつと大陸と海洋をつなぐ国、北東アジアの平和と繁栄の秩序を先導する国になれます。われわれは地政学的位置をわれわれの強みに変えていかなければなりません。これ以上、他に振り回されず主導していくというしっかりとした目標をもつべきです。
&#13;
　かつて臨時政府の趙素昻先生は人と人、民族と民族、国と国の間の均等を唱えました。それが平和と繁栄に向けたわれわれの基本精神です。
&#13;
　わが国民が日本の経済報復に対して成熟した対応を示しているのもまた、わが国の経済を護り抜こうとする強い意志を持ちながらも、両国国民同士では友好が損なわれないことを願う高い水準の国民意識があるからです。
&#13;
　わが政府が推進する「人間中心の共生繁栄に向けた平和共同体」は、われわれからスタートして韓半島全体と東アジア、さらには世界の平和と繁栄にまで拡大していこうとするものです。
&#13;
　新北方政策は大陸に向かって走っていくわれわれの抱負です。中国やロシアだけでなく、中央アジアと欧州にまで協力の土台を拡大し、北東アジア鉄道共同体により多国間協力、多国間安保の礎を築きます。
&#13;
　新南方政策は海洋に向かって走っていくわれわれの抱負です。アセアンおよびインドとの関係を主要周辺国レベルまで格上げし、共同繁栄の協力関係へと発展させていきます。
&#13;
　今年11月には韓-アセアン特別首脳会議と韓-メコン首脳会議が釜山で開かれます。それらはアセアンおよびメコン諸国との画期的な関係発展を図る道しるべになるはずです。
&#13;
　南北の間で途絶えた鉄路と道路をつなぐことは、東アジアの平和と繁栄を先導する橋梁国家へと進む第一歩です。韓半島の地と空、海に人や物流が行き来する血脈(道)をつなぎ、南北が大陸と海洋を自由に出入りすることができれば、韓半島はユーラシアと太平洋、アセアン、インド洋をつなぐ繁栄の土台になるはずです。
&#13;
　アジア共同体はある1国が主導する共同体でなく、平等な国同士の多様な協力が花開く共同体になることでしょう。
&#13;
　第三に、平和により繁栄を実現する平和経済を構築し、統一によって独立を完成していきたいと思います。
&#13;
　分断体制を乗り越え、民族のエネルギーを未来繁栄の動力にしていかなければなりません。
&#13;
　平和経済は、韓半島の完全なる非核化を土台に、北韓が核ではなく経済と繁栄を選ぶよう対話と協力を続けていくことから始まります。
&#13;
　南北と米国は、この1年8ヶ月間、対話の局面を続けました。最近北韓による数回の懸念すべき行動にもかかわらず対話ムードが揺らいでいないことこそ、政府が進めてきた韓半島平和プロセスの大きな成果であります。一度の北韓の挑発により韓半島が揺さぶられたこれまでの状況とは大きく様変わりしています。 依然として対立を煽る勢力が国内外に少なからず存在しますが、わが国民の平和への切実な願望に支えられ、ここまで辿り着くことができました。
&#13;
　今年6月末の板門店会談以降、第3回北米首脳会談に向けた北米間の実務者交渉が模索されています。おそらくこれは、韓半島の非核化と平和構築に向けた全過程における最も重大な山場になると思います。南・北・米の三国が、北米の実務者交渉の早期開催に力を集中しなければならない時期です。
&#13;
　不満なところがあるとしても、対話ムードを壊したり、壁を立てて対話を妨げたりするのは決して望ましくありません。不満があるならば、それも対話の場で問題を提起し、議論すべきであります。国民の皆様にも、対話の最後の山を乗り切ることができるよう、ご声援のほど、よろしくお願いいたします。
&#13;
　この危機を乗り越えれば韓半島の非核化がより一層近付き、南北関係も大きく前進するはずです。経済協力が加速し、平和経済が始まれば、いずれ自ずと統一は目の前の現実になると思います。
&#13;
　IMF(国際通貨基金)は、韓国が第4次産業革命をリードし、2024年頃には一人当たり国民所得が4万ドルを突破するとの見通しを示しています。
&#13;
　そこに南北の能力を合わせれば、それぞれの体制を維持しながらも8千万人規模の単一市場を生み出すことができます。韓半島が統一を果たすことになれば、世界第6位圏の経済大国になるとの見通しを示しています。2050年頃には国民所得7万~8万ドル時代を達成できるという国内外の研究結果も出ています。
&#13;
　平和と統一がもたらす経済利益が非常に大きくなるということは明らかです。南北の企業にも新しい市場とチャンスが広がります。南北はいずれも膨大な国防費はもちろん、「コリアディスカウント」という無形の分断費用を削減することができます。今われわれが経験している低成長、少子高齢化の解決策も見出せるはずです。
&#13;
　しかし、何よりも光復のあの日のように、わが民族の心に芽生える希望と情熱が大事です。希望と情熱より大きな経済の成長エンジンはありません。
&#13;
　釜山からスタートして蔚山と浦項、東海と江陵、束草、元山と羅津・先鋒へと続く環東海経済は、ウラジオストクを経由する大陸経済、北極航路と日本をつなぐ海洋経済へ伸びていくはずです。
&#13;
　麗水と木浦からスタートして群山、仁川を経て海州と南浦、新義州へと続く環黄海経済は、全羅南道のブルーエコノミーやセマングムの再生可能エネルギー新産業、そして開城工業団地と南浦、新義州へと続く先端産業団地の育成により、中国・アセアン・インドに向けた雄大な経済戦略を完成することになります。
&#13;
　北韓も経済建設総路線へと国家政策を切り替え、市場経済の導入が行われています。国際社会も北韓が核を放棄すれば、経済成長を支援すると約束しています。
&#13;
　北韓を一方的に助けようとするわけではありません。互いの体制の安全を保障しながら、南北両方の利益を図り、両方の繁栄を目指そうということです。世界経済の発展に、南北が一緒に貢献したいということです。
&#13;
　平和経済を通じてわが国経済の新成長エンジンを作っていきます。われわれの力をこれ以上、分断に消耗するわけにはいきません。平和経済にわれわれがもつ全てを注ぎ込んで、「新しい韓半島」の扉を切り開いていきます。
&#13;
　南北が手を携えて韓半島の運命を主導しようとする意志があれば実現できることです。分断を乗り越えるときに、ようやくわれわれの光復は完成し、誰も揺るがすことのできない国になるはずです。
&#13;
　「北韓はミサイルを打ち上げるのに平和経済を語るのか」と反論する人たちがいます。しかし、われわれはあちらより強力な防衛力を保有しています。
&#13;
われわれは状況を注視しながら、韓半島の緊張が高まらないように管理に万全を期していますが、それも究極の目標は対立ではなく、対話にあります。
&#13;
米国が動揺せず北韓と対話を続け、日本も対話を進めているという現実を直視していただきたいと思います。理念にとらわれて自ら孤立しないでいただきたいと思います。
&#13;
　われわれの団結した力が絶対に必要です。国民の皆様も志を同じくして、同行してください。
&#13;
　尊敬する国民の皆様、
&#13;
　独立有功者とご遺族の皆様、
&#13;
　海外同胞の皆様、
&#13;
　私は本日、光復節を迎え任期内に非核化と平和体制を確固たるものにすると誓います。
&#13;
その土台の上で平和経済に着手し、統一に向けて歩んでいきます。
&#13;
　北韓と共に「平和の春」に蒔いた種が「繁栄の木」に育つように、対話と協力を発展させていきます。
&#13;
　2032年にはソウルー平壌共同五輪を成功開催し、2045年の光復100周年には平和と統一で一つになった国(One Korea)として世界にしっかり位置づけられるよう、その土台を強固に築いていくと約束します。
&#13;
　臨時政府が「大韓民国」という国号とともに「民主共和国」を宣布してから100年が経ちました。
&#13;
　われわれは100年間省察し、成熟しました。もはやどのような危機も乗り越えられる自信を持てるようになり、平和と繁栄の韓半島を実現するための国民の能力が高まりました。われわれは「誰も揺るがすことのできない国」をつくることができます。
&#13;
　南岡・李昇薫先生のお言葉をかみ締めます。
&#13;
　「私は種が地の下から重い土を持ち上げて芽立つ時、自分の力でない他の力を借りて上がってくるのを見たことがない」
&#13;
　われわれの力で分断を乗り越え、平和と統一へ進む道こそ、責任ある経済大国への近道となります。われわれが日本を追い越す道であり、日本を東アジア協力の秩序へと導く道です。
&#13;
　韓半島と東アジア、世界の平和と繁栄をけん引する「新しい韓半島」がわれわれを待っています。
&#13;
　われわれはできます。
&#13;
　ありがとうございました。</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>chenzj8309: </b><br>
<span>文在寅光复节演说（韩联社中日双语版）</span><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 chenzj8309 于 2019-8-15 15:59 编辑 </span><br>
<span>尊敬的全体国民，独立有功人士和其家属，以及旅外同胞们：在迎来三一独立运动和临时政府成立100周年的今天，我们在独立纪念馆举行光复74周年纪念仪式，意义深远。今天的大韩民国是先烈们以百折不挠、坚韧不拔的精神造就的。他们渴望"三角山翩翩跳舞，汉江水喷涌而出的那一天"到来，奉献自己一切的那股精神永远活在国民心中。今天，我要向先烈们、有功人士及其家属致以深深的敬意，和全体国民一道描绘祖国光复那天普罗大众以激动的心情梦想的国家，继承先贤遗志共同建设理想国度。我们所梦想的国家是一起幸福生活的国家，是所有人都有公平的机会，即使失败了也能重新站起来的国家。我们所梦想的国家是韩国西部莞岛的少女在东部蔚山学习氢工业，去朝鲜南浦创业，向蒙古和西伯利亚出口环保汽车的国家；是在朝鲜会宁长大的少年在韩国釜山海洋大学读书，毕业后成为一名船舶驾驶员，驾驶一艘集装箱船前往东盟国家、印度洋、南美智利的国家；是农业专业的青年在阿穆尔江畔与韩朝俄三国的农夫一起耕种大面积的豆田，而身在韩国瑞山的弟弟用哥哥生产的豆子喂牛的国家；是跨越豆满江通往大陆，横跨太平洋前往东盟国家和印度，生活与想象力被无限放大的国家；是经济活动范围超出韩半岛南方一侧，与周边国家合作共赢的国家。"点起熔炉之火，在新国家的心脏抽铁丝，添钢筋，搭铁板，在混凝土、铁和希望之上建设一个谁都无法动摇的新的国家。"解放后，一位诗人如此歌颂迎来光复的新国家之梦。"谁都无法动摇的新的国家"，这是摆脱外来势力的侵略和统治的新生独立国家本该拥有的梦想。从那之后74年后的今天，我们成为世界第6大制造强国和第6大出口强国，具备强有力的经济实力。我们开启了人均收入3万美元时代，并在逐渐实现金九先生所追求的"文化国家"的梦想。但我们还没能建设"谁都无法动摇的国家"，这是因为我们还不够强大，祖国仍处于分裂状态。看到以毅然的态度面对一切危机的国民，今天我再次下决心，定要把祖国建设成我们所梦想的"谁都无法动摇的国家"。尊敬的全体国民！我们遵守自由贸易秩序，集中发展了半导体、IT、生物等我们可以做好的产业。在国际分工体系中，任何一个国家都能梦想凭借自身优势获得成功。在近代化过程中一度落后的东亚基于分工和协作再次实现经济腾飞，全球称之为"东亚的奇迹"。东亚有过侵略和战争，但与之相比，人员交流和贸易往来的历史更长。从青铜器文化到现代文明，东亚各国互相传播文化和共享文明，实现了人类历史上最长时间的交流与合作。光复节不光是我们的好日子，也是甲午战争、俄日战争、满洲事变、中日战争、太平洋战争这60多年一系列战争结束的日子，是整个东亚光复的日子。日本国民同样摆脱军国主义的压迫，从侵略战争中解放出来。我们没有停留在过去，而是不断与日本在安全、经济领域开展合作，尝试与日本一道疗愈日本殖民统治时期受害者的伤痛，我们以史为镜，坚持携手合作的立场。反省历史并不意味着停留在过去，而是要摆脱历史走向未来。我们希望日本反省给邻国带去的不幸历史，与我们一道引领东亚的和平与繁荣。只有合作才能携手发展，才能实现可持续发展。世界通过高度的分工机制实现了共同繁荣，日本经济也同样在自由贸易的秩序中实现分工和发展。在国际分工机制中，任何国家若把自身优势领域作为武器，就无法维持和平的自由贸易秩序，先发展起来的国家绝不能剥夺后起发展国家的机会。若日本此刻走对话与合作之路，我们愿意配合，并将与其一道打造公平贸易与合作的东亚。去年韩国举办了平昌冬奥会，明年日本将办东京奥运，2022年中国将办北京冬奥会，这是奥运历史上首次由东亚地区接力办赛。这将是东亚巩固友好合作基础，走向共同繁荣之路的良机。正如全世界人民在平昌见证了"和平韩半岛"一般，希望东京奥运会也能带来友好与合作的希望。为了让东亚的下一代看到通过合作实现繁荣，我们将竭尽所能。尊敬的全体国民!今天的大韩民国已非昔日的大韩民国，而是克服无数挑战和折磨变得更加坚强和成熟的大韩民国。为了建设我们所梦想的"全新的韩半岛——谁都无法动摇的国家"，我提出如下三个目标:——第一，作为负责任的经济强国，维护全球自由贸易秩序，促进东亚地区的平等合作。韩国国民造就了奇迹般的经济发展，其成果和潜力可与世分享，但不能被夺走。我们只有掌握经济主权，才能作为韩半岛命运的主宰者，不为外力所动摇。全体国民凝聚力量将危机化为机遇，挑战会让我们变得更强大。无论是中东炙热的沙漠，还是太平洋的大浪，我们都毫不畏惧，一心实现经济发展。我们先后发展轻工业、重化工业、信息通信产业，最终成为了名副其实的IT强国，如今还引领5G等全球技术标准。过去，我们努力追赶发达国家，而今率先迎接挑战，逐步实现经济领先。面对日本政府不当的限贸措施，我们坚持走负责任的经济强国之路。政府将把现有经济结构转变为"包容、共赢"的经济生态系统，通过促进大中小企业之间、劳资之间的合作，提升材料、零部件、设备产业的国际竞争力。我们还将营造鼓励科学家和技术工人敢于挑战、包容失败的社会氛围，打造谁都无法动摇的经济强国。我相信，只要审视自己的不足，不自卑，互励共勉，就能做到这一切。我们将以与经济实力相应的责任感，进一步扩大开放合作，与邻国共同发展。——第二，连接大陆与海洋，为实现全球和平与繁荣发挥桥梁作用。从地缘政治角度看，韩国是世界上唯一一个被四大强国包围环绕的国家。当我们的力量渺小时，无论在陆地还是在海洋都被排挤在边缘，有时甚至沦为强国角逐的角斗场。这就是我们经历过的历史。不过，只要我们拥有力量，就能成为连接大陆和海洋、引导东北亚和平与繁荣的领袖国家。我们应把地缘政治上的劣势转化为优势，并制定明确的目标，主动开辟未来，而不是被外力所左右。大韩民国临时政府要人赵素昻先生曾提倡人与人、民族与民族、国与国之间建立平等关系。这是我们追求和平与繁荣的基本精神。面对日本的经济报复措施，全体国民齐心协力守护国家利益，同时保证两国友好关系不受损害，这是因为韩国国民拥有成熟的公民意识。韩国政府所推进的"以人为本、互利共赢的和平共同体"旨在实现韩半岛、东亚乃至世界的和平与繁荣。"新北方政策"是开辟通往大陆之路的远大构想。除了中国和俄罗斯之外，我们将把合作范围扩展至中亚和欧洲地区，并通过东北亚铁路共同体奠定多边合作、多边安保的基础。"新南方政策"是开辟通往海洋之路的远大构想。我们将与东盟和印度的双边关系升级为与周边主要国家相同的水平，发展成互利共赢的合作关系。今年11月，韩国-东盟特别峰会和韩国-湄公峰会将在釜山举行，这将是推动韩国与东盟、韩国与湄公国家关系发展的又一划时代的里程碑。连接韩朝铁路和公路是韩国为实现东北亚和平与繁荣迈出的第一步。若韩朝实现陆、海、空全方位互联互通，打通物流动脉，恢复人员往来，半岛将变成连接亚欧大陆、太平洋、东盟以及印度洋的重要关口。届时，亚洲共同体将会绽放合作之花，而非由任何一国主导。——第三，通过构建以和平促繁荣的和平经济，以统一实现完整的光复。我们要克服分裂，将民族的能量升华为实现未来繁荣的动力。和平经济是基于半岛完全无核化，始于通过对话与合作让朝鲜弃核并选择走向繁荣的战略。在过去的1年8个月间，韩朝美三方始终保持对话势头。近来，朝鲜几番做出令人担忧的行为，但对话的势头没有因此受到影响，这是韩国政府推进构建韩半岛和平进程的一个巨大成果，也明显不同于过去朝鲜一发起挑衅即撼动韩半岛局势的情况。虽然国内外仍有不少煽动对抗的势力，但正是全体国民对和平殷切的期盼推动我们走到今天这个阶段。韩朝美领导人6月底在板门店会晤后，朝美尝试进行工作层磋商讨论第三次首脑会谈事宜。这可能是韩半岛实现无核化和构建和平机制的过程中最重要的关卡。当下，韩朝美应集中力量推动朝美早日举行工作层磋商。哪怕事有不如意，但打破对话局面或设限让对话变得困难的做法不值得提倡。如果有不满意也应在对话的框架下提出问题，并讨论解决方案。希望全民万众一心，推动对话顺利通过最后一个关卡。若顺利通过这一关，韩半岛将朝着无核化的目标迈近一大步，韩朝关系也将取得重大进展。待经济合作提速、和平经济时代开启后，统一也会自然而然地实现。国际货币基金组织预测韩国将引领第四次工业革命，2024年左右人均收入将超过4万美元。如果韩朝在维持各自体制的基础上合聚力量，我们将能开启8000万民族市场，韩半岛统一后有望成为全球第6大经济体。国内外研究显示，人均收入到2050年左右可以达到7-8万美元。无可置疑，和平与统一带来的经济利益是巨大的。韩朝企业也将迎来全新的市场和机会。韩朝不仅可以省下巨额国防费用，还可以减少"韩国折价"（Korea Discount）这种无形的分裂费用，找到低增长、低生育、老龄化的解决方案。最重要的是，要像迎来光复那天那样在全民心中种下希望与热情，没有比这个更大的经济增长动力。从釜山到蔚山、浦项、东海、江陵、束草、元山、罗津、先锋的环东海经济圈将经符拉迪沃斯托克与大陆经济、北极航线、日本相连，实现海洋经济发展；从丽水、木浦、群山、仁川到海州、南浦、新义州的环黄海经济圈将把全罗南道"蓝色经济"、"新万金"的环保新产业与开城工业园区、南浦、新义州对接，推进高端产业园建设，最终完成面向中国、东盟、印度市场的宏伟的经济战略布局。朝鲜也调整了国家战略，引入市场经济体制，大力推动经济建设。国际社会承诺，只要朝鲜弃核，将大力支援其经济发展。我们不是要单方面向朝鲜提供帮助，而是维持各自现有体制，携手奔向互利共赢的康庄大道，从而为全球增长做出贡献。政府将通过发展和平经济打造新增长动力。我们不能再将精力耗费在分裂的历史上，而是要把所有力量投入到发展和平经济，开启"新韩半岛"之门。如果韩朝携起手勇下主导韩半岛命运的决心，我们定能获得成功。只有结束分裂，我们的光复才算完整，我们的国家才能任谁都无法动摇。有人说，朝鲜不断射弹谈何和平经济，然而我们拥有强大无比的防卫力量。我们严密注视倾力防备，不让韩半岛紧张局势升级，我们最终的目标不是对抗，而是对话。希望大家认识到，目前美国和朝鲜持续进行对话，日本也在推进与朝对话，希望我们不要成为固执于意识形态的落伍者。我们需要国民团结一致的力量，希望全体国民同心协力，同舟共济。尊敬的全体国民，独立有功人士和其家属，以及旅外同胞们！在今天光复节之际，我决心在任期内巩固推进无核化与和平机制，并在此基础上开启和平经济，走向统一。为了让韩朝一道播下的"和平之春"的种子茁壮成长为"繁荣之树"，我们要发展对话推进合作。我承诺，为了在2032年由首尔和平壤成功联办奥运会，在2045年迎接光复节100周年时让和平统一的国家（One Korea）屹立于世界之林而奠定稳固的基础。临时政府确立"大韩民国"国号和宣布"民主共和国"成立已有百年。我们在这百年间不断反思，变得成熟。如今我们拥有能战胜任何危机的自信，实现韩半岛和平与繁荣的国民力量无比壮大，能够建立"谁都无法动摇的国家"。南岗李昇薰先生说过"我从未见过种子穿透层层重土发芽成长时，不靠自己，而是借助其他力量"。靠我们的力量战胜分裂走向和平统一之路，是发展为负责任的经济强国的捷径，也是我们赶超日本，将日本引导至东亚合作秩序的道路。引领韩半岛、东亚乃至世界和平与繁荣的"新韩半岛"正在等待我们。我们能够做到！谢谢！</span><br>
<span>(8.15) 第74周年光復節慶祝辞</span><br>
<span>　尊敬する国民の皆様、</span><br>
<span>　独立有功者とそのご遺族の皆様、</span><br>
<span>　海外同胞の皆様、</span><br>
<span>　3.1独立運動と臨時政府樹立100周年となる今年、光復74周年記念式が特別に独立記念館で行われることを大変意義深いものであると考えております。</span><br>
<span>　今日の大韓民国はいかなる苦難にも屈することなく、あきらめなかった独立先烈の強い精神が作り出したものです。</span><br>
<span>「三角山が起きあがり、肩を踊らせて舞い、漢江の水が逆巻きたぎり立つその日」を渇望しながらすべてを捧げた先烈の熱い精神は、今この瞬間にも国民の胸に息づいています。</span><br>
<span>　私は本日、独立先烈と有功者、そのご遺族の方々に深く敬意を表すると共に、光復のその日にあふれる気持ちで築き上げようとした国、そして本日、われわれがその意志を継承して作っていこうとする国を国民の皆様と一緒に描いてみようと思います。</span><br>
<span>　われわれが夢見る国は「共に豊かになる国」、誰もが公正な機会に恵まれ失敗しても立ち直ることのできる国です。</span><br>
<span>　われわれが夢見る国は、莞島(ワンド)に暮らす島村の少女が(南の)蔚山で水素産業を学び、(北の)南浦で起業してモンゴルやシベリアにエコカーを輸出する国です。(北の)会寧で育った少年が釜山の海洋学校を卒業し、アセアンとインド洋、南米のチリまでをつなぐコンテナ船の航海士になる国です。</span><br>
<span>農業を専攻した青年がアムール川辺で南北とロシアの農民たちと大規模な大豆栽培を行い、その青年の弟は(南の)瑞山で兄の大豆を餌にして牛を育てる国です。</span><br>
<span>　豆満江を渡り大陸へと、太平洋を越えてアセアンとインドへと、われわれの暮らしと想像力が広がる国です。われわれの経済活動エリアが韓半島南部を超え、隣国と協力しながら共に繁栄していく国です。</span><br>
<span>　「溶鉱炉に火をつけよ、新しい国の心臓に鉄線を引いて鉄筋を伸ばし鉄板も延ばそう。セメントと鉄と希望の上に誰も揺るがすことのできない新しい国を築いていこう」</span><br>
<span>　解放直後、ある詩人は光復を迎えた新しい国の夢についてこう詠いました。</span><br>
<span>　「誰も揺るがすことのできない新しい国」。それは外国の侵略や支配から解放された新興独立国として持つべき当然の夢でした。</span><br>
<span>　そして74年が経った今、われわれは世界トップ6の製造大国、世界トップ6の輸出大国の立派な経済力を持つようになりました。国民所得3万ドル時代を切り開き、金九先生が願望していた文化国家という夢も実現しつつあります。</span><br>
<span>　しかし「誰も揺るがすことのできない国」はまだ実現できていません。それはわれわれがまだ十分強くないためであり、われわれがまだ分断状態にあるためです。</span><br>
<span>　私は本日、改めていかなる危機にも毅然として対処してきた国民を思いながら、われわれが作りたい国、「誰も揺るがすことのできない国」を誓います。</span><br>
<span>　尊敬する国民の皆様、われわれは自由貿易秩序に基づいて半導体、IT、バイオなどわれわれの得意な産業に集中することができました。国際分業体制の下でどの国も自国の強みを活かして成功を夢見ることができました。</span><br>
<span>　近代化に立ち遅れていた東アジアは分業と協業により再び経済発展を成し遂げました。世界はそれを「東アジアの奇跡」と呼びました。</span><br>
<span>　侵略と紛争の時期がなかったわけではありませんが、東アジアにはそれよりはるかに長い交流と貿易の歴史があります。青銅器文化から現代文明にいたるまで東アジアは互いに伝播し、共有し合いました。人類歴史の中でもっとも長い交流と協力が行われ、共に文明の発展を果たしました。</span><br>
<span>　光復はわれわれだけに嬉しいものではありませんでした。清日戦争と露日戦争、満州事変と中日戦争、太平洋戦争にいたるまで、60年以上にわたる長い戦争が終わった日であり、東アジア独立の日でもありました。日本国民も軍国主義の抑圧から抜け出し侵略戦争から解放されました。</span><br>
<span>　われわれは過去に留まることなく日本と安保・経済協力を続けてきました。日本と共に日帝強制占領期における被害者の苦しみを実質的に癒すために取り組み、歴史を鏡とし固く手を結ぼうとする立場を堅持してきました。</span><br>
<span>　過去を省察するのは過去にこだわることではなく過去から立ち直り未来へと進むことです。日本が隣国を不幸にした過去を省察する中で、東アジアの平和と繁栄を共にけん引していくことをわれわれは望んでいます。</span><br>
<span>　協力してこそ共に発展し、その発展が持続できるものです。世界は高度の分業体制により共同繁栄を実現してきました。日本経済も自由貿易の秩序の下で分業を行い、発展してきました。</span><br>
<span>　国際分業体制の下で、どの国であろうと自国が優位にある部門を武器化すれば平和な自由貿易秩序は壊れてしまいます。先に成長を達成した国がその後を追って成長している国のハシゴを蹴り飛ばしてはいけません。</span><br>
<span>　今からでも日本が対話と協力の道へと出るのであれば、われわれは快くその手を握るはずです。公正に貿易して協力する東アジアを一緒に作っていきます。</span><br>
<span>　昨年の平昌冬季五輪に続き来年には東京夏季五輪、2022年には北京冬季五輪が開催されます。五輪史上初の東アジアでのリレー開催です。東アジアが友好と協力の土台をしっかりと固め共同繁栄の道へと進む絶好のチャンスです。</span><br>
<span>　世界の人々が平昌で「平和の韓半島」を目撃したように、東京五輪で友好と協力の希望を持てるようになることを願います。</span><br>
<span>　われわれは東アジアの未来世代が協力による繁栄を経験できるように、われわれに与えられた責任を果たします。</span><br>
<span>　尊敬する国民の皆様、今日のわれわれは過去のわれわれではありません。今日の大韓民国は数多くの挑戦と試練を乗り越え、さらに強くなり、成熟した大韓民国です。</span><br>
<span>　私は本日「誰も揺るがすことのできない国」、われわれが作りたい「新しい韓半島」を目指して３つの目標を提案します。</span><br>
<span>　第一に、責任ある経済大国として自由貿易の秩序を守り、東アジアの平等な協力を引き出したいと思います。</span><br>
<span>　わが国民が奇跡のように成し遂げた経済発展の成果と底力は分け合うことはできても、奪われるわけにはいきません。経済での主権がしっかりしているとき、われわれは自らの運命の主人となり、ぐらつかなくなります。</span><br>
<span>　統合された国民の力は危機を機会へと変え、挑戦はわれわれをさらに強く、大きくしました。</span><br>
<span>　われわれは中東の熱砂も、太平洋の波も恐れることなく経済を成長させました。軽工業、重化学工業、情報通信産業を次々と育成し、世界的なIT大国となりました。今や5Gなど世界の技術標準をリードする国となりました。</span><br>
<span>　今までわれわれは先進国を追いかけてきましたが、今は率先して挑戦し、先導する経済へと生まれ変わりつつあります。日本の不当な輸出規制に立ち向かい、われわれは責任ある経済大国への道を地道に歩んで参ります。</span><br>
<span>　わが国の経済構造を包容と共生の生態系へと変化させます。大中小企業と労使の共生協力により素材・部品・装備産業の競争力強化に力を入れます。科学者と技術者の挑戦を応援し、失敗を尊重することにより誰も揺るがすことのできない経済を作ります。</span><br>
<span>　われわれに不備があるところを省察しながらも自らを卑下せず共に激励し合うとき、われわれは目標を成し遂げることができると信じています。</span><br>
<span>　われわれは経済力にふさわしい責任を持ってより大きく協力し、より広く開放することで隣国と共に成長していきます。</span><br>
<span>　第二に、大陸と海洋を問わず平和と繁栄を先導する橋梁国家になろうとしています。</span><br>
<span>　地政学的に4国もの大国に囲まれた国は世界にわれわれしかありません。われわれがみすぼらしく力がないときは、韓半島は大陸でも海洋でも辺境になり、ときには諸大国が角逐する場となりました。それがわれわれが経験した過去の歴史でした。</span><br>
<span>　しかし、われわれが力をもつと大陸と海洋をつなぐ国、北東アジアの平和と繁栄の秩序を先導する国になれます。われわれは地政学的位置をわれわれの強みに変えていかなければなりません。これ以上、他に振り回されず主導していくというしっかりとした目標をもつべきです。</span><br>
<span>　かつて臨時政府の趙素昻先生は人と人、民族と民族、国と国の間の均等を唱えました。それが平和と繁栄に向けたわれわれの基本精神です。</span><br>
<span>　わが国民が日本の経済報復に対して成熟した対応を示しているのもまた、わが国の経済を護り抜こうとする強い意志を持ちながらも、両国国民同士では友好が損なわれないことを願う高い水準の国民意識があるからです。</span><br>
<span>　わが政府が推進する「人間中心の共生繁栄に向けた平和共同体」は、われわれからスタートして韓半島全体と東アジア、さらには世界の平和と繁栄にまで拡大していこうとするものです。</span><br>
<span>　新北方政策は大陸に向かって走っていくわれわれの抱負です。中国やロシアだけでなく、中央アジアと欧州にまで協力の土台を拡大し、北東アジア鉄道共同体により多国間協力、多国間安保の礎を築きます。</span><br>
<span>　新南方政策は海洋に向かって走っていくわれわれの抱負です。アセアンおよびインドとの関係を主要周辺国レベルまで格上げし、共同繁栄の協力関係へと発展させていきます。</span><br>
<span>　今年11月には韓-アセアン特別首脳会議と韓-メコン首脳会議が釜山で開かれます。それらはアセアンおよびメコン諸国との画期的な関係発展を図る道しるべになるはずです。</span><br>
<span>　南北の間で途絶えた鉄路と道路をつなぐことは、東アジアの平和と繁栄を先導する橋梁国家へと進む第一歩です。韓半島の地と空、海に人や物流が行き来する血脈(道)をつなぎ、南北が大陸と海洋を自由に出入りすることができれば、韓半島はユーラシアと太平洋、アセアン、インド洋をつなぐ繁栄の土台になるはずです。</span><br>
<span>　アジア共同体はある1国が主導する共同体でなく、平等な国同士の多様な協力が花開く共同体になることでしょう。</span><br>
<span>　第三に、平和により繁栄を実現する平和経済を構築し、統一によって独立を完成していきたいと思います。</span><br>
<span>　分断体制を乗り越え、民族のエネルギーを未来繁栄の動力にしていかなければなりません。</span><br>
<span>　平和経済は、韓半島の完全なる非核化を土台に、北韓が核ではなく経済と繁栄を選ぶよう対話と協力を続けていくことから始まります。</span><br>
<span>　南北と米国は、この1年8ヶ月間、対話の局面を続けました。最近北韓による数回の懸念すべき行動にもかかわらず対話ムードが揺らいでいないことこそ、政府が進めてきた韓半島平和プロセスの大きな成果であります。一度の北韓の挑発により韓半島が揺さぶられたこれまでの状況とは大きく様変わりしています。 依然として対立を煽る勢力が国内外に少なからず存在しますが、わが国民の平和への切実な願望に支えられ、ここまで辿り着くことができました。</span><br>
<span>　今年6月末の板門店会談以降、第3回北米首脳会談に向けた北米間の実務者交渉が模索されています。おそらくこれは、韓半島の非核化と平和構築に向けた全過程における最も重大な山場になると思います。南・北・米の三国が、北米の実務者交渉の早期開催に力を集中しなければならない時期です。</span><br>
<span>　不満なところがあるとしても、対話ムードを壊したり、壁を立てて対話を妨げたりするのは決して望ましくありません。不満があるならば、それも対話の場で問題を提起し、議論すべきであります。国民の皆様にも、対話の最後の山を乗り切ることができるよう、ご声援のほど、よろしくお願いいたします。</span><br>
<span>　この危機を乗り越えれば韓半島の非核化がより一層近付き、南北関係も大きく前進するはずです。経済協力が加速し、平和経済が始まれば、いずれ自ずと統一は目の前の現実になると思います。</span><br>
<span>　IMF(国際通貨基金)は、韓国が第4次産業革命をリードし、2024年頃には一人当たり国民所得が4万ドルを突破するとの見通しを示しています。</span><br>
<span>　そこに南北の能力を合わせれば、それぞれの体制を維持しながらも8千万人規模の単一市場を生み出すことができます。韓半島が統一を果たすことになれば、世界第6位圏の経済大国になるとの見通しを示しています。2050年頃には国民所得7万~8万ドル時代を達成できるという国内外の研究結果も出ています。</span><br>
<span>　平和と統一がもたらす経済利益が非常に大きくなるということは明らかです。南北の企業にも新しい市場とチャンスが広がります。南北はいずれも膨大な国防費はもちろん、「コリアディスカウント」という無形の分断費用を削減することができます。今われわれが経験している低成長、少子高齢化の解決策も見出せるはずです。</span><br>
<span>　しかし、何よりも光復のあの日のように、わが民族の心に芽生える希望と情熱が大事です。希望と情熱より大きな経済の成長エンジンはありません。</span><br>
<span>　釜山からスタートして蔚山と浦項、東海と江陵、束草、元山と羅津・先鋒へと続く環東海経済は、ウラジオストクを経由する大陸経済、北極航路と日本をつなぐ海洋経済へ伸びていくはずです。</span><br>
<span>　麗水と木浦からスタートして群山、仁川を経て海州と南浦、新義州へと続く環黄海経済は、全羅南道のブルーエコノミーやセマングムの再生可能エネルギー新産業、そして開城工業団地と南浦、新義州へと続く先端産業団地の育成により、中国・アセアン・インドに向けた雄大な経済戦略を完成することになります。</span><br>
<span>　北韓も経済建設総路線へと国家政策を切り替え、市場経済の導入が行われています。国際社会も北韓が核を放棄すれば、経済成長を支援すると約束しています。</span><br>
<span>　北韓を一方的に助けようとするわけではありません。互いの体制の安全を保障しながら、南北両方の利益を図り、両方の繁栄を目指そうということです。世界経済の発展に、南北が一緒に貢献したいということです。</span><br>
<span>　平和経済を通じてわが国経済の新成長エンジンを作っていきます。われわれの力をこれ以上、分断に消耗するわけにはいきません。平和経済にわれわれがもつ全てを注ぎ込んで、「新しい韓半島」の扉を切り開いていきます。</span><br>
<span>　南北が手を携えて韓半島の運命を主導しようとする意志があれば実現できることです。分断を乗り越えるときに、ようやくわれわれの光復は完成し、誰も揺るがすことのできない国になるはずです。</span><br>
<span>　「北韓はミサイルを打ち上げるのに平和経済を語るのか」と反論する人たちがいます。しかし、われわれはあちらより強力な防衛力を保有しています。</span><br>
<span>われわれは状況を注視しながら、韓半島の緊張が高まらないように管理に万全を期していますが、それも究極の目標は対立ではなく、対話にあります。</span><br>
<span>米国が動揺せず北韓と対話を続け、日本も対話を進めているという現実を直視していただきたいと思います。理念にとらわれて自ら孤立しないでいただきたいと思います。</span><br>
<span>　われわれの団結した力が絶対に必要です。国民の皆様も志を同じくして、同行してください。</span><br>
<span>　尊敬する国民の皆様、</span><br>
<span>　独立有功者とご遺族の皆様、</span><br>
<span>　海外同胞の皆様、</span><br>
<span>　私は本日、光復節を迎え任期内に非核化と平和体制を確固たるものにすると誓います。</span><br>
<span>その土台の上で平和経済に着手し、統一に向けて歩んでいきます。</span><br>
<span>　北韓と共に「平和の春」に蒔いた種が「繁栄の木」に育つように、対話と協力を発展させていきます。</span><br>
<span>　2032年にはソウルー平壌共同五輪を成功開催し、2045年の光復100周年には平和と統一で一つになった国(One Korea)として世界にしっかり位置づけられるよう、その土台を強固に築いていくと約束します。</span><br>
<span>　臨時政府が「大韓民国」という国号とともに「民主共和国」を宣布してから100年が経ちました。</span><br>
<span>　われわれは100年間省察し、成熟しました。もはやどのような危機も乗り越えられる自信を持てるようになり、平和と繁栄の韓半島を実現するための国民の能力が高まりました。われわれは「誰も揺るがすことのできない国」をつくることができます。</span><br>
<span>　南岡・李昇薫先生のお言葉をかみ締めます。</span><br>
<span>　「私は種が地の下から重い土を持ち上げて芽立つ時、自分の力でない他の力を借りて上がってくるのを見たことがない」</span><br>
<span>　われわれの力で分断を乗り越え、平和と統一へ進む道こそ、責任ある経済大国への近道となります。われわれが日本を追い越す道であり、日本を東アジア協力の秩序へと導く道です。</span><br>
<span>　韓半島と東アジア、世界の平和と繁栄をけん引する「新しい韓半島」がわれわれを待っています。</span><br>
<span>　われわれはできます。</span><br>
<span>　ありがとうございました。</span><br>
</p><p><b>红夜殇雨: </b><br>
<span>在寅又在做梦了</span><br>
</p><p><b>大脑升级人: </b><br>
<span>从地缘政治角度看，韩国是世界上唯一一个被四大强国包围环绕的国家。</span><br>
</p><p><b>WindBlade: </b><br>
<span>先来次大革命清算掉一批人再说吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>xwr: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 xwr 于 2019-8-15 16:52 编辑 </span><br>
<span>从地缘政治角度看，韩国是世界上唯一一个被四大强国包围环绕的国家。当我们的力量渺小时，无论在陆地还是在海洋都被排挤在边缘，有时甚至沦为强国角逐的角斗场。这就是我们经历过的历史。</span><br>
<span>不过，只要我们拥有力量，就能成为连接大陆和海洋、引导东北亚和平与繁荣的领袖国家。我们应把地缘政治上的劣势转化为优势，并制定明确的目标，主动开辟未来，而不是被外力所左右。</span><br>
<span>若韩朝实现陆、海、空全方位互联互通，打通物流动脉，恢复人员往来，半岛将变成连接亚欧大陆、太平洋、东盟以及印度洋的重要关口。届时，亚洲共同体将会绽放合作之花，而非由任何一国主导。</span><br>
</p><p><b>依然荏苒: </b><br>
<span>愿景是美好的，但是德国统一的阵痛至今没有结束。</span><br>
</p><p><b>法皇干政: </b><br>
<span>文眼镜兄说得好，先把驻韩美军撤了再谈吧</span><br>
<span>----发送自 Sony G8142,Android 9</span><br>
</p><p><b>瓦拉几亚之夜: </b><br>
<span>饼要往大里画，牛要往大里吹</span><br>
</p><p><b>關羽: </b><br>
<span>文大总统我怎么感觉是你把一带一路的某些思路拿过来用啊。。。</span><br>
</p><p><b>兰开夏: </b><br>
<span>看的真的好感动啊...</span><br>
<span>在过去的1年8个月间，韩朝美三方始终保持对话势头。近来，朝鲜几番做出令人担忧的行为，但对话的势头没有因此受到影响，这是韩国政府推进构建韩半岛和平进程的一个巨大成果，也明显不同于过去朝鲜一发起挑衅即撼动韩半岛局势的情况。虽然国内外仍有不少煽动对抗的势力，但正是全体国民对和平殷切的期盼推动我们走到今天这个阶段。</span><br>
</p><p><b>毛玉子: </b><br>
<span>文在寅把逼装完了，烂摊子自然交给后人来处理啦</span><br>
</p><p><b>smdzh2: </b><br>
<span>下一步就是等着鑫将军派人过来和谈，提出主动分享核武器的建议了</span><br>
</p><p><b>天地明察: </b><br>
<span>连接韩朝铁路和公路是韩国为实现东北亚和平与繁荣迈出的第一步。若韩朝实现陆、海、空全方位互联互通，打通物流动脉，恢复人员往来，半岛将变成连接亚欧大陆、太平洋、东盟以及印度洋的重要关口。届时，亚洲共同体将会绽放合作之花，而非由任何一国主导。</span><br>
<span>这会成为南棒的希 望 之 花 吗</span><br>
</p><p><b>yurejian_2: </b><br>
<span>一个被日本经济殖民、被美国军事殖民的伪国家，拉几把倒吧。</span><br>
</p><p><b>佐塚間桐: </b><br>
<span>朝韩两国对于邻国的心态都挺有意思</span><br>
<span>朝鲜最高领导人的名字有汉字写法，但是从来不直接通报中国，而是以日本报纸转发汉字写法的形式告知。而韩国也从来不直接问朝鲜，而是先去问日本</span><br>
</p><p><b>ChellyL: </b><br>
<span>说的比唱的好听</span><br>
</p><p><b>你妈的为什么: </b><br>
<span>南朝鲜配不上文统领</span><br>
</p><p><b>supersnake0410: </b><br>
<span>平心而论，稿子写的不错</span><br>
</p><p><b>无梦女: </b><br>
<span>没啥，铁雨这电影都拍出来了，又不是现在开始吹</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HUAWEI PCT-AL10, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>共和政治文彦博: </b><br>
<span>有理想挺好，这还有20多年呢</span><br>
<span>1970年的东德，西德人</span><br>
<span>也没想到20年后就能再合并</span><br>
</p><p><b>死宅真恶心: </b><br>
<span>原来合并后就能解决少子化老龄化等难题啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>chenzj8309: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 chenzj8309 于 2019-8-15 20:10 编辑 </span><br>
<span>死宅真恶心 发表于 2019-8-15 19:40</span><br>
<span>原来合并后就能解决少子化老龄化等难题啊</span><br>
<span>这么说吧：</span><br>
<span>北方人均国民生产总值只有南方的4%</span><br>
<span>悲观的人一看：靠，北方佬那么穷，怎么能消费我们南方的产品？</span><br>
<span>乐观的人看了：我靠，北方是穷、基建是差，那反而意味着我们南方首先有很多基建项目可以做，其次意味着北方肯定要与我们搞合资与合作，这样一来就需要大量的韩国基建技术人员、中层管理人员，就业岗位就来了。把南北铁路打通之后，中朝铁路和俄罗斯远东铁路也可以利用，最终利用中国的一带一路和俄罗斯的振兴远东把我们韩国的商品快速而安全地运到欧亚大陆去！（最后一点就是韩国的新北方政策）</span><br>
</p><p><b>s1_hxh: </b><br>
<span>讲的不错，看看蹲几年</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Sony G8142, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>sagajytc: </b><br>
<span>xwr 发表于 2019-8-15 16:45</span><br>
<span>国防都不能自主的鼻屎国家还想领袖地位，这人不读史啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>夜明的月下: </b><br>
<span>天地明察 发表于 2019-8-15 18:25</span><br>
<span>这会成为南棒的希 望 之 花 吗</span><br>
<span>不要停下来啊（指世界岛铁路）</span><br>
</p><p><b>semerita: </b><br>
<span>我不明白为什么在泥潭有中文还要贴日文。。。</span><br>
<span>媚日啊媚日</span><br>
<span>况且是韩国人发言。。。</span><br>
</p><p><b>戴里克·伯格: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 戴里克·伯格 于 2019-8-15 23:44 编辑 </span><br>
<span>佐塚間桐 发表于 2019-8-15 18:33</span><br>
<span>朝韩两国对于邻国的心态都挺有意思</span><br>
<span>朝鲜最高领导人的名字有汉字写法，但是从来不直接通报中国，而是以日本 ...</span><br>
<span>真是张口就来呢，所有朝鲜官员名字的汉字写法都要看朝中社，连韩联社都不准经常和朝鲜官方不符，更不要说半岛造谣新闻加工厂日本媒体</span><br>
<span>官方渠道更是有礼宾司负责 开会的牌子是两面放名，对着自己的是本国语言，面向对方的是他国语言。这点事都做不明白外交部可以集体辞职了</span><br>
<span>www.kcna.kp</span><br>
</p><p><b>佐塚間桐: </b><br>
<span>戴里克·伯格 发表于 2019-8-15 23:38</span><br>
<span>真是张口就来呢，所有朝鲜官员名字的汉字写法都要看朝中社，连韩联社都不准经常和朝鲜官方不符， ...</span><br>
<span>你才是张口就来，去看看金正恩这三个字最先是哪家报道对的？之前又是哪家报道的金正银？</span><br>
</p><p><b>狒狗: </b><br>
<span>不错啊在寅，做得一手好梦</span><br>
</p><p><b>marxel: </b><br>
<span>semerita 发表于 2019-8-15 23:33</span><br>
<span>我不明白为什么在泥潭有中文还要贴日文。。。</span><br>
<span>媚日啊媚日</span><br>
<span>况且是韩国人发言。。。</span><br>
<span>因为这是喊话给中日看的版本啊</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 6, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>semerita: </b><br>
<span>marxel 发表于 2019-8-16 01:09</span><br>
<span>因为这是喊话给中日看的版本啊</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 6, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2 ...</span><br>
<span>不明白，在s1不是100%的中文用户吗。</span><br>
<span>泥潭又没有日文用户，消息来源也不是日文。</span><br>
<span>也没有规定转贴必须各种语言原文100%。。。</span><br>
<span>不懂啊不懂啊</span><br>
</p><p><b>marxel: </b><br>
<span>semerita 发表于 2019-8-16 01:11</span><br>
<span>不明白，在s1不是100%的中文用户吗。</span><br>
<span>泥潭又没有日文用户，消息来源也不是日文。</span><br>
<span>也没有规定转贴必须各种 ...</span><br>
<span>中日原文都是韩方发布的</span><br>
<span>你看得懂中文就看中文，看得懂日文也可以参考看看日文</span><br>
<span>“我看不懂的东西你不准贴”未免太自我中心了一点？</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 6, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>semerita: </b><br>
<span>marxel 发表于 2019-8-16 01:39</span><br>
<span>中日原文都是韩方发布的</span><br>
<span>你看得懂中文就看中文，看得懂日文也可以参考看看日文</span><br>
<span>“我看不懂的东西你不准贴 ...</span><br>
<span>日本語わからないとは言いません。</span><br>
<span>日本語の翻訳を貼り付ける必要がないと訴えるだけです。</span><br>
</p><p><b>marxel: </b><br>
<span>semerita 发表于 2019-8-16 01:44</span><br>
<span>日本語わからないとは言いません。</span><br>
<span>日本語の翻訳を貼り付ける必要がないと訴えるだけです。 ...</span><br>
<span>「必要がない」だけで、「出てはいけない」のことにはならないのでは？</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 6, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>衛藤美彩: </b><br>
<span>semerita 发表于 2019-8-16 01:11</span><br>
<span>不明白，在s1不是100%的中文用户吗。</span><br>
<span>泥潭又没有日文用户，消息来源也不是日文。</span><br>
<span>也没有规定转贴必须各种 ...</span><br>
<span>贴韩方中日文本的理由是s1懂韩文的人少</span><br>
</p><p><b>semerita: </b><br>
<span>marxel 发表于 2019-8-16 01:47</span><br>
<span>「必要がない」だけで、「出てはいけない」のことにはならないのでは？</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 6, Android ...</span><br>
<span>需要がないのに過剰に日本語を晒し出す意味はなんですか。</span><br>
<span>外国語をつけるならもっとポピュラーな英語はいかがですか。</span><br>
<span>中国語だけで十分だろうと思う私がおかしいですか？</span><br>
</p><p><b>marxel: </b><br>
<span>semerita 发表于 2019-8-16 02:02</span><br>
<span>需要がないのに過剰に日本語を晒し出す意味はなんですか。</span><br>
<span>外国語をつけるならもっとポピュラーな英語は ...</span><br>
<span>Address by President Moon Jae-in on Korea's 74th Liberation Day</span><br>
<span>August 15, 2019</span><br>
<span>Fellow Koreans, decorated patriots who dedicated themselves to the nation's independence, their relatives and Korean compatriots abroad,</span><br>
<span>As we mark the centenary of both the March First Independence Movement and the founding of the Provisional Government of the Republic of Korea this year, I find it particularly meaningful to hold the ceremony commemorating the 74th Liberation Day here at the Independence Hall of Korea.</span><br>
<span>The Republic of Korea we see today was created by the indomitable spirit of our forefathers who fought for independence while refusing to buckle or give up in the face of any tribulation. Our patriotic forefathers gave their all, aspiring for "the day when Samgaksan Mountain would rise up and dance and the waters of the Hangang River would roll in its bed and soar". Their passionate spirit lives on in the people's hearts even at this very moment.</span><br>
<span>Today, I would like to convey my deepest respect to our independence activists and their bereaved families. At the same time, I would like to join with the people in envisioning the nation that our forefathers sought to build with exuberance on the day Korea was liberated, and the country that we aim to create by carrying on where they left off.</span><br>
<span>The country that we desire is one in which we all prosper together and where everyone is given a fair chance and can get back on their feet again even if they fail.</span><br>
<span>The country that we desire is one in which a girl from a small town on the southwestern island of Wando can study hydrogen industry in the southeastern city of Ulsan, start a business in the northwestern city of Nampo and help export eco-friendly cars to Mongolia and Siberia. It is a country where a boy raised in the northeastern city of Hoeryeong can graduate from a maritime school in the southeastern port city of Busan and become a navigator aboard a container ship that sails to the ASEAN region, the Indian Ocean and all the way to Chile in South America. It is also a country where a young man who majors in agriculture can grow soybeans on a massive scale along the Amur River together with farmers from South and North Korea as well as Russia and where his younger brother can raise cattle in the West Coast city of Seosan that feed on these soybeans.</span><br>
<span>This is a country that expands our lives and imagination beyond the Dumangang River onto the continent, and across the Pacific to the ASEAN region and India. This is a country that cooperates and prospers with its neighboring countries, going beyond the limited scope of economic activities within the southern half of the Korean Peninsula.</span><br>
<span>Ignite the furnace,</span><br>
<span>Let us extract wires, extend steel bars and flatten iron plates upon the heart of a new nation,</span><br>
<span>Upon the foundation of cement, steel and hope</span><br>
<span>Let us build a new nation that will not be shaken</span><br>
<span>Shortly after Korea gained independence, a poet sang out this dream of a newly liberated nation.</span><br>
<span>A new nation that cannot be shaken: It was the legitimate dream of a newly independent country that threw off the shackles of foreign invasion and rule.</span><br>
<span>Now, after 74 years have passed, Korea has proudly become an economic powerhouse renowned as the world's sixth largest manufacturer and exporter. It has embarked on the era of per capita income of 30,000 USD and is on the road to becoming a country of thriving culture, which was the dream of independence activist Kim Gu.</span><br>
<span>However, we have yet to become an unshakable nation. That is because we still lack sufficient strength and remain divided.</span><br>
<span>Today, I renew my commitment to meeting the aspirations of the people to build an unshakable nation by reminding myself of our people who have demonstrated remarkable resilience in the face of a series of crises.</span><br>
<span>My fellow Koreans,</span><br>
<span>Upon the foundation of a free-trade order, we were able to focus on those industries in which we could excel: semiconductors, IT and biotechnology among others. Within the framework of the international division of labor, all countries were able to dream of success by harnessing their respective strengths.</span><br>
<span>East Asia had lagged behind in the process of modernization, but once again rose to achieve economic development through the division of labor and collaboration. The world described it as the 'East Asian Miracle'.</span><br>
<span>Although there have been periods of aggression and conflict, East Asia is steeped in a history of exchanges and trade that stretches much further back. From the Bronze Age through civilizations up to modern times, East Asia has engaged in mutual dissemination and sharing. Some of the oldest cases of exchanges and cooperation in human history have taken place in this region, and the advance in civilization has been achieved together.</span><br>
<span>Liberation was not just a cause for celebration for us alone. It was a day that marked the end of longstanding wars that had raged for over 60 years, including the First Sino-Japanese War, the Russo-Japanese War, the Manchurian Incident, the Second Sino-Japanese War and the Pacific War. It was also the day of liberation for East Asia. The Japanese people were also able to cast off the yoke of imperialistic oppression and were liberated from wars of aggression.</span><br>
<span>We have not dwelt on the past. Instead, we continued to engage in security and economic cooperation with Japan. Together with Japan, we have tried to practically assuage the suffering of victims from the Japanese colonial period. We have consistently maintained the position that we should learn from history and steadily work together.</span><br>
<span>Reflecting on the past does not mean clinging to the past but overcoming what had happened and moving toward the future. We hope that Japan will play a leading role together in facilitating peace and prosperity in East Asia while it contemplates a past that brought misfortune to its neighboring countries.</span><br>
<span>Only when we work together will we be able to achieve joint growth that is sustainable. The world has achieved common prosperity through a highly sophisticated division of labor. Japan has made progress by engaging in the division of labor upon the platform of the free trade order as well.</span><br>
<span>Within the international division of labor, if any country weaponizes a sector where it has a comparative advantage, the peaceful free trade order will inevitably suffer damages. A country that achieved growth first must not kick the ladder away while others are following in its footsteps.</span><br>
<span>Better late than never : if Japan chooses the path of dialogue and cooperation, we will gladly join hands. We will strive with Japan to create an East Asia that engages in fair trade and cooperation.</span><br>
<span>Following last year's PyeongChang Winter Olympics, the Tokyo Summer Olympics will be held next year while the Beijing Winter Olympics is slated for 2022. This will mark an unprecedented series of Olympics held in East Asia. It will be a golden opportunity for East Asia to solidify the framework of friendship and cooperation and to progress along the path toward common prosperity.</span><br>
<span>Just as people around the world witnessed a "Peaceful Korean Peninsula" at the PyeongChang Olympics, I look forward to seeing the Tokyo Olympics become a source of hope for friendship and cooperation.</span><br>
<span>We will fulfill the responsibilities entrusted to us so that future generations in East Asia will be able to experience prosperity through cooperation.</span><br>
<span>My fellow Koreans,</span><br>
<span>Today, we are no longer what we were. The Republic of Korea today has grown stronger and more mature while surmounting countless challenges and tribulations.</span><br>
<span>I put forth today three objectives for "a nation that cannot be shaken" – the new Korean Peninsula that we are aspiring to build.</span><br>
<span>First, as a responsible economic powerhouse, we aim to uphold the free trade order and facilitate equitable cooperation in East Asia.</span><br>
<span>The miracle of economic development that Korea has achieved as well as the underlying strength can be shared with other countries, but they can never be taken away. When we retain a firm grip on our economic sovereignty, we will be able to stand firm as the master of our own destiny.</span><br>
<span>Unified strengths of the people have turned crises into opportunities, and challenges have helped our country emerge stronger and greater. Undaunted by the burning sands of the Middle East and the rough waves of the Pacific, we achieved economic growth. In succession, we successfully nurtured light industry, heavy and chemical industry and information and communication industry and have become a global IT powerhouse. Korea has now become a nation that leads 5G and other global technical standards.</span><br>
<span>Until recently, Korea has been playing catch-up on advanced countries, but now our economy is evolving into one that helps set the pace, taking on challenges ahead of other countries. In the face of Japan's unwarranted export restrictions, we will continue our determined march toward a responsible economic powerhouse.</span><br>
<span>We will transform the structure of our economy into an ecosystem marked by inclusiveness and co-existence. We will also channel our efforts into enhancing the competitiveness of domestic materials, parts and equipment industries through mutually beneficial cooperation between SMEs and conglomerates as well as between labor and management. By encouraging scientists and engineers to take on new challenges and embracing unsuccessful attempts, we will build an economy that will never be shaken.</span><br>
<span>If we do not belittle ourselves and encourage each other even while reflecting on our own shortcomings, I believe we will be able to pull it off.</span><br>
<span>With a sense of responsibility befitting our economic strength, we will pursue broader cooperation and open up our markets even more and facilitate shared progress with neighboring countries.</span><br>
<span>Second, we aim to build a country that serves as a bridge by taking the lead in promoting peace and prosperity on the continent and out in the ocean.</span><br>
<span>In geopolitical terms, no other country in the world is surrounded by four major powers as we are. When Korea didn't have much clout and was deemed insignificant, the Korean Peninsula was also cast to the periphery of the continent and ocean and was even reduced to an arena where global powers competed. This is the history that we had to endure.</span><br>
<span>However, if we build a strong nation, we will be able to play a leading role in upholding peace and prosperity in Northeast Asia, connecting the continent with the ocean. We must turn our country's geopolitical position into a strength. We must establish a clear goal to take the initiative and not be pushed around by others anymore.</span><br>
<span>Cho So-ang, one of the founding members of the Provisional Government of the Republic of Korea long ago advocated for equality among individuals, peoples and nations. This defines Korea's underlying spirit that is oriented toward peace and prosperity.</span><br>
<span>The Korean people's mature response to Japan's economic retaliation is also attributable to a distinctly mature public sentiment that does not want to see damages to the friendly ties between the people of Korea and Japan, even while mustering their determination to protect our economy. The people-centered community of peace and prosperity that my government seeks to build is all about promoting peace and prosperity on the entire Korean Peninsula first and then spreading them to East Asia and the whole world.</span><br>
<span>The New Northern Policy represents our aspiration to advance into the continent. We will expand the foundation for cooperation not only with China and Russia but also with Central Asia and Europe and lay a cornerstone for multilateral cooperation and security through the East Asian Railroad Community initiative.</span><br>
<span>The New Southern Policy encapsulates our ambition to navigate through the oceans. We will upgrade our relations with ASEAN and India to a level equivalent to those with our major neighboring countries and develop them into a cooperative relationship for common prosperity.</span><br>
<span>In November this year, the ASEAN-Republic of Korea Commemorative Summit and the inaugural Korea-Mekong Summit will be held in Busan. This will mark a milestone in the groundbreaking development of relations with ASEAN and the Mekong countries.</span><br>
<span>Connecting the severed railroads and roads between South and North Korea is the first step toward a country that serves as a bridge, which will spearhead the efforts to promote peace and prosperity in East Asia.</span><br>
<span>If Korea's arteries for the passage of people and goods are reconnected all over the land, seas and skies of the Peninsula, and if the two Koreas are given free access in the continent and the ocean, the Korean Peninsula will emerge as a land of prosperity that connects Eurasia, the Pacific, ASEAN, and the Indian Ocean.</span><br>
<span>The Asian community will not be led by a single state but will instead become a community where diverse cooperation blossoms among countries on an equal footing.</span><br>
<span>Third, we aim to establish a peace economy in which prosperity is achieved through peace and also complete our liberation through the unification of the Peninsula.</span><br>
<span>By overcoming the division of the Peninsula, we must transform the Korean people's energy into a driving force for future prosperity. The peace economy begins with the efforts to continue dialogue and cooperation so that North Korea can choose economic prosperity over nuclear program upon the foundation of complete denuclearization of the Korean Peninsula.</span><br>
<span>The two Koreas and the United States have engaged in dialogue for the past 20 months. In spite of a series of worrying actions taken by North Korea recently, the momentum for dialogue remains unshaken– which is a significant result of</span><br>
<span>my government's peace process on the Korean Peninsula. Compared to the past when the whole Peninsula experienced turbulence whenever North Korea engaged in a provocation, the situation has definitely changed.</span><br>
<span>Even though numerous forces still exist at home and abroad that seek to stir up conflict, we have been able to come this far thanks to our people's fervent desire for peace.</span><br>
<span>Following the meeting in June among the leaders of the two Koreas and the United States at Panmunjeom, North Korea and the United States are exploring working-level negotiations ahead of the third summit. This will probably constitute the most critical juncture in the entire process of achieving denuclearization and establishing peace on the Korean Peninsula. Now is the time for both Koreas and the United States to focus on resuming working-level negotiations between Pyongyang and Washington at the earliest possible date.</span><br>
<span>Even if there is a cause for dissatisfaction, making dialogue difficult by spoiling the mood or erecting barriers is by no means a desirable course of action. If there is dissatisfaction, it too should be raised and discussed at the negotiating table. I hope the people will also pull together to ensure that we can overcome the last hurdle in the dialogue process.</span><br>
<span>When we pass this hurdle, denuclearization of the Korean Peninsula will move closer and inter-Korean relations will also make significant strides. When economic cooperation accelerates and the peace economy begins, unification will beckon as stark reality before us someday.</span><br>
<span>According to IMF estimates, Korea will lead the Fourth Industrial Revolution and its GDP per capita will surpass 40,000 USD around year 2024.</span><br>
<span>In addition, if we combine the capabilities of the two Koreas, even while maintaining our respective political systems, it will be possible to create a unified market of 80 million people. Once the Korean Peninsula is unified, it is expected to become one of the six largest economies in the world. There have been research findings both at home and abroad that concludes that an era of GDP per capita of 70,000 to 80,000 USD will be possible around 2050.</span><br>
<span>It is clear that there will be enormous economic benefits from peace and unification. New markets and opportunities will open up for both South and North Korean businesses. Both Koreas will be able to reduce not only huge defense expenditures but also the invisible cost of the division, the so-called 'Korea Discount'. We will also be able to find solutions to problems we currently face,</span><br>
<span>such as low growth, low birth rate and an aging society.</span><br>
<span>However, the hopes and passions that will stoke the hearts of the people just as they did on that day of liberation will be more important than anything else. There can be no greater driving force for economic growth than hope and passion.</span><br>
<span>The East Sea Rim Economic Belt that starts in Busan and encompasses Ulsan, Pohang, Donghae, Gangneung, Sokcho, Wonsan, Najin and Seonbong will reach out to the continental economy through Vladivostok and to the maritime economy that connects the Northern Sea Route to Japan.</span><br>
<span>The Yellow Sea Rim Economic Belt that begins with Yeosu and Mokpo and includes Gunsan and Incheon and heads toward Haeju, Nampo and Sinuiju will help complete the grand economic strategy that looks toward China, ASEAN and India by nurturing the Blue Economy in Jeollanam-do; the new renewable energy industry around Saemangeum; and the high-tech industrial parks of the Gaeseong Industrial Complex, Nampo and Sinuiju.</span><br>
<span>North Korea has also shifted its national policy toward concentrating all of its efforts on economic development and is in the process of adopting market economy. The international community has also promised to assist its economic growth if it abandons its nuclear program.</span><br>
<span>Our intention is not to unilaterally assist North Korea. Rather, our intention is to promote mutual benefits for both Koreas and prosper together while guaranteeing the security of our respective regimes. The plan is for the two Koreas to contribute to the development of the global economy.</span><br>
<span>We will create new economic growth engines through the peace economy. We can no longer afford to let division consume our capacities. We will open the door to a new Korean Peninsula by pouring all we have into the peace economy.</span><br>
<span>This will be possible if South and North Korea join forces and commit themselves to deciding the fate of the Korean Peninsula. When we overcome division, our liberation will finally be completed and Korea will become a country that cannot be shaken.</span><br>
<span>Some people express skepticism regarding the wisdom of talking up peace economy when North Korea is firing missiles. However, we possess defense capabilities that are even stronger. Although we are paying close attention and doing all we can to manage the situation to prevent the escalation of tension on the Korean Peninsula, the ultimate goal that these actions serve is dialogue, not confrontation. I hope these skeptics face up to the reality: the United States is continuing dialogue with North Korea without derailing while Japan is also seeking talks with Pyongyang. I hope these skeptics won't remain prisoners to ideology.</span><br>
<span>The unified strength of the people is essential. I ask the people to pull together as one.</span><br>
<span>Fellow Koreans, decorated independence fighters and their bereaved families, and Koreans overseas,</span><br>
<span>As we commemorate the Liberation Day today, I pledge to solidify denuclearization and peace regime on the Korean Peninsula during my term in office. I will initiate the peace economy upon this foundation and move toward unification.</span><br>
<span>We will advance dialogue and cooperation so that seeds sown together with North Korea in the spring of peace will grow into trees of prosperity.</span><br>
<span>I pledge to solidify the foundation so that we can successfully host the joint 2032 Seoul-Pyeongyang Olympics and stand tall in the world as one Korea by achieving peace and unification by 2045, which will mark the 100th anniversary of liberation.</span><br>
<span>It has been one hundred years since the Provisional Government declared the founding of a democratic republic named the Republic of Korea.</span><br>
<span>We have reflected on ourselves and matured over the past 100 years. We now have the confidence that we can prevail over any crisis. The people's ability to achieve peace and prosperity on the Korean Peninsula has grown stronger. We can create a country that will not be shaken by anyone.</span><br>
<span>I remind myself of the words of independence activist Lee Seung-hoon, who goes by the pen name of Namkang:</span><br>
<span>"When seeds buried under the ground spring up and rise above the heavy soil, I have only seen them do this by themselves – never through the strength of others."</span><br>
<span>The path that allows us to prevail over division and move toward peace and unification will be the royal road to becoming a responsible economic power. This is the road to overtaking Japan and guiding it toward a cooperative order in East Asia.</span><br>
<span>A new Korean Peninsula, one that will bring peace and prosperity to itself, East Asia and the world, awaits us.</span><br>
<span>We can do it!</span><br>
<span>Thank you.</span><br>
<span>(END)</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 6, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>semerita: </b><br>
<span>最初からやってよ　笑</span><br>
<span>知道大家爱学习</span><br>
</p><p><b>LightersFAN: </b><br>
<span>演说对中国这一存在的模糊已经到了让人在意的程度……（同中国在韩国地缘、经济版图中的实际地位相比）好奇是什么原因</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HUAWEI EVA-AL10, Android 8.0.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.0</span><br>
</p><p><b>戴里克·伯格: </b><br>
<span>佐塚間桐 发表于 2019-8-16 00:10</span><br>
<span>你才是张口就来，去看看金正恩这三个字最先是哪家报道对的？之前又是哪家报道的金正银？ ...</span><br>
<span>BBC和野鸡网的说法</span><br>
<span>https://www.bbc.com/zhongwen/trad/world/2010/10/101001_brief_korea_kim_name</span><br>
<span>http://news.ifeng.com/mainland/special/jinzhengenfanghua/content-2/detail_2010_10/10/2737410_0.shtml</span><br>
<span>同期日媒关于汉字表字的讨论，在朝鲜官方解释前还在纠结金正云还是金正银</span><br>
<span>https://m.chiebukuro.yahoo.co.jp/tag/%E9%87%91%E6%AD%A3%E9%8A%80?type=list&page=5</span><br>
</p><p><b>戴里克·伯格: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 戴里克·伯格 于 2019-8-16 06:49 编辑 </span><br>
<span>佐塚間桐 发表于 2019-8-16 00:10</span><br>
<span>你才是张口就来，去看看金正恩这三个字最先是哪家报道对的？之前又是哪家报道的金正银？ ...</span><br>
<span>金正恩政府对中美俄韩的态度的确一直在变，对日本的态度在他实际掌权的9年里是完全没有变化的，就是（表面上的）极尽厌恶。可以从9年如1日朝鲜媒体对日本的谩骂，对日本谣媒的蔑视和斥责就可以看出来</span><br>
</p><p><b>igifans: </b><br>
<span>LightersFAN 发表于 2019-8-16 05:41</span><br>
<span>演说对中国这一存在的模糊已经到了让人在意的程度……（同中国在韩国地缘、经济版图中的实际地位相比）好奇 ...</span><br>
<span>为了避免事大主义的指责吧。朝鲜长期顺服于中国，后被日本殖民、吞并，自从朝/韩独立来，名义上获得了独立自主的机会，实际上深受苏/美控制，因此对“自主”这一概念非常重视。可谓最想要的就是最得不到的。</span><br>
</p><p><b>王怡人: </b><br>
<span>别说了别说了，精日不开心了</span><br>
</p><p><b>marxel: </b><br>
<span>igifans 发表于 2019-8-16 06:47</span><br>
<span>为了避免事大主义的指责吧。朝鲜长期顺服于中国，后被日本殖民、吞并，自从朝/韩独立来，名义上获得了独 ...</span><br>
<span>即便如此把爱莉也抬进四大强国也太过了吧。。。</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 6, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>nooooooo: </b><br>
<span>戴里克·伯格 发表于 2019-8-16 06:46</span><br>
<span>金正恩政府对中美俄韩的态度的确一直在变，对日本的态度在他实际掌权的9年里是完全没有变化的，就是（表 ...</span><br>
<span>怼日本是朝鲜基本国策阿,没了这一点他们就彻底没有合法性了,伟人还是很懂得 </span><br>
</p><p><b>佐塚間桐: </b><br>
<span>戴里克·伯格 发表于 2019-8-16 06:46</span><br>
<span>金正恩政府对中美俄韩的态度的确一直在变，对日本的态度在他实际掌权的9年里是完全没有变化的，就是（表 ...</span><br>
<span>少东拉西扯，金正恩的名字是先通报的日本。朝中社在东京可没有分部，通告的对象是日本支持的机构。</span><br>
<span>朝鲜要真想通报中国，之前二胖访华见九天王的时候就会说，而不是这种鸡贼操作。所以你之前洋洋洒洒瞎bb的都是错的</span><br>
</p><p><b>戴里克·伯格: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 戴里克·伯格 于 2019-8-16 11:21 编辑 </span><br>
<span>佐塚間桐 发表于 2019-8-16 11:11</span><br>
<span>少东拉西扯，金正恩的名字是先通报的日本。朝中社在东京可没有分部，通告的对象是日本支持的机构。</span><br>
<span>朝鲜 ...</span><br>
<span>请出示论据啊</span><br>
<span>我在TGFC/微博看的/我舅舅和我的聊天记录什么的</span><br>
</p><p><b>佐塚間桐: </b><br>
<span>戴里克·伯格 发表于 2019-8-16 11:19</span><br>
<span>请出示论据啊</span><br>
<span>你自己贴的自己不看一看？bbc报道的</span><br>
</p><p><b>戴里克·伯格: </b><br>
<span>佐塚間桐 发表于 2019-8-16 11:21</span><br>
<span>你自己贴的自己不看一看？bbc报道的</span><br>
<span>據日本朝鮮通訊社稱，朝鮮中央通訊社說金正日幼子的漢語名字是「金正恩」。</span><br>
<span>引用的朝中社报道哎这是非常常见的A网站引用B网站，B网站称C网站说的转述，您刚上网冲浪吗？</span><br>
</p><p><b>佐塚間桐: </b><br>
<span>戴里克·伯格 发表于 2019-8-16 11:23</span><br>
<span>據日本朝鮮通訊社稱，朝鮮中央通訊社說金正日幼子的漢語名字是「金正恩」。</span><br>
<span>是通报了所谓的日本朝鲜通讯社。</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1853629[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
