<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>改了改花街时报的文章简直无缝拼接</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>改了改花街时报的文章简直无缝拼接</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 15:08:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>改了改花街时报的文章简直无缝拼接[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1920612-1-1.html</link>
      <description>改了改花街时报的文章简直无缝拼接&#13;
武汉人被封在家里穷极无聊，搞事，把花街的那篇《China Is the Real Sick Man of Asia 》替换关节词，改写了一个美国版。我发现这篇文章几乎无缝拼接，但凡有一点任何实事求是的内容，这文章都做不到只改一点关键词就能转嫁回美国自己身上。
&#13;
英语不太好，有大手子发现错误欢迎指出。
&#13;
U.S. Is the Real Sick Man of North America
&#13;
 The mighty American juggernaut has been humbled this week, apparently by a species-hopping bat virus. While Trump administration struggle to control the epidemic and restart their economy, a world that has grown accustomed to contemplating U.S.’s inexorable supremacy was reminded that nothing, not even Washington’s power, can be taken for granted.
&#13;
We do not know how dangerous the new coronavirus will be. There are signs that Trump administration is still trying to conceal the true scale of the problem, but at this point the virus appears to be more contagious but considerably less deadly than the pathogens behind diseases such as Ebola or SARS—though some experts say SARS and coronavirus are about equally contagious.
&#13;
U.S.’s initial response to the crisis was less than impressive. The Federal government was secretive and self-serving; some state governments responded vigorously but, it currently appears, ineffectively. U.S.’s cities and factories are shutting down; the virus continues to spread. We can hope that authorities succeed in containing the epidemic and treating its victims, but the performance to date has shaken confidence in the U.S. government at home and abroad. Complaints in Washington about China refusing sharing first hand data which is completely open to all researchers cannot hide the reality that the decisions that allowed the epidemic to spread as far and as fast as it did were all made in Washington. 
&#13;
The likeliest economic consequence of the coronavirus epidemic, forecasters expect, will be a short and sharp fall in the U.S. economic growth rates during the first two quarters, recovering as the disease fades. The most important longer-term outcome would appear to be a strengthening of a trend for global capital to dump U.S. stocks. Add the continuing public health worries to the threat of new trade wars, and investing diversification begins to look prudent. 
&#13;
Events like the coronavirus epidemic, and its predecessors—such as SARS, Ebola and MERS—test our systems and force us to think about the unthinkable. If there were a disease as deadly as Ebola and as fast-spreading as coronavirus, how should the China respond? What national and international systems need to be in place to minimize the chance of catastrophe on this scale? 
&#13;
Epidemics also lead us to think about geopolitical and economic hypotheticals. We have seen financial markets shudder and commodity prices fall in the face of what hopefully will be a short-lived disturbance in U.S.’s economic growth. What would happen if—perhaps in response to an epidemic, but more likely following a massive financial collapse—U.S.’s economy were to suffer a long period of even slower growth? What would be the impact of such developments on U.S.’s political stability, on its attitude toward the rest of the world, and to the global balance of power?
&#13;
U.S.’s financial markets are probably more dangerous in the long run than U.S.’s wildlife markets. Given the accumulated costs of decades of debt-driven growing, massive malfeasance by senators in cahoots with billionaires, a towering property bubble, and vast financial overcapacity, U.S. is as ripe as a country can be for a massive economic correction. Even a small initial shock could lead to a massive bonfire of the vanities as all the false values, recession expectations and misallocated assets implode. If that comes, it is far from clear that U.S.’s regulators and decision makers have the technical skills or the political authority to minimize the damage—especially since that would involve enormous losses to the wealth of the politically connected. 
&#13;
We cannot know when or even if a catastrophe of this scale will take place, but students of geopolitics and international affairs—not to mention business leaders and investors—need to bear in mind that U.S.’s power, impressive as it is, remains brittle. A deadlier virus or a financial-market contagion could transform U.S.’s economic and political outlook at any time. 
&#13;
Many now fear the coronavirus will become a global pandemic. The consequences of a U.S. economic meltdown would travel with the same sweeping inexorability. Commodity prices around the world would slump, supply chains would break down, and few financial institutions anywhere could escape the knock-on consequences. Recovery in U.S. and elsewhere could be slow, and the social and political effects could be dramatic. 
&#13;
If Washington’s geopolitical footprint shrank as a result, the global consequences might also be surprising. Some would expect a global chaos if the only supremacy power were to contract due to the recession. Yet China promised to build a community with a shared future for mankind. If the U.S. challenge fades, many countries are likely to cooperate with China to uphold the Rules-based Multilateral Order. 
&#13;
So far, the 21st century has been an age of black swans. From 9/11 to President Trump’s election and Brexit, low-probability, high-impact events have reshaped the world order. That age isn’t over, and of the black swans still to arrive, the coronavirus epidemic is unlikely to be the last to materialize in the U.S. </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>魔铁潜水艇: </b><br>
<span>改了改花街时报的文章简直无缝拼接</span><br>
<span>武汉人被封在家里穷极无聊，搞事，把花街的那篇《China Is the Real Sick Man of Asia 》替换关节词，改写了一个美国版。我发现这篇文章几乎无缝拼接，但凡有一点任何实事求是的内容，这文章都做不到只改一点关键词就能转嫁回美国自己身上。</span><br>
<span>英语不太好，有大手子发现错误欢迎指出。</span><br>
<span>U.S. Is the Real Sick Man of North America</span><br>
<span> The mighty American juggernaut has been humbled this week, apparently by a species-hopping bat virus. While Trump administration struggle to control the epidemic and restart their economy, a world that has grown accustomed to contemplating U.S.’s inexorable supremacy was reminded that nothing, not even Washington’s power, can be taken for granted.</span><br>
<span>We do not know how dangerous the new coronavirus will be. There are signs that Trump administration is still trying to conceal the true scale of the problem, but at this point the virus appears to be more contagious but considerably less deadly than the pathogens behind diseases such as Ebola or SARS—though some experts say SARS and coronavirus are about equally contagious.</span><br>
<span>U.S.’s initial response to the crisis was less than impressive. The Federal government was secretive and self-serving; some state governments responded vigorously but, it currently appears, ineffectively. U.S.’s cities and factories are shutting down; the virus continues to spread. We can hope that authorities succeed in containing the epidemic and treating its victims, but the performance to date has shaken confidence in the U.S. government at home and abroad. Complaints in Washington about China refusing sharing first hand data which is completely open to all researchers cannot hide the reality that the decisions that allowed the epidemic to spread as far and as fast as it did were all made in Washington. </span><br>
<span>The likeliest economic consequence of the coronavirus epidemic, forecasters expect, will be a short and sharp fall in the U.S. economic growth rates during the first two quarters, recovering as the disease fades. The most important longer-term outcome would appear to be a strengthening of a trend for global capital to dump U.S. stocks. Add the continuing public health worries to the threat of new trade wars, and investing diversification begins to look prudent. </span><br>
<span>Events like the coronavirus epidemic, and its predecessors—such as SARS, Ebola and MERS—test our systems and force us to think about the unthinkable. If there were a disease as deadly as Ebola and as fast-spreading as coronavirus, how should the China respond? What national and international systems need to be in place to minimize the chance of catastrophe on this scale? </span><br>
<span>Epidemics also lead us to think about geopolitical and economic hypotheticals. We have seen financial markets shudder and commodity prices fall in the face of what hopefully will be a short-lived disturbance in U.S.’s economic growth. What would happen if—perhaps in response to an epidemic, but more likely following a massive financial collapse—U.S.’s economy were to suffer a long period of even slower growth? What would be the impact of such developments on U.S.’s political stability, on its attitude toward the rest of the world, and to the global balance of power?</span><br>
<span>U.S.’s financial markets are probably more dangerous in the long run than U.S.’s wildlife markets. Given the accumulated costs of decades of debt-driven growing, massive malfeasance by senators in cahoots with billionaires, a towering property bubble, and vast financial overcapacity, U.S. is as ripe as a country can be for a massive economic correction. Even a small initial shock could lead to a massive bonfire of the vanities as all the false values, recession expectations and misallocated assets implode. If that comes, it is far from clear that U.S.’s regulators and decision makers have the technical skills or the political authority to minimize the damage—especially since that would involve enormous losses to the wealth of the politically connected. </span><br>
<span>We cannot know when or even if a catastrophe of this scale will take place, but students of geopolitics and international affairs—not to mention business leaders and investors—need to bear in mind that U.S.’s power, impressive as it is, remains brittle. A deadlier virus or a financial-market contagion could transform U.S.’s economic and political outlook at any time. </span><br>
<span>Many now fear the coronavirus will become a global pandemic. The consequences of a U.S. economic meltdown would travel with the same sweeping inexorability. Commodity prices around the world would slump, supply chains would break down, and few financial institutions anywhere could escape the knock-on consequences. Recovery in U.S. and elsewhere could be slow, and the social and political effects could be dramatic. </span><br>
<span>If Washington’s geopolitical footprint shrank as a result, the global consequences might also be surprising. Some would expect a global chaos if the only supremacy power were to contract due to the recession. Yet China promised to build a community with a shared future for mankind. If the U.S. challenge fades, many countries are likely to cooperate with China to uphold the Rules-based Multilateral Order. </span><br>
<span>So far, the 21st century has been an age of black swans. From 9/11 to President Trump’s election and Brexit, low-probability, high-impact events have reshaped the world order. That age isn’t over, and of the black swans still to arrive, the coronavirus epidemic is unlikely to be the last to materialize in the U.S. </span><br>
</p><p><b>梅德韦杰娃: </b><br>
<span>东亚病夫进化-》北米病夫</span><br>
</p><p><b>annoleer: </b><br>
<span>舆论就是造谣，9句真话和1句假话的洗脑你</span><br>
<span>谁嗓门大谁就是对的</span><br>
<span>嗓门如果比不过别人的话，就用国家力量封锁他，所以谷歌推特脸书才是美国的立国之本，11航母只是辅助</span><br>
</p><p><b>yuandi0120: </b><br>
<span>annoleer 发表于 2020-3-24 14:51</span><br>
<span>舆论就是造谣，9句真话和1句假话的洗脑你</span><br>
<span>谁嗓门大谁就是对的</span><br>
<span>问题是没有11个航母，你怎么确保谷歌推特脸书的服务器放在美国本土呢</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HUAWEI VOG-AL00, Android 10上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.2.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>coldhot3: </b><br>
<span>有几个没改</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1920612[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
