<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>开一个川皇的推特专楼吧（更新了赞歌）</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>开一个川皇的推特专楼吧（更新了赞歌）</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 20:33:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>开一个川皇的推特专楼吧（更新了赞歌）[50-100]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1831842-1-1.html</link>
      <description>开一个川皇的推特专楼吧&#13;
昨天有潭友发了个专门分发川皇推特加中文翻译的链接https://twittercn.live/，结果今天就登不上去了，有没有巨巨有空随时更新川皇的推啊，这简直是快乐源泉，停不下来</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>roy1996: </b><br>
<span>avayazhg 发表于 2019-5-20 06:51</span><br>
<span>唯一指定真实媒体正在堕落！GEE！</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 samsung SM-G9350, Android 8.0.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2 ...</span><br>
<span>CBS的华莱士，那比你们（指克里斯·华莱士）不知道高到哪里去了！啊，我跟他谈笑风生。</span><br>
</p><p><b>roy1996: </b><br>
<span>川 剧 变 脸</span><br>
<img src="https://s2.ax1x.com/2019/05/20/EvBJje.png" title="https://s2.ax1x.com/2019/05/20/EvBJje.png"><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>Our Economy and Jobs Market is BOOMING, the best in the World and in our Country’s history – and we have just started!</span><br>
<span>— Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) May 19, 2019</span><br>
<span>我们的经济和就业市场爆爆爆，我们是这个世界上有史以来最屌最炸的国家（居然没有KAG!)</span><br>
</p><p><b>Cortana: </b><br>
<span>川皇属实推特艺人</span><br>
</p><p><b>kuanyesine: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 kuanyesine 于 2019-5-20 16:31 编辑 </span><br>
<span>特朗普指责中方破坏中美“协议”，外交部回应：中美11轮经贸磋商未达成协议，根本原因在于美方试图通过极限施压实现不合理利益索求，美方又想混淆视听转嫁责任。（人民日报）</span><br>
<span>今日份儿的外交回应，川大大又说啥了？</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>The Democrats are on a fishing expedition, wanting to interview the same people, and see the same things, as we just went through for two years with Robert Mueller and the 18 Angry Dems. Never happened to a president before. Never even happened to President Obama!</span><br>
<span>— Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) May 22, 2019</span><br>
<span>民主党在钓鱼，但是象阿川我这种泥潭巨魔高级培训班毕业的绝不可能会上当，（依然没有KAG!!!)</span><br>
</p><p><b>roy1996: </b><br>
<span>儒雅随和特朗普</span><br>
<span>Donald J. Trump</span><br>
<span>‏认证账号 @realDonaldTrump</span><br>
<span>In a letter to her House colleagues, Nancy Pelosi said: “President Trump had a temper tantrum for us all to see.” This is not true. I was purposely very polite and calm, much as I was minutes later with the press in the Rose Garden. Can be easily proven. It is all such a lie!</span><br>
<span>上午3:28 - 2019年5月23日</span><br>
</p><p><b>roy1996: </b><br>
<span>川式民调，谁说民调没用的</span><br>
<span>Donald J. Trump</span><br>
<span>‏认证账号 @realDonaldTrump</span><br>
<span>71% of Voters rate the Economy as Excellent or Good. The highest number in more than 18 years! @QuinnipiacPoll</span><br>
<span>上午9:19 - 2019年5月24日 </span><br>
</p><p><b>avayazhg: </b><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/24/5ce77bffd4e8a83291.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/24/5ce77bffd4e8a83291.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/24/5ce77c006382053657.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/24/5ce77c006382053657.jpg"><br>
<span>看来还是比较在意自己发型的</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 samsung SM-G9350, Android 8.0.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>Wow! CNN Ratings are WAY DOWN, record lows. People are getting tired of so many Fake Stories and Anti-Trump lies. Chris Cuomo was rewarded for lowest morning ratings with a prime time spot – which is failing badly and not helping the dumbest man on television, Don Lemon!</span><br>
<span>— Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) May 24, 2019</span><br>
<span>CNN要完蛋了，天天菲客牛屎，不理智不客观不中立，我看你CNN是药丸</span><br>
</p><p><b>chenluwolf: </b><br>
<span>川普现在无视美股暴跌了吗</span><br>
</p><p><b>roy1996: </b><br>
<span>只要你讨厌拜登，我们就是异父异母的亲兄弟</span><br>
<span>      Donald J. Trump‏认证账号 @realDonaldTrump                                                    </span><br>
<span>                North Korea fired off some small weapons, which disturbed some of my people, and others, but not me. I have confidence that Chairman Kim will keep his promise to me, & also smiled when he called Swampman JoeBidan a low IQ individual, & worse. Perhaps that’s sending me a signal?上午6:29 - 2019年5月26日</span><br>
</p><p><b>roy1996: </b><br>
<span>安培陪领导打球</span><br>
<span>      Donald J. Trump‏认证账号 @realDonaldTrump                                                    </span><br>
<span>                Going to play golf right now with @AbeShinzo. Japan loves the game. Tremendous fans of @JackNicklaus, @TigerWoods, and @PhilMickelson — I said what about @GaryPlayer, they said we love Gary too!</span><br>
<span>                        上午8:33 - 2019年5月26日          </span><br>
</p><p><b>fore_long: </b><br>
<span>安倍这回不会再掉坑了吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>z.s: </b><br>
<span>还能继续快乐5年</span><br>
</p><p><b>roy1996: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 roy1996 于 2019-5-26 12:48 编辑 </span><br>
<span>日本通共实锤</span><br>
<span>Donald J. Trump</span><br>
<span>‏认证账号 @realDonaldTrump</span><br>
<span>Great fun and meeting with Prime Minister @AbeShinzo. Numerous Japanese officials told me that the Democrats would rather see the United States fail than see me or the Republican Party succeed - Death Wish!</span><br>
<span>下午12:37 - 2019年5月26日</span><br>
</p><p><b>roy1996: </b><br>
<span>该跪还是要跪的</span><br>
<span>Donald J. Trump</span><br>
<span>‏认证账号 @realDonaldTrump</span><br>
<span>Great progress being made in our Trade Negotiations with Japan. Agriculture and beef heavily in play. Much will wait until after their July elections where I anticipate big numbers!</span><br>
<span>下午12:39 - 2019年5月26日</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>Democrats and the mainstream media loved to talk about transparency until they learned @realDonaldTrump was declassifying documents about how the Russia investigation started. </span><br>
<span>They're for every investigation except AG Barr's. </span><br>
<span>Funny how that works, isn't it?</span><br>
<span>— Ronna McDaniel (@GOPChairwoman) May 25, 2019</span><br>
<span>民主党说我通俄，我告诉你们怎么样才是真正的通俄！！！哼!!!</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>Impeach for what, having created perhaps the greatest Economy in our Country’s history, rebuilding our Military, taking care of our Vets (Choice), Judges, Best Jobs Numbers Ever, and much more? Dems are Obstructionists! https://t.co/NrTIxU9ZnA</span><br>
<span>— Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) May 27, 2019</span><br>
<span>我来告诉你们什么是对，我，人类最伟大的帝皇，创造了最好的经济，最强大的军队，最好的就业数据等，民主党去吃屁啦</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>Back from Japan after a very successful trip. Big progress on MANY fronts. A great country with a wonderful leader in Prime Minister Abe!</span><br>
<span>— Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) May 29, 2019</span><br>
<span>从日本回来了，安倍人不错，很nice，就是吃的什么嘛玩意</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>Hearing word that Russia, Syria and, to a lesser extent, Iran, are bombing the hell out of Idlib Province in Syria, and indiscriminately killing many innocent civilians. The World is watching this butchery. What is the purpose, what will it get you? STOP!</span><br>
<span>毛熊，伊朗和叙利亚你们去炸恐怖分子?那可不行，那都是我的下属，马上停下来！！！</span><br>
</p><p><b>royp: </b><br>
<span>      Donald J. Trump‏认证账号 @realDonaldTrump</span><br>
<span>                If the totally Corrupt Media was less corrupt, I would be up by 15 points in the polls based on our tremendous success with the economy, maybe Best Ever! If the Corrupt Media was actually fair, I would be up by 25 points. Nevertheless, despite the Fake News, we’re doing great!民调不高都是fake news的错</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>House Democrats, fresh off a Republican victory against them (in Federal Court) on the Wall, keep asking people to come and testify regarding the No Collusion Witch Hunt. They are very unhappy with the Mueller Report, especially with his corrective letter, & now want a Do Over!</span><br>
<span>— Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) June 5, 2019</span><br>
<span>民主党在猎巫，他们想弄死阿川，哼！</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>“The President has received glowing reviews from the British Media. Here at home, not so much. MSNBC Ramps up hateful coverage and promotes conspiracy theories during Trump’s trip to Europe.” @seanhannity The good news is that @maddow is dying in the ratings, along with @CNN!</span><br>
<span>— Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) June 6, 2019</span><br>
<span>阿川在英国那，受到了媒体的热烈欢迎，但在家里那国老是用菲克牛屎来黑我，我不要做（美国）总统了，JOJO!!!</span><br>
</p><p><b>royp: </b><br>
<span>NASA重返月球？莫得牌面，应该星辰大海！</span><br>
<span>Donald J. Trump‏认证账号 @realDonaldTrump            For all of the money we are spending, NASA should NOT be talking about going to the Moon - We did that 50 years ago. They should be focused on the much bigger things we are doing, including Mars (of which the Moon is a part), Defense and Science!上午1:38 - 2019年6月8日</span><br>
</p><p><b>a.r.i.a: </b><br>
<span>刚刚墨西哥的可以贴下……他到底要墨西哥买农产品还是控制难民？说好的拿自己的钱不贴农民救助贫困饥荒地区呢？</span><br>
</p><p><b>royp: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 royp 于 2019-6-8 09:12 编辑 </span><br>
<span>一级价格歧视（大嘘）</span><br>
<span>Donald J. Trump‏认证账号 @realDonaldTrump   If we are able to make the deal with Mexico, & there is a good chance that we will, they will begin purchasing Farm & Agricultural products at very high levels, starting immediately. If we are unable to make the deal, Mexico will begin paying Tariffs at the 5% level on Monday!上午1:16 - 2019年6月8日</span><br>
<span>如果我们能够与墨西哥达成交易, & 我们很有可能, 他们将开始购买非常高价格的农产品和农产品, 立即开始。如果我们无法达成这笔交易, 墨西哥将在周一开始向关税支付5%水平的费用!          </span><br>
</p><p><b>royp: </b><br>
<span>Donald J. Trump‏认证账号 @realDonaldTrump </span><br>
<span>I am pleased to inform you that The United States of America has reached a signed agreement with Mexico. The Tariffs scheduled to be implemented by the U.S. on Monday, against Mexico, are hereby indefinitely suspended. Mexico, in turn, has agreed to take strong measures to stem the tide of Migration through Mexico, and to our Southern Border. This is being done to greatly reduce, or eliminate, Illegal Immigration coming from Mexico and into the United States. Details of the agreement will be released shortly by the State Department. Thank you!上午8:31 - 2019年6月8日</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>Mexico will try very hard, and if they do that, this will be a very successful agreement for both the United States and Mexico!</span><br>
<span>— Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) June 8, 2019</span><br>
<span>墨西哥努力了，认怂不怪他，你说他不行，你行你上啊。阿川觉得他行，他就行，不行也行，所以这协议，没毛病</span><br>
</p><p><b>a.r.i.a: </b><br>
<span>royp 发表于 2019-6-8 09:10</span><br>
<span> 一级价格歧视（大嘘） Donald J. Trump‏认证账号 @realDonaldTrump   If we are able to make the deal...</span><br>
<span>不是高价格吧？高数量吧？</span><br>
</p><p><b>royp: </b><br>
<span>以前谈了但没签字的就算现在谈的协议，协议还有大杀器没有公布！</span><br>
<span>Donald J. Trump‏认证账号 @realDonaldTrumpAnother false report in the Failing@nytimes. We have been trying to get some of these Border Actions for a longtime, as have other administrations, but were not able to get them, or get themin full, until our signed agreement with Mexico. Additionally, and for many years,Mexico was not being cooperative on the Border in things we had, or didn’thave, and now I have full confidence, especially after speaking to theirPresident yesterday, that they will be very cooperative and want to get the jobproperly done. Importantly, some things not mentioned in yesterday pressrelease, one, were agreed upon. That will be announced at the appropriate time.There is now going to be great cooperation between Mexico & the USA,something that didn’t exist for decades. However, if for some unknown reason.there is not, we can always go back to our previous, very profitable, positionof Tariffs - But I don’t believe that will be necessary. The Failing @nytimes,& ratings challenged @CNN, will do anything possible to see our Countryfail! They are truly The Enemy of the People!下午8:26 - 2019年6月9日</span><br>
</p><p><b>royp: </b><br>
<span>推特干涉言论自由！</span><br>
<span>Donald J. Trump‏认证账号 @realDonaldTrump Twitter should let the banned ConservativeVoices back onto their platform, without restriction. It’s called Freedom ofSpeech, remember. You are making a Giant Mistake!下午8:45 - 2019年6月9日</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>royp 发表于 2019-6-9 20:48</span><br>
<span>推特干涉言论自由！</span><br>
<span>Donald J. Trump‏认证账号 @realDonaldTrump Twitter should let the banned Conserva ...</span><br>
<span>我刚想发这个········你比我快</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>Trump wins historic landslide election.</span><br>
<span>Democrats – "Russia did it."</span><br>
<span>Trump sets economic records.</span><br>
<span>Democrats – "Obama did it."</span><br>
<span>Trump strikes historic immigration deal with Mexico.</span><br>
<span>Democrats – "Nothing changed."</span><br>
<span>— Bill Mitchell (@mitchellvii) June 9, 2019</span><br>
<span>转一个川皇最爱的赞歌</span><br>
<span>阿川我赢了，民主党说我通俄</span><br>
<span>阿川我KAG!了，民主党说黑驴早搞定了</span><br>
<span>阿川我让amigo跪了，民主党说什么都没发生过</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1831842[50-100]</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>开一个川皇的推特专楼吧（更新了赞歌）[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1831842-1-1.html</link>
      <description>开一个川皇的推特专楼吧&#13;
昨天有潭友发了个专门分发川皇推特加中文翻译的链接https://twittercn.live/，结果今天就登不上去了，有没有巨巨有空随时更新川皇的推啊，这简直是快乐源泉，停不下来</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>开一个川皇的推特专楼吧</span><br>
<span>昨天有潭友发了个专门分发川皇推特加中文翻译的链接https://twittercn.live/，结果今天就登不上去了，有没有巨巨有空随时更新川皇的推啊，这简直是快乐源泉，停不下来</span><br>
</p><p><b>StarsPlatinum: </b><br>
<span>前排留名</span><br>
</p><p><b>fenglingke: </b><br>
<span>前排围观</span><br>
</p><p><b>xingling00: </b><br>
<span>这也太真实了吧，我昨天刚分享泥潭就不能用了，权重太高受不了</span><br>
</p><p><b>NF17: </b><br>
<span>泥潭对川普还没深爱到这地步，喜欢的话自己上推看，最新一条还是6小时前的</span><br>
</p><p><b>feirenhenduo: </b><br>
<span>前排坐等</span><br>
</p><p><b>另一个唐唐: </b><br>
<span>川皇太勤劳，还经常发视频- -</span><br>
</p><p><b>StrangerJ: </b><br>
<span>泥潭对川普还是爱的，有的时候同一条推能发两三个贴</span><br>
</p><p><b>Kurishi: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 Kurishi 于 2019-5-16 10:19 编辑 </span><br>
<span>像這樣?</span><br>
<span>https://imgur.com/a/MjlBFuB</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>暂时川皇还没发推，只找到最近一个和他相关（歌颂）的新闻：</span><br>
<span>Kelsey Grammer praised President Trump, blasted the ‘bunch of clowns’ running Washington, DC, and said his support for conservative politicians has not affected his career in liberal-dominated Hollywood.</span><br>
<span>‘I’m not aware of taking a hit for it  but now, certainly passions run high, and certainly he has touched on an extraordinarily passionate response,’ the Frasier star said of Trump during an interview with PBS.</span><br>
<span>凯西格拉默说，川皇说得对做得好，打破组织结构是件好事，</span><br>
<span>‘I don't know if it's as serious or horrible as everybody wants it to be.’</span><br>
<span>Grammer was asked about Trump ‘disrupting the fabric’ of Washington, DC, to which he replied: ‘Well I think fabric being disrupted is a good thing.’</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>Kurishi 发表于 2019-5-16 10:18</span><br>
<span>像這樣?</span><br>
<span>对对对，给你加鹅</span><br>
</p><p><b>细雨湿流光: </b><br>
<span>前排留名</span><br>
<span>我永远喜欢唐纳德特朗普，还有大家</span><br>
</p><p><b>忠义无双汪精卫: </b><br>
<span>儿童英语学习角</span><br>
</p><p><b>凯特雷特: </b><br>
<span>不如搞个完形填空</span><br>
</p><p><b>与天争锋LZ: </b><br>
<span>我今天开始单推推特艺人川川子</span><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/16/5cdcd41219d9184126.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/16/5cdcd41219d9184126.jpg"><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 5s Plus, Android 7.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>赛璐珞: </b><br>
<span>还是分散点发吧，容易被和谐，上次大选楼连渣都不剩了</span><br>
</p><p><b>東方凌: </b><br>
</p><p><b>无聊者X: </b><br>
<span>你想知道我发川皇御推有多少楼被管理员锁了吗</span><br>
<span>还是分开比较好</span><br>
<span>点我看我发帖领悟川皇精神</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 HUAWEI MHA-AL00, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>masm: </b><br>
<span>我也发一个</span><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/16/5cdcdc2fece8258315.png" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/16/5cdcdc2fece8258315.png"><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MIX 2S, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.0.4-play</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>无聊者X 发表于 2019-5-16 11:41</span><br>
<span>你想知道我发川皇御推有多少楼被管理员锁了吗</span><br>
<span>还是分开比较好</span><br>
<span>点我看我发帖领悟川皇精神</span><br>
<span>没鹅了</span><br>
</p><p><b>有妹是老婆: </b><br>
<span>前排留名</span><br>
</p><p><b>626704053: </b><br>
<span>真爱楼，估计得成为第一高楼</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 vivo X9s, Android 8.1.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>叉子: </b><br>
<span>有漫画也不错。看过几个川普的政治漫画。很有意思。</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi MI 9, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>若荼泱: </b><br>
<span>占座喝茶</span><br>
</p><p><b>521op@163.com: </b><br>
<span>大统领可以vtuber化了</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi Redmi Note 5, Android 8.1.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>lqchina: </b><br>
<span>東方凌 发表于 2019-5-16 11:39</span><br>
<span>为啥要等到2020年</span><br>
</p><p><b>東方凌: </b><br>
<span>lqchina 发表于 2019-5-16 12:43</span><br>
<span>为啥要等到2020年</span><br>
<span>2020总统大选吧</span><br>
</p><p><b>博丽灵梦的御币: </b><br>
<span>前排留名</span><br>
</p><p><b>首fool: </b><br>
<span>521op@163.com 发表于 2019-5-16 12:14</span><br>
<span>大统领可以vtuber化了</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 Xiaomi Redmi Note 5, Android 8.1.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2 ...</span><br>
<span>大统领有自己官方真人的油管频道 </span><br>
<span>不知道为什么就是火不起来</span><br>
<span>当选后就把之前浏览量不到四位数的都删了</span><br>
</p><p><b>Lozs: </b><br>
<span>有趣，想要更多川皇精神</span><br>
</p><p><b>StarsPlatinum: </b><br>
<span>无聊者X 发表于 2019-5-16 11:41</span><br>
<span>你想知道我发川皇御推有多少楼被管理员锁了吗</span><br>
<span>还是分开比较好</span><br>
<span>点我看我发帖领悟川皇精神</span><br>
<span>哈哈哈哈哈原来全是你发的</span><br>
</p><p><b>熊吉同学: </b><br>
<span>怎么打不开，上面的那个链接我打开了啊。</span><br>
</p><p><b>midearth: </b><br>
<span>也是时候开个真爱楼2.0吧，明年就大选了</span><br>
</p><p><b>lqchina: </b><br>
<span>東方凌 发表于 2019-5-16 15:41</span><br>
<span>2020总统大选吧</span><br>
<span>对不起我犯蠢了，我忘了2020就是明年了……通宵后脑子不清醒，看到2020我直觉以为是20年后……</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>熊吉同学 发表于 2019-5-16 15:58</span><br>
<span>怎么打不开，上面的那个链接我打开了啊。</span><br>
<span>大熊弟，不开梯子我这边打不开呢</span><br>
</p><p><b>年轮: </b><br>
<span>留名</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>Chinese people rush to buy £2 'Donald Trump toilet brushes' amid trade war with the US and joke 'Trump can be so useful'</span><br>
<span>Cleaning tools that look like the U.S. President are popular online in China </span><br>
<span>One seller boasts his 'Trump' toilet brushes have powerful cleaning effect</span><br>
<span>Another seller gives out free toilet paper with Trump's image on it to buyers</span><br>
<span>'Toilet brushes' is a trending search phrase on Taobao, China's answer to eBay</span><br>
<span>The shopping trend was reported after China waged a 'people's war' on the U.S.</span><br>
<img src="https://i.dailymail.co.uk/1s/2019/05/16/13/13569268-7036679-image-m-68_1558010246987.jpg" title="https://i.dailymail.co.uk/1s/2019/05/16/13/13569268-7036679-image-m-68_1558010246987.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.dailymail.co.uk/1s/2019/05/16/13/13569284-7036679-image-m-46_1558009846792.jpg" title="https://i.dailymail.co.uk/1s/2019/05/16/13/13569284-7036679-image-m-46_1558009846792.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.dailymail.co.uk/1s/2019/05/16/13/13571202-7036679-image-a-47_1558009851594.jpg" title="https://i.dailymail.co.uk/1s/2019/05/16/13/13571202-7036679-image-a-47_1558009851594.jpg"><br>
</p><p><b>扎夫特议长: </b><br>
<span>tremendous预定</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能看大图的 Stage1官方 Android客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>SunriseKaRai: </b><br>
<span>占个位置，神皇为我带来快乐</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>giogioG: </b><br>
<span>建议附上顺便底下美国喷子的回复，效果更佳</span><br>
<span>发自我的iPhone via Saralin 2.1.7</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<span>'I think it's great!' Trump comes out in favor of gay marriage as Pete 'Boot Edge Edge' becomes serious challenger whose husband could become America's first gentleman</span><br>
<span>President Trump voiced his support for gay marriage when talking about openly gay Democratic candidate Pete Buttigieg</span><br>
<span> 'Yes, I think it's great,' Trump told Fox News in an interview set to air Sunday. </span><br>
<span>He noted that some people could 'have a problem with' it, likely a nod to conservative Vice President Mike Pence who has long opposed the institution</span><br>
<span>The South Bend, Indiana mayor has been married to his husband, Chasten, since June 2018</span><br>
<span>川皇诏曰，童星脸，那是相当的好！！！不是小好，而是大好！！！</span><br>
</p><p><b>甲児: </b><br>
<span>maga！</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>larthasliu: </b><br>
<span>他的推真的是简单易懂啊。。我这水平都能看懂。。</span><br>
</p><p><b>flyreder: </b><br>
<span>Kurishi 发表于 2019-05-16 10:18:26</span><br>
<span>⊙∀⊙！说话不算是小狗哦</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>kingsin: </b><br>
<img src="https://i.dailymail.co.uk/1s/2019/05/17/17/13628830-7041945-image-a-36_1558111537904.jpg" title="https://i.dailymail.co.uk/1s/2019/05/17/17/13628830-7041945-image-a-36_1558111537904.jpg"><br>
<span>都是弗林的错，他没告诉我他是个坏人！！！</span><br>
</p><p><b>秦心heart: </b><br>
<span>坐等川皇买了s1给你们都塞口球</span><br>
<span>-- 来自 能搜索的 Stage1官方 iOS客户端</span><br>
</p><p><b>avayazhg: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 avayazhg 于 2019-5-20 07:03 编辑 </span><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/20/5ce1db68e7c1f70532.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/20/5ce1db68e7c1f70532.jpg"><br>
<span>今天的口号，Never Again！</span><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/20/5ce1db695513421530.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/20/5ce1db695513421530.jpg"><br>
<span>虽然半年前就Never Ever Again！了(</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 samsung SM-G9350, Android 8.0.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>avayazhg: </b><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/20/5ce1dc09b194d87864.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/20/5ce1dc09b194d87864.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/20/5ce1dc095d8bd18070.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/20/5ce1dc095d8bd18070.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/20/5ce1dc090796e46385.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/20/5ce1dc090796e46385.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/20/5ce1dc08a84d048720.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/20/5ce1dc08a84d048720.jpg"><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/20/5ce1dc0856baa51604.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/20/5ce1dc0856baa51604.jpg"><br>
<span>以及我如何活成了我最讨厌的人的样子</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 samsung SM-G9350, Android 8.0.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>avayazhg: </b><br>
<img src="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/20/5ce1dda5d7f7c60643.jpg" title="https://i.loli.net/2019/05/20/5ce1dda5d7f7c60643.jpg"><br>
<span>唯一指定真实媒体正在堕落！GEE！</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 samsung SM-G9350, Android 8.0.0上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>lanslort: </b><br>
<span>Gee, he never speaks well of me  </span><br>
<span>太草了</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1831842[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
