<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>服气，这样的狗屎文章也能行？教会福音无边？</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>服气，这样的狗屎文章也能行？教会福音无边？</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 17:06:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>服气，这样的狗屎文章也能行？教会福音无边？[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1864958-1-1.html</link>
      <description>服气，这样的狗屎文章也能行？教会福音无边？&#13;
 本帖最后由 驴和标签 于 2019-11-11 12:52 编辑 

科学上一篇文章，说是教会六世纪禁止近亲结婚后改变了整个欧洲的社会结构，减少家庭抱团，使欧洲人走向个人主义、民主、民众互信、公平竞争、高收入……
&#13;
真的神奇，看完摘要一脸问号。这尼玛也行？
&#13;
西周：我难道没说过同姓不婚？
&#13;
http://static.saraba1st.com/image/smiley/face2017/221.pnghttp://static.saraba1st.com/image/smiley/face2017/221.pnghttp://static.saraba1st.com/image/smiley/face2017/221.png
&#13;
         The Church, intensive kinship, and global psychological variation
&#13;
[*]Jonathan F. Schulz1,*,
&#13;
[*]Duman Bahrami-Rad2,
&#13;
[*]Jonathan P. Beauchamp1,
&#13;
[*]Joseph Henrich2,3
&#13;
            Science08 Nov 2019:
&#13;
Vol. 366, Issue 6466, eaau5141
&#13;
DOI: 10.1126/science.aau5141      
&#13;
                                    Cultural evolutionThere is substantial variation in psychological attributes across cultures. Schulz et al. examined whether the spread of Catholicism in Europe generated much of this variation (see the Perspective by Gelfand). In particular, they focus on how the Church broke down extended kin-based institutions and encouraged a nuclear family structure. To do this, the authors developed measures of historical Church exposure and kin-based institutions across populations. These measures accounted for individual differences in 20 psychological outcomes collected in prior studies.Science, this issue p. eaau5141; see also p. 686
&#13;
Structured AbstractINTRODUCTIONA growing body of research suggests that populations around the globe vary substantially along several important psychological dimensions and that populations characterized as Western, Educated, Industrialized, Rich, and Democratic (WEIRD) are particularly unusual. People from these societies tend to be more individualistic, independent, and impersonally prosocial (e.g., trusting of strangers) while revealing less conformity and in-group loyalty. Although these patterns are now well documented, few efforts have sought to explain them. Here, we propose that the Western Church (i.e., the branch of Christianity that evolved into the Roman Catholic Church) transformed European kinship structures during the Middle Ages and that this transformation was a key factor behind a shift towards a WEIRDer psychology.
&#13;
RATIONALEOur approach integrates three insights. First, anthropological evidence suggests that diverse kin-based institutions—our species’s most fundamental institutions—have been the primary structure for organizing social life in most societies around the world and back into history. With the origins of agriculture, cultural evolution increasingly favored intensive kinship norms related to cousin marriage, clans, and co-residence that fostered social tightness, interdependence, and in-group cooperation. Second, psychological research reveals that people’s motivations, emotions, and perceptions are shaped by the social norms they encounter while growing up. Within intensive kin-based institutions, people’s psychological processes adapt to the collectivistic demands of their dense social networks. Intensive kinship norms reward greater conformity, obedience, and in-group loyalty while discouraging individualism, independence, and impersonal motivations for fairness and cooperation. Third, historical research suggests that the Western Church systematically undermined Europe’s intensive kin-based institutions during the Middle Ages (for example, by banning cousin marriage). The Church’s family policies meant that by 1500 CE, and likely centuries earlier in some regions, Europe lacked strong kin-based institutions and was instead dominated by relatively independent and isolated nuclear or stem families.Our theory predicts that populations with (i) a longer historical exposure to the medieval Western Church or less intensive kin-based institutions will be more individualistic, less conforming, and more impersonally prosocial today; and (ii) longer historical exposure to the Western Church will be associated with less-intensive kin-based institutions.
&#13;
RESULTSWe test these predictions at three levels. Globally, we show that countries with longer historical exposure to the medieval Western Church or less intensive kinship (e.g., lower rates of cousin marriage) are more individualistic and independent, less conforming and obedient, and more inclined toward trust and cooperation with strangers (see figure). Focusing on Europe, where we compare regions within countries, we show that longer exposure to the Western Church is associated with less intensive kinship, greater individualism, less conformity, and more fairness and trust toward strangers. Finally, comparing only the adult children of immigrants in European countries, we show that those whose parents come from countries or ethnic groups that historically experienced more centuries under the Western Church or had less intensive kinship tend to be more individualistic, less conforming, and more inclined toward fairness and trust with strangers.
&#13;
CONCLUSIONThis research suggests that contemporary psychological patterns, ranging from individualism and trust to conformity and analytical thinking, have been influenced by deep cultural evolutionary processes, including the Church’s peculiar incest taboos, family policies, and enduring kin-based institutions.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>驴和标签: </b><br>
<span>服气，这样的狗屎文章也能行？教会福音无边？</span><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 驴和标签 于 2019-11-11 12:52 编辑 </span><br>
<span>科学上一篇文章，说是教会六世纪禁止近亲结婚后改变了整个欧洲的社会结构，减少家庭抱团，使欧洲人走向个人主义、民主、民众互信、公平竞争、高收入……</span><br>
<span>真的神奇，看完摘要一脸问号。这尼玛也行？</span><br>
<span>西周：我难道没说过同姓不婚？</span><br>
<img src="http://static.saraba1st.com/image/smiley/face2017/221.pnghttp://static.saraba1st.com/image/smiley/face2017/221.pnghttp://static.saraba1st.com/image/smiley/face2017/221.png" title="http://static.saraba1st.com/image/smiley/face2017/221.pnghttp://static.saraba1st.com/image/smiley/face2017/221.pnghttp://static.saraba1st.com/image/smiley/face2017/221.png"><br>
<span>         The Church, intensive kinship, and global psychological variation</span><br>
<span>[*]Jonathan F. Schulz1,*,</span><br>
<span>[*]Duman Bahrami-Rad2,</span><br>
<span>[*]Jonathan P. Beauchamp1,</span><br>
<span>[*]Joseph Henrich2,3</span><br>
<span>            Science08 Nov 2019:</span><br>
<span>Vol. 366, Issue 6466, eaau5141</span><br>
<span>DOI: 10.1126/science.aau5141      </span><br>
<span>                                    Cultural evolutionThere is substantial variation in psychological attributes across cultures. Schulz et al. examined whether the spread of Catholicism in Europe generated much of this variation (see the Perspective by Gelfand). In particular, they focus on how the Church broke down extended kin-based institutions and encouraged a nuclear family structure. To do this, the authors developed measures of historical Church exposure and kin-based institutions across populations. These measures accounted for individual differences in 20 psychological outcomes collected in prior studies.Science, this issue p. eaau5141; see also p. 686</span><br>
<span>Structured AbstractINTRODUCTIONA growing body of research suggests that populations around the globe vary substantially along several important psychological dimensions and that populations characterized as Western, Educated, Industrialized, Rich, and Democratic (WEIRD) are particularly unusual. People from these societies tend to be more individualistic, independent, and impersonally prosocial (e.g., trusting of strangers) while revealing less conformity and in-group loyalty. Although these patterns are now well documented, few efforts have sought to explain them. Here, we propose that the Western Church (i.e., the branch of Christianity that evolved into the Roman Catholic Church) transformed European kinship structures during the Middle Ages and that this transformation was a key factor behind a shift towards a WEIRDer psychology.</span><br>
<span>RATIONALEOur approach integrates three insights. First, anthropological evidence suggests that diverse kin-based institutions—our species’s most fundamental institutions—have been the primary structure for organizing social life in most societies around the world and back into history. With the origins of agriculture, cultural evolution increasingly favored intensive kinship norms related to cousin marriage, clans, and co-residence that fostered social tightness, interdependence, and in-group cooperation. Second, psychological research reveals that people’s motivations, emotions, and perceptions are shaped by the social norms they encounter while growing up. Within intensive kin-based institutions, people’s psychological processes adapt to the collectivistic demands of their dense social networks. Intensive kinship norms reward greater conformity, obedience, and in-group loyalty while discouraging individualism, independence, and impersonal motivations for fairness and cooperation. Third, historical research suggests that the Western Church systematically undermined Europe’s intensive kin-based institutions during the Middle Ages (for example, by banning cousin marriage). The Church’s family policies meant that by 1500 CE, and likely centuries earlier in some regions, Europe lacked strong kin-based institutions and was instead dominated by relatively independent and isolated nuclear or stem families.Our theory predicts that populations with (i) a longer historical exposure to the medieval Western Church or less intensive kin-based institutions will be more individualistic, less conforming, and more impersonally prosocial today; and (ii) longer historical exposure to the Western Church will be associated with less-intensive kin-based institutions.</span><br>
<span>RESULTSWe test these predictions at three levels. Globally, we show that countries with longer historical exposure to the medieval Western Church or less intensive kinship (e.g., lower rates of cousin marriage) are more individualistic and independent, less conforming and obedient, and more inclined toward trust and cooperation with strangers (see figure). Focusing on Europe, where we compare regions within countries, we show that longer exposure to the Western Church is associated with less intensive kinship, greater individualism, less conformity, and more fairness and trust toward strangers. Finally, comparing only the adult children of immigrants in European countries, we show that those whose parents come from countries or ethnic groups that historically experienced more centuries under the Western Church or had less intensive kinship tend to be more individualistic, less conforming, and more inclined toward fairness and trust with strangers.</span><br>
<span>CONCLUSIONThis research suggests that contemporary psychological patterns, ranging from individualism and trust to conformity and analytical thinking, have been influenced by deep cultural evolutionary processes, including the Church’s peculiar incest taboos, family policies, and enduring kin-based institutions.</span><br>
</p><p><b>wangandh: </b><br>
<span>可天主教跟自课绝罚的新教徒有什么关系吗</span><br>
</p><p><b>Sliverstrike: </b><br>
<span>盎萨日耳曼蛮子脑子不好需要信点什么才能当文明人没毛病啊</span><br>
<span>让他们自主思考可不就只能艹自家姐妹了么（参考欧洲皇室）</span><br>
</p><p><b>mintpie: </b><br>
<span>那个年代教会还真没准是进步力量。日耳曼高卢蛮子有多蛮可能超出你想象。可能</span><br>
</p><p><b>kamarus: </b><br>
<span>一脸懵逼东部教会的懵逼.jpg</span><br>
</p><p><b>梦回星海: </b><br>
<span>Sliverstrike 发表于 2019-11-11 13:00</span><br>
<span>盎萨日耳曼蛮子脑子不好需要信点什么才能当文明人没毛病啊</span><br>
<span>让他们自主思考可不就只能艹自家姐妹了么 ...</span><br>
<span>教会组织对信众的影响毕竟是客观存在的，而且中世纪基督教吸收了很多希腊人文主义和逻辑学的营养（毕竟传教和翻译圣经的都是些罗马-希腊人），不然也不会成为一个吸引了若干代僧侣沉迷释经学的逻辑迷宫。</span><br>
<span>说起来有趣，我忘了在哪本书上看过篇引用的古人书信，信里那哥们讲弟弟娶妻太贵，干脆跟妹妹结婚好了，也不知道是口嗨还是真打算这么干。</span><br>
</p><p><b>依然荏苒: </b><br>
<span>非要说，想读书必须得去当修士呢，可不是社会进步力量。</span><br>
</p><p><b>yizi: </b><br>
<span>最近听了邓晓芒老师的讲座里关于基督教是自由的宗教的论述感觉很有道理，基督教从教义上就有个人主义的倾向，这也是为什么后来有新教改革，罗马教廷衰败，现在各种基督教邪教家庭教会遍地。</span><br>
</p><p><b>葡萄牙的高山: </b><br>
<span>基督教的确对西欧有促进作用</span><br>
</p><p><b>绝赞販売中: </b><br>
<span>西周说过同姓不婚，但是西周没办法影响北狄西戎，基督教利用宗教对日耳曼的洗脑确实有一手.中国比较接近的例子是藏传佛教在吐蕃西夏灭亡后迅速影响了元朝，排挤了全真教使得藏传佛教一直到明清之交对于蒙古仍有巨大话语权.</span><br>
</p><p><b>索尔之怒: </b><br>
<span> 本帖最后由 索尔之怒 于 2019-11-11 14:58 编辑 </span><br>
<span>啊？哎？</span><br>
<span>为啥我记得是说，同时期罗马的近亲结婚很常见，而蛮族反而不多</span><br>
<span>因为军事首领制度的存在，如果允许近亲通婚会很容易造成财富的过度集中在某几个甚至某个家族中，从而打破轮流坐庄的力量平衡</span><br>
<span>而罗马，嗷，罗马！</span><br>
<span>容我去找找出处</span><br>
<span>===================================补充==============================================</span><br>
<span>果然记忆靠不住，原文引用自《关于西方古代的近亲结婚》，感谢皇帝@F·U·罗格纳 </span><br>
<span>近亲结婚的概念对欧洲古人来说与我们今天很不一样。在罗马帝国，近亲婚配禁忌仅限于直系血亲或者旁系尊卑亲属、收养形成的尊卑亲属，《罗马法》所要禁止和预防的是道德上的”乱lun“而不是生物上的近亲繁殖。当然，有些统治者出于私欲在法律上开过口子，如克劳狄皇帝为与侄女阿格利品娜结婚，立法允许叔伯与侄女结婚，不过终究在君士坦丁王朝被废止了。而堂、表血亲平辈之间的婚姻完全不在《罗马法》禁止之列。</span><br>
<span>而对于基督教，与一般人的印象不同，其实一开始完全不存在后世那些严格的婚姻禁忌，《圣经》里的近亲、乱lun婚姻本就比比皆是。有观点认为，中世纪的近亲婚姻禁忌除了《罗马法》的影响，主要是日耳曼人部落遗风的残余：一个部落内，成员之间普遍都有血亲关系，如果放任近亲婚配，容易在部落里形成势力庞大的家族，土地财产也会高度集中，不利于成员之间的平等和军事民主首领的权威。中世纪的教会只是沿袭了日耳曼人的传统，包装上《利未记》《申命记》里那些含混不清的说法，制订出更严格的近亲婚姻禁忌。</span><br>
<span>这种禁忌在11世纪到达人类历史上的最高峰，《教会法》规定，七等亲之间的婚姻都是非法的。《教会法》计算亲等和方法与《罗马法》不同：《罗马法》是两人先追溯到一个共同祖先，然后将两人各自到共同祖先的代数相加，和即为两人的亲等，比如表兄妹共同的祖先是外祖父，每人各传两代，表兄妹即四等亲，同理，外甥和舅舅是三等亲；《教会法》则是追溯到共同祖先后，取两人之中与共同祖先代数较大的那一个作为亲等，相同即取该值，因此在《教会法》里表兄妹成了二等亲，而外甥和舅舅也是二等亲。</span><br>
<span>用《教会法》的计算方法，旁系亲属的尊卑意义不大，因此不是很科学，也在一定程度上瓦解了《罗马法》对于乱lun的严格禁忌。当然，直系尊卑亲属之间的禁忌始终存在，收养形成的尊卑也被教父母和教子女之间的婚姻禁忌所代替。（中世纪人想离婚，有一个方法就是捏造两人之间是教父教女，或者教母教子，可以因此宣布婚姻无效）</span><br>
<span>《教会法》中的七等亲是非常非常疏远的亲戚关系，上溯到曾曾曾曾曾曾祖辈都不能有交集，要找在这之外的人进行婚配，对于有联姻传统的贵族而言，几乎是不可能完成的任务，即使是平民，由于中世纪人口流动非常缓慢，也是非常困难，因此大家无不怨声载道。终于，在1215年由英诺森三世主持的第四次拉特兰公会议上，教会把标准放宽到了三等，大体上满足了社会需要。不过，经常进行家族联姻的王室和贵族，无论怎么算，往往还是出不了三等，因此需要特别向教宗求得婚姻特许权。</span><br>
<span>===================================补充==============================================</span><br>
</p><p><b>火星飞船: </b><br>
<span>绝赞販売中 发表于 2019-11-11 14:44</span><br>
<span>西周说过同姓不婚，但是西周没办法影响北狄西戎，基督教利用宗教对日耳曼的洗脑确实有一手.中国比较接近的 ...</span><br>
<span>元朝那个不如说蒙古文化太落后，信仰得长生天之类原始宗教和藏区苯教很容易亲近，和道教这种比较高级的汉地文化反而生分，而藏传佛教里融入大量苯教元素。</span><br>
</p><p><b>苑生百花: </b><br>
<span>儒教讲同姓不婚，但是不同姓（如表兄妹）可以结婚</span><br>
</p><p><b>苑生百花: </b><br>
<span>火星飞船 发表于 2019-11-11 14:59</span><br>
<span>元朝那个不如说蒙古文化太落后，信仰得长生天之类原始宗教和藏区苯教很容易亲近，和道教这种比较高级的汉 ...</span><br>
<span>明显是竞争不过喇嘛教（开平辩论）</span><br>
</p><p><b>KujoJotaro: </b><br>
<span>明明是黑死病的功劳，能存活下来的基本上是优中选优的白皮</span><br>
</p><p><b>绝赞販売中: </b><br>
<span>火星飞船 发表于 2019-11-11 14:59</span><br>
<span> 元朝那个不如说蒙古文化太落后，信仰得长生天之类原始宗教和藏区苯教很容易亲近，和道教这种比较高级的汉 ...</span><br>
<span>其实和蒙古文化先进落后无关吧，西蒙古基督教影响比较重，西蒙古的基督教是源自于唐朝的景教北迁，也算是有不小汉化色彩.成吉思汗还没打下西夏就重点扶持全真教，但是全真教是内丹派，而藏传佛教的观念比全真教更符合统治阶级的要求，他们要的满足不是对自己严苛修行，所以当年佛道之辩除了本身水平不济其实和以前南北朝佛教大流行差不多，论精神慰藉佛基穆御三家太能打了</span><br>
</p><p><b>火星飞船: </b><br>
<span>苑生百花 发表于 2019-11-11 15:22</span><br>
<span>明显是竞争不过喇嘛教（开平辩论）</span><br>
<span>道教答应辩论本身就是以短击长。</span><br>
</p><p><b>志摩凛: </b><br>
<span>文章没太看懂...</span><br>
<span>教会喜欢强调“天主保佑，上帝的福音”云云，有什么好事都是上帝带来的。</span><br>
</p><p><b>苑生百花: </b><br>
<span>火星飞船 发表于 2019-11-11 15:37</span><br>
<span>道教答应辩论本身就是以短击长。</span><br>
<span>说到底还是缺乏竞争力</span><br>
</p><p><b>cmsufo: </b><br>
<span>元代佛道辩论缺乏公平，大汗亲自下场站佛，全真一开始就注定失败，和辨法细节关系不大</span><br>
<span>而且辩论主题还是唐代已经打成伪作的老子华胡经，可以说这事是佛教徒联合坑道教的一场戏</span><br>
</p><p><b>秋月涼: </b><br>
<span>mintpie 发表于 2019-11-11 13:03</span><br>
<span>那个年代教会还真没准是进步力量。日耳曼高卢蛮子有多蛮可能超出你想象。可能 ...</span><br>
<span>已经是中世纪了啊，实际上在当时伊斯兰教更进步一些……</span><br>
</p><p><b>Jagdpanther: </b><br>
<span>yizi 发表于 2019-11-11 13:34</span><br>
<span>最近听了邓晓芒老师的讲座里关于基督教是自由的宗教的论述感觉很有道理，基督教从教义上就有个人主义的倾向 ...</span><br>
<span>邓晓芒自从和刘小枫大战一回合就有点神神叨叨，有变成死抱圣贤书的老学究倾向，跟不上时代了。基督教的基色是最先发明群众与普世精神，个人关系实在不是主要。</span><br>
</p><p><b>Jagdpanther: </b><br>
<span>天主教会在黑暗时代是西欧唯一的闻名之光，古典文化于精神的唯一传承，当然也借机大改了一把。在大多数时间内，也是社会进步的重要甚至主要推动力量。</span><br>
</p><p><b>正义の脚男: </b><br>
<span>Jagdpanther 发表于 2019-11-11 17:24</span><br>
<span>邓晓芒自从和刘小枫大战一回合就有点神神叨叨，有变成死抱圣贤书的老学究倾向，跟不上时代了。基督教的基 ...</span><br>
<span>但这得跟希腊罗马的政治体制和思想观念结合起来，基督教本身不追求个人解放，但古典时期人只是政治动物和城邦公民，基督教第一次让人觉得“一辈子只为城邦这个集体活着未免太亏”。</span><br>
</p><p><b>F·U·罗格纳: </b><br>
<span>这个看你从哪个角度讲</span><br>
<span>相对于罗马的传统而言，基督教在生活的很多方面的确相对更尊重“个人”，比如说，在罗马的父权制下，男性家长对儿女是有着几乎生杀予夺的权利，随意为他们制定婚姻，甚至将他们变卖为奴等等，都是可以的。但基督教却说，上帝面前人人平等，家长你也没有这个权利；相爱的年轻男女只要在一个神职人员的见证下就能合法结婚，其他人的意见完全可以不care……</span><br>
</p><p><b>不容易注册上: </b><br>
<span>对于混乱的中世纪，教会确实是文明火种，至于以后嘛就另说了。这就像伊斯兰教产生在沙漠地图里面确实也是提高了当地的文明水平的</span><br>
</p><p><b>yizi: </b><br>
<span>Jagdpanther 发表于 2019-11-11 17:24</span><br>
<span>邓晓芒自从和刘小枫大战一回合就有点神神叨叨，有变成死抱圣贤书的老学究倾向，跟不上时代了。基督教的基 ...</span><br>
<span>邓晓芒在反国学上确实有点走火入魔，个人情绪太重了点，其实想想都是历史进程的一部分，对的终究是对的，错的终究是错的，用不着着急上火。</span><br>
<span>— from OnePlus GM1917, Android 9 of S1 Next Goose v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>sylali: </b><br>
<span>这文章最可耻的不是什么教会对西方的先进性，而是试图用欧洲的结论简单推广到教会没有影响的全世界范围。这里面图1那些东亚/东南亚灰色部分和图二灰色数据点的scatter不让作者和审稿人汗颜吗？这种缺乏数学证据和科学性的狗屁玩意儿也能上science？怎么不给自己期刊改个名叫Theology?</span><br>
</p><p><b>Corruptwing: </b><br>
<span>KujoJotaro 发表于 2019-11-11 15:29</span><br>
<span>明明是黑死病的功劳，能存活下来的基本上是优中选优的白皮</span><br>
<span>抗病能力优秀并不代表其它任何方面优秀，不要乱讲</span><br>
</p><p><b>vampiar: </b><br>
<span>精祆激怒</span><br>
</p><p><b>驴和标签: </b><br>
<span>sylali 发表于 2019-11-12 03:47</span><br>
<span>这文章最可耻的不是什么教会对西方的先进性，而是试图用欧洲的结论简单推广到教会没有影响的全世界范围。这 ...</span><br>
<span>Exactly，这种毫无严谨性的东西怎么上的science？因果联系在哪里？</span><br>
<span>上面回复一大堆问题都不知道在哪不知所云的</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1864958[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
