<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>唏嘘，沈阳机床居然破产了</title>
    <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/</link>
    <description>唏嘘，沈阳机床居然破产了</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 18:48:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>唏嘘，沈阳机床居然破产了[0-50]</title>
      <link>https://bbs.saraba1st.com/2b/thread-1848732-1-1.html</link>
      <description>唏嘘，沈阳机床居然破产了&#13;
多年以前，我买它股票亏过钱</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>暗黑大将军: </b><br>
<span>唏嘘，沈阳机床居然破产了</span><br>
<span>多年以前，我买它股票亏过钱</span><br>
</p><p><b>klmmmx: </b><br>
<span>蛤？这家不是还被拿出来当做典型吹过一波吗</span><br>
</p><p><b>江南映月: </b><br>
<span>大连的光洋机床不是很牛逼么</span><br>
</p><p><b>自组织临界: </b><br>
<span>30 November 2018</span><br>
<span>France welcomes the takeover of NFM Technologies by Mühlhäuser</span><br>
<span>NFM Technologies had been grappling with serious financial difficulties since the end of 2016 due to the failures of its shareholder, the Chinese group NHI, and had to be placed into receivership on 2 August this year. From the time it first ran into difficulties until the decision of the Court, the company was closely monitored by the Commissioners for Corporate Restructuring and the Prevention of Business Difficulties and by the Interministerial Delegate for Corporate Restructuring.</span><br>
<span>The takeover of NFM Technologies by Mühlhäuser will safeguard 80 industrial jobs and the specialised know-how of the company, in Creusot and also in the Lyon metropolitan area. It is also a unique opportunity to create a Franco-German player offering a full range of equipment in the field of underground works.</span><br>
<span>COMPANY NEWS</span><br>
<span>NFM for sale from insolvent Chinese owner 20 Sep 2018</span><br>
<span>Shani Wallis, TunnelTalk</span><br>
<span>Financial insolvency of its Chinese parent company NHI has resulted in French TBM manufacturer NFM negotiating with new investors to keep its French office and manufacturing base in Lyon and Le Creusot. NFM became part of the NHI Group in 2007 when the objective was for NFM to introduce NHI to TBM manufacture and for NHI to become the number one TBM supplier of TBMs in China with design remaining in France and principle components manufactured in the La Creusot factory going to China for assembly into Chinese manufactured shields and other large Chinese-manufactured elements. NHI was also interested in the NFM nuclear manufacturing expertise for China’s nuclear power construction program.</span><br>
<span>Promising relations at the beginning, according to NFM CEO at the time Luc Devaux, became strained in 2011 when NHI imposed a business strategy to double turnover with the same staff. “This was not possible and disagreeing with this strategy I left the company in 2011.” The NFM business continued in the intervening years with significant TBM order successes in China, Hong Kong, Australia, Egypt and in Europe but financial troubles for NFM were mounting.</span><br>
<span>Early in 2018, NHI sold its NFM Energy Business Unit to French oil and gas industry specialist REEL and adopted a new strategy to concentrate its efforts solely on the underground construction market. “In June 2017, I was asked by NHI and agreed to come back to the position of CEO for NFM to oversee this new strategy,” said Devaux, “but at the time I did not know of the financial status of NHI. I became aware of this when the state banks of China refused to restructure the NHI debt earlier this year.”</span><br>
<span>Insolvency of a large Chinese heavy industrial manufacturing enterprise is something of a new phenomenon. According to information on its website, NHI (Northern Heavy Industries Group Co Ltd), is a wholly state-owned company which, after taking over NFM in 2007, became one of the top 500 Chinese enterprises and ranked among the top three heavy machinery industry manufacturers in China with a facility that covers an area of about 1 million m2 and has more than 10,000 employees. The insolvency administrator is in negotiations with Chinese banks to reduce the debts of the NHI Group and will participate in a process of find a new shareholder for NHI Group to replace the current shareholder, Shenyang City.</span><br>
<span>When the insolvency of NHI became clear, NFM, which had retained all its intellectual property and its office and manufacturing base in France, began the search for a new shareholder to keep the company viable. “We have a deadline of end of October to conclude a sale from NHI,” said Devaux, “and we are in talks with four interested parties. Due to confidentiality clauses I can say no more than that. We are currently in the process of due diligence with these potential shareholders and are hopeful of a successful outcome. No one in NFM in France has left the company and all obligations to our current TBM customers are, and will be honoured. We have the liquidity to meet all these obligations, and to our staff. We are also being supported in our efforts by the French State.”</span><br>
</p><p><b>jctc: </b><br>
<span>那么总经理有没有带着小姨子跑路呢？</span><br>
</p><p><b>wqmx2008: </b><br>
<span>沈机不是破产很多年了吗，好像一直st来着，去年刚重组完吧，和云南机床一起</span><br>
<span>怎么又又又又双叒叕破产了？</span><br>
<span>到底是楼主致远星了还是我火星了？</span><br>
</p><p><b>自组织临界: </b><br>
<span>wqmx2008 发表于 2019-7-23 15:01</span><br>
<span>沈机不是破产很多年了吗，好像一直st来着，去年刚重组完吧，和云南机床一起</span><br>
<span>怎么又又又又双叒叕破产了？</span><br>
<span>沈阳机床股份有限公司关于控股股东沈阳机床（集团）有限责任公司被申请重整的提示性公告</span><br>
</p><p><b>枝条: </b><br>
<span>我怎么感觉好像早就破产了。</span><br>
</p><p><b>食人魔法师: </b><br>
<span>[f:001能力有限，东北企业的股票一点都不敢碰啊……</span><br>
</p><p><b>coffinzh: </b><br>
<span>炒过，好像还牛气过几次</span><br>
<span>发自我的iPhone via Saralin 2.1.7</span><br>
</p><p><b>永远的访客: </b><br>
<span>枝条 发表于 2019-7-24 02:44</span><br>
<span>我怎么感觉好像早就破产了。</span><br>
<span>去年就不行了，破产重组中</span><br>
</p><p><b>maoyou: </b><br>
<span>以前数控厂干过，一憨憨副厂长买了个沈阳机床，烂的一逼</span><br>
<span>—— 来自 samsung SM-N9600, Android 9上的 S1Next-鹅版 v2.1.2</span><br>
</p><p><b>hjjqjqs: </b><br>
<span>一个公司破产有什么大惊小怪的，国家还破产呐。</span><br>
</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1848732[0-50]</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
